<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1446</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apparently the Shaun The Sheep Movie is only coming out in the US now. You should all go see it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:32:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It came out here a good few months ago and it's terrific, I'd love to see a British stop motion animated film do well in America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:00:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know I was just playing along with nomefish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But The Muppets Show is in the same universe as the latest two films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And only a week after they said we wouldn't see it. For anyone who doesn't know the actual show is about the Muppets working on a talk show hosted my Miss Piggy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What should be on everybody's bucket list? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:30:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably my favourite Hollywood Handbook episode and one of my firsts. The Bababooey bit is so funny to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:00:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say the fish in Finding Nemo were more similar to real fish than that main dinosaur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:35:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely. I actually watched the G.I Joe episode of Community recently and I could only hear Diane and not Annie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:33:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was actually Daniel Radcliffe?? I thought it was Paul F. Tompkins again, since it sounded like  his Andrew Garfield. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 11:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly this status could very much just mean Tig is officially leaving, the show might still continue without her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 01:47:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha I meant non-main character. 

Yeah, last night I was actually watching the G.I Joe episode of community and I heard Diane whenever Alison spoke instead of Annie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:33:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was hoping we'd get a full episode about the Back To The Future 9/11 conspiracy video.

Also does anyway have a link to the original Harmontown Hollow Earth episode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the credits it says "This film was shot on location in New York City, which is almost like another character." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:17:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You really remind me of someone but I can't put my finger on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:08:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know it's been a while but music rights work completely differently for UK television, anything that isn't scripted sort of has the same rules as radio. They own the rights to play it, not to sell it. As long as you don't sell DVD's with the music you can put any music the channel owns, and all of the big channels have deals with the music studios. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 02:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't believe people seem blind to this fact. For some people under the age of 30 Star Wars is some old films they haven't seen or those 3 films that came out that everyone hated. I have quite a few friends who only went to see the prequels when they came out during the hype and are turned off Star Wars completely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 21:46:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I really need Simon for the christmas livestream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:12:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like an actual Christmas Special though, with actual character development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 13:53:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never realised she did Vincent! You can hear her all over though yeah, most notably the older girl of Horsin' Around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> me too. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pm please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 17:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you haven't watched Bojack Horseman, he's in the new season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 11:20:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Especially because it looks like they did a HD conversion of the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:08:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did he link to my facebook page? I guess he just reversed image search? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hollywood Facts: The Theme Song: The Board Game </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:40:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What? But this is way too spooky for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm probably going to have this for about a year. I had my last one for a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:58:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really, basically just take a screenshot of your facebook page and put it in the layer above the picture. Then I exported the image that fit in the profile box and then I exported the image that fit in the cover box. The templates are just sort of the ones on  Facebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:56:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh shit. Well fuck mobile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:10:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not actually literally set a few neighbourhoods over from Phineas and Ferb. If you read the source for that it says "And what's really cool is that -- in my mind, anyway -- Mikey Murphy just lives a couple of neighborhoods over from Phineas and Ferb." It's not like a true spin off or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My new Facebook cover and profile picture. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:48:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:21:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My laptop doesn't play it better. Simple as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anybody still play Minecraft on Xbox 360? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:37:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All of the people I used to play with have migrated to different games or the One. So if you still play this please add GT: 
"CianHatesPeople." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 12:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I can't really imagine Kermit sticking his hands up in the air and screaming awwwaaahahhaha in this new style and tone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 12:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can have both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 12:06:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Enjoy the karma s4082211.

Also feeling a little down since this is the first UTU2TM since Harris left us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:49:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow I'm surprised they didn't show Elizabeth Banks in the trailer. Maybe they're doing the same joke in the actual premier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TruTV Prank Lineup </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:35:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 11:53:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or 18.
Source: Born in 97 and am 18. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm hoping for it to come out this week. Only two more days then!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure you're thinking about this way more than Paul but the other british characters from him are.. the pie minister, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A subreddit or website that has a list of real life achievements that you can claim by submitting proof. A new achievement is available everyday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:24:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/showerorange could be one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:20:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the problem with this is that to offer a sale on an item it has to have been that price in the past month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 11:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good one.

EDIT: I thought Spontenation had begun at the end there since I had it queued up. I was confused as to why Paul was reading an ad for his show on his show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:07:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Billy and Mandy and Codename Kids Next Door were on the same level of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I seen the thumbnail I assumed puppeteers would be under the table but they're fully visible! I love this so much. If you're willing to have writers on comic con panels the puppeteers should be there too. 

This is a very rare occurrence and I'm surprised it happened. It's probably the only thing I disagree with Jim Henson on, he was on the side of always keeping the puppeteers a secret.

EDIT: Also wow that whole Promo we seen is completely thrown out the window. I will say the plot to this show sounds more Muppets Tonight that The Muppets Show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:58:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a TV movie. They've done a bunch of these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:02:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It feels like a biopic about the inventor of time travel at times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:55:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should get her to do this if she hasn't seen Star Wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:55:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 15:12:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd prefer if the bits where they are themselves was live action filmed during the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 15:03:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a little short film. It will be on my portfolio to get into college. I've done skits and stuff before but this is my first time working on something serious with other people acting in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 14:46:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm shooting my first short film today and currently getting ready for the actors coming over. I'm pretty nervous and very excited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Colin the Carpet Man </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 14:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:10:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the excuse they use for the comics, I don't know if it's been mentioned in the TV show. But in the comic universe they've said the Zombie mythology was never a thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 12:31:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's amazing how different Spaced is about Star Wars between the first and second season. Mostly because Phantom Menace came out between the two.

Also the voice of Darth Maul is featured in both.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. Looking forward to it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it helps that they're playing characters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:02:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where's the face OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 10:53:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looking forward to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 10:53:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! Thank you so much. That's perfect. I'll make a post here when it's done, and I'll send everyone who was in it PM's is well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah on WTF, I think, Rob was talking about how he doesn't really consider himself and actor and see's himself being a writer or a director after Sunny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Have you seen the original Star Wars movie? If not, please read on. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 00:56:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a few friends who have never seen Star Wars and I've recorded them telling me the plot of the movie from what they've heard in pop culture. I'm going to edit it into a big supercut to try and create a story that resembles some amount of sense, and I'll probably animate some of it.

However I need more clips to make it the way I want. So you haven't seen Star Wars, have a spare five minutes and half a camera/webcam/camera phone could you please record yourself describing what you believe the plot of Star Wars is beginning to end?

Then just pop it onto youtube and post it on here or PM me. Obviously if you do those things I'm assuming you don't mind the footage being put into the final project (Which will just be put onto youtube.)

I believe this has been done before but just with one person, plus this is just a little Summer project for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 00:28:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm also from Ireland and was very confused while reading this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 21:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone actually sort of did this. They watched every movie referenced in season one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:26:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I need all of the spoilers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:26:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really, really loved the last scene in this with the homeless people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:17:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's been just as long as last time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:14:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sky are normally pretty good at airing things close to it's original airing so I'm very happy about this. It'll fit nicely there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:56:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh shit. This loop really could go on forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While were on the topic of CBB crossover universes. The comedy bang bang tv show and the movie "The Interview" have a big connection in that Ben Shcwartz plays an agent in both, but is only named in CBB. So in my head canon it's the exact same character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:55:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0425112/trivia?tab=mc ref_=tt_trv_cnn

This is going to be tougher than I thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:37:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That would be impossible though, since the references will always be to previous movies. Everything you watch will have been made before the movie you watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If someone else creates this chain I'll do it. I just might not be that good at spotting the chains.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:07:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because I want to see what it's like. DVD's, webplayers, nothing will do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> holy shit, that shark is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Hot Fuzz Challenge: Watch Hot Fuzz from start to finish but every time there is a movie reference you have to pause Hot Fuzz and watch the movie being referenced. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chrome extension that lets you watch movies backwards on Netflix </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:12:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:53:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there was a lot of stuff happening behind the scenes with that one though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm back now!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're releasing it on a radio show that's not UTU2TM?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm going to be in this tinychat all day if anyone wants to come chat. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://tinychat.com/khsunny786

Subreddit: /r/teenagerstinychat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well you just ruined What We Do In The Shadows funniest jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was a very strange trailer. It felt like a clip cut out of an actual trailer.

Also yay the invisible friend. He's not really a monster he was just a human stuck in a world of monsters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:54:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A new series was just published a few years ago and they still always put out reprints. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:50:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've gotten excited about this project "finally being made" too many times in the past. I won't believe anything until there is a trailer.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah Blue Screen is still used a lot, but it was used the most up until they changed to green for Superman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They mostly used blue screen until Superman. And then they were like: shit we need a new colour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:01:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The real life of this sub is actually in "new." A lot of great discussion happens there that never even makes it to the front page. If you stick to "hot" you're going to have shitty time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also the list of other names they were going to call Magnitude is the list of names Jeff says as he says bye to everyone leaving the party.

Magnitude will always be Ben from Tracy Beaker to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So does that mean we will probably get that episode, because I love that lineup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:22:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope they release some other poster in that style for them movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's the Heidecker Gelman ep everyone is talking about in the AMA? Is it real or a bit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:08:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scott, when are you we going to get an Entourage recap on CBB for the movie??? I need to know what happened.

Edit: whoops someone already asked this. By the way if people do want to see Scott's take on the entourage movie he popped during the entourageathon and spoke about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Clips of the muppets with the muppets edited out so it's just celebrities talking to themselves. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good on you for editing the wiki! I always get so happy when I see people doing things like that. I would love to hear an episode of the podcast where they go through the wiki correcting things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! Back then the character would just have one little thing prepared and everything else was a new slate. Like Ice-T and his inventions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:13:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> -s-s-s-s-s.

I got you OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:12:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My favourite Reggie moment is when Scott does the beginning "thanks for playing the song, bye Reggie" thing and then a few minutes later he actually comes on mic and asks can he stay for the show.

I was binge listening and didn't see the guest list so it was a total surprise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:05:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know what Avenue Q is but I was talking about the custom puppets you see advertised online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I loved that show so much. I also love the live action Muppet Babies in The Muppets Take Manhattan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't believe they're available for sale anywhere and it wouldn't really be worthwhile. They'd be about 100 dollars each to buy but only 20 dollars or so to make. 

Edit: Eh...sorry for answering your question? If you need help making them I can give you a hand I've made quite a few puppets but none of the quality of those in the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Muppets Minus Muppets: Clips of the muppets with the muppets edited out. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:10:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 14:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you guys not like Jim Gaffigan, I've only really heard of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 11:52:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one where he talks about, I think it's a Woody Allen movie, is my favourite of his appearances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 10:45:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He seemed similar at the entourageathon, I think he's just more comfortable when he's hosting his own stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Luckily this episode was only based over two nights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep it's a fake stomach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:02:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually disliked that shot because I found it sort of unrealistic that all of the photos were recent of all kids. The photos in my home and other homes I know of normally have a mix of old and new.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 16:56:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That book to me is by far the stupidest part of the whole series. It makes absolutely no sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 16:55:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's why I feel like I relate more to Z than Y. I feel like my life was more like the lives of late Z's than early Y's. 

Edit: I changed Y for X.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 16:53:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh yeah I should explain. Generation Y is considered the people born between the 80's and early 90's/early 2000's based on who you ask. And Generation Z is people born between mid 90's/early 2000's and late 00's based on who you ask.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do you consider yourself Generation Y or Generation Z? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 16:45:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm very interested in the whole generation name things. And most of the people on this sub could be in either depending on who you ask. Except some of the younger ones are pretty much definitely Generation Z. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 16:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope it's satire but you shouldn't let that affect your enjoyment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 16:29:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well the project it's from is very much someone trying to do Tim and Eric. http://youtu.be/75z7BM5FsNY It's not nearly absurd enough for my taste though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 15:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone have a link to the song? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 23:17:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like today :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 22:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> News stories? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 22:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish there was a solution as easy as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 22:36:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That could be a bot though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 22:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What sort of things? Can you give me an example of something that has already happened today I could predict? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If I was stuck in a Groundhog Day type situation how would I prove it to the internet? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 22:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just checking so I can get help if it happens again tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What improv4humans had this video in it? I remember the Belfast accents in the scene after were hilarious but I can't find it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 03:31:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:40:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well yeah if you couldn't get through Pride and Prejudice you shouldn't be able to get through Pride and Prejudice and Zombies. The whole point is that it is as similar to the original as possible but eith zombies. If this film will follow suit I imagine it to have similar soundtrack, direction and cinematography of a normal period drama but with the zombie plot added in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 18:48:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is currently /r/blackout2015 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 18:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:17:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had trouble with this too recently. It seems a bunch of the old ones were with playmo.tv and they've stopped doing it. I'll have to try out ones linked in the comments here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 12:25:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are the best scenes yet to come? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a feeling a lot of visual stuff was going on. Expecially that second scene with the teacher and the students. The audience were laughing at moments of pure silence for us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> LIVE from DCM 17 Pt. 1, episode #194 of improv4humans with Matt Besser on Earwolf </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 11:38:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess so but it technically isn't really related. Schrodinger's Cat isn't really about timelines. They just fit it in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:41:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The new Rick and Morty got it right, didn't it? They were just a bunch of flying cats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:32:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But which on are the mods going to go with? The guy who wants to ban you for using it or you????? Ehhhh.... should I say it or not...

What about a word like it....


like....

RAVIOLI RAVIOLI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> He's like 3 years old. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:03:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say they would be more similar than just animated actually. Both of them revolve around a family dynamic mixing with high concept sci-fi. Infact the character dynamic feels similar in the pilot with Jerry trying to "bust" Rick similar to Candace.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could donate to Harmontown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 01:14:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I fucked my dog since there is no laws during the leap second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:51:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The UK Apprentice. It feels very classy for a reality show and I think the fact it's on the BBC helps. There is only "last times" and "next times" at the start and end of each show rather than between commercials since there aren't any commercials. Also while the show does focus on the drama between contestants it doesn't do it as blatantly as other shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:48:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well this is a kids tv show so I'd say this doesn't represent him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:28:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a feeling Community will be blamed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good job! I wanted the one holding the puppet to be on the right in both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:56:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In all Pixar movies or all the toy story movies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:24:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would look like an iPhone, and a computer, and an iPad. In the future will everything just be black rectangles?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should record yourself talking and then watch it in a year and see if you piss yourself off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:57:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think there is any real correlation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Luckily we have the "gas leak" to explain that mess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:33:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YOUUR WIIIIFE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:25:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Already did. It's doing better here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 18:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know, why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You found her! Also didn't expect her to be that old by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:35:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's actually my least favourite episode of the entire series, even though I love puppets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's definitely not the intended order though. You don't watch the finale where Jeff and Pierce leave as the third last episode. The rest of it seems pretty correct though. 4 is supposed to be episode 2 anyway. I remember that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 16:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Community does it too in their puppet episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 16:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Season 4 was aired completely out of order. There is a correct order somewhere on this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It doesn't help that he capitalised "Room." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:51:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think I'd ever have the confidence to do something like that. Good job mate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:14:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. I get to talk to myself even more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I made a puppet version of myself. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:48:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:03:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes and.. the movie would be relevant to our times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:50:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's true though. My little cousins spend all of their time playing with apps rather than toys. They got itunes gift cards for christmas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Comedies tend not to have podcasts like dramas do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:13:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not having a relationship in 3 years is weird? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also missed the start. Top Gear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's actually what this comes from. The light bulb in my fridge is burnt out and I have yet to notice any difficulty without the light.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:29:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that an irish thing? Eh.. cupboards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But we don't have lights in presses. It seems we would face the same problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:26:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know that much about it, but the thing I do to change region is enter in different settings on my xbox.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why do fridges have lights? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:13:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:10:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope, on my xbox I used a different DNS setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:02:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Day needs my saving expertise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 01:52:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think my interest in film helps. I'm constantly paying attention to sets, background extras and the like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's some pretty big problems with the widescreen version.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I have questions about widescreen on Netflix. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I'm currently watching Buffy for the first time on UK Netflix and the first 3 season were in 4:3 which was all fine. Then with season 4 it changed to widescreen. However I'm now watching Angel alongside it and the stream I found online was in 4:3 which confused me considering they were both shot at the same time. 


After some research and annoyance I found out both Angel and Buffy were on US Netflix so I used a DNS to switch to that and it saved me a lot of trouble trying to find streams. However on the US Netflix Buffy season 4 is in 4:3 and Angel is in widescreen! It's like they have both changed ratios with each other.


 I've done some searching in this subreddit and it seems the consensus is Buffy was made for 4:3 and should be watched that way. My main question is "which way should Angel be watched, widescreen or 4:3?" And also why are they putting up different versions for different regions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 21:55:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have a link to the original thread? I'd like to find out what this is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 21:54:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hitrecord.org is a great website for stuff like this. A subreddit would be cool is well though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:39:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It doesn't take a minute to send a snap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:47:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will all food be dehydrated in the future? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:44:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please, please do this for the whole stream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe Funny Or Die invited them. They invited Johnny Bananas is well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:41:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rick and Morty is sort of a mash of all the shows Justin did for Channel 101. I really hope there is a reference to Cup at some point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Woosh.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Community? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/9Rd1E4x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:50:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess [this](http://i.imgur.com/yQxjywp.gif) gif is incorrect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Win A Chance To Have Adam Scott Crash Your Slumber Party! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. http://community-sitcom.wikia.com/wiki/Pavel_Iwaszkiewicz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:59:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get wicked cold bros, mad sleepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:58:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most definitely. They must have forgot they were supposed to be there when shooting and added them in for continuity sake. Although personally I think it would have been less jarring to just leave them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:57:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The reason they changed it originally was that they weren't allowed to show boobs. (Yes even cartoon boobs.) Funnily enough though they kept the boobs and just took away the woman. Censorship is weird.

And then the Halloween one is a female skeleton with boobs. Which was allowed.


So basically on television you are allowed dead skeleton boobs or floating boobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:50:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Curb Your Enthusiasm has a lot including Paul F. Tompkins and Scotty Aucks himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:47:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Especially since he went to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:47:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And of course Hollywood Facts. My favourite of Scott's fake quizzes was when David Cross didn't realise that Hollywood Facts was a bit and he started arguing his answer was right. I think that was one of the last ones. 


And of course: Alive Or Dead- Dick Wolf?
Answer: Dead. His dick was eaten by a wolf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is what it's like for the characters in a movie when someone bursts into song </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And in at least one you die in the next 5 minutes. Who knows which one it will be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:23:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, "trigger" trigger people who are sensitive to gun talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Below the what???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:21:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have to say the idea of Dan doing Minecraft videos is a very strange but also comforting feeling. Especially considering he seems to want to do Tutorials rather than Let's Plays. The fact that somebody who has a career in television still wants to take up a hobby in Internet entertainment tells a lot about the feeling doing that stuff does to people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 12:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. There are not yet any plans for the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 09:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She was an extra for that season though, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:18:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is what I'm going to go with. She panicked and needed somewhere to hide the card so stuck it into a part of the van. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 16:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But just put the plastic over the top of the bottle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:16:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd watch a Weekend At Bernies type idea with the president. The president dies and the others politicians have to convince terrorists he's alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cops in America have been playing too much GTAV and now they think cops act like that </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:14:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I quite like If I Were You with Jake and Amir. Featuring earwolf guests like Ben Scwartz and Thomas Middleditch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like there is going to be an origin story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:04:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Downcast tells you what day a podcast uploads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 02:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine if they did that though. New extreme if remake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-21 20:21:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does this actually happen in real life to people? I've seen it in so many movies but I've never seen it in real life.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My summer hairstyles </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:05:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 20:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you listen to the Season 3 writers room? I sort of want a weekly podcast where it's a new writers room for a different show every week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 16:48:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Art Of Discourse is one of my favourites. It has my favourite Troy and Abed plots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 14:22:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually have a genuine Torque question I want to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:39:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This thing is going to be a lot UTU2TM references, which honestly I'm fine with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:34:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Listening now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess they don't have it anymore. They've been saying there going to let us pick flair for a while now so soon hopefully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tom Cruise </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Comedy Bang Bang Season 3 and The Birthday Boys Season 2 should now be on Netflix </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 13:28:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can anyone confirm? I don't currently have US Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 11:57:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think we have the plot for Justice League here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:52:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hitrecord.org could be an easy place to do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 13:28:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope second season. Bill Hader and Fourvel were the guests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 12:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He put vhs effects on the cuts but not the actual video. It's not hard to run a video through a vcr. All you need is a vcr, a DVD player and a AV to USB cable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:05:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh around the 20 minute mark. Unfortunately no uhh-ing but it is a little kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cmon it's Jurassic Park, there is more than one famous line. Which one do you want? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah maybe he got mixed up or he meant after they got the second season on ABC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 00:07:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Scrubs_characters#Recurring_characters

I can't find any characters missing from the 8th season on this. Are you sure it wasn't the 9th season? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:53:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I meant the best Lizzie McGuire one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:51:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's first year to the end of fourth year I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The downvotes are especially rude considering she seems to be trying to answer as many questions as possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:37:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard that the lines in the "kiss" scene in JW was improvised. Also that there were other versions of the scene. I was wondering what happened in them?

Also shoutout to /r/earwolf! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah you can have a cunt if it's a lighthearted one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:02:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the best fan theory I've ever read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:50:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like "NOT Farts" is going to be number 1 no matter what episodes come after this purely because of how much we loved Harris. Sort of like when the Oscars give an award for an actor who has died's last movie even if it wasn't really for that movie but the actor themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You just made me realise my problem with Spontaneanation. It takes me a while to realise what's happening in the scene if I stop paying attention for a minute. Improv4Humans doesn't have this problem because of the short scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 00:54:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When the stream went down as FIFA finally ended I lost it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In 2002 some kids recreated the whole of Jurassic Park shot for shot. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:23:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:53:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can think of two that looked animatronic and definitely would be easy to do with them. But yeah no massive animatronics for the big dinosaur like JP1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:21:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't think you're a cheapass just because you don't pay for video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:14:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! I was dreading that this would turn out like Utopia. I'm not surprised with how much marketing they've done for this though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 06:06:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is by far my favourite Paul Scheer character. I was really hoping we would return for Pitch Perfect 2 but sadly no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 22:20:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah they talk about their mother. Also the head girl and Lauren Lapkus talk about orders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There used to be a pretty popular tinychat for teens on reddit but no one is really on it nowadays. I think it would be quite nice to get it popular again for this Summer. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the tinchat: http://tinychat.com/khsunny786 and there is a subreddit at /r/teenagerstinychat

EDIT: A lot of people are coming and leaving when they see there is not many people on. If you come on you could just leave it on in the background until some people join :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the lack of ams and pms in this made me confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:19:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but in 2D animation aren't all the mouth shapes sort of ready to go for each character and they just choose whatever one fits for each frame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:16:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was the spike in 2008 for the Big Bang?

EDIT: Also it's cool the way you can see each season on the Big Bang Theory search. It seems to be decreasing in popularity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh wow I've never heard of them doing that before. Is it difficult? I figured it would be pretty easy nowadays to sync mouths up with different dubs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Staff Infection is on </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:07:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Kill The Baby" A hilarious dark web series. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:10:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 12:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In case anyone doesn't know Jake and Amir have a podcast that Benny Schwazzz and Middleditch are sometimes on.

Also does anyone know which Jake and Amir sketch it is where they keep holding up DVDs? I think Schwartz was in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 12:03:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was that Ellie Kemper in the check one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 11:07:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't believe this is a problem he has. It's like complaining about the old animation in the G.I Joe episode. But it's even worse considering the puppet tv shows still mostly have rods. The only thing were they are edited out is probably the latest Muppet movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 11:00:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay. Most of the time when I put out a video I lose a subscriber or two so I'm glad this one got me some. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 10:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 10:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I though the editing was a bit choppy but it's gotten a very nice response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 10:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I made it myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I used to play Club Penguin nearly everday so I made a video of myself revisiting it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:01:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 14:30:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here in Ireland It's Always Sunny has been gaining popularity since it's been added to Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drizzle, No Apologies, episode #191 of improv4humans with Matt Besser on Earwolf </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 11:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, if we got the subreddit to the front of /r/teenagers once I'd say it will have people on everynight until the end of summer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:05:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always thought it was weird how all the sneezing in the whole series took place in one episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 12:07:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/teenagerstinychat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 22:47:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have actually heard every episode of Harmontown except for that one. I believe I feel asleep at the start and it seemed Dan wasn't in the best mood. I'll have to go listen to it now I know Adomian came on, thanks very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 22:40:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is this from? I don't remember it in the Comedy Bang Bang episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:46:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The BOYS have just FIRED RON and the CATSKILLS ARE GOING HAYWIRE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 16:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's funny because here in Ireland we would associate guns with Texans more than Mexicans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is the original that he says "we have lots of Mexicans" or "lots of guns" because the second one works better from an irish standpoint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Entourageathon is ending now. The room is full of earwolf people, go watch the last episode with them. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 22:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 20:02:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suppose the idea is that he's a comedian and so it has an entertainment value to watch him. It's similar to how most people would be willing to watch a comedian do stand-up but not a normal person. 

I'll admit it's not for anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gil Ozeri is currently watching all of Entourage in a row. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 17:45:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:50:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The energy was just about to die and then Benny Schwaz showed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use Downcast but it's been very slow for me lately so I have a question about other podcast apps. When I'm catching up on podcasts I normally listen to 3/4 series at once and I listen to them in the order they were released in. So for example in my current relisten I'm on May 2013. So in downcast I click on Downloaded and all my podcast episodes (doesn't matter the series) are sorted by date. That means I listen to the one at the top.

In past experience podcast episodes were always sorted by the actual podcasts. Has this changed in most other apps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:48:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You get used to it very quickly. Eventually it gets to a point where if you changed to normal speed it all seems in slow motion. 

I should add I listen in 1.5 most of the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Will Change The Way You Watch Pulp Fiction </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 18:54:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 00:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha you've not watched "It's Always Sunny" have you? It's pretty dark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 14:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but it wasn't called that then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Postcoital Mess: LIVE at UCBsunset, episode #190 of improv4humans with Matt Besser on Earwolf </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 14:11:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 12:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what I was thinking. I remember the first time seeing the movie very clearly and being amazed at that first dinosaur scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 00:27:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's because it was Dan Harmon's voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 01:10:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am one of the people who had one of these videos that got sort of popular. I was thinking about doing a post about the information I can get about people who watch these videos on my youtube analytics page. Would anyone be interested? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wasn't it timely at the time of it originally airing?
Edit: Yeah Episode III hadn't come out yet at the original airing of that episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 20:17:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want someone to do a version of the movie like that. I'm sure with the original footage you'd be close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 18:36:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like a remaster with no dinosaurs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 16:40:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love how Ben dropped his character but kept the voice when he told that story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:46:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The subreddit was full of hatred for the show but also for others. Everyone kept giving out about people who were being positive about the show, but they didn't really exist. The subreddit spent most of it's time just discussing itself (much like this weeks Community) but in a bad way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You catch more of the jokes but the feeling of "jumping out of your seat and clapping your hands while you giggle" only happens during the first watch for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our lowest time was before you joined. This Subreddit during season 4 was a genuinely vile place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 09:40:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's my first thought when I see this as well. They all look well into their 20's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 09:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should. There are a bunch of these on YouTube but this is the earliest I could find.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 00:42:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It could very well be. But since the CBB episode was recorded a few weeks back it seems like too much of a coincidence they released this video today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 00:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should at least skim it. The moment when it's just his legs is hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Video] 29 years ago somebody taped their last day of High School. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 22:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 22:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Happy late-Birthday.
2. Try doing driving related things and see if it hurts.
3. If it does, you should probably cancel. The driving instructor won't mind. The decision will mostly only affect you so do what is best for you.
4. If it doesn't hurt GO PASS THAT TEST EYELIKEPIE2!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 22:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We need to get a post high on /r/teenagers. It should be easier since Sunny is a mod there ... but I don't know if he still comes here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 22:08:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I knew that though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [spoilers]Jon Snow Is Above The Rim </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 22:04:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 21:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was going to post this to /r/woahdude but I figured it might be too much noise and stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:36:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That would be a very tough one to do. Not really any long shots to use, he'd have to just be in the background.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:32:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd buy an album of just remixes of the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:32:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. Someone with a stronger computer could do a version of this with all 30 Shia's at once though. That would be amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That should be the name. If someone does a better version of this they should name it that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 16:33:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried to match the pauses together at certain spots but I think that's the only noticeable one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 09:55:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait Paul F. Tompkins isn't playing ball droid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I edited as many of the clips as I could on top of each other. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 09:49:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 12:20:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least she hasn't given 36 blowjobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 12:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That video was hilarious. I can't wait to hear the scene they do of it and the return of Eric! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 01:03:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Wasn't series 2 delayed because of the episode with all the shooting in an Americian high school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 23:30:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you seen Danger 5? It's very similar to Kung Fury. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 22:18:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's my second favourite one. The one where he keeps saying SnapLegs is my personal favourite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 21:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A network is basically the company inbetween you and youtube. They call themselves networks but I don't know if they fit the definition of one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Too Much Shia LaBeouf </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 17:59:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 09:35:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope most Youtubers join a network when they're big enough. Especially gaming youtubers, since the network can protect them from video game company's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 22:30:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whoever told you a million views is a grand was way off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apes Will Fight If We Must, episode #189 of improv4humans with Matt Besser on Earwolf </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 09:31:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 08:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does this mean Nathan For You isn't back this Summer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If House Of Mouse was made now it would probably have The Avengers and Star Wars characters </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:13:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NATHAN FIELDER STOPS BY DAVID DINEEN-PORTERS RETRO VIDEO ARCADE: HOT SISTER </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 19:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 23:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As somebody who doesn't anything about WOW or MMO culture I am very familiar with Leeroty Jenkins. It's not a very unknown thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 23:44:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The teenager character is so good because he's playing a character of himself playing a character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 16:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He also has a very important cameo at the end of "Tim and Eric's Billion Dollar Movie." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 14:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I'm sure that's it. The flower scene in the trailer rings familiar. It's just that the memory has been in head for so long it's changed a lot over the years. 

That's not an actual link to the film by the way. As far as I can tell it's not streaming anywhere online.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 13:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, you're just a "grower not a shower" as they say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 11:37:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You used the same link for Yo La Tengo and Once In A While. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 11:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess this must be it. I think I morphed the movie so much in my head though that watching the trailer isn't making me feel like I found it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 02:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope it wasn't animated. Live action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [TOMT] A kids movie/series I watched on Nickeleodeon in the early 2000's. A group of kids had a clubhouse that was in danger. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 01:55:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here is the very random plot points I remember.
-The main characters sister was part of the club
-The main character's crush may have been a princess but to prove it they had to prove a series of conditions one of which was that she was allergic to flowers. There was a dinner scene where the main character distracted the girl while the rest of the group tried to figure out if the girl was allergic.
-I believe in the end it turned out the sister was the princess. 
-At one point the clubhouse was split directly in two.

If anyone could help I would greatly appreciate it. I've been trying to find the name of this movie for the past 10 years.

I should also mention I watched it on the UK Nickleodeon and while I'm sure it wasn't british it could have been made anywhere else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 01:17:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll play it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 01:17:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was doing alright upvotes wise and then it all went downhill. My 15 seconds are over goodnight guitarknowitall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 23:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But carpe diem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 23:36:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This happens to me twice or three times a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 23:25:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One day man. One day... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When your crush catches you Googling her </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 23:17:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 23:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you get the owners permission? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 22:38:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> May I ask how you went about getting the location?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 19:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Waitress!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 19:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you mind explaining how the dog fight went above other comedies. I feel like I've seen that exact same scene before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! That was terrific too. I think the main reason there has been very little Rizzo is that the puppeteer for him now does Kermit and other Jim Henson characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember that! I got through the first minute of his "web series" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Moone Boy is about as Irish as Game Of Thrones in that it films here. You can put Father Ted in that same category except I don't think that was filmed here at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 21:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're cool, but in regards to your kickstarted maybe you should look into a Patreon. I wouldn't be able to pay either way but that seems more appropriate for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 21:31:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Rizzo! Rizzo has only had one line in the past 10 years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 21:30:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The muppets did that before Abed! But I'd say it was just a one off joke in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 21:29:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was a pigs in space movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:29:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some multicams cost more purely because they're often more popular and so the cast get paid much more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 20:09:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 15:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not too sure. It must have been after he stopped doing the "thanks for playing the theme song reggie" since that's how he used to start the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can we start this up again this Summer, please? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 15:22:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 14:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what people said when Scott retired "What's Up Hot Dog."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I feel like there hasn't been enough discussion about the fact that Scott has chosen a catchphrase. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 13:39:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's been a big staple of the show for a few years now and he finally chose one. It's a pretty big step in terms of canon of the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 22:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it uploaded anywhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 20:30:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [There are also these two without a match.](http://imgur.com/TL8Pfa9) I normally just randomly choose two out of these five and hope no one sees me with my feet close together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I have three odd socks that look similar but have no match. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 20:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 19:18:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The main difference seems to be that this one keeps forcing the message after the sex starts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 18:26:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah Candance has anyone but she never catches Phineas And Ferb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ham Hat - Under A 100 Views And Uploaded Two Years Ago </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 11:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 23:39:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's lower than the picture on the website? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 18:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well Grown Ups 2 isn't even close. That fight scene at the end drags on for quite a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 18:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's the deal with carnivores? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 18:13:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dan plays Minecraft a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:43:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know Jon was on so many MTV2 shows. Are they any good? I assume not from the way he used to plug them on Improv4Humans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 22:53:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone want to make a list of everyone's catchphrases? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:08:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I was inspired by your comment to finally press the button and get my favourite number 27. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 13:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oooh people from "No You Shut Up!." I want more puppeteers at earwolf so eventually we'll get a puppet episode of CBBTV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 10:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe I started regularly listening around the 3rd anniversary so this means from now on I have officially regularly listened for more than half of the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sonic Screwdriver </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:49:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bane? I may be filming a video where I do famous movie impressions for the year anniversary of this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eh..thanks. It does drag on way too long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 18:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am not like that at all. I regularly doodle on books that I'm in the middle of reading. I think the fact I do that is the same reason the line going down in the middle of the triangle being lobsided doesn't bother me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 16:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eh..Avengers Spoilers bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Easiest Fan Art Ever </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 16:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 13:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a much better version of a [video](http://youtu.be/wJr0u7GaDRw)  I did a while ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:04:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I.T Crowd is not a cult show. It's very popular here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:02:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you give rundown on what was and wasn't filmed live right in front of the audience in that episode. As far as I remember everything looked like a proper set except for the basement scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 19:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure that's at the start of the prisoner-monitor episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 19:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks like we need Superman IV The Quest For Peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 11:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> India, I guess, still do 4:3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 21:03:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's already out here!I loved it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 18:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WEtsMqBfSyg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 18:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got very excited with the guest in the season 3 finale.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sonic Screwdriver </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 14:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why are people commenting they haven't seen it yet?


I went to the midnight release last night where it followed the first Avengers and Winter Solider. Watching it in this order definitley improved the experience and there are some little things I definitley wouldn't have noticed if I hadn't seen Winter Solider directly beforehand.

It seemed everyone's problem with the movie would be too many characters but that wasn't a problem for me. My only gripe with the storylines were one pointless tangent that sort of comes back. The movie is structured very similarly to the first Avengers except for the beginning. The movie also had an extremely unexpected ending for me.


It was also very very funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 21:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad we.. uh.. managed to get it up here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 18:49:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lot's of Huell Howser videos on youtube for you. 
[This](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ImpGsMenmSs) one is probably the best and there is a reference to it in Huell Howser's last episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 20:59:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That cat video is obviously just a sketch ucb comedy made. You can see their watermark underneath the everything is terrible one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 16:58:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh wow I just realised how similar the plot seems to be to Dan's pitch. I hope this one has Superman going on holidays to a beach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 21:38:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like press conferences are the new dances at Greendale. We've had three this season so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:51:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tanks but no thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 19:17:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No this is definitely it. They must have forgotten the whole Changnesia thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 19:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Read the question again there mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 14:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The phase never truly leaves you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 14:20:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But our head mod lives in England, doesn't he? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 12:20:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really, let me try mine *********
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 12:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We play Countdown here in the UK. No Rachel Ryan though :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Guide to The Button </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 20:33:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 20:01:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least it's not here where there is only rain 24/7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 20:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I need to start playing The Sims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 15:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Time Bobby
Farts and Procreation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 14:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It keeps getting posted every 2/3 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 12:09:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never had an ad that was more than 30 seconds long and unskipable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 01:53:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep first season is well. One of the first movie homages in the series. Marge has the choice between bowling and Homer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Game Boy mystery PART 2- My personal favourite video on the whole of youtube. Biggest "wait for it" on the whole website </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 00:50:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 00:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to love Scotts fake games so much. David Cross doing Hollywood Facts is one of my favourite moments.

"Have you seriously not realised this is a bit, David?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lauren Adams "Gretchen" is doing an AMA right now! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 23:53:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 23:43:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At what point did you find out the show was going to be a Netflix Original? Did this change your role on the show much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> They should make a live action pokemon movie where the actor who plays Brock always has their eyes closed. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 22:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Knock Knock - It's Joe Lo Truglio </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 21:45:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do you have to watch the show in the correct order? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 21:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I stopped watching season 1 but I forget where I was. Can I just jump into whatever episode appears interesting to me or is there a strict continuity in later episodes. I remember the first few episodes being quite form free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 17:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's all about whether you click on it or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 13:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to say it was this, especially considering she played Paul's wife on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are your favourite "classic" YouTube videos? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 13:57:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean those early youtube videos you used to watch again and again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 12:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's 5 seconds and then you get to skip it. Who gives a shit what the ads are for if it means money for the creator. Uninstall Adblock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 12:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad to see these changes
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New episode of "Adam Goldberg: Programmed to Annoy" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I haven't been watching that much Yogscast since Christmas? Slowly getting back into it, so any hilarious moments I probably missed? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 22:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What type of jokes do seals like? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 17:48:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Suh-real humour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's your favourite dick joke from a tv show? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 21:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I con't belieb dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I con't belieb dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:26:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I con't belieb dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:25:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I con't belieb dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I con't belieb dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:25:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I con't belieb dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I con't belieb dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:25:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I con't belieb dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:25:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I con't belieb dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How would you describe the physical appearance of Victor and Tiny? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 13:08:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I'm finally going to get around to animating The Victor Podcast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 01:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd always known it as fast five, fast and furious six and furious 7.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 22:14:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Another other podcast appearance was an episode of Harmentown he appeared on. Another example of him showing up, being hilarious and just getting on with everybody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 22:05:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You make a 3D model of the whole set though couldn't you? It would take a lot of work but you could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 22:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait so they used the same title sequence for 6 and 7? Why??? I liked the fact each was different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 13:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, oh no. I wonder how I got so many Swedish subscribers in the first place. Now I've lost them all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 13:03:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Sorry,] (http://www.boards.ie/vbulletin/showthread.php?p=77421375) it doesn't seem to be available here. I may buy some Swedish food next time I'm in IKEA though and try it in a video.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 10:50:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two people at most normally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 00:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What? I'm not even going to try understand this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! How bad was my speaking at the end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hey, You Swedish People </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:06:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I still haven't listened to all of Hollywood Handbook. I'm still in 2013 on my backlog so I'm only listening to The Reality Show Show from them right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bababooey? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:51:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is this reference, I've seen it all over the sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 01:54:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, you can show a naked doodle of a skeleton woman but not a normal woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 01:53:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was the Zooks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 11:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 13:59:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or his own p-cast/podcasting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 13:04:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess PFT just dropped in for a few minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 20:50:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hope? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are there any other reddit teenager tinychats or something like it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 17:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I normally use this in the summer when people are on but I have two weeks off school now and no one goes on this during the year so I have nowhere to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 16:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds like that actually... went.. pretty well. Don't question it when things go well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 16:55:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Staring into your soul.](http://imgur.com/ZKPUihN) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 16:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations! Do you have a link to the film? I'd love to check it out. I was just in a film festival the other week. It was amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 16:48:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here, we can always use calculators. Is there certain questions where you have to show you didn't use one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 19:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so cool. Not long left to vote too. It was really interesting learning about all of the different stuff. I think I may have voted for too many things to even make a difference! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 22:30:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks I hope so. I have exactly a year today to get my film portfolio for college ready! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 22:19:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hate season 3 Abed, he's extremely frustrating. He seems more disconnected from reality than at the start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A short film I made got into a film festival and I got to watch it on the big screen. I feel like I've already accomplished a life goal! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 22:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't win anything for it so my family seem to assume I'm upset but it was so great to see it in the cinema I don't really care. I just really wanted to share how happy I am with you guys. Have ye accomplished anything that you thought would be a life long goal?

[This] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v7GakCW6MWY)  is the film if any of you are interested in watching by the way. It's not very long or very good but I enjoyed making it a lot.
(https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v7GakCW6MWY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 22:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but that was the last creepy non-human thing he did right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Abed's development the past two seasons has been amazing. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 21:04:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems pretty obvious that Abed has actually changed a lot since the start of the series, something that wasn't that obvious in series 3. Now he smiles and laughs a lot more and seems to have developed a very serious relationship with Annie. With Troy it never felt like he was really friends with him and understood what that meant but now Abed has grown a lot.

I can't wait to see how much he changes in the future season/seasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 08:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe the movie will be about the group travelling back in time and placing the Greendale flag in a bunch of places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 18:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First time I heard a character in CBB, I had no idea it was character for so long and I was freaked out I hadn't heard of this city if big people. Listening to it now I feel so stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 09:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Question. I wear headphones a lot but listen at an extremely low level. Does this make the chances of this happening much lower or is it about the constant noise more than the volume? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 20:37:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's the podcast or commentary? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 17:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've heard mention of a podcast or commentary type thing for the show. I've done some googling but I can't find it. Can anyone explain what it is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 07:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did the title different for each one so at least one would be right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Late Late Late Show </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 20:46:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An Irishman, a Scottish-man and a English man walk into a bar... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 20:29:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the bar they meet an Americian man. He's pleased to meet them and introduces them to a Spanish man and a German man. There is a Mexician man nearby but he's too nervous to introduce himself. 

The six men decide to get a drink from the bartender who is a French man. Once seated together they begin to tell stories of their home countries, explain their cultures and their ways. The German man decided to head into the bathroom because he's quite thirsty. This subject confuses the Irishman, the Englishman and the Scottishman for they have never gone to the bathroom when thirsty before. The Americian man, the Spanish man and the German man laugh for this practise is very common in this bar.

All six head into the bathroom, inside there is an Africian man. The Americian man, the Spanish man and the German man begin to suck the blood out of the Africian man. The Africian man screams. Eventually all of the men join in. 

After a few minutes the shy Mexician man wanders in and says "Is there any room for a little Mexician to suck some of this Africian mans blood."

The American man says "Sure what shall we build around this man."
And then the English man says "Fencing." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 20:26:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hasn't it been used way more recently than that? I remember Dan did it like twice in a recent show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 18:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, that's it! His craziness is so much better when he's not all in your face about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 18:37:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chang was so good throughout both episodes. I really liked him during season 5 too right up until near the end. Chang as a villain is so much worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 10:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jonathan Banks didn't make it in last year. I think they like to wait a year before putting them in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 22:12:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As anyone from outside the U.S. gotten one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some good teen/high school movies? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 19:37:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bad Jokes As Gaeilge </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 19:20:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>