<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5580</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i recently saw ant-man and this is what the fight scenes reminded me of </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 13:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://youtu.be/YfchQpxeGyo

yeah go ahead and laugh, also before anyone breaks out the attacks, i'd like to point out i enjoyed ant-man, it was very charming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what movie made you aware of chris pine? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:16:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for me it was star trek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whats wrong with my train_subject5580 viewing order

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:00:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whats wrong with my train_subject5580 viewing order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> presenting the train_subject5580 viewing order! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:56:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> take them to the theater </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 09:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> every star wars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:35:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You underestimate my power! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you mean? And btw our flair is relevant to each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [META] I want episode VII to feel unique, and original </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so if this is a tv movie, technically it shouldnt even be on r/movies, it should be on r/television </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Idea on how to make a fourth trilogy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:57:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Start with episode XIII and make XIV, and XV, so that way makers of a fifth trilogy will have the challenge of making episode X-XII, think about it, george Lucas had a blank slate for the prequel trilogy, he just had to make the ending tie into the beginning of the original trilogy, what I'm saying here is to link together both a hypothetical episode X to a hypothetical episode XIII </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> star wars related shower thought- what does a drought on kamino look like? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 10:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EDIT: that is, what does it look like with no rain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is star trek V: the final frontier canon? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:05:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just wondering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 07:11:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they might be on to something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Some other poster asked if episode 7 will have wipe transitions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 05:47:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i notice in movie prequels theres always more of something </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 07:51:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for example

in the star wars prequel trilogy theres more lightsabers

in the flintstones in viva rock vegas theres more of those shells they use for currency

and in monsters university theres more of those scream canisters

anyone think theres a connection, or am i just mental? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 11:51:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> deleted scenes you say? the same person who deleted all referances to lasagna probably deleted that one scene from episode 3 where yoda starts his exile to dagobah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is there lasagna in star wars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 11:47:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think IT is known as a "mummy dressed as snow white" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:05:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what do you mean "too much"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:01:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ''just like'' isnt something to judge someones opinion over, if you read professional critic reviews, clearly they enjoy them, also think about the insults the cast gets everyday, chris pine getting called wooden, zach quinto getting called homophobic slurs, and zoe saldana getting called a slut. you can not stop me from enjoying them dont even try!!! you can respond back to me but dont talk me out of not enjoying them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:20:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i just like the cinematography, tthe cast and i like the sense of wonder, so unlike you im able to enjoy a movie, i dare you to top that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:57:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i like it for every reason it gets criticised, so my review would be the polar opposite of a haters review </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm saying that they did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> when episode 7 comes out, will the saga films be released on individual blu rays? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 13:27:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im only asking because im hoping that disney doesnt change the movies any further. and if they do they should put in that new fanfare for the lucasfilm logo. but keep the movies otherwise the same as the blu rays that came before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 11:55:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you know its funny, i tell people that the reboot cast gets persecuted everyday, implying they should sympathize with them. im worried that zach quinto gets called homophobic slurs, and zoe saldana gets called sexist things like 'slut' and 'whore'. and chris pine gets called names im sure but i dont know what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 10:09:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im not going to even bother anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> har har har, lensflare joke, you mustve spent alot of time coming up with that, you should audition for SNL, youll be the next eddie murphy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> this is why im overprotective about the jj abrams star trek movies x-post from r/movies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:06:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> this is why im overprotective of the star trek reboots </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:56:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ever since i saw this snl skit back in 2009, i was freaking phsyched to see the new reboot, and then this snl skit came and shat on my excitement:

http://www.traileraddict.com/star-trek-xi/snl-weekend-update

now after i actually saw the movie, ive been saying to reboot haters that i hate them, i wish they were all dead etc. etc. but now im thinking its not worth it, ill never convince the haters to stop hating the star trek reboots, i am literally sobbing at my defeat! ive told haters about the rave reviews, jj abrams charity work, NOTHING, they still hate the reboots. every attempt ive made to convert the haters FAILED!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is it ok if i like the jj abrams star trek movies? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you know the drill, im sick of hearing the criticisms, yada yada yada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:17:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> also jj no being a fan has nothing to do with the quality of the movie, i dont care that he likes star wars more, i am trying to keep reboot haters like you persecuting us reboot fans! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:10:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this proves my point that reboot haters will never change, i bet you and your wife will conceive a reboot haterling, and raise him to be a hater just like you,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> obviously you dont read **professional** critic reviews, and clearly the majority of **PROFESSIONAL** CRITICS, enjoy it, and seeing as youre not a professional critic yourself your criticism means nothing to me, ill continue to enjoy it along with other fans, and you can do nothing to stop us, i speak for reboot fans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> whats the use getting excited about star trek beyond? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 07:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> all the reboot haters will hate it regardless if a fan writes it or not. ever since 2009 ive been telling the haters that it was good and i like it, and ive been seen as a bully, they should be kissing their asses!!! they saved their franchise!!!! i swear to god if i hear ONE MORE TIME that it doesnt follow gene roddenberrys utopian vision of the future i will scream and commit suicide!! thats right i hate reboot star trek criticism THAT much. they will probably never change!!! theyll marry other rboot haters, have children and raise them to hate the reboots then we'll have anothergeneration of reboot haters!! ITS FUCKING BULLSHIT!!!!! i just wnt people to be grateful, but nooo the reboot haters are too busy wishing they couldve sucked leonard nimoys geriatric cock before he died. i hate star trek reboot haters, hate them hate them HATE THEM, i hate the parents who birthed them and the children theyll raise!!! i would read trekkers reviews but i prefer going to professional critics (you know people who go to movies nearly daily) oh god if all reboot haters died of cancer that would be so awesome. i mean look at this video! and youll see who REALLY doesnt get star trek (hint:it isnt jj abrams or bob orci)

https://youtu.be/YRWUeUK6kKQ

there! now you see that jj has a heart, which is an alien concept to reboot haters. im sick of hearing criticism about the writing, im sick of hearing criticism about the cast, im sick of criticism of jj abrams!!!! so bottom line if you dont like it, why didnt they come to YOU to make it, so fuck all reboot haters to damnation of mankind!! i like the reboots DEAL WITH IT!!! i liked the stories, i liked the new look, and i liked the cast. oh god that would be so awesome if star trek reboot criticism was outlawed and made illegal. i would be so happy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 07:21:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same here,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 06:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh god that singer, after that barney the dinosaur one that was it for me, ive seen enough. and then the catdog video comes around, and im like "holy fuck, no! they didnt," it was one of my favorite cartoons of all time, and that inspired me to make this post, to check to see if my fears were confirmed, and since they are i havnt a reason to watch it, i have a feeling there will be a day, like i swore to myself that id never see the human centipede (the first one) and low and behold me and my parents watched it together. ill never see the next two human centipede movies, just like ill never watch the scientifically accurate catdog video (i hope) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:10:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats one of my favorite anime episodes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 11:23:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> uuuuhhhh yeah im not watching this video then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 10:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what does "technically yes" mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:45:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this not a fun time for train_subject5580 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Question about powerline from goofy movie </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 13:19:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does powerline have Marfan syndrome? Because he lacks meat on those bones, and he's unusually taller than most other characters in the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 14:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a bummer, he was a good actor too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what movie made you aware of natalie portman? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 07:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for me it was star wars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> man, i SERIOUSLY need to check legends more often </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what other sports are there in star wars? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:21:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> besides podracing, i know in episode 2 when obi-wan ran into that 'sports cantina' i guess ill call it. there were sports playing on the screens, i just never learned the names of said televised sports, and i would love to know their names </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 06:03:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> darth maul looks good with his beard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:30:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i just got served </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 11:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well of course if youve seen the movie, you remember other stuff, but the majority of people remember the dancing scene the most, dont get me wrong its an excellent movie, but like i said its a one scene wonder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what people remember from 'risky business' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 10:56:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 99%- the underwear dancing scene

1%- everything else

risky business is a one scene wonder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> whats that ship from the beginning of episode II called? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 08:43:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the one that looks like a WWII bomber </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 04:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but heres the thing though, i care more for the eventually to be 9 saga movies, than the anthology films. when i think the saga movies i think bacardi rum, when i think the anthology films i think cheap champagne. im not saying the anthology films will be BAD, its just that i dont feel theyll be neccessary for like a viewing party or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 04:25:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i thought they said there would be like 4 or 5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> im a little weary of all the spinoff films in development </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i mean i probably WILL see them, and buy the blu rays, but if i have a marathon of star wars ill probably just watch the saga films, and leave the spinoff films out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 09:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and the saga will be a trilogy of trilogies, on a side note star wars is all about trilogies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:17:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't wanna be a type A fan like me? We could've been friends, if you're a type A fan you have 6 count em 6! (And more) movies to watch! :D a marathon can last a week a WEEK I say! But that's just the upside, and im a glass half full person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't wanna be a type A fan like me? We could've been friends, if you're a type A fan you have 6 count em 6! (And more) movies to watch! :D a marathon can last a week a WEEK I say! But that's just the upside, and im a glass half full person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 09:31:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh the feels, THE FEELS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 08:00:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what makes you say that? i ask because liam neeson as that character is like burned into my brain so im curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:19:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "This is why i hate flying" - obi wan episode 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> id go for a count dooku movie set before episode 1 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 06:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i hope some actor out there looks like a young christopher lee (i think thats who played dooku) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 06:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a vader movie set between III and IV you say? that would be cool, they could probably show vader looking at photos. but i dont know im a little overwhelmed with how much spinoff films theyre making, but we'll see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 04:13:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My reaction was "alright now I don't have to watch just 6 Star Wars movies!!" But then it hit me, the sequel trilogy will divide the Star Wars fan base in the same way the prequel trilogy did. And if and when it does, I'll be ready </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> idea for episode IX ending </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 12:13:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the as yet to be named human badguys are defeated and are somehow put on a meteorite, while the heroes are celebrating, the meteorite lands on earth killing the dinosaurs and the badguys decide they should populate the planet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 11:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well, i USED to figure, since the series takes place in a galaxy far far away like the intro says, i thought they were humanoid aliens, as opposed to humans like you and me, so NOW my question is, since they are human, what did they evolve from?, since there's no primates in that part of the galaxy and earth is too far away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [META] TIL the humanoid creatures in star wars are called 'humans' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 10:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 06:09:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 06:02:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a zabrak you say? ive never heard of that race until you brought it up (i only follow the movies, because i think following the movies is easier, what can i say, im a simple guy), i just thought darth maul was a crazy looking freak of nature. when theyre being born do they damage the birth canal with the horns? yeah im such a noob i know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 05:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maul was never a Jedi...

ok bad example, if he were like an accountant (theres currency in star wars, right?) before he was a sith, id be surprised </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> did darth maul always look like that? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 21:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> with the horns and face pattern, because man if he used to be a jedi knight himself id be surprised, but then again jedi knights are (more or less) good judges of character. i mean when sidious approached him was he like, "join the dark side, and give you horn implants and a face tattoo." i dont know, i ask only because a character like darth maul just looks like he can only be a sith lord, and nothing else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 09:54:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whats the copyright date on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what does coruscant do about pollution and smog? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 08:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i mean in episode 1 they mention the entire planet is one big city, and then i wondered what they do for oxygen and water, then someone else mentioned that they import oxygen and water, and NOW im wondering about the pollution, like how do they manage it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> advice for room for error on a job or project </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:13:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dont base your room for error around how often you think people will look in certain spot, because there will be times where people will find them and thats all theyll notice whenever they walk into a room. MY advice for room for error should be based on how too big a piece of material is, its better to have too big a piece than too little a piece because you can trim a too big piece, whereas a too little piece is wasting money and material </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 08:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think it could go either way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> if they make a hunter x hunter live action adaptation who should this man play? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 07:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/gallery/h8A09QY

https://youtu.be/qMVJnWd4idE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 06:49:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well i wouldnt say DEFENSIVE about any one mcu movie necessarily, but there was this on youtube troll whod make fun of people who enjoyed iron man 3, which was mildly displeasing, they got banned. but i digress, i thought age of ultron was GOOD, its just the plot was a little weaker than the first avengers movie. if the first avengers is casino royale, and age of ultron was quantum of solace, i hope infinity war part 1 is skyfall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 04:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when we see some i cant say, but actual size ant man figures will be a major choking hazard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 00:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is he william h macy's character from 'mystery men'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> halloween costume ideas yet again </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 08:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (note: some halloween costume ideas in this post may have been in my past submissions)

homestar runner- eric roberts as the master

coach z - powerline (from 'a goofy movie')

the cheat - the midget from men without hats safety dance video

strong bad - max headroom

marzipan - jack in the box homer simpson

pom pom - jiminy glick

strong sad - garth algar

bubs - buzz lightyear

strong mad - donkey kong

the poopsmith - derek zoolander

the KOT - don king

homsar - 'yip yip yip' alien from sesame street

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 10:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm saying that I can't watch the first 6 until episode 7 is nearly in theaters, because if I watch them now, an wait until episode 7 I won't have the story fresh in my mind because of the huge time I've been waiting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ever since i saw the star wars episode 7 trailer... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 07:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ive been so ready to watch the first 6 star wars movies so bad i probably need to go to rehab, star wars is like crack to me. However, episode 7 doesnt come out until december, and seeing as how i like to have a story fresh in my mind i wouldnt be able to watch the first 6 movies out of morality, and that is a situation what i affectionately refer to as 'fucking bullshit', any questions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 10:08:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Woah scary :0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Comment about craig schwartz in 'being John malkovich' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 10:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's played by John cusack, he's a puppeteer, but my first look at him gave me the impression that his passion was writing accordion based song parodies, amirite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does the reboot cast get a lot of negative tweets at all? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 11:42:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what do i do if someone insults a fandom which i am part of </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 06:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> like on imdb there are like these 2 users who like insulted this fanbase that im part of (which i wont say). one said "intelligent moviegoers didnt see that movie" and "theyre (franchise) fans of course theyll eat it up theyre like sheep" and the other was like "oh man if they do a (franchise) then im done with this series" and it really hurt me so, and now im bashing my head against a wall over having read such nasty things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 07:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nimoy approved quinto, END OF DISCUSSION, but then again youre a reboot hater, and they never want to listen to reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 06:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> are you saying jj abrams works for al qaeda? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 05:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i like how theyre doing this as a continuation, kinda like that shaft movie from 2000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 05:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> star wars episode IV a new hope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 05:42:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i give it a 7.9 out of 10, i wanted to give it a higher score, but the plot seemed like it caught the quantum of solace virus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i have confession to make </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 00:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 07:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> steve martin- that looney toons movie, leap of faith, the prince of egypt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 10:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't doubt Abrams 1 percent, its just that I'm emotionally prepared for the same bullshit that I've been hearing for 16 years and I'm sick of it! There's gonna be a third trilogy and the fanbase will be divided even further! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> this one time i was watching the seinfeld episode "the pick" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 09:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and i was like "how come (jerrys girlfriend) is making such a huge stink over that?" and my parents are like, "because she thought he picked his nose, but he didnt" and then i asked "yeah but even if he DID pick his nose, why would she freak out over it anyway?" and then theyre like "BECAUSE PICKING NOSES IS GROSS!! THATS WHY!" and then i shrugged "fair enough" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 05:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> me myself and irene </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 07:29:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> youre missing my point, when was the last time YOU did someone a kindness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 07:22:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he did them a kindness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 06:56:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> absolutely nothing but he did them a kindness, which alot of people are incapable of doing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> to anyone who believes star wars episode 7 will be bad or dissappointing or thinks jj abrams is a bad director, remember this story </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 06:18:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [this story here](http://comicbook.com/2015/04/16/jj-abrams-buys-pizza-for-everyone-waiting-in-line-at-star-wars-c/) should shed some light on the subject. of course some of you may say, this is a publicity stunt, or hes bribing the fans , or other bullshit heartless things like that. what would YOU DO if a famous hollwood director bought YOU food? huh? of course the movie doesnt even come out for another 8 months, i shouldnt even be having this discussion, yet. just remember this story when you walk out of episode 7 (when it comes out of course) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 09:30:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do not know any serious Star Wars fan who truly enjoyed films 1-3.

you do now! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> my predictions for when star wars episode 7 gets released </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 08:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i predict i will accept it equally with episodes 1-6 and meanwhile there will be people online or on blogs putting a puss on, bitching about how its in league with the prequel trilogy, and how jj abrams is a bad director, and ruined star trek and other such bullshit.But at this point its no use getting upset or acting surprised. there will be people disliking a star wars regardless of what trilogy its part of. i for one enjoy all o them. i dont know how to end this so ill just leave it at that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> do kids watch daredevil? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 08:57:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not that i have kids of my own but if theres like overprotective parents out there, and their kids are into the mcu, would their parents research this show and be like "no (son/daughter) you cant watch it youre not old enough" "aw but its in the mcu'' "i dont give a shit!, you are not old enough, (we the parents) will watch it after you go to bed" see what i mean, before you call me an idiot or whatever, id like to point out i enjoy daredevil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> a game where you solve picture puzzles in weird and quirky ways </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 05:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well, no, BUT i would reccomend it just for the events sake, because youll recognize some of them. (especially, the effects of the events of CA: the winter soldier on agents of sheild) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 04:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well that doesn't prove that civil war is filming, it might just be a hanging blue tarp... oh wait nevermind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 10:12:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> willy wanka, is that what people in england call him? (which is weird because that story is FROM england) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 09:13:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> to answer your question, no they do not know, and i predict when the gotg eventually meet the avengers, quill will be like confused gandalf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 08:46:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if i had to choose, inside out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> more halloween costume ideas </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 06:29:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> homestar runner - john bender

strong sad - powerline 

coach z - ali g

marzipan - mona lisa

strong bad - max headroom

the cheat- ren hoek

the poopsmith- a cyberman

strong mad- mark mcguire

the KOT - zz top member

pom pom - jim carrey as the riddler

bubs - bananaman

homsar- 'cool' lisa simpson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 06:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good point,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ok they must mention the gotg on aos!! or else im gonna flip one!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 05:27:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> like that kree that recently came to earth with the amnesia thing,(whos name i dont remember), couldve brought like a video document of some kind showing that battle on nova prime, and coulson would be like, "was that a raccoon? and a tree creature?" you get the idea, the reasdon why i bring this up is because theres not really a whole lot connecting GOTG with the avengers and sheild, beyond a few references to other mcu movies and thanos, and thats pretty much it. the point im getting to is the GOTG  so far just EXIST, but imo there needs to be some mention on aos or something to make a good strong connection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> this one time i did an image search on perducci on google images </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 07:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there were recurring images of goofy appearing, can someone explain please, i mean try it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 05:51:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i read that ant man is set before and during phase 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 05:50:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and i read somewhere that ant man is set before or during phase 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 05:43:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah but for all we know Rocket in GOTH couldve been bipedal for 6 or 7 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Idea for an ant-man post credits scene </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 08:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First the lead up: an alien crew and its captain visit earth for some reason and they talk to dr pym, and one of them asks "say doc, do you think you can get us a raccoon, we need a test subject for some experiments," dr pym says "ummm sure but why a raccoon?" Alien says "because, we want to" then he gets them said raccoon and the aliens leave

The actual scene: we go back to the aliens in their ship and there's a mini montage of hacking and slicing stitching etc... But then the raccoon awakes and the aliens look over it all amazed and shit, and we cut to the raccoon and its revealed to be rocket from GOTG, and then rocket reacts "oh why do I feel different, and why am I speaking?" Fade to black </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 04:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not according to acdc-1989 and his supposed followers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is it ok if i like the daniel craig james bond movies? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 04:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i came to the conclusion that daniel craig haters are sociopaths, i enjo them but whenever someone critisises them they gather in a group, making me feel like an outcast. and worse yet theres a user on imdb that copies and pastes the same criticism over and over again, i want him to die, and he goes by acdc-1989 hes probably the leader of the daniel craig haters, hes probably having a rally as we speak, and theyre probably burning a daniel craig dummy on a string and poking it with spears. and theyre probably planning on burning down dvd sections in all targets, walmarts, kmarts, etc. and get this, Bump, is their slogan probably, because acdc-1989 starts a topic and just says bump the other self posts. all im saying is as soon as you find out someones a daniel craig hater. stop being friends with them immediately, theyre evil and heartless, thank you, if theres a valid reason why i shouldnt like the daniel craig james bond movies please state why please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do I come to terms with the existence of reboot haters? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 09:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is why I think Star Trek reboot haters are bad people </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 00:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> search.yahoo.com/search?fr=mcafee type=B210US0D20111102 p=star+trek+weekend+udate+snl

this is the video where it started it all, now im searching for reboot haters and teaching them a lesson ever since, now you see why i hate people who dislike the reboots, its because theyre ASSHOLES!! and theyre trying to ruin jj abrams career, by doing this so i ask for all haters to stop being haters!!!! i want all criticisms to stop!!!! thank you, not any one of you will amke me not like the reboots i know your game!! you want jj abrams to suffer and bob orci and jurtzman to suffer, well i wont have it!! thats how careers get ruined. dont you see? btw i enjoyed into darkness, and no one i repeat NO ONE will try to convince me otherwise, you may be thinking "but people have different opinions" Adolf hitler had an OPINION, kkk members have an OPINION, terrorists have OPINIONS. People have been telling me that for years and it's brought me nothing but misery, so I'm warning you Star Trek reboot haters, I'm on to you, someday I'll catch you all having a rally burning a jj Abrams dummy on a string and poking it with spears, and lynching a reboot fan, LIKE ME!! So don't be surprised if I report you to a hate crime division </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well in that case i see your imgur image and a raise you:

http://youtu.be/YRWUeUK6kKQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:33:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whats the context of you posting that image? is it my rambling or my (apparent) nonsense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> reboot haters are forming an underground group, planning an attack against bad robot and all involved, they may be planning on an attack on, reboot fans AS WE SPEAK!! you may be thinking ''youve been watching too many marvel movies'' but it could happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:21:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i mean i wouldnt be surprised if reboot haters formed a kkk-esque group, where they lynch and burn reboot fans! or have nazi-esque rallys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and btw im not orci, im just a really frustrated person who enjoys movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:19:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but theres people like you being an ungrateful shit!! i mean it got rave reviews for christs sake, you only need to be literate to see that!!its not rocket science </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> THIS is the reason why i hate abrams trek criticism!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:12:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 04:58:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> look all im saying is treat people who like the reboots like you would want to be treated, dont treat them like lesser human beings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 19:23:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sure you and other reboot haters don't meet in an underground arena to hold rally's where your unnamed leader gives anti reboot speeches. And you salute him a la' the nazis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 18:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I Mean whenever someone insults the reboots I just wish a painful death upon them. And I don't know why, it's like will thy be that way forever? I mean you may be saying "why are you wasting your breath saying some few people didn't like a movie?" Well before you respond to that, is it true that:

a) reboot haters are sociopaths

b)burn jj Abrams effigies kinda like the KKK 

c) lynch reboot fans also like the kkk from a speeding car

d) there's a conspiracy to destroy anyone and anything involved with the reboots?

e) reboot haters are conspiring to hack paramount 

Are any of these true? Why or why not
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 09:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EThink about it this way, if you were a filmmaker and someone with a terminal disease, was going to die before the films premiere, would you screen the film for them? Or would you be willing to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 09:27:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well if you'd actually watch the video, he said te patient wanted to watch it, and he enjoyed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hey reboot haters prepare to be one no longer!!!! (Leonard nimoy would've wanted you to see this) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 09:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 12:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First, Marvel did not buy Spider-Man back. They got the right to use the character in their films and discuss with Sony how to use the character. That's very different from owning all the rights.

fuck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> why doesnt the wikipedia mcu page not list spider man, yet theres all this big news that marvel bought back spider man </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 09:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> like scroll down to the 'films' section

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marvel_Cinematic_Universe

i mean wtf man!? however the mcu wiki is up to date

http://marvelcinematicuniverse.wikia.com/wiki/Phase_Three

i mean what gives who do i believe? AND to add insult to injury check out this paragraph from the list of mcu films from wikipedia:

In December 2014, emails between Sony Pictures Entertainment Co-Chairman Amy Pascal and president Doug Belgrad were released after the November hacking of Sony's computers, stating that Sony wanted Marvel to produce a new trilogy of Spider-Man movies while Sony retains "creative control, marketing and distribution". Marvel also wanted to include Spider-Man in Captain America: Civil War. However, discussions between Sony and Marvel broke down, with Sony wanting to go ahead with its already planned slate of Spider-Man films.[284]

i mean wtf!? who do i believe? the moderator for that page is probably sipping some scotch on the rocks being entertained for his not up to date page </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 05:46:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the boondock saints </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-13 08:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> man, the incredible hulk is the one mcu movie that gets the LEAST love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> two concerns about spiderman joining the mcu </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-13 04:47:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. how will they have the daily bugle, if at all? because i dont recall any mention of the daily bugle in any previous mcu media, they'll need to introduce the daily bugle at some point, or at the very least show an adult peter parker looking back on his life, and in a flashback show a young peter parker working there and then in present day say it closed down, or something

2. if they have j. jonah jameson, how strong  will his dislike for spider man be? because if there's other superheroes he'd be totally fine with it.
"i really hate spiderman!" "but sir we report on the avengers all the time, and you seem totally fine with them.'' "oh yeah, alright then no harm done.''

see what i mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 09:23:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh yeah i saw that deviant art thing too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> (belated) idea for costumes for a halloween episode </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 08:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> homestar runner - mr snrub

coach z - 'intergalactic' beastie boys member

the cheat - pikachu

strong bad - jack skellington

marzipan - the violinist from 'deus-suds and soda'

pom pom - a metroid

strong sad - zz top member

bubs - peter gabriel

strong mad - borg cube

the poopsmith - powerline 

the KOT - chef boyardee

homsar - engineer from 'conjunction junction' 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 00:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> believe whatever you want but, this guy is a clever, imposter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 00:13:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this guy is tring to frame me ill report him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-08 04:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the vision doesnt look too shabby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> when was the last time the super mario bros. actually did a plumbing job? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-01 03:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> their yelp reviews must be MURDEROUS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> a question why maximiliano hernandez is on the americans </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 05:11:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> did his character in the marvel cinematic universe get killed off, so he can be on this show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i pray the man featured in this video be a guest star on the simpsons </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 04:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://youtu.be/qMVJnWd4idE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 06:58:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but im on reddit where he cant get me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 04:59:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> eraserhead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> if i'm lucky that is </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 01:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 07:25:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh its ON NOW!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is it ok if i liked avatar? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 05:09:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because i get REALLY fucking tired of people bitching about it, i wish they were suffering for the rest of their days, especially doug walker, oh god do i hate doug walker, hes probably the leader of the avatar haters, they probably have big ralleys in some huge undeground or abandonned auditorium, with huge pictures of doug everywhere, with him up on a pedestal, giving huge anti avatar speeches, i also surely believe he has a conservative agenda which he uses with his nostalgia critic character, because not only avatar with a liberal message he bashed, he bashes OTHER movies with liberal agendas too, district 9 BASHED IT, a troll in central park BASHED IT, and he likes chuck norris whos another conservative jackass. now you may be thinking, "theres haters for star wars, for the godfather, for annie hall, for star wars, for robocop, theres a hater for EVERY movie" well youre right, but i liiked avatar and i will make sure no one will influece me otherwise, ill open a big can of whoopass! on the next person who says, "the story sucks", or "its only made to look pretty", or "theyre smurfs" or other bullshit like that, doug walker is probably gathering followers for his anti liberal cult as we speak! if im wrong about ANY of these please state why, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-25 01:48:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i saw it today and it was ok, not a classic but funny at times, even hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> starting a movie series from the beginning, and starting a movie series from the middle </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-24 03:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if you start one from the beginning you'll be like her:
https://i.imgflip.com/25w8.jpg
if you start one from the middle you'll be like him:
https://i.imgflip.com/grb00.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-24 03:49:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they didn't wanna pay rick baker? i mean granted it was convincing, but i mean c'mon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> my take on whether the pokemon movies (past movies 1 and 2) are canon to the anime or not </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-20 11:31:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> an age old fan question "are the pokemon movies (past movies 1 and 2) true canon to the anime?" i would say 'no', BUT they complement their respective seasons so well, they may as well be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-16 03:30:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> are the atmosphere and characters the same as you imagined from the books? id say 'close enough' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> where im from, "senioritis" is called "turning into a lazy sack of shit" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 05:50:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-04 12:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i dont want to live on this planet anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> While I was watching 'the grand Budapest hotel' the other day </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 03:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-01 03:54:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well its not so much that people are telling me i cant like them, its just that the haters are everywhere and they wont give up, making me feel like a jackass,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 01:22:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He needs to rethink his life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> how come the name of a food is never insight as to where it originated? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 06:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a la english muffins, french toast, german chocolate cake, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> remember when IFC was the 'Independent Film Channel'? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 07:44:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> now it's the 'whatever the hell we wanna show' channel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is it ok if i like the star trek reboots? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-24 18:09:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you know the rest
if so why?
if not why?
please dont hesitate
and look at my other posts to get an idea of my ordeal, also how can i help live with people who dont like them? and how can i get some to stop bullying those who like them? also will they ever come to terms with them? because generally i come to beleive some were huge jerks so, yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> when you watch an anime thats a few episodes in </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 04:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i'm not sure if i'm in support of a power rangers reboot movie or not </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 03:13:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i mean i'm not entirely clear on whether they want to reboot the whole series or want to make a tangent of reboot movies, but whatever the case im not sure if i want them to make it or not, i mean on the one hand it could be an avengers quality superhero romp, but on the other hand it would suck if 20+ seasons were just thrown away, IDK im hoping itll stand on its own feet and not have to interfere with the tv show, but thats just me

EDIT: OR they can create another timeline like star trek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> this may have been posted on r/pokemon before but just in case </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 07:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i was searching up 'doug jones mewtwo' because i thought doug jones could play mewtwo in a live action pokemon and somebody beat me to it, check it out:

http://www.comicbookmovie.com/fansites/KCatCreations/news/?a=36185

also keep in mind im typing this from my perspective </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 02:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> in that case keep up the good work, im sorry if i sounded upset </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 01:13:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> help me daniel abraham youre my only hope. why is no one concerned of the changes from the books? why didnt you put it on hbo? they wouldve kept the swearing, it wouldve broken new ground for hbo, instead its on syfy where itll just be another battlestar galactica, wont the expanse lose its edge if its on syfy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 23:14:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perfectly fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> tv executives and the expanse </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 10:35:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 03:06:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that does not look like fun for the horse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 03:05:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> more like SNUFFED his toe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-02 04:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its also like an urban legend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> this super sentai show wouldve made a good power rangers season IMO </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-02 04:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://youtu.be/zExMcJ2aUO4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-30 03:45:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> who the hell is chespirito? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-29 07:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> to that guy who took forever in that starbucks bathroom </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-29 06:54:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and heard a loud banging sound on the door, THAT WAS ME!!, how much cheese have you consumed within the last 24 hours?, or are you just naturally selfish? you took forever in the bathroom, i went to that starbucks to get some breakfast, and i wanted to use bathroom and i try to open the door and its locked so i go sit down and eat my breakfast, so then like 10 minutes goes by i go try again its still locked, and i go back to my seat and play with my phone, 10 more minutes go by i try again its still locked!! so then 5 minutes later i flat out start banging on the door! so the i go back to my seat to blend in and i see you walking out and you looked mad, GOOD! and you still dont know who i am!! youre probably one of those people who wakes up early in the morning to watch Power Rangers: super turbo mega space dino mystic dino space turbo mega force or whatever the hell its called this season, and goes right back to bed afterwards and sleeps in till 5pm. the point is dont stall in the bathroom at starbucks! thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> how do you keep a stupid, boorish, unnatractive, and uneducated person hanging? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-29 06:34:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-29 06:31:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you suck mcbain!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-28 04:45:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is that bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ok go </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-28 04:13:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-28 02:47:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if a radio can be national and public, why isnt there any schools that are private and public? im pointing out an oxymoron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> if theres 'national public radio'? (npr) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 09:43:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is there also 'private public schools'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 09:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i dont get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> anorexia prevention hotline </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 05:07:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> announcer: are you a size zero? would waldo have a hard time finding you? when you go to the park do the ducks feed YOU pieces of bread? then call the anorexia prevention hotline at 555-1701 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is "attempted theft" exactly? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 21:25:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean it's not like you see school librarians seeing a student use Wikipedia on one of the computers and puts them in detention for "attempted plagiarism" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 19:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You hit a lot of good points, especially the wishing death part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 07:57:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> help me out then, enlighten me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i had a unique boilermaker today that i made myself </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-22 08:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and i discovered magic hat wilhelm scream pumpkin ale (or ANY pumpkin ale for that matter) and jack daniels honey whiskey are a NASTY combination!! but if you want a good buzz use regular ale and ANY whiskey, im amazed i can still spell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> x/post from r/angry whats the star trek fandom coming to? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-22 04:31:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> jj abrams revives the franchise and there are people who complain about it not feeling like old star trek, NEWS FLASH THEY GOT 95% AND 87% ON ROTTEN TOMATOES!!!!! OBVIOUSLY PEOPLE THINK ITS GOOD LIKE ME!!! and i try to convince people and they see me like a 2-headed freak especially on the star trek subreddit, its like if they have the slightest criticism of jj abrams or anything or anyone else involved in the star trek reboots, i imediately wish they die of cancer someday, DO YOU PEOPLE THINK I LIKE WISHING PEOPLE TO DIE OF CANCER!?!?!?!?! DO CRITICS RAVE REVIEWS MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU !?!?! "but wait people have the right to opinions and stuff" yes but they need a good reason for those opinions! its like the world doesnt want me to like a movie. am i going in sane? are critics reviews relevant AT ALL? if you ask any film critic theyll have a thing called a 'college education' something that star trek reboot haters shouldve invested in. man i hate star trek reboot haters!! i wish theyd die and decent smart educated people like me can live in peace. its hard to enjoy a movie if theres haters in the world, i go through life hearing about critically acclaimed movies and agreeing that they deserve it, and for what? to get people like star trek reboot haters to lurk around and attack those who like them, i mean i thinki they should be considered dangerous. like the reboots and you should too!! now look at me! ive read enough comments sections and blogs to the point where i ask if its ok to like something like wtf! who else does that!? do trekkers even LIKE star trek anymore!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> whats the star trek fandom coming to? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-22 04:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> jj abrams revives the franchise and there are people who complain about it not feeling like old star trek, NEWS FLASH THEY GOT 95% AND 87% ON ROTTEN TOMATOES!!!!! OBVIOUSLY PEOPLE THINK ITS GOOD LIKE ME!!! and i try to convince people and they see me like a 2-headed freak especially on the star trek subreddit, its like if they have the slightest criticism of jj abrams or anything or anyone else involved in the star trek reboots, i imediately wish they die of cancer someday, DO YOU PEOPLE THINK I LIKE WISHING PEOPLE TO DIE OF CANCER!?!?!?!?! DO CRITICS RAVE REVIEWS MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU !?!?! "but wait people have the right to opinions and stuff" yes but they need a good reason for those opinions! its like the world doesnt want me to like a movie. am i going in sane? are critics reviews relevant AT ALL? if you ask any film critic theyll have a thing called a 'college education' something that star trek reboot haters shouldve invested in. man i hate star trek reboot haters!! i wish theyd die and decent smart educated people like me can live in peace. its hard to enjoy a movie if theres haters in the world, i go through life hearing about critically acclaimed movies and agreeing that they deserve it, and for what? to get people like star trek reboot haters to lurk around and attack those who like them, i mean i thinki they should be considered dangerous. I like the reboots and you should too!! now look at me! ive read enough comments sections and blogs to the point where i ask if its ok to like something like wtf! who else does that!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 18:07:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I promise I'm not a schizophrenic or a preteen im a normal person with normal emotions just like you, I'm just stressed out that the expanse tv show won't have the edge the books have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 18:06:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I should've left out the 'must be educated' part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> why is the expanse gonna be on syfy instead of hbo? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 05:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And why do people seem ok with it!?! I keep telling people on reddit "they will change stuff from the books" "they will neuter the characters and turn them into wimps" "they will rearrange the sequences of events" and people keep telling me that the writers of the books are gonna be involved in writing and are producers, as if that'll make the show any more faithful to the books, the syfy tv executives have a bigger hand in the show! I mean do people really wanna see characters they're attached to to lose their edge!?!?! and the story lose its edge? Like wtf?!?
you know what enjoy your watered down, neutered 'expanse' ill read the books, they contain the PROPER stories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 05:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but theyll take out the SWEARING!!!!!!!! dont you get it, itll be just another bsg without it, the characters will be turned into wimps, the expanse wont have its EDGE!!! why doesnt anybody get that!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 11:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> if they EVER make a live action pokemon movie i propose THIS MAN play mewtwo: </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 10:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just look at the following links people:

http://imgur.com/gallery/h8A09QY

http://youtu.be/qMVJnWd4idE

and heres an image of mewtwo to show why i choose him

https://encrypted-tbn3.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcQGMZ9l1Dx0xxVv-6nfE3BcKmHyxOlwm365MaDUt0anpd2DAF1G

any questions or responses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 06:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tell me how i make mountain dew frosting, I MUST KNOW!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 03:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> youll thank me later </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 01:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats part of what gives 'the expanse' its EDGE! without it itll just be another bsg or defiance, which is why I believe it should've been on HBO, heed my words theyll replace fuck with fnaq, and shit with skerb or something like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 05:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but theyll take out the swearing and make it appeal to teens regardless, thanks to 'artistic liscence' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Am i the only person on this earth worried about the expanse tv show!? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 02:58:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i mean im warning people saying "THEY WILL CHANGE STUFF FROM THE BOOKS!!!" and people just brush it off like, "hey guy, people change stuff from the books all the time!" but how do you know it'll be faithful!! god, i wish it were a movie instead, it could've been the next star wars for fucks sake!! whoever the names of the two guys with the pen name james S.A. corey, YOU FUCKED UP!!! do you know what SYFY will do to your own story!? they will take out the swearing and sex and add twilight-esque relationships, they will change what the characters were described in the books, order of events, designs of the ships! EVERYTHING!! WHAT WERE YOU THINKING!?!?!!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 23:48:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he looks like some schlub they found in a college parking lot smoking pot and drunk, and asked him "do you wanna star in a sci-fi epic?" and he said 'yes' without paying closer attention to the question at hand. and after his supposed 'audition' hes wondering "how the hell did i get THAT role!? i must've been high.'' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 22:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may not be aware, but the authors are heavily involved in the scripting process. 

Robert kirkman is invoked in the writing in the walking dead tv show, and that show is like 'Loose Adaptation: The Series!' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 12:22:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> None taken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 11:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck you!! They're great! you probably just have dyslexia, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 11:51:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I told you not to give any names!! Luckily I'm only on the first book so I'll forget his name by book 2 probably </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> why is the master like the mcrib (from mcdonalds)? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 08:41:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> theyre both always BACK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> so im like fairly new to the expanse and i wanna know if there are any named antagonists </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 07:07:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if so dont tell me their names, a simple yes or no will do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im like 140 pages into the first book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:19:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats a bad sign if my 'aggressive geeking' as you call it, has a 'style'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> btw howd you find out i was that same person, am i a celebrity in the star trek subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:00:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i could do that,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> theyre adding a character i havnt even heard of oh great! first they cast a babyfce guy as jim holden now they add a character who im not even at in the books!? they shouldve gotten influence from han solo for jim holden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 03:54:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sadly yes i am, but i promise im working on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 03:13:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they are going to RAPE the expanse!!!! dont you get it!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> im nervous about the expanse tv show </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 03:03:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> theyll change a bunch of stuff to appeal to teenagers and preteens, theyll t6ake out the swearing and theyll leave stuff out of the books! i feel like the mary poppins broad when she heard the songs for the first time!, they will literally CHANGE the books! whoevers developing the show right now if youre reading this, put it on hbo that way itll have the swearing and shit. because chances are the book series will run longer than the show. if i ever as much as see ONE thing out of place from the books youll have one less viewer, and ill wait until they get turned into MOVIES!! it couldve been the next star wars or alien franchise but instead you make it into a tv show on a cheap cable network!? BOTTOM LINE: MAKE A FAITHFUL ADAPTATION DAMMIT!!! IF THIS ONE ISN'T, thank you for reading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 02:21:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i started reading the first book a week 1/2 ago, and im already worried theyll change stuff, i DO care </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 01:33:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> looks better than the sly cooper movie redesign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 21:14:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look at the 2009 watchmen movie, to me that is how you adapt something, not changing too much stuff or taking stuff out, it's made just how the graphic novel is, and look at the walking dead that was faithful to the comics from the first episode until the y went to the city and rode in a tank. THEY NEVER RODE IN A TANK IN ANY OF THE COMICS!!! And THATS what makes me worried, that and they'll throw in an obligatory love triangle (thanks TWILIGHT!!) and they'll probably change the ages too of the characters to appeal to teens and preteens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 07:06:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> c'mon people!!! they're going to CHANGE STUFF FROM THE BOOKS!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> im concerned about 'the expanse' being on syfy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 05:03:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because

1. theyll not have any of the swearing 

2. they may create new future slang in lieu of the aforementioned swearing 

3. theyll change god knows what else,

4. and theyll take stuff OUT from the books

 if i see even ONE thing not in the books im not watching, and ill wait until they make a movie out of it, which i beleive is the proper way to adapt them, or if not that remake it for HBO
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 07:24:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> one art please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 03:53:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not something i would've made myself, but neat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 04:53:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> looks like dr seuss drew the death star </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 13:52:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have no soul! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 11:06:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no hes asking if the avengers was made in 1980, who would be cast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 11:00:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i got carried away and it got downvoted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 04:46:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what you just typed goes beyond my comprehension as a user </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 03:12:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> debatable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i have difficulties being comfortable with my opinions about movies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 02:51:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ive read enough imdb message boards, disqus comments, and youtube comments to the point where i ask if its ok if i like something, and other times i really flip a shit like in this discussion:

http://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/2l48r1/is_it_ok_if_i_like_jj_abrams_as_a_director/

anyway how can i be more comfortable with my opinions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 02:21:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ah dammit! that explains why i only got random images on google </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 02:16:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> whats this hairstyle called? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 02:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 23:49:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who you calling nerdy!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 17:47:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why won't you leave me alone!!! Ive reported you many times I hoped you'd get the message by now I don't like you and I can report you for harassment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 16:48:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know what fuck you!! I hope all reboot haters get blasted off into space and the world would be a better place!!, I and other people like the new movies, DEAL WITH IT!!! You can't change the way people think!!!! God do I hate reboot haters with a passion!! I wish they were all dead!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 10:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But the downside of the expanse being on syfy means they'll take out the swearing, and change God knows what else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 10:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so fucking sick of comparisons to transformers  telling you Trekkers are the skinheads of sci-fi fandoms, they never appreciate anything. Am I gonna be forced to live in a world where fandoms hate what they're fans of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 03:50:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> defiance, revolution, the upcoming 12 monkeys, znation, theres enough of those just like theres too many "your favorite fairie tales but gritty" shows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 21:10:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The new movies got 95% and 86% on rottentomatoes christ do you think they get those reviews magically?! Christ I'm sick of people like you giving me a hard time, it's like I say something positive about the new star treks and so called "fans" want me hunted. It's like Trekkers are the skinheads of sci fi fandoms! It's not fair! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 21:02:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the new movies are great!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 09:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that could be funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 03:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good point about space operas being expensive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 03:30:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hmmmm westworld </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 03:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hmmm, westworld </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 03:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but maddaddam is like a dystopian future show theres enough of those on tv already im talking a space opera, with spaceships, aliens, battles, and evil badguys, and maybe an empire too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> HBO needs to have more sci-fi shows </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 02:45:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> or sci-fi shows period, i dont care what its about, instead its like "oh you need a GOT fix and that movie you didnt see in the theater, but still want to see plays next month, well instead heres some more guilt exploiting documentaries about global warming, and homophobia, and AIDS themed miniseries, because we need more emmys and golden globes and youll nominate them because youll feel like a huge jackass if you dont!! because THATS how we do it!." i mean seriously i mean global warming and all that stuff is a serious issue but whoever owns HBO right now if youre reading this, please consider a sci-fi show (preferably space opera), thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> whats the deal with shemales? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-26 07:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you don't call them she, and they're not male </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> why i hate whatculture.com </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-26 06:52:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they lie and lie and lie and LIE, like recently there was an article on why beinga movie buff ruins your life, and i say whoever wrote that article YOURE EVIL AND I HATE YOU being a movie buff is great!!!!!!! theres just liars and liars and more liars, they ruin EVERYTHING about cinema, and they should be launched into space into the sun!!! anyone who disagrees please state why now, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what is the most common second language in the united states? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:13:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dora the Explorer spanish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MFW whatever i was fapping to a few hours ago is still on my computer screen </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-17 08:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> you know what'd be weird on gotham? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 04:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if john munch appeared </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 04:18:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this episode taught me that 'cannoli' can be plural AND singular apparently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 06:31:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> touche </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> am i the only human being on this earth that has ZERO complaints about gotham? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 06:53:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i mean seriously, i watch the show and reddit is bombarded with bitching, whining, nitpicking little babies, that dont find a thing to their liking. the show is like an awesome vacation spot, and reddit after the episodes is like coming back home finding out your hometown is overrun by zombies that wanna kill you, imagine that each and every week!! its miserable is what im trying to say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-12 11:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how many awards have YOU won, hmmmmm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-11 10:34:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hellraiser was cool, but thats not what im asking, im asking who you think doug JONES can play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-11 10:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm not talking about andy serkis (don't get me wrong i like his work but) im talking about DOUG JONES, so who do you think he should play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-11 10:31:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the first movie was decent, so i guess i can check it out,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i don't necessarily want a live action pokemon movie, but if they do make one i'd like doug jones to be in it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-11 09:42:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the question is which character? id prefer if he'd play a pokemon and i have a good idea which one, can you guess? heres some links to both help you out, and to let you know who im talking about:

http://imgur.com/gallery/h8A09QY

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qMVJnWd4idE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 04:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im so fucking sick of transformers comparisons id rather commit suicide if i hear it ONE MORE TIME!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 04:01:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes i have and i like the new movies, and quit judging people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 00:36:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like mystery men, I only watched the first 20 minutes of bowfinger (I watched GOLDfinger though) bowfinger seemed pretty funny though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 23:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hes won nearly 20 awards though, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 19:25:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Benedict is a good actor though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 10:17:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Persecution complex you say? You may be on to something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 08:24:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how do you keep finding me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 07:38:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh christ your one of those people who say 'nutrek', thats like a trend that shouldve passed in 2011, its hopeless, ill never have a civil discussion about ''nutrek'' as you call it. theres just no hope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 07:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> see this is what i never understood, i have zero complaints about a movie, but its made hard to enjoy because people keep pointing out the flaws, like going out to get gourmet chocolate pudding with friends and enjoying it, and then you hear the people you were with at the time complain about it either looking like a doggie doodie, or not being flavored to their liking? it wears you down

EDIT: btw this isnt grammar class i can type stuff however i please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 06:22:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but why cant i have an opinion? :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> can i like the reboot movies pretty please :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 06:00:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> without being seen as a bully, i mean i like them and no one can take that away, people can complain about them not being made to their liking, or the classic "they dont follow genes vision" excuse but we have the franchise back and thats something that a sci fi fan can appreciate. also i think we should give bob orci a chance, i mean think about it, the new movies got rave reviews, and we have 2 new movies already i wanna know what dont people like about the new movies, and ill share why i like them, and i like them because they bring life into this franchise with these talented actors in beautiful action packed fight scenes. and thats why i like them, and now why cant i have that opinion i ask? explain why, itll give me clarity to this kerfuffel

EDIT: i swear to god if i hear ONE MORE COMPARISON TO TRANSFORMERS ill flip a shit!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I made a post insulting people that don't like Gotham and I feel bad about it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 21:14:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 06:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FOR FUCKS SAKE!!! were only like 3 episodes into the show people!! 91% on rotten tomatoes dont come from fucking review fairies!!! like you think bruno heller made a wish one day and was like,"starlight starbright and all that shit, i wish my new show had a good tomatometer rating!"? reviews come from critics with age and experience!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 04:12:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok so i CLEARLY implied that im sick of hearing those words. How to you did that translate to "give it a try ill, like that very much" explain to me please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 04:10:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you know what im done talking to you, go piss someone else off i dont have time for you, what about YOUR mother knowing what you do on the internet? i am looking forward to episode 7 and i think jj abrams is the right man for the job, no further discussion is required!!!! so stfu go bother someone else, i bet your mother is very proud of you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 02:17:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't have time or punctuations, and my mother loves me very much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 08:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok the answers to your questions is because YOU SUCK!!! there all done, well its been real see ya around, adios! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 08:16:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh god SHUT UP ill have to report you for harassment!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 07:53:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i asked for advice to deal with assholes not INVITE any. also i think jj abrams is a great director and will make a great star wars!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 06:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe i seem to notice the nitpicking more, its like an overpowering sauce in a soup it takes away the flavor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> everyone is complaining about the easter eggs in the show </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 04:43:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im fucking sick of it!! especially when people complain that they arent 'subtle' if they werent subtle how would you know what villains they were? subtlety sucks!!! thats how the show is DEAL WITH IT!! either start accepting that or stop watching it! hell im still amazed my sister still claims shes into harry potter but nitpicks about it any chance she gets. same thing with star wars fans or trekkers. i swear to god if i hear ONE MORE TIME about the fucking villain name dropping im gonna LOSE MY SHIT!!! you cant stop people liking a tv show. i swear the people who criticize this show are the worst! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 04:19:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that isnt what i asked! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 02:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FUCK OFF!!! He's great!!! Are you TheSolarSailor by any chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-04 08:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> badly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-04 07:57:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i thought i WAS being the bigger man

EDIT: besides if i didnt call them out how will they know hes causing people misery and know when to stop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 23:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because I don't have an imdb account of my own, and God help if I get an intelligent answer there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I need advice about dealing with people on imdb who are total ASSHOLES to people who like a movie </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 21:33:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because man there are so many users on imdb like TheSolarSailor, he SAYS he doesn't care about Star Wars or Star Trek but CONSTANTLY picks on people of they like it especially episode 7, he even said he's looking forward to picking on all the disappointed people when it comes out. TheSolarSailor if you're reading this I HATE YOU Motherfucker! People like you give movie buffs a bad name. There's gonna be Star Wars fans whether you like it or not!!!! If anyone has advice either for me or TheSolarSailor don't hesitate to give it, thank you! At the very least at least tell TheSolarSailor to stop being an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 03:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That titles reminds me o that part in that Ed, edd, n eddy episode where they make that city in the alley out of cardboard boxes. And at one point Ed says "I was the balloon guy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 19:52:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was just fine they've just fallen under the haters spell.

EDIT:ok maybe I overeacted a little  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 18:12:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cmon people!!! This is a subreddit for Gotham but you still make fun of it?!? How is that possible?!?
And don't downvote me for liking the show that started this subreddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it ok if I like Gotham? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 16:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i mean its like the world is trying to convince me that "you are not allowed to like this show, people wont like you for it!" type of thing, and its like the rave reviews dont come from review fairies people!! (bruno heller: i wish my new show had rave reviews. Fairie: your wish has been granted) theyre from all natural real human persons!!! i hate what i hear from you people "its bad because theres no batman" "some actors arent the right age" i mean its bad enough that there are people who dislike the marvel universe movies (and i avoid them as much as possible, and if i DO come across them, they make an enemy for life.) am i bad for liking a show? i swear to god if i hear ONE MORE TIME it doesnt meet your petty expectations or there's too many Easter eggs or too many cameos there'll be HELL TO PAY and you'll make an enemy FOR LIFE!! if anyone has a good reason why i should or shouldnt like gotham, dont hesitate to explain why. thank you

EDIT:dear god, why do i keep asking for permission to like stuff i should know better by now, I'm probably better of binging my money and time on booze </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 15:56:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FUCK PENNY ARCADE Gotham is great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 12:12:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you just made an enemy FOR LIFE!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is it ok if i like gotham? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 10:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i mean its like the world is trying to convince me that "you are not allowed to like this show, people wont like you for it!" type of thing, and its like the rave reviews dont come from review fairies people!! (bruno heller: i wish my new show had rave reviews. Fairie: your wish has been granted) theyre from all natural real human persons!!! i hate what i hear from you people "its bad because theres no batman" "some actors arent the right age" i mean its bad enough that there are people who dislike the marvel universe movies (and i avoid them as much as possible, and if i DO come across them, they make an enemy for life.) am i bad for liking a show? i swear to god if i hear ONE MORE TIME it doesnt meet your petty expectations youll make an enemy FOR LIFE!! if anyone has a good reason why i should or shouldnt like gotham, dont hesitate to explain why. thank you

EDIT:dear god, why do i keep asking for permission to like stuff i should know better by now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-27 06:11:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i chose GOT as an example because that and veep are the only two shows i can think of that are not in their final seasons, with like true blood and boardwalk empire ending </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> remember when people watched movies on HBO? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-27 05:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i mean HBO still PLAYS movies, but now people want it for the shows, its like the movies they play are just filler for when GOT comes back on

EDIT:*for UNTIL GOT comes back on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> which dragon ball characters can doug jones play in a live action role? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 08:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> in case you dont know who doug jones is check this link out!

http://imgur.com/gallery/h8A09QY

EDIT: since no one yet has said it i say he plays beerus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 07:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because i yearn for a smart imdb user to be conceived, but its all ignorance and insults, which is why i have no imdb account of my own because they are MONSTERS theyre not people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> imdb should stand for 'impudent miserable douche bags' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 07:19:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> peoples views on simpsons guest stars then and now </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 04:22:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1993: oh wow! thats that guy from that movie i liked, its a huge honor that theyre on the simpsons!

2014: man, you need to be THAT desperate for a PAYCHECK, to be on the simpsons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-21 04:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have a sucky imagination though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-21 03:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i know of the audio dramas, id check them out but i prefer a tv show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is there propane in doctor who? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-20 08:37:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because i watched all 800+ episodes (and i do mean all) and no episode mention propane, to my recollection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-20 08:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you know it really stinks that doctor 8 didnt get a full series, because man i watched the tv movie and reminded me of the x files, and i thought man if this was a full show, the x-files wouldve been the perfect lead in show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 18:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But this one is here to stay, I swear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 18:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh there's others but this user sticks out like a sore thumb, I think he has an agenda and writing plans as we speak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Remember when people were EXCITED for a new Star Wars? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 18:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> good guy mst3k </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 11:26:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 00:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You actually keep track how many times you say something? Damn talk about keeping track. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Am I allowed to say ANYTHING good about the new Star Trek movies!? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 23:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because I feel very unsafe and I need holding and protection. The haters are out to get me. So I ask is it ok if I like the new movies to be into Star Trek at all? Because I feel that I have the right to say what I think is right. That's all, so I ask will I ever see another Star Trek watcher who likes the new movies? And am I wrong for doing so? I say this from the bottom of my heart. I mean I feel as if I say EVEN ONE POSITIVE THING, people want me executed or something, I just want people to enjoy the new movies, and Talk to them, is that so wrong, anybody know any whiskeys good for binging in one sitting?

P.S. At least this isn't imdb the users are probably not even people, they're MONSTERS (in a literal and hypothetical sense) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Guess which DBz character I think the man in this video should play in a live action role. Winners get an upvote </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 16:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-14 02:06:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because people influence other people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 05:56:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not until they make 28 seconds, minutes, or hours later first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 21:05:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man, What a dummy I am for not being aware of those subreddits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 21:02:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok that was a pretty funny response actually  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> one question you'd ask John Ringo </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 07:00:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In light of series 8 of doctor who (the revival series) premiering last Saturday </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-28 20:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> a good dentist and a bad dentist finds out about a new candy store opening </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-25 08:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good dentist: oh man, i hope the people who go there brush and floss regularly

bad dentist: ALRIGHT!!! job security! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> theres a disqus troll about star wars episode 7 im having a grudge with </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-25 04:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-23 08:29:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can never tell whether i like his movies or not, but this looks nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-23 07:43:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sounds like i have ALOT to learn apparently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-23 07:39:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *haters people, but what that makes sense though, but then when i say it civilized i STILL get downvoted, what gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> im done defending the new star trek movies! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-23 07:28:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whats the point of expressing my opinion if im just gonna be called an idiot, or a moron, and insulted? i thought trekkers were supposed to be for tolerance!!! i cant say ANYTHING good bout the new movies without being seen as a skinhead or something, its just not fair! so on behalf of your franchise and your fandom i bid you all, GOOD FUCKING LUCK!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> good guy the wire </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-23 06:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is there moonshine in pokemon? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-17 08:52:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because ive never heard any one character whether in the games, the anime, manga, etc... mention or drink moonshine which leads me to wonder, is there moonshine in the pokemon universe, hey this is making me be in the mood for a mixed drink </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> mr monk and the elephant in the room </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 22:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if adrian monk has a germ phobia, why does he work as a homicide detective? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm sorry for being a jerk on the Star Trek subreddit :( </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 17:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've said things like "I wish all reboot haters die horrible painful deaths", I called them jerks, pussies, fags you name it. I just wish people were more grateful about new str trek and weren't jerk to people who do like them, that's all. Hear me out people are probable planning to downvote me already, but I NEED TO KNOW, IS OK IF I LIKE THE JJ ABRAMS STAR TREK MOVIES OR NOT!!!!! And is it ok if I like the writing I the new movies?! And is it ok if I look forward to Star Trek 3 with bob orci directing? Again, hear me out I'm speaking as a movie fan and sci fi fan with an honest heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-09 07:05:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> reninds me of porygon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 08:13:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ive heard of cd burning, but this is ridiculous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mr monk and the irony </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 19:53:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> how 'big fan' got made </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 10:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> producer: i wanna make a movie that revolves around a scene where patton oswalt chokes the chicken, and pair him up with one of those lesser insignificant guys from goodfellas

other guy: but sir, wont patton oswalt spanking the monkey repulse people?

producer: DAMMIT MAN I DONT WANT EXCUSES! get me a shitty script with unlikeable characters, a whiny protagonist, and a fapping patton oswalt, NOW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 13:08:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey man I like marvel movies, I don't wanna get insulting, When I get insulting I get mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Being a sci-fi fan SUCKS ASS!!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 12:31:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever a new sci fi movie comes out there's always the usual "it's not like the source material" "this'll be worse than the prequels" "the director isn't good" "that ship wouldn't work in real life" why is it so hard to like Star Trek or Star Wars?when there's all these little pussies who call themselves "fans"? I can't go 5 internet articles on sci fi without finding those people,is the universe TRYING to tell me something? Am I doomed to live a living hell as a sci fi fan? Are people TRYING to make a dons smaller? Please tell me someone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 07:37:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dat ass on the second one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bill murray in zombieland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 08:48:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> all the ones with Doug Jones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 08:47:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NOW you're talking!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> its just not gonna happen </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 06:08:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Awesome (IMO) idea for a professor oak prequel </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-17 16:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok so this prequel for professor oak first act is the usual going to college, graduating, earning his phd, getting married, having kids, having grand kids (Gary), and (establishing) a laboratory, and then later on professor oak finds a stray pichu, he brings it back to his lab, and he studies it an researches it and finds out it evokes into pikachu, so then he tries many methods to make it evolve which are unsuccessful, and then on the night before Gary and ash get their own pokemon that we're all familiar with there's a break in at the lab (possible by team rocket) an professor oak runs to the lab, then he sees the pichu he's been trying to get to evolve is fending off the theives with its electrical shocks. and all the pokemon are 
unharmed and then we see the pichu start to glow that white color were all familiar with and much to professor oaks delight is celebrating on the inside of its victory. And before cutting back to the evolving pichu, professor oak then says to himself "I hope it'll stay in its pokeball." And then we cut back to the still evolving pichu, and cut to black. ROLL CREDITS what do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 08:59:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *oil SPILL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 08:58:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (singing) "suicide is painless...." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 06:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> reminds me of a terry gilliam movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-13 11:47:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im sorryv that was a little harsh, but im just saying theres records for breaking stuff with peoples heads in there, so if THOSE can get into record books, THIS can get into record books (or SHOULD) anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-13 11:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hmmm i must've missed that one, but still in the yearly edition that'd be cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-13 10:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dude, ANYTHING GOES in record books,so stfu

EDIT: ok that might have come out a little harsh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL the pokemon anime is the longest running tv series based on a videogame </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-13 05:50:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well technically i knew it for a while i just slowly got around to starting a discussion. but anyway, i think Guinness world records should have it in their next edition. like i can imagine that paragraph as follows:

pocket monsters (or pokemon depending on where youre from) is an anime based on the videogame series of the same name (also known as pokemon in english speaking markets) has ran for 17 seasons as of (insert date here) for over 800 episodes. pocket monsters also has been made into 16 feature films as of (insert6 date here and yes im aware theres a 17th movie coming out) making that the longest running film franchise based on a videogame.

wouldnt that be awesome? i say make this happen!! put that in the next guinness world records book! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 23:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey! He is not z-list! He's listless! You however just made my list! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i pray this man be a guest star on the simpsons </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 05:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/h8A09QY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 05:13:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ah poopie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 05:12:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ah poopie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 05:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well what i wrote here i wouldnt write in english class. so in other words im not in school i can write whatever. even if it might offend some which i probably did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 04:18:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no but im quite a fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is the pokemon anime the japanese doctor who? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 04:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i found similarities between the anime and doctor who, and they are as follows

. both ash ketchum and the doctor travel to weird and wonderful places

. both always happen to go somewhere where something bad is happening

. both ash ketchum and the doctor change their looks
   1. ash ketchum changes his outfit from time to time
   2. the doctor changes his whole damn body

. both ash ketchum and the doctor have an ever changing array of traveling companions 

i dont know about you guys but im on to something here, if i missed any other similarities let me know 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 03:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In what way did you enjoy it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I it ok of I like jj Abrams work and Star Trek movies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 02:56:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 02:24:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Infect or repulse, I'm having a hard time determining which is being used as the negative term </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-11 03:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> patrick star lost his shit
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what characters (preferably pokemon) could Doug Jones portray in a live action role? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 10:56:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just in case you don't know who he is here's a link explaining who Doug Jones is:

http://imgur.com/h8A09QY

anyway who would he be good to play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> who are some anime characters Doug Jones could portray in a live action role? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 10:46:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just in case you don't know who he is here's a link explaining who Doug Jones is: 

http://imgur.com/h8A09QY

anyway who would he be good to play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> anime episode 38 electric soldier porygon (aka the seizure episode) discussion:thoughts and should it be considered a 'fan favorite'? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-02 10:25:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> before i watched the aforementioned episode i waited a 24 hour period so i could prepare myself for watching it, and i didnt have a seizure. but the flashing lights kinda gave me a little headache which went away. as for the episode itself its kinda interesting showing them go inside the machine kinda like TRON. and porygon was well represented. but all things considered the quality of the episode feels irrelevent, for its more (in)famous for the incident it caused, in fact most people dont even know what the episode is even about. and it brings me to the question, Should 'electric soldier porygon' be considered a 'fan favorite'? yes or no and explain why in the comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-02 07:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh man i hope i end up disagreeing with you, ive been waiting MONTHS to watch this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-02 03:19:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i hope so, i could barely hold back tears at the end of movie 6: jirachi wish maker AND they top it off with a song to boot. i mean cmon man that wasnt fair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> so im about to watch movie 8: lucario and the mystery of mew... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-02 03:10:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> can someone get me in the right mindset to get ready to cry or be sad (or both) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-14 03:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i thought itd be a nickelodeon logo at first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alternative titles for 'closet coon' (take 2) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 20:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My alternative titles are 'live and let BI', 'the living GAYlights', 'closet of solace', 'the BI who loved me', 'goldenBI', 'you only come out twice', 'come out another day', 'COONraker', 'BIamonds are forever' or 'closet royale' what do you guys think? Also whoever gets what all these alternative titles have in common will get an upvote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 07:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im craving ocean spray cranberry juice all of a sudden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-09 03:34:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that would be a cool glass eye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-22 09:02:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> reminds me of: https://encrypted-tbn2.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSb-Vu1auDcS2POpxPJIjiG7BuVgG6qX9IHhQip-ktkJHh6VHg_ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alternative titles for 'closet coon' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-17 10:34:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My Alternative titles would either be 'live and let BI' 'the living GAYlights' or 'closet of solace' what do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is it ok if I think Roberto orci will make a great star trek 3? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-14 08:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because man I freaking hate people who don't like the reboots, they literally wrote the highest grossing and rated star treks of all time! rotten tomatoes does not lie people!!!! all im asking is for once I would like to have a thoughtful and intelligent discussion about the movies and not trigger these bitchy ungrateful "long time fans" to shit on my good time! I mean does 95% and 87% mean ANYTHING TO YOU PEOPLE!? anyway I would like to see what bob orci has in store and sorry if I offended some people but youre still ungrateful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> anime episode 15 "battle aboard the st anne" question </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-11 10:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you know like the part where the team rocket soldiers in the black shirts reveal like those wind blowing devices on the ship? and then like they show some trainers whose pokeballs are flying off their belts and then they cut to the main three who are surrounded by said team rocket soldiers demanding them to hand over their pokemon and misty is like saying "no way!" in that same scene they have those same air blowing devices and somehow the main characters just get asked to give up their pokemon while all thes trainers pokemon are literally flying away!? this is a troubling question from an otherwise great story arc. and i mean GREAT story arc. i get like a doctor who vibe from this episode . hell i often compare the anime to doctor who anyway. anyway i just thought it was weird that these team rocket grunts who had this high tech pokemon theft equipment just ask them for pokemon. any thoughts on that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> alternative titles for seattle fur </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-11 07:30:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how about 'from seattle with love' 'live and let BI' or 'the living GAYlights' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is it wrong that i like the jj abrams star trek movies? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-11 06:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i thought they are fun and action packed. i mean ive heard some people say like "it doesnt have the heart of star trek" "i hate the new actor for spock and hes gay" "i hate the actors" "i hate the new enterprise" the list goes on. meanwhile here i am not having too high standards wanting to be entertained and agreeing with the rave reviews (a movie doesnt get 95% or 87% on rotten tomatoes magically people!) its like one moment its like "critics and audiences agree the new star trek is awesome" and then its like "PSYCHE! heres some asshole mean spirited,ungrateful and hateful purists to keep it interesting" im literally afraid to have discussions of the new star treks on this site fearing ill get a hate message of some kind. because some trekkers are very royal. i swear to god if i hear ONE MORE TIME about it not having genes vision i will slip into a stress induced coma. if anyone has a good reason why i should or shouldnt like the jj abrams star trek movies dont hesitate to explain why. thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-07 08:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ive seen tblt MANY times and its great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I wanna rap about 'a goofy movie' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-03 18:24:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just so you know this kind of an edit of another post I did because someone pointed out the bad grammar and punctuation and this is an improvement over it. So anyway about 'a goofy movie' Man, I watched the HELL out of that movie as a kid, I havnt seen it in a while but I'm sure I still do today. I mean imagine for a moment you're a producer for Disney and you're waiting for an idea for a 'goof troop' spinoff film and you want it to appeal to the current generation (when the 1990's WAS the current generation) and make it as trendy and hip as possible. And just when you thought all hope was lost, someone comes into your office and is like (spoilers) 

guy: I have an idea for that gestating goof troop spinoff film. 

Producer: alright let's hear it 

guy: ok so max is in high school now and gets in trouble. 

Producer: hmmmmmm that's interesting tell me more 

guy: ok so after the principal calls goofy and Tells him if max keeps this up hell get in trouble in life.

Producer: ohhhhhhh yessssss keep going 

guy: ok so goofy arranges to go on a cross country road trip to get their relationship back to normal but max wanted to watch this concert on tv with his girlfriend. But now can't. And now that max and goofy are on said road trip they come across many strange characters and obstacles including Bigfoot. And they learn a little something about each other in the process. 

Producer: I love it!!! It's a sure fire winner! Let's make it a musical and yo got yourself a deal.

If I ever met the guy who wrote the screenplay to 'a goofy movie' I would thank the HELL out of him for such an amazing childhood film. Know what I mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> after seeing jjs 2 star trek movies.... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-26 03:16:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I wanna conversate about 'a goofy movie' for a moment </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-14 19:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man, I watched the HELL out of that movie as a kid, I havnt seen it in a while but I'm sure I still do today. I mean imagine for a moment you're a producer for Disney and you're waiting for an idea for a 'goof troop' spinoff film and someone comes into your office and is like (spoilers) 

guy: I have an idea for that gestating goof troop spinoff film. 

Producer: alright let's hear it 

guy: ok so max is in high school now and gets in trouble. 

Producer: hmmmmmm that's interesting tell me more 

guy: ok so after the principal calls goofy and Tells him if max keeps this up hell get in trouble in life.

Producer: ohhhhhhh yessssss keep going 

guy: ok so goofy arranges to go on a cross country road trip to get their relationship back to normal but max wanted to watch this concert on tv with his girlfriend. But now can't. And now that max and goofy are on said road trip they come across many strange characters and obstacles including Bigfoot. And they learn a little something about each other in the process. 

Producer: I love it!!! It's a sure fire winner! Let's make it a musical and yo got yourself a deal. 

Know what I mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-11 07:08:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i want him to like turtles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-11 00:16:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes, and if they arent do any pretend to regenerate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> question about 'closet coon' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-09 13:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do any characters regenerate? if so whom? and if not, does anybody at least pretend to regenerate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-03 22:48:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I see, but still saying that synopsis must taste pretty damn good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> EDIT: I wish I were the guy who pitched 'space jam' to a studio </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-03 19:12:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean pretty much any kid who grew up in the 1990's knows what 'space jam' is I mean I'm jealous of the guy who was able to walk into a studio and tell a producer: (spoilers)
Guy: ok here's the idea, the owner of this intergalactic theme park which is panned by its customers, wants to improve the park by having the looney toons work there . So he sens his henchmen to kidnap the looney toons.
Producer:hmmmmmm that's interesting, tell me more.
Guy: so then when the henchmen attempt to kidnap the looney toons, the looney toons challenge the henchman to a no holds barred basketball game with the aid of a soon to be retiring nba superstar Michael Jordan.
Producer: I LOVE IT!!! We'll get started immediately!
I mean that takes some balls to have that plot just pass your lips like that. You know you'd have a ball pitching it. That guy must've had the best day of his life then. I mean (the late) siskel and ebert both gave it a thumbs up.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I've said really mean things to people who disagree with me about the jj Abrams Star Trek movies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-27 20:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I said stuff like "wash the c*m out of your mouth" "good luck losing your virginity" "fag" stuff like that. I mean, is it wrong that I liked into darkness? I mean all I'm saying is that I want to feel safe saying something and not have anybody push me around. I mean do those rotten tomatoes scores mean anything to Trekkers? Anyway I'm sorry for all the mean stuff I said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-12 18:41:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I get it! You're checking both the man and woman out whose skating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Question about 'associated student bodies' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-21 22:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do any characters regenerate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-29 08:39:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think of the war doctor as 'the 8th doctor mark II' because it was eights decision to take the form while still alive with that face, and even after eight changed into john hurt he still bore a slight resemblance to eight, just throwing that out there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> as if we needed one of those memes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-28 07:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-14 09:39:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see a beautiful kissable ass but no tatoo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-14 01:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh yeah, that's gross </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-13 02:29:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 181 year old "preserved" head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> EDIT: whoever started using that other template didn't see office space </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-13 00:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-07 14:53:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes and make an album while your at it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is it ok if i liked into darkness </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-22 03:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i thought it was fun and action packed, why are trekkers so ungrateful. im not afraid to say that. i wanna say that without getting treated like i insulted someone whose loved one passed away. it seems as if whiskey is my only friend. Why do I even bother? What's the point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i liked benedict cumberbatch as khan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 02:22:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fuck me right? i thought it was an interesting take, and im looking forward to possible sequels with him. i like his performance. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AD Quotes in caveman dialect </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-21 13:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Made huge mistake!" "Need favor" "just blue self" okay so it's not the best. But if you want you can contribute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-21 07:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> arrested development is so much better a show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Don't you hate it when "fans" say the masses are stupid? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-17 17:56:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The jetsons theme song </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-15 19:22:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is there lasagna in star trek? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-15 18:59:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a non sequitur but seriously though I never once heard any characters mention lasagna </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-14 13:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm deleting that one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> vanilla ice </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-14 08:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it ok if I like the jj Abrams Star Trek movies? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-14 05:36:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because if I hear an opinion different from mine I question my place in the universe and the future of humanity, I thought it was fun and action packed. But thi subreddit is like thunder done people starting arguments left and right. Wanna join the Star Trek fandom? It's easy! All you gotta do is say IT SUCKS to everything new and there you go your a Star Trek fan. Also anyone know any good vodkas to help me get through this stressful ordeal? Because I wanna say I like something without getting treated like I insulted someone's disability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-12 09:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WOAH THAT IS SO COOL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what are humorous ways of saying "ive made a huge mistake"? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-12 01:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have:
caveman: "made huge mistake"
underwater without breathing apparatus: "bloob bloob bubb boob bloob bloob bloob" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-20 19:57:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is one of those few shows were they think of everything. It's like "nope this scene isn't funny enough, lets make it better!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-18 05:08:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> favorite "board" game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-18 04:58:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-17 06:42:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just goes to show you that people have taste </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-17 06:28:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> let me guess: walmart? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-16 21:54:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The cast is great you're mental </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-13 12:35:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I enjoyed the movie too. (Go away stevenjohns) I've been defending this movie for ages almost like a mental case. I just don't want injustice in the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-13 12:25:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh joy! Another unnecessary remake. (It could be good, but I'm being cautious) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-13 05:17:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe they could do that all along they just didnt happen to do it till now. (Ok maybe that's not the best reason) I don't wanna fight about it I love the movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-13 04:17:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IT DOESN'T EVEN FUCKING EXIST AS OF YET! So for all we know its impossible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-12 10:59:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a thing called 'science FICTION' it can work however they want it to work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-11 23:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think both movies are fun and action packed. I've been defending these movies for like forever and I still feel I haven't accomplished anything. Jj saved the franchise DEAL WITH IT. And if you don't like it TOUGH! I just don't like it when people criticize the new Star Trek. I can tell you why if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-11 08:19:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ENOUGH WITH THE FUCKING UNDERWEAR SCENE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-11 08:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i had a few criticisms.... nah i'm just kidding, i loved every second of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-10 17:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am quite looking forward to getting this movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-10 17:33:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I made a bold statement, this fandom needs to get its shit together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-10 13:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This fandom needs to get it shit together and I mean seriously. I love the new movies. I've been defending them for like forever. From people given them crap. All I want I people to accept change and not be biased based on the writers past projects. So what if they made a couple crappy transformers movies. They made two awesome Star Trek movies isn't that what's important. In fact I'm leaving this fandom until someone gives me a good reason. Try keeping your little franchise alive. I wish you all GOOD FUCKING LUCK!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-06 02:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cute ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm not the only one who remembers weird shit I'm sure </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-04 08:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Here's my thoughts on STID </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-04 04:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was freakin amazing and fun and it a great cast an did great justice to Star Trek.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I notice they never talk about 'weird al' yankovic on arrested development </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 10:18:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So that raises the question whether he exists in their universe or they just haven't gotten around to mentioning him, an appearance would be cool what do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 10:16:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would do that but I prefer not being in jail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 09:50:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't give two shits about the extras I just like the movie and the cover that goes with it, if I wanna see all the extras ill go on youtube. But yeah that sounds good cause I don't make much money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 06:42:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh a grammar nazi are we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> which star trek into darkness blu ray do you reccomend </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 04:46:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i liked the movie it was fun and action packed. anyway which blu ray edition sounds good. theres nothing wrong with a star trek movie with action  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-02 08:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well i like a good action movie THIS WAS ONE OF THEM! its fun and action packed and breathed new life to the franchise,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-02 08:29:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i thought it was fun and action packed DEAL WITH IT BITCH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-30 23:44:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It just does  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-30 10:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's no bond actor in Shaun of the dead but there's one in hot fuzz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-27 09:51:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These guys are great, if anyone says otherwise, never speak to them again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-25 13:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It also shows they have good taste in comedies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 07:19:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> post pictures of your ass! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-10 04:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not sure if i should send to friends and family because its funny and its the avengers, or not send to friends and family at the risk of being disowned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-08 05:35:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was a smart move unlike what I did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-06 10:20:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How long did it take you to type that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> star trek "plot holes" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-06 06:29:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this argument needs to stop, i don't think plot holes are real, i don't know what people think plot holes are, i think its one of those bandwagon things people say like "hey they don't like this movie because it has plot holes i hate this movie too because of that" christ "plot holes are defined differently from person to person JUST STOP IT PLEASE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! the star trek movies are what they are if you see something wrong with the plot TOO BAD!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-05 10:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I don't see why not, I also don't see why." -Dr. J. Zoidberg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-04 11:02:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i say the theme of the previous one was about determining your future and making the right decisions and in the end you may become what your destiny determined </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I HATE IT WHEN PEOPLE CRITICIZE THE NEW STAR TREK! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-04 10:34:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i mean it all started with that one weekend uopdate on SNL with chris pine and zachary quinto, and here i am today looking for the haters comments to the point where i find their reactions to all the critical praise  hilarious, i just want it the criticism to STOP!!!!!! im on the verge of losing my shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-04 09:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YOU DON'T SAY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-03 04:09:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool now Make a Spock edition plz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL Lucille Bluth was... Fran Sinclair from Dinosaurs!? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-03 03:56:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-02 04:32:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe a little of both sorry I'm not good at this type of thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-01 10:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not doing yourself any favors, and what's with that username? Here ill send you reddit gold so you can buy yourself a brain, a clue, and a soul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-01 05:38:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and a lovely hump it is
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-01 00:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> your meme is bad and you should feel bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who here is anxious to get Star Trek into darkness on blu ray? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 11:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This guy is who else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 08:24:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh joy people complaining about nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Regarding candy crush saga </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 00:29:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I've been doing this lately </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-27 02:01:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Due to my newfound love of total drama for me this is inevitable </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 10:43:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> better yet, Do you remember Amanda Bynes? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 05:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-21 04:54:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats not bad luck thats just a minor inconvenience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> the morpheus meme is becoming a jerk lately </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-21 02:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> something about goof troop i shouldve realized when i was like 8 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-20 03:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I just got into total drama recently and it's great and I made this </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-19 07:56:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is true to me I like webcomics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-12 00:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Watch the episode and see for yourself </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-07 13:34:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> that's right i tell you </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-07 01:14:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Same thing with Tetris </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-03 01:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> don't get me wrong it was an excellent movie but... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-23 11:10:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i saw gardening scrabble at a barnes and noble one time and i was thinking... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-19 06:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-17 12:27:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems that way yeah for like the last 5 or 6 he's been absent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> you'll laugh i guarantee </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-16 12:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> im sure fans of epic meal time (like myself) will understand </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-16 11:45:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> bad luck bran has it fairly easy nowadays </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 08:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You bet your ass i remember </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-14 10:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This hit me when I watched the Bourne legacy, some might disagree but whatever </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-12 22:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> To me it now feels like a completely different show </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-11 17:59:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> At least in MY area </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-11 03:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm sure some people feel the same way here </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-10 11:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-10 04:31:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why doesn't he have that hat in this picture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i'm sure i'm not the only one who remembers this </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-09 10:56:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> please fucking like this meme </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-09 07:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I certainly remember </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-09 05:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> reaction to a trailer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-23 07:35:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-02 10:22:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't want to live on this planet anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> They could REALLY use dr zoidberg  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 10:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm sure people can relate </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-23 05:35:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-23 02:35:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok I'll keep that in mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> two and a half men isn't funny - Sudden clarity clarence | Meme Generator </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-22 22:45:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I think this meme I made is funny </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-21 09:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> not sure if freddy kreuger used to actually be scary or i was just 8 - Futurama Fry | Meme Generator </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-21 04:47:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>