<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7371</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just wanted to remind people that this was here. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:14:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fire and Rain by James Taylor. It's about his girlfriend dying on a trip home to surprise him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Frankly I think it's ridiculous that anyone sees more potential in Brown than they do Revere. Brown has proven to be ineffective in every outfield position and his offense is terribly inconsistent. He is at best a AAAA-level ball player; too good for the minors but not good enough for the majors. I'd take Revere over Brown any day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 16:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was always a fan of Next Door Nikki </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:17:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because the point of the sub is to pick one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First off let me just say you're FAR too hard on yourself. The first step in success in changing how you view yourself. Find one thing you do like about yourself and, for a time, focus on how awesome you are at that. Then build from there.
Second, ADHD will always keep you from being "normal" but that doesn't mean it has to hold you back. There are a lot of ways that those of us with ADHD have it better than those without; we have more varied interests, we can get to be good at a lot of different things, and we can task-shift better (good in jobs requiring attention to lots of things), to name a few. 
ADHD is an obstacle that needs to be overcome, but it is far from impossible. All it takes is you making the decision to not let it get you down and to find a way to make it work for you. Figure out what pulls your attention and focus your energies on it, and you can and will succeed. 
You can do this, man. I believe in you.

Also, let me just add that you have a very good writing voice. Maybe try writing more: journals, short stories, poems, whatever. Not only is it good for our brains to write stuff down like that, but you may find your path in it. Just a thought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 18:19:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:24:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I'm totally ok with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:26:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> +Victoria Justice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 15:28:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Afto to Gati Pou Thelo by Kaiti Garbi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 20:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha! Thanks for playing along  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 20:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you another one of those Hard Copy guys?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hey reddit, what do you know about Ray Finkle? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 20:47:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 20:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for sharing your experience. I've known about neurofeedback for some time but always wanted to hear a first hand account. How old are you, OP?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 15:54:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sonic and Knuckles. Try as hard as I could I was never able to beat the final boss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 20:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also check out Jet Li's "Fist of Legend". It's a bit older but it has some of the best fight sequences I've ever seen in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 02:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me: Hi I'm Woody and I'll be your server tonight.
Jackass: Hi Woody, I'm Jackass. I'll be your customer tonight.

You are hilarious sir.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The only time people offer you gum is when theyre putting some in their mouth or when they want you to put some in yours. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 18:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-08 20:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First thing I would recommend is to change your perspective. Stop beating yourself up, and start being your biggest supporter. It is incredibly important and it's ridiculous how big a difference that can make in your own success. 
The second thing is to decide what you want to do. It doesn't matter if it seems impossible right now, just pick a direction and go. I've noticed that I'm less distractible when I have a goal to focus on, and even if I get distracted I know which direction to realign with.  You don't need an exact plan, just know where you want to go. The path will form itself.
Keep in mind that things will not change over night. It will take hard work and patience (A LOT of patience), but it is very doable. ADD does not make us dysfunctional, it makes us function differently. 
You can do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 01:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Phillies fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dogs marking a tree is the canine equivalent of foursquare. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-27 22:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-11 18:15:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excellent response time and you delivered exactly what I needed. Thanks so much!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 08:52:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is awesome! Thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 18:08:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am the brother and I can vouch for this. It was a strange few moments of conversation when everyone discovered that we were back-to-front wipers. However I feel like we stood our ground enough that we put a shadow of doubt in their heads concerning their current wiping methods. I'm confident they tried it our way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-05 03:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Righties laughing when I tell them that Lefties are the people most discriminated against ever in the world.

Also nobody makes a quality tape measure that Lefties can read. They only offer a "read from any angle" tape which uses print so small and chaotically set you'd be better off guessing how much tape got pulled out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>