<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3450</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:41:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What? How? And FUCK YEAH!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was.. Dana Carry ad libbed the line to mess with Mike Meters. The reaction was so good they kept it for the film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:33:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This.... I am so glad this is a thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:32:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are those really 20's?? Would have guessed 16's maybe 18's tops... Either way I fucking love your ride man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:30:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sons of Anarchy fallout </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about adding the Kuchi Kopi to the Louise tattoo?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Harry Nilsson, John Lennon, and Alice Cooper drinking backstage. 1974 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:26:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That must have been tough.. Sorry you and your family had to deal with that... Is she okay?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:14:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went in to the bathroom to get her a cold wet rag.. Even though she had cleaned it all out while she was in the shower the smell was so strong I threw up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:13:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? No shit? I would have guessed by some of the signage hanging that was a WF.. Great display.. Going to have to check that one out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:50:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To me the white balance in the video (all be it unintentional) reminds me of the filming style of begotten. Also looking at Alice Coopers face, particularly his eyes while he's singing The Second Coming, to me is just creepy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No.. But blood pressure drop.. We had to expedite our flight home and she was in the hospital for a week after emergency surgery 

Edit: auto correct error change </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are they balistically similar to grapes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:42:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Serious: which whole foods is this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Alice Cooper video from early in the band's career </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:39:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:35:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That I'm not a felon unlike every one of her other ex's (I don't know what the hell I wax thinking) and also I'm the only boyfriend I had who didn't cheat on her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:33:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Retaliate with Lingenberries  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:32:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wine 

Ftfy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:31:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd get it tattooed to look like NASA's Saturn V Rocket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On vacation in a hotel.. My ex who had multiple health problems had a digestive hemorage in the shower and bled out profusely anally. The smell was so bad they had to relocate everyone within two rooms of ours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:20:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Katiebird *Certifiable Crazy Person 

Split screen view of a serial killer and her victims.. Incredibly overwhelming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 19:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drop the comment in eh parenthesis and you'd have a decent post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of music do you play here? 

Oh we play both kinds. Country AND Western!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:15:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good candidate for /r/idiotsfightingthings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:11:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Super fucked up, not arguing that... But my guess is this kids case is more an "oh shit I fucked up oh shit" than being arrogant or entitled.. Super fucked up either way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 13:40:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had something for this.. Shit... I always keep a couple boob puns on hand but nothing comes to mammary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 13:37:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A rouse you idiot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bear gets fed up, flips cube into a deep lake on principle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Your eyes are too close together"
May not be shattering.. But it stops them in their tracks and weakens self confidence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:25:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know... Not that you'd want to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:48:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started with two upper body days and two lower body days with a mid section day and 2 rest days and was getting results before I stepped it up... 

My routine was 10 - 15 minutes light cardio to warm up, deep stretching, weights for the day, 30 minutes of cardio just intense enough I thought I couldn't make it and finish out with 2 or 3 core exercises and more deep stretching.. Do core every day (my trainer says even just one or two quick core exercises on rest days)

Change up what weight routines you do weekly so your body doesn't adapt and essentially "get bored" of your work out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:25:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the hell is that message about anyways?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 00:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The guy who is down in front... Has the old am cap one style... Cigar.. Slicked back hair, dressed sharp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Early 1920's. The "Al Capone" looking for down in front was my great grandfather, one of Cincinatti's biggest bootleggers. He shot himself the day before the feds would have locked him up. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:41:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Making sure I read that right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:40:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That can die too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:47:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Tommy Boy 
2. Road to Perdition 
3. Halloween </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You laughed out loud out loud?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:44:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 56 Guys who signed the declaration are on fleek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:09:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You misspelled bandwagon moron brigade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sense of elitism that shows up on reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scene where Katie gets drug out by her feet still bothers me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  one of few where the sequel is equally terrifying... Something unnerving about being alone in a hospital </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:39:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's no build up to any of the scares... Shot just comes out of no where without warning.. No false scares... The opening credits alone are unsettling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome.. Can we edit a little yellow jumpsuit on him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 11:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Zip disks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 18:08:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your not alone. Recently I've been thinking of dropping Reddit and this just kind of affirmed my decision. Blacking out and choosing who gets to be a part of major subs goes against what Reddit is about. IMO it's also a little elitist. This whole blackout and random uninformed people jumping on the bandwagon just proves to me there is a sheep mentality even here, it's just better disguised.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:16:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Am I the only one who really thinks this is all one big case of cutting off noses to spite our own faces? What guarantee is their that any of this will even work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:09:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In short: CEO fires important employee. In return the admins of the site protest by becoming incredibly exclusive. The exclusivity (which goes against everything this site was stands for) will drive people away lowering traffic numbers and forcing the CEO to either higher the admin who was fired or shut the site down, thus punishing the vast majority of users who are uninvolved. 

Tl;dr: an odd case of cutting off your nose to spite everyone else's faces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:25:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you think the start is hard core wait till season 3 finally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a hale mairpiece </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know. That would mean he'd have to believe in something that he can't take credit for creating himself...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I figured scuffs, wasn't aware of the adhesive. Admittedly I've jumped in twice, both recently. I saw the scuff but they buffed out, no sign of adhesive or anything stuck to it. I wonder if it fades in the weather or with contact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:55:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please specify. I think we might be thinking of two different groups of people. Not sure where you're leaning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those poles are kind of a joke. A 4cyl 2 door honda civic can make it through. They bend over very easily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So please enlighten me... Please list all of the nations that would actually join into a holy war in the name of the church. Please find some sort of educated source beyond your own personal opinion, that supports States supporting a religious war, in the name of the Catholic Church, against Islam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:31:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I figured Donald Trump was just Joaquin Phoenix in great make up reaching his highest acting challenge ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:25:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Notice I said American Catholic. Not a lot of Holy Wars being waged out here in the suburds... Besides, isn't most of the fighting going on in Northern Ireland for political control? Granted, historically religion played a part decades, even a century ago. But isn't independence and social control the real issue?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry. American Catholic with German Irish and Norweigian roots. The Catholic church (especially on the community level) is a peaceful one. 

Edit: And yes. I believe I said back woods rednecks... Of course that includes Scotsmen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So it's bush league to not pick up the phone, but it's not to take EVERY beef you have with someone to social media? When is DEBC going to learn that their president is their own worst enemy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:51:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The FAR vast majority of Catholics wouldn't even consider it. I think if anyone did follow it'd be back woods rednecks claiming to be Catholic just for a chance to jump in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:12:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anodyne is solid. I liked it a lot. Whole foods park lane has it on and they have a Crowler machine. I talked to Waide their beer specialist,, he said it holds good for up to two months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 16:30:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the coolest Holy Shit moment of the week  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 15:50:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 32oz of 9.25%abv. You have to build a tolerance to something like that ha... But on an empty stomach at the end of the day..... Yeah I was done too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 15:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait.... I didn't know that BOB SAFER RAPED AND KILLED A GIRL IN THE 1990'S  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:59:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obligatory myopic, cliche and sexist joke about wanting to see the honeymoon, from a male Internet user. 

Congrats y'all. Don't let anyone take your happiness away. 

Edit: wow, apparently the sarcasm in the first half of my comment got missed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'd insert a dirty pun about the can not being the only big thing, but I'm way to relaxed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a fan. Was very excited. Thought if a brewery was going to do a raspberry Wit community would be the one to nail it. Had an unpleasant bitter after taste like fruit or berry seeds. Also just seem to be a 1 demensional beer. Was kind of let down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have captured the exact reason I don't watch me a soccer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Much smaller leagues back then. To get to a full season and series playoffs you had to have more series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ideally yeah... A separation between church and state with a union would be great... But realistically our government is run by corrupt and flawed humans. The only function of the government is to provide public service and protect citizens from harm. In no way is it the right for the government to decided what moral decisions we should make if they do not cause financial or physical harm to others. Saying a governing body of a nation this big should be the moral police is horrifying. Historically theocracies kill more of its own citizens than they protect. In now way now, nor ever was it the United States governments job to decide what was morally right for its people... That's up to the person to do. Don't look to the Hill for moral guidence, look to the Gospel, your family and yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wiki can explain it better than I can. In short,, tradition from the 50's revolving the playoffs 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Legend_of_the_Octopus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:06:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are correct, sorry for the incorrect information of squid v octopus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:53:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On the upside: this is further distancing the gap between church and state. Our Gov obviously does not always govern based on moral decision... Laws are supposed to be written to keep people safe. For some reason our government thinks it's their job to tell it's people what is right and wrong, it's not, it's their job to tell us what is legal and illegal. I hope this reminds everyone to remain faithful to their faith before their country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It doesn't work if you don't remain abstinent... If you actually maintain abstinent you won't get yourself or someone else pregnant. Once you have sex how ever abstitence only is null and void. Sex however is way to awesome for will power and discipline to prevail for 99.9999% of the population </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:38:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does this mean when she visits Detroit we can throw squids at her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Blue Bell announced to roll onto shelves with the flavor soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:39:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are certainly right about both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 05:48:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty wild. Do you have more pics at different angles?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:56:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm curious what the weight of this bike is vs the weight of its original model. If your a daily rider and spend time on busy highways adding this kind of weight to a sporty could solve push around from drafting problems... Any which way, to answer your question. If you like it, then yes, it's cool. Fuck what everyone else thinks. Your bike, your money, your opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well done sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [gif request] Tina Dancing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a scene from the Fron Files season 4 ep 12 where Tina is dancing and seducing the zombie basketball team. Does anyone have a gif of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So are we from here on our going to ignore that the civil war even happen??? Will civil war, confederacyI and Stone Wall Jackson or Robert E Lee be banned words by the FCC eventually?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 06:46:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A sportster modded out to an old style Dresser........ I can dig it... It's one of the most creative sportster mods I've seen here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 06:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best words ever spoken on this sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 17:56:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello Texas State Fair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 05:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not too unreasonably far from there.  Where is it, part of a park? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 22:43:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 19:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I sure as shit hope 9ts the last place you look, otherwise you're just wasting time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 06:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's odd.  The only thing that doesn't look photoshoped is the face.  Underwear and sticking even look artificial </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for night school for medic cert </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm currently working for a retailer.  I love the company I work for but trying to make my way into the medic field.  I am looking for a program or examples of programs here in the U.S. who offer night classes for nursing and/or paramedic programs.  The great Google gods have turned up no such resources so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:49:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the prison mullet, at first I thought it was in cornrows or braided </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sour chocolate with red food coloring.... nah, I'm good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This new alliance was my favorite development over the whole season.  Dogget drops a lot of her white trash and grows, and Boo ki m d of becomes a mom.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:42:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeowza! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:41:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreeing with Spartan and Loller, sometimes it's also an issue of face time.  Almost every time I've switched jobs I've had success because I had time to get in front of people.  I worked as a line cook for years training to be a chef.  Almost every job I got was because I went in and worked for free for a few days to show my skill.  A few jobs were because I knew someone who was opening a restaurant or they had a friend who was.  After a while in had success working in several great places and the resume got me the job.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:10:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mad Max Road warrior and Beyond the Thunder dome were hands dowm better than the original </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 06:25:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who the hell is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Had to look up the term "festering boil" image results more than I could ever hope for </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 20:00:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 05:44:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've seen him in his 19 70's B Film space hero outfit and his 60's hippie get up.  I've also seen videos of him in an episode 4, white robe Pincess Leah costume complete with ear buns and an obsoletely terrifying scare crow costume draped in rope lights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 05:41:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, one or two early on was okay (at best)  Her voice reminds me of that one awesome lady who sings really well at church.  But it really breaks the 4th wall hearing her, especially during a Montage or scene that has her in it or focuses on her  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 05:40:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All three actually.  The maker is The Electric Guitar Company.  It anodized aluminum powder coated tangerine, lights turn it a little red. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:52:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You misspelled "festering boil" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:49:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not always.  Buzz always does, he has several different ones.  Jeff Pinkus  (current bass player) has a standard uniform of sleeveless shirt, ball cap, jeans and cowboy boots.  Last night Dale Cover was in athletic shorts and an under armor shirt.  I've seen him in everything from a flashgordon hawkman costume to a ladies night gown.  Whatever is weird, light and breathes.  I totally dig the fact that Buzz only wears PF Flyers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:42:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They tour almost non stop, their shows are on the inexpensive side, all you have to do is show up early and not move from your spot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Got up close, front and center for The Melvins tonight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 08:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 23:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, who really uses fructise shampoo, that stuff is horrible for your hair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:56:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gemma singing 

Edit: Katy Sagal singing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit, I was not prepared to see that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:08:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Hemmingway.  His writting was incredibly detailed and he painted vivid pictures with words.  That being said he was a hard core alcoholic with wicked temper issues who let his demons win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:06:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck Yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is everyone'vs opinion on a cheat day. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 18:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2 months into my journey and I've made progress.  I finally have the discipline in hitting the gym everyday.  I've been disciplined in my diet and taking steps.  I'm now 2 weeks into no diary, no bread, no booze.  But today I've been having intense cravings for EVERYTHING I've committed to no eating. Do you practice cheat days?  24 hours of whatever I want.  Or should I stay strong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is the worst date you, or someone you know, have ever been on? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:23:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm back on the dating scene and had some what of a lack luster experience last night.  With as many stories as I have, I got to thinking.  I know I can't possible have the most interesting or or worse date experiences.  So let's hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 04:59:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a feeling...  Throw a pot reference in the title = upvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 04:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Normally I think the 3D figures look a little weird, this one is spot on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 02:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thought 69....?

Edit:  I stand corrrected.  Learned something new today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Grace Slick and Janis Joplin (69' summer of love) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:24:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 18:46:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo Gina!  I heard you were dating some guy who looks like that bitch, Amy I went out with last winter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:22:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really don't think you need the springer seat, it's going to raise you up and you may feel less stable.  Plenty of old school bobber go straight rigid seats,  reference any indian larry bike </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 15:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And this is why there is a  "No Mary Jane before a job" clause on the rule books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 15:17:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just nod if you can hear me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 14:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been asked more than once, "why don't they have seat belts on motorcycles?"  Or, "They should put seat belts on motorcycles"  after a frustrated and let down sigh I always try to explain how that's the worst idea ever and why.  Now instead of explaining it, I'm just going to show them this picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 14:37:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn.  I seriously love the tank raises on the nightster.  Well done sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 14:35:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought maps were supposed to be green yellow and red? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 14:33:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was just as worried about the heels on the vinyl seats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 14:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, one of the first HD's I've seen in a little while that nails the bobber look to a T.  Congrats to your brother, very envious.

EDIT: Don't change a thing, it all looks great together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 07:09:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes to the super glide (I believe superglide custom) but newer model year.  TBars, thunder header tail pipe, wind screen on the front  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 05:55:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bummer, gonna take down the post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 04:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty cool, but what did I miss as far as "unexpected" goes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 04:22:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe I Love Lucy did an episode about this, reference that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 04:19:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want to get really crazy look into the types of fats and research that.  There are monounsaturated fats, polyunsaturated fats, saturated fats, and Trans fats.

Mono: Good for you, plant fats, firm up in the fridge
Poly:Not too bad in small doses, stay fluid, think canola oil.
Saturated:Animal fats, try to avoid when you can
Trans:Chemically altered polyunsaturated fats to maintain nearly infinite shelf life.  Human body doesn't process.  Horrible for your health, avoid at all cost.  SUPER TASTY ex: crisco or any other shortening, shit inside of twinkies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 04:10:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2 years of culinary school and 8 years in kitchens and NOW is when none of my garlic puns come mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 04:06:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here.  After we cleared the board I went back out, took the big red five fingered balloon off, retaped, regloved and went back to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:30:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make it into a ring, or stick it in a ring? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:28:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know right.  I'm in 30's and love farting.  I may go get a blast at sonic just to Rev up the symphony tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:26:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try x/posting in /r/beards. They may appreciate this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:24:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My proudest was surviving taking my finger out on the meat slicer.  It was Saturday night and we had a little over 400 on the books and it was about as fine dinning as you get here in Dallas.  It was about 2/3 of the way through my shift.  I was on pastry and prep.  One of our Souxs yelled back to knock out ten plates of carpaccio on the meat slicer.  I bust them out, plate them up and take them to the hot line.  While cleaning I racked my middle finger right into the blade.  I split the tip of my middle finger open on one side down to the bone.  I yelled, and everybody knew what happen.  I yelled for our intern to grab duct tape, a trash can, some gloves and our chef.  I was in the hallway behind the restaurant when Chef Tre saw me wrapping up my finger in duct tape and told the GM not to send home since "Mike knows what he's doing"  I wrapped my finger in tape and two gloves taping them at the wrist and finished out my shift.  After I was done I went to the ER and got my 12 stitches.  When I came back to work a few days later Tre gave me a "dinner for 2" ticket to the restaurant for being a bad ass and sticking it out.

Tl;Dr: split my finger open on the meat slicer.  Taped and wrapped up. Finished my shift, got my stitches.  Stuck it out like a boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Craft beer knowledge or Archer trivia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:00:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It has been for a while.  It's for customers who are professionals such as contractors who shop in high quantities.  It gets them in and out quickly.  I'm actually all for it.  Moving that much in and out of trucks in the middle of the parking lot raises probability of other people'people's cars getting damaged (holy shit I'm starting to sound like my father) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 01:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Super creepy.  I remember when The ring came out these were popular.  Still weird as shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 00:15:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would be a great x/post for /r/nonononoyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 16:14:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good.  I'd have to warn you that you'd be one of many she's screwing around on and sticking that giant scorpion tail into </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 05:00:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's really rude to make someone who was hurt so bad the butt of a joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 04:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your actually right, even after severe brain trauma neurons can randomly fire off and cause muscle spasms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 01:55:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does she live in Mesa AZ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Been there, the stitching on the seat of my first bike split, had to sit on bungled down oven mits for a week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:15:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good deal, thank you for the info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 16:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My only question is can you use those credits earned to spend in ges you've already purchased.  I have a serious boom beach problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 04:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well played sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:12:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Astrology finally makes sense to me.  After seeing Scorpio it describes my cheating ex fiance.  This image catches her soul perfectly.  Thank you reddit for clarification. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:01:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pumping 5 hard inches into Uma Thurman?  I'm game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:56:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While there's a lot of buzz on this post about the pipes, there's buzz about reckless bikers and dangerous riding activity.  The post itself points it out by mentioning motorcyclists not wearing helmets.  Before people start bitch in about bikers who don't wear helmets, they need to notice that when a rider doesn't wear a helmet they only put their own well being at steak.  When someone drives distracted by choice by picking up their phone, they endanger themselves and everyone else.  It goes back to the old adage about not throwing stones in glass houses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:06:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't even continue reading their comments.  Their ignorance and judgentalness is louder than most pipes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:04:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, I'm curious.  How many people on this thread complaining about "scumbag bikers" drive a car and talk/text/ or check ANYTHING on your cell phone while operating a vehicle of any kind.  Be honest with yourself before sounding off or pointing a finger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 18:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or in a cage on their cell phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 17:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me Too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 17:57:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just glad I finally have an erections that didn't involve homeless people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 17:56:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 17:55:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 17:55:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 17:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 16:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely stunning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow you're good.  Not just just anyone can bring me to a climax in front of my mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I know... it's this little thing called situational awareness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 21:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy crap, you are a genius amongst archer fans.  I never realized that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 05:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Triple dukes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Y'all I must be running out of... carburator... or something (In honor of this weekend's big race) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 01:47:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For once I'm not the Whitest thing in the shower </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 22:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 02:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Muchas gracias </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 17:21:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone know who is in the red checkered shirt with blue hair? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 17:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Playing. Edie. Money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 17:19:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or a great horrible movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 07:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 31 yo and Texan.  Growing up k-5 we had a flag in every room and said the pledge every morning.  I remember most mornings we also sang the star spangled banner, Texas our Texas, or the school fight song.  Jr High we said the pledge and had flags, I don't remember singing though.  In highschool we had flags, but I don't remember saying the pledge much.  I participated in Army JROTC all 4 years and we said it there, but I don't remember saying it in any other class.  The attack on Sept. 11th 2001 was my Senior year of HS.  We started saying the pledge in some classes after that once a week on fridays, but that was it.  I never once remember saying it in college and do not specifically remember flags in classrooms.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure the go cart he drives to work has shit for acceleration but a great top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:20:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bet that dude has a great vertical leap, especially for his size! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DANGED.... OL'...   DISRESPECTFULL... MAN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:50:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I kept digging last night.  It's called The Slaughter  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 08:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Danged ol'.. that's just wrong man, know'm  sayin.  Just dang ol' disrespectful, man.  Like flag burnin' l..  just no attention to detail man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 08:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what I was looking for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 08:16:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, smaller name, lower budget, was straight to dvd/on demand but fairly impressive and well done for what it was  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for a specific movie and can't remember the title. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 07:15:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The premise is a little to familiar but the movie itself was a lot of fun.  Came out recently in the mod-late 2000's.  Teenagers have to survive the night in a house but there's of coarse a curse that makes it difficult to survive.  The opening scene is in black and white and it's a bunch of witches dancing around a fire nude (of course).  The title of the film was only one word, possible had the word "The" I'm not including that.  Does anyone have any ideas what movoe I'm looking for?  It had an evil dead feel to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 05:35:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which ep?  When Stevie gets awarded for politeness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 03:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Want.... must...  have.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 23:18:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either one of you guys have done it?  If so pics?  I'd like to see the shape of the bike and how it changes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 01:48:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just did actually last week, it's worth it though, just for the peace of mind.  I've had to replace a few of the motorsport plastic housings and got tires of it.  This go around yesterday was actually the water pump.  Took the thermostat housing off for easier access and to replace the hose that connects the two as well.

Edit.  Just for clarity it's an '06 4.0. Later this week I'm replacing all 4 shocks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 21:54:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Lemur got into the pudding cups again Sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Not a bad way to spend my Sunday morning. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 21:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 08:16:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So do you have head hunters that hunt tiny heads, or really really tiny head hunters that hunt normal heads? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 07:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention not stopping for a school bus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:48:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guy in the middle should have gone for the goat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:42:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If only he'd nut up and try for varsity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are you talking about?  His butterfly stroke is on the ball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:40:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That or he's really limited on pocket space and his wallet is poking out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:39:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know man, I'm in the same boat.  Godzilla could be emerging from the pool and I wouldn't notice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:36:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sir, deserve gold.  My only regret in life is that I have none to give. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:32:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ENHANCE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And the circle is complete </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:30:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe he just chose the meet as his moment to come out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know,  tan lines is looking pretty good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You dont, it only kills you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:02:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And one old lady with a staticky sweater and it's "Oh the humanity!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 09:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For such a creepy film why us this the only still that's ever seen on the internet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 09:42:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And shots that are so washed out you can't really see what's going on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 09:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you imagine reading that when you're REALLY high? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:22:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very cool departure from the norm on here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:13:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Constantly having to readjust, especially at the gym.  I have a constant fear that people think I'm just randomly touching myself.  But sitting down at the gym to stretch or lying down on a bench to press I have to lift and shift.  Even in a fresh pair boxer briefs, I still have to over stuff around when I sit in public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 08:16:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful, good job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 07:20:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Upon starting a new manogamous relationship, require your SO and yourself get full STD checks, look at each others results and religiously use condoms.  If you remain faithful and an STD comes up, you'll know you're in the clear and the other was unfaithful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 00:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah.  Not my style but fits the lines and shape of the bike.  Post this and ask over on /r/easyriders see what they think better.  It's more of a custom focused reddit

Edit: typos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 18:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm surprised no one else has asked.  What do you ride?  Depends on your bike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Yeah... it's been one of those nights </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 06:17:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 17:08:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hooray for small miracles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think in this case it was really a choice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 00:24:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Bill Cries* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 00:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooooo, maybe they cope with their horrible lives.  I would too if I lived with that Peggy Hill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 00:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank God I'm not the only one who noticed.  The scales are patterns pasted on and not well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:10:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your pedometer is an enabler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:33:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good to know.  My ride is only at 133k and I've just installed the 4th one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 04:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where did you get the 6 pack fitness meal bag and can you post a pic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Emma Fucking Watson.  Yes she is attractive.  Yes she is a good actress.  But when it comes down to it she's just another human being.  She has her faults.  Just like every other human being she has done something to hurt someone else or piss off someone.  Just because she was in Harry Potter doesn't mean she's an internet, gaming nerd who relates to us all.  She didn't volunteer for the role, she was a paid actress doing her job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:06:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Found one on the interwebs thanks to /u/michalegraves6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 01:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes.  This time it was the drainage tube going downwards.  Wasn't just seeping it was a full on gush (phrasing)  This particular part, 2005-2010 are 3 separate plastic pieces pressed together and they ward under being heated and cooled off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Today I'm going oem, but as soon as I have a few extra bucks I'm buying the piece listed above </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 22:25:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much, just bought a replacement plastic one since I'm in a pinch.  Will probably buy this one soon.  This is exactly what I'm looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 21:36:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes Sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 21:29:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 06, 6 cylinder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:38:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 piece plastic park pressed together.  The original lasted me 90k miles, now I'm replacing it due to total failure once a year it seems.  Can anyone suggest a quality part to replace it with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone else have to replace their F*ing thermostat housing unit as often as I do? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 01:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds about right, I knew ours was a couple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 00:54:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The machine?  No, but I can ask.  I can however twach you how to you is.  It's rediculously simple.  I hadn't even thought of using it for homebrew.  Genius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meh.  Imperial Sweet stout made at 7.8% by an awesome brewery..... No fucks given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:08:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Negative. S2E15 We met both of Lois' parents played by Cloris Leachman and Robert Loggia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is there an episode where Lois' father dies? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 20:37:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or do I keep missing something?  The first episode I notice it being mentioned is the Christmas episode of season 3 in which Francis spends Christmas with Grandma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 20:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very true on the "Get what you pay for" stance.  I planned on going Paugcho with a 21' up front.  Please let me know of all the misc shit that comes up during your build.  Much love to an HD brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just got a 32oz Crowler machine at work. Let's just say the beer isn't the only thing that's Big Lushious and in the shower. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:35:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let me know how the switch goes.  I'm saving up for a Softail standard (or custom) and want to make the springer switch.  Like most project I know there's going to be a lot of odds and ends that pop up while working on the project.  Keep us posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:33:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's solid, I can dig it.  I do like the black and chrome contrast.  I saw you said you were going to go all black and those were expiremental pieces, but I like it as it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What all do you have left to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:15:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> May be the best title in this sub.  Well played </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 17:12:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See.. /u/Sheiko19 gets the humor of driving in Dallas traffc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 06:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So does that mean we can drive 85 now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Signs of good pizza </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:17:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Nephew awaiting his first Holy Communion </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 17:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 23:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Upvote for title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 16:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, but I had a guy who was a reg at the dealership I used to work for (HD of Dallas in Allen TX) who could do it on a stock drive train with a 96' with a six speed.  No bored out jugs, no top end kit, no new cams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 16:56:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or, you know, when you shoot the springs out the top of you for tubes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:28:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I know this is the worst thing you can do to the front end of your bike.  Harley' are not made for wheelies.  But I still really want to know how on a bagger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 08:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be upfront and honest before hand.  Do what's natural.  Don't over think anything.  Sometimes don't think at all.  Have fun.  Be respectful.  Don't hurt yourself or anyone else. That's what I got for ya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 08:40:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have had ladies thank me after getting them off.  I thought it was cool.  Made felt like I did a good job and knew what I was doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 08:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1) have fun, don't be drunk, don't over think it.

2) high fives for the metaphore, just be upfront honest and direct

3) it last as long as it lasts

4) no clue, I have a penis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 08:34:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Different from woman to woman, that's one of the great things about them.  The one thing I would share.  Is if they feel rock hard or don't spread out or sink into herself when she lays on her back, they are fake.  Rock hard boobs are not always the case with breast auentation, but it's a sign of bad ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 08:32:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, it comes down to a few things.  The over all size of the guy and gal really.  If he's a very large guy and she's a very petite woman, vaginal death grip can occurr.  If he's small and she's a bit of a naturally larger woman in the lady parts area, he may not feel much.  But if both kind of mesh up in body type and size it can be tough to maintain stamina.  

You are right though, frequency or masturbating and style of grip can affect things.  It could also be the amount of time a guy has been masturbating with out having sex that could cause him to not be able to climax, with a virgin or not.  You just get used to how our own hand feels any thing else may be tough to get to finish with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:05:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed, and I hope they do.  I'd love to roll on a new street glide one day.  Have the ad ons planned out in my head and everything.  Just wish they had just stuck with the cable system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed.  A 110' engine with a six speed transmission is A LOT of power.  My old man has an 07 Ultra with a 96' and a six speed transmission.  As heavy as it is, that thing still flys.  If you put another 14 cubic inches of displacement on a lighter bike you'll be able to outrun most of your friends on older bikes.  If you throw a 120r on it, you'll be excited for a while, and dissapointed later on for a long time.

EDIT:  Don't be afraid to look into a used or older Street Glide.  The touring models over the last few years (3 I think) have had quite a few recalls.  They've switched over to hydrolic clutches and electronic throttles.  They've been running into a lot of failure problems.  Ive had two different bikes, one am 07 street bob, I've never had a problem with the cable throttle and clutch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:26:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never felt that Theo Rossi' acting tanked.  Charlie Hunnam's accent from time to time......   I wouldn't assign hate to Jax, I just see at as a total downfall.  For me it's more interesting just seeing how he's fallen apart without assigning emotion to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm hoping I'm just stating the obvious and you already made the connection, but it's a reference to the reaper.  And it being on the end of a M16 references the clubs roots being that of Vietnam War Vets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's l I keep a game of Snake when you eat your own tail, but with cum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 15:54:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meh.... things are coming back around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 21:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So the next question is do you take off the excess skin when you are 50lbs away from GW or wait until you hit the GW and be even lighter after the procedure?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 21:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Got it, upside to belts on HD's, graraunteed for life and almost no maintanenece.  Downside, loss of power.  That's all I really have.   Not cleaning and oiling a chain every 500 miles is nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:40:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too lazy to read everything (ironic In this sub I know)  But if you elect to get surgery to remove all you excess skin once you reach your GW.  How many pounds of skin do you think they'll remove? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:33:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This may be the most helpful post on reddit ever.  Good job sir! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like that handlebar set up a lot more with the taller risers, good pick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:26:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I've heard.  And riding next them they sounded horrible.  Lots of creeks and squeeks.  One of the guys I rode out of Arlington TX with, his primary wasn't even properly aligned and he had no idea.  Couldn't figure out why it was so loud and squeeky  (more so than a normal 3 inch BDL, I'm aware they can be loud and slap a little)  He was another guy who loved bikes, had a ton of cash, but no actual working knowledge.  No judgement to the guy, but it's a bummer to see someone drop so much cash on something that wasn't built with any respect or love.  Even though the guy spent his $ at his own ignorance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:15:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you asking more, "Why do some models have belt drives on the left and some on the right?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Met and rode with 2 different guys who bought and rode OCC when they first hit their hight of popularity around '02 or '03.  Both said it was the worst $80k they've ever spent.  I thought of a lot of things I felt were wrong with that statement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:06:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love MDK, didn't know this was still a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's possible.  I thought the same.  The only reason a small bit of me was doubting it was a bot was the profile had 4 or 5 pics of the same woman, none of them professionally taken.  Most were solo pics, no selfies, only 1 or 2 with friends.  But fishy was the first thing I thought.  Also possible that it was a real person and just drunk late on a friday.  All of this started going on around 1am my time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I was about 80% certain this was a bot or someone messing with me.  The fact that a 25yo woman couldn't even spell masturbating right was was a pretty strong give away.  Not worth wasting time on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's an angler apparently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:29:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, thought did cross my mind.  I was about 80% sure it was a bot or someone messing with me, wasn't really going to waste time on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:28:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:25:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am a male, female sent me that message </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:19:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was actually the first thing I noticed, don't think it bothered me as much as it did you though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "All of them babe, you're so fucking sexy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 08:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, apparently I don't know the difference between to and too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How the hell else do you respond to this? (Slightly NSFW) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 08:43:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 07:42:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> John Wayne Gacy, American Serial killer, in the 70's I believe.  He targeted teenage boys, 3 of which were buried in the crawl space under his house.  For secondary income he would dress and perform as a clown at children's parties.  The clown character, which he named, "Pogo the Clown" was considered to be Gacy's second persona or alter ego. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:14:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Saving Private Ryan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 03:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Umm... The Interview?  The only "The Interview" listed on netflix in the US is the Seth Rogan film.  Please tell me you were referencing something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:46:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man, what I wouldn't give to fluff her sleeves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Over all its better for your body to take in nutrients through out the day.  Your body will get rid of whatever it doesn't need at a certain time.  Similar to water, a lot of people say you need to dri m 8, 8oz glasses of water a day.  It does your body no good to drink 64 oz. All at once, once a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pogo the clown. John Wayne Gacy's alter ego. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 06:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:36:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And they cost 10 cents a piece, and we couldn't stop people from sending them to use racking up our bill! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 04:38:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well played sir, well played </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 04:38:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rawr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 17:28:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's one of our many graced </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 17:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably just to say he was there.  I don't get it either.  I really wish The MLB office would actually enforce the 12 second pitch rule, I think more people would be in the stands if it moved faster.  Looks like this lady was just trying to get to her seat.  But yeah.... The fans need to be more active and support their teams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/trampolines is pretty fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most exciting seats ever.  MLB wants to make the game more interesting I say drip all the nets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 01:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did the retard cross the street?  Cuz Nate fired him. (We fired an unpaid intern [he was actually that bad]  The next morning we found out he had heavy learning disabilities we didn't know about.  We thought he was just am immature ass hole) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 07:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Former employee here.  There was an incredibly generous side to him.  I had both seen and experienced first hand.  There was the dark side though.  I'm surprised the article didn't mention the sexual harassment lawsuit of 2010 and hardly mentioned the pending lawsuit coming this summer.  After certain interactions with him, I came to realize a lawsuit was one of his greatest fears (I still don't know why specifically)  What really dissapointed me I'd he really didn't know limitations and was master of reinvention.  If he had lost this lawsuit, I'd bet he'd be the person that could lay low for a while and rebuild a new empire later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I've never had a threesome in the shower, but I did just score a texas triple in one! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 06:52:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 21:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of the many, Many benefits of having a beard is avoiding these situations.  I highly recommend growing one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 21:21:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want to spend A LOT of time working on it and A LOT of money in machine shops to get proper parts made go for it, go for it.  I know this is absolute heresy in this sub, and I may be casted to HD Down vote hell, but a mid 70's Honda CB750 may be a better project bike if that's the style and era you're going for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 13:40:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That may be the most honest and real thing I've seen on reddit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 13:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, I really wish the original comment wasn't deleted.  Out of context this is amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 13:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Charitable and generous givers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 13:32:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like to see a statistic in relation to divorce rate and couples who had stripper bachelor/ette parties that went to far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 13:10:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not exactly.  We (The United States) currently provide South Korea with armed forces to secure it's boarder against North Korea.  We are not in In a state of physical conflict with North Korea, just guarding its southern boarder.  Think of it this way.  You're a parent and your child gets beat up on the way home from school daily by a kid twice his age and size.  You'd like to teach your child to stand up for himself, but the bully is far bigger and a fight would result in a bigger beating for your child.  Instead, you just walk your kid home yourself, to deter the bully from starting anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 12:37:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Poor Richard's in Plano at Avenue K and Park </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 12:35:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, 3 whole people on the internet don't like the fact you don't like duck dinasty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 12:17:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's what cream dreams are made of </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 16:11:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How about, "Cass Blumpkin"?   Oooo!  "Citizen Dick Bag" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the same way.  There's a lot of people coming to the family which is great, but seeing the same 883, 48's time and again doesn't do it for me like seeing the classics.  There is so much beauty in the classics that people put time, work, and heart into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:15:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did not know, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 20:46:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not crazy, that theory is pretty popular (Brook's mother) my favorite fan theory is that the homeless woman is the Angel of Death.  Every time she appears it is right before  (and in one case right after) a major death, even appearing in Ireland.  She still may be the ghost of Brook's mother, maybe both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It might be, the bridge kind of leans that way, the rest of the track kind of goes back to his more ambiguous style of writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just like rain on your wedding day isn't Ironic, it's just tragic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Horse s**t.  It's about the consumerism and over consumption of bottled water destroys development in third world countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most his are.  He gets pretty inventive in creating imagery with his lyrics.  But some of his songs seem fairly direct in his writing.  Be aggressive is about rough, forced oral sex and Flash Back (Tomahawk) is about child molestation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just make sure you use a solid bushing in your risers and you'll be good to go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 09:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 01:07:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 23:29:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was 16 when I saw it, 15 years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 20:15:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep it up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 19:40:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You really need to repost this to /r/MURICA The fireworks and zebra cakes made my day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 19:00:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A friend showed me this picture on an old site called www.phun.org, thought it was funny, kept looking around, not really that "wtf" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The photo that brought me to the internet. Been keeping it around for years. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 08:54:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep it going! Stay commited, stay strong, stay patient </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It's been 2 months since the last Super Bowl. Some of Katy Perry's back up dancers are still struggling to find work. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 16:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 16:49:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just repost post it, that's the easiest imo.  When you put up a title just make sure to put "x/post funny" somewhere.  Some redditors are dicks about calling out people who dont </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 08:07:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ohnplease, please x/post this to r/creepy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 07:55:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Inbred...

Ftfy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 07:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 07:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The picture alone is a good candidate for /r/creepy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 07:34:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As they say in Vermont, Gracias </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 07:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Am I still the only one who is dissapointed the article doesn't even say what the motto is?  Still waiting in suspense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:19:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh, weird.  I always thought from the bottom of my knee to the top of my ankle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 04:11:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I can hear my bangs growing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 19:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wish I could upvote this several times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wait, I'm confused, who actually won? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 14:33:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 14:04:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed, the guy's an arrogant drunk.  No matter what this situation is of a Dallas sports team, his comments are always patronizing or condescending.   As far as his public opinions, all he's doing is taking the popular high road.  None of his thoughts are ground breaking.  I agree with him most of the time, but he's such an ass I hate to admit it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 01:22:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got all my nephews their first piggy (coin) banks for their first bitthdays.  Each one I got at things remembered and had their name and birthday engraved on it with "from (my real name)" on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:56:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Extra gym class.  Detention as a kid was usually some hard core punishment in gym after school.  Now, in my 30's, gym time is time to zone out and improve myself, accomplish something and feel like a badass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 01:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excellent, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Immunizations in Plano </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 23:47:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone know of any clinics that offer immunizations and testing at a low cost.  I know low is a relative and undefined term.  I have no health insurance and am applying to EMT school and need to have a TB test, tetanus (TDaP), two vericella vaccinations, Hepatitis B, Flu and Menigitis.  Anyone know of the best options to have these done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 18:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was going to join in, but I think this thread is dying.  Time to jump ship on all these puns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 06:48:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Y'all my car is slowing down! I must be out of.... carburetor or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 17:11:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in the U.S.A.  I'd have to say ours is Ground Hogs Day.  The commissioner of the ceremony dresses as if it's the early 1900's and places a ground hog (large friendly rodent) in the tree stump.  When he pops out, his reaction to his shadow determines whether or not we continue to have winter or move onto spring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Redditors around the world, what is the most ridiculous holiday your country or culture celebrates? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 17:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What day does your country celebrate and what do you do on that day, that really, to an outsider, would seem completely absurd? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Found this piece of art in a Deep Ellum antique store </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 01:56:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 03:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was so damn fast I had to rewatch it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is a Belgian Blue Bull. It is a steroid free animal. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 23:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 21:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry, but your authority is not recognized in Fort Kickass

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 21:26:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me Too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 21:24:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd she were a president she'd be Baberham Lincoln </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 21:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or his series of children's books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 20:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Normally I'm very opposed to government over reach, but... ya know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 20:17:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watched it on demand, Mike delivering a lightening fast throat punch was the best thing I've seen on TV this week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 19:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least he would have gotten the Nobel prize for something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your right *tear* sometimes dreams are all you have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 16:10:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Burn the house down and GTFO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 15:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something happen with my dvr.  Not sure what, cable may have cut out.  During the commercial breaks it skips from when Chuck calls HHM to the scene with Mike actually running the protection job.  I never noticed the skip since I fast forward through commercials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 08:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In The words of Bam Margera Fuuuuuuuuuuuunck this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 08:04:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a little sleep deprived and have had 3 drinks on an empty stomach to Fall asleep.  I know it's probably bull shit, but I'm not thinking straight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 07:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dear God let this be.  If this is a April fools joke or satire site I'll kick somebody's ass I tell you what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 01:28:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Howdy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 01:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, go ahead and set up a profile, send me the link to it in a pm and I'd be glad to give as much feedback as you need </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 01:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know how your approaching online dating, the site your using, or anything else about what your doing.  So flying blind, here are some tips. 1) Take your time but be confident.  Forcing a meet up too soon seems aggressive. 2) Avoid talking about sexual topics before the second or third date, also seems aggressive. 3) avoid using snapchat and the like for anything until after a few dates.  You basically want your prospect to feel comfortable with you while still being confident to actually make it too and past the first date.  It's kind of a balancing act between social pace setting and taking the lead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 22:30:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reached this time on demand.  I don't know if it was a glitch, but my dvr missed the entire second act.  It also missed the scene at HHM where Jimmy is offered the deal.  Everything makes so much more sense, glad I rewatched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 22:16:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know, don't really care, got the info I needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:52:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> S1E9? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:42:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, I'm thoroughly confused.  I saw the teaser last week which included shots of the parking garage scene and I've seen people post screen shots or stills from that scene on this sub?  I watched the episode and fast forwarded through  it twice and never saw it.  Wtf is going on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:31:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriiusly, wtf, how did I miss this whole scene, is it in the pimento episode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:23:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed, documentaries are for education, films are for entertainment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:19:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed.  The special effects were entartaining for the first half of the film, then that wore off.  The effects remained good, but that's not enough to hold my attention.  The movie should have been called "Oh Shit Oh Shit Oh Shit"  or "Everything that could ever possibly gone wrong.... in space"  the movie itself wasn't horrible, but not worth they hype it got. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, stay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know this is probably an unpopular opinion on reddit, but I think James Franco and Seth Rogan are starting to slip.  I really felt that was the weakest of all their films and a little too predictable.  The jokes are starting to just run from movie to movie.  Rogan started out great with all his other films, but unless they spend a little more time writing and a little less rushing movies, they won't turn it around.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:54:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So do I assume the parking garage scene will probably been in next week's episode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 15:32:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm seriously confused.  I saw the parking garage scene teased last week in "scenes from next week's episode" and I never saw this parking garage scene where someone pulls a gun on Mike.  Also the descriptor write by the cable company says "Mike's ability to complete a job is questioned."  What the hell am I missing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:47:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My physical trainer had me do something like that.  The laws of physics were a little tougher on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 03:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 03:44:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bowser.  He's a 8 foot tall, spike shelled fire breathing dinosaur that commands his own army with a pension for kidnapping.  Not to mention a 10 foot vertical leap.  No good comes of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 03:42:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's just realy depressing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 03:23:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed, shorter and lighter pipes would make a big difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 17:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recognized the low end set up.  My first bike was an 04 ACE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 07:02:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's the up and out on the frame.  Also, does the design obstruct your view, how do you see around your tank? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 06:58:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honda shadow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 05:24:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too many sexual partners (one of them left me stunned and speachless with her number)  willing to do sexual things first date.  The other texted me dirty photos unprovoked the night before our first date to "get me ready" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're not really going to post a real question here, just don't post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:43:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you can follow directions, Steak au Puave.  Why, got a date tonight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:41:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am and I have.  I was on it years ago.  Oddly enough, the trashiest girls I ever met while dating online were from catholicmatch.com.  I'm not saying they all are/were, just 2 of the trashiest I've been on dates with were from that site and said yes to 7 of 7 ideologies (including contraception and premarital sex) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 18:23:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's shorthand for "redditor for redditor"  it's essentially a personal ad.  There is one for all of reddit.  I know some major cities (mine for sure) has one for their cities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do we have a r4r geared towards catholic dating? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 17:52:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And if not why don't we.  The structure would be to connect and promote safe dating for catholic redditors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 23:24:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean gloves like these right here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 19:08:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What color is it?  Black? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 16:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can actually hear you getting harder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 16:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really think we need to reconsider bringing back the "phrasing" thing, guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 16:30:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's not enough liquor and therapy in the world to erase this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 13:02:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you ever think that when Bugs Bunny dressed up like a girl Bunny that he was kind of hot?

Me neither. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:46:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really wish there were more unique HD'S on here like this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:19:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ew, this coke has gone bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 23:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 22:49:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Naw man, you just tell her the reservation or event is earlier than it actually is.  For example, if you have a table booked for 8:00pm on a friday, you just tell her the reservation is at 6:30..... on Thursday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 22:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do was with conditioner about every other day and cut back to washing hair with shampoo once a week.  Was cinitioning the beard with the same frequency.  What exactly do you mean by CO-washing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 19:46:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I think it's gotten better. I think towards the beginning of cougar town she went overboard on the facelifts, her skin was frighteningly tight and unnatural.  I've seen her recently and she looking great.  True she's not the perky fox she once was, I'm just more for a more natural graceful aging, such as stated above with Jennifer Aniston </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 19:38:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been there, I've worked for him.  As far as sexual harassment, yeah, it happen.  And I can speak for the fact that the ownership did  know right from wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 19:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And maybe not sexually harass employees, practice illegal payroll policies, not steal from investors. You know, maybe not making bad desicions that get you in legal trouble in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was really hoping for a topochico episode myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel weird saying this, and I don't really know why, but, agreed.  She is holding together pretty well for someone her age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:01:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not gonna lie, hope this makes a comeback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 17:57:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not trying to day that BB fans were over analyzing things... are you?  That's a stretch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 17:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The increasing number of obvious face lifts.  It was most obvious at the end of friends and the first few seasons of cougar town.  She's let up since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 17:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your grandma is Dolly Parton? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 17:27:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No but I'll ask for one at work and see what they have (I work at a whole foods) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 16:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well Chris Jones left and moved onto new horizons and kitchens a while ago, so did Ben Roche.  Richie is now the principle leadership.  I don't know if he will stay or not.  Cases like this, many times the principle leadership is promoted and offered a chance to buy into a piece of ownership.  If this is the case I think Richie would be a great fit and it would be an exceptional opportunity for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 16:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you ever rep up near Dallas or stick to central/south Texas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 16:36:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What brand of shampoo do you use.  I use the main and tail conditioner but every shampoo I've tried strips it dry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 16:34:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're in the wrong neighborhood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 15:44:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I interned in the kitchen and worked as a server there in 2010 and 2011.  At that level of restaurant the executive chef owner many times (as in this case) is a public figure head who is rarely in the kitchen.  The day to day leadership when I was there was Chris Jones, and Richie Farina.  Cantu spends most of his time working on other ventures.  The restaurant could easily survive, thrive even, without him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 06:25:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Lounge against the Machine is playing to boot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Celebrating an EPIC (irl) karma victory in the shower tonight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 06:25:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Moto and Berrista In Limbo After Chef Homaro Cantu Rocked With Lawsuit - Eater Chicago </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 06:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Different kind of post. Moto and Berrista In Limbo After Chef Homaro Cantu Rocked With Lawsuit - Eater Chicago </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 19:52:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 15:25:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of my ex's soul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:11:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trapper John MD.  Serious spinoff of MASH about a character who hasn't been on the show for about 6 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:08:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When someone you don't even know openly talks hateful, ignorant shit to you, just let it go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clarity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:04:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 7 7 7 7 7777777 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:02:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Despite it only being 2.5cm in diameter, the human colon can withstand and abscess infection pocket the size of a baseball </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:58:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A Remington 870 express </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:58:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stronger than a locomotive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:55:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucks given - 0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I pay a personal trainer,  exercise 5 days a week to loose weight and work at whole foods.  Late nights coming home from work I'll stop at In and Out for dinner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any healthy weight loss is a victory.  Keep up the healthy lifestyle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy crap you're beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 16:13:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An emotionally disturbed twelve year old called my sister a wetback.  We are German/Irish.  We had a pretty good laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 16:07:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very beautiful in its own way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 16:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your welcome here anytime.  We have a city and neighborhood for whatever your taste.  You'll find most  people here friendly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 16:03:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a proud Texan, agreed.  We are a state of people who in our history fought our own war for independence, then survived tough years until we were accepted as a state.  Hell or high water (and given the climate here were see both frequently) no one's taking that from us.  

I also feel sorry for anyone who invades Michigan or Illinois.  It would be the equivalent of invading Russia in the winter, there's no success their. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy crap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very weird, I thought I was posting this on the ELI5 post of "Why do Christians and people of other faiths who believe in eternal reward become sad when someone passes away?"  Don't know how this happen.  May have something to do with starting my Sunday Funday with an 8% beer at 11am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very cool.  May be a good candidate for /r/oldschoolcool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:07:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clean bike, but you'll have better upvote luck in one of the bike subreddits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:04:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just the general shittiness and rudeness of some people towards strangers.  I get it, it's the Internet and everyone has an opion, but some folks are just shitty for no reason.  I just learned to to respond. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 17:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From being in the service industry and bartending for so long, people who are generally thankful, gracious, and just nice to complete strangers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 17:54:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CD anti theft protection? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 17:53:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Simply enough, it's a selfish response knowing you will never interact with that person ever again.  I've felt it.  You just know you're never going to see or speak to that person ever again after spending so much time building a relationship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 17:49:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is a lot of warning signs people can look out for.  Whether you are looking for yourself or someone else  they can be spotted by knowing the list and being a little self aware.  In my case I noticed it when I was choosing to always stay home, sometimes in bed, instead of accepting my friends invitations to go out.  Staying in and solitude can be beneficial, but I was turning down every invitation so I could be alone.  Search signs of depression and you can find a list, just keep in mind what sources are credible and which arent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 17:43:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know of any science or studies behind it, but I've noticed the same thing.   The only explication I can come muster is the more people, and more good times equals up to more distractions from just drinking.  If you focus on drinking you notice how tired or buzzed you are.  The bigger the party, the more you are focused on having fun.

"It's way more fun to have six buddies with one beer each, then to be a dude with a six pack"  Nick Offerman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Had an ass h-whipping of a night behind the bar, so I finished it with this bad boy. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 16:23:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 12:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But, "Awesome" isn't spelled B A D.....? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 12:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People probably got tired of being sucked into engine turbines </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 06:26:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What.... the... fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 05:17:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Another chain but the nachos at Fuzzy's is good, just north of park on the west side of 75 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 15:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That might be the greatest statement made today.  Thank you sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I question all the decision I've made in my life that lead to me swiping right to this fine young lady. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 15:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 06:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see what you did there, hahaha.... "Place"..  haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 03:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty cool.  I'm not a fan of the red (not downing it, just my own personal preference) but the front wheel plays well with the fender.  I also like the continuation of the black streak along the entirety of the bike.  I can tell whoever worked on it put a lot of love and care (and cash) into it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:57:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the info, I've always wondered.  I'll keep my eye on the website and Fatbook.  Anything new or interesting coming up for the dyna family? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 01:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good deal, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 22:10:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great ride.  Educate me (I simply don't know) war sets it apart as "California" style? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:33:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any chance for an old style up swept fishtail exhaust for the modern dyna family?  I love the old school style but the new performance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:15:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIL Monica Lewinsky is now kind of hot.... kind of... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 13:42:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started on a Honda 750 ACE.  I got it when I was 19 and it was the perfect starter bike (for me at least)  750cc engine with a 5 speed got me around well even on the highway but lacked a lot of low end power.  In my case, the lack of power was for the better.  I was a first time rider off in my own.  Gave me a chance to learn to ride without the ability to do something stupid first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL Bob Odenkirk, Saul of Breaking Bad, was the creator of Chris Farley's "Matt Foley, Motivational Speaker" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 15:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Normally not a fan of the duece, but that's a pretty sweet looking bike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 07:58:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may possibly have the perfect body, just saying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ain't no shame with some Grapefruit Sculpin </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 06:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I never noticed how evil my Simpsons socks looked </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 21:09:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:43:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh wow, You'll have it running in a few days then, congrats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 15:50:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Other than air filter or breather what needs work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 05:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Much love to you, that's a fun bike and welcome to the family </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 15:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...my favorite bench </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 00:42:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good to know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm guessing because of the angle at which the tank sits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-08 08:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The tank "lasts longer"?  Please elaborate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-08 08:45:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you do it post pics.  I'm curious how it looks on a  bagger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 18:54:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously, if I had met you before, and met you after, I wouldn't know it's the same person  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 18:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out jpcycles.com or the drag specialties fat book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 16:10:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Taste so good make a grown man cry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 16:00:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're welcome.  What style of filter and breather are you going for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Questions about nursing school MD the Navy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 05:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm looking at starting school for nursing in the fall.  I have 3 semesters of prerecs' before I'm even applying to nursing school.  I was wondering if the Navy provides nursing school, or only accepts graduates?  Trying to explore all of my options and interested in serving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-06 14:48:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it looks great.  Really brings back the old style.  Are you thinking of lower the back end at all, it me help bring the lines and shape together, make things more continuous... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-06 13:42:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any loss is a victory.  25 lbs is also a big deal.  Keep on going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 21:23:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He'll yeah it's the best place for kolaches.  God bless Texas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 16:13:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slow Loris making a come back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably too wide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 05:02:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And this is why the show is more intelligent than people give it credit for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 04:58:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> N64 GoldenEye
Edit: all of puberty, most of highschool, and enough in college to lower my GPA .2 at least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 08:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think it's down vote worthy,  but disagree.  Was their over acting....Sure, bit I think that scene was one of the better delivered scenes early on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 18:43:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sin Mint is still on tap at Whole Foods Park Lane.  No where near FW I know, but just letting folks know it's out there if they want it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 18:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had to do a shot and a beer to settle after watching it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 18:37:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably Jimmy Smitts greatest moment as an actor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 18:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The final scene of Na Triobloidi: Jax screaming on his knees on the docks was a rough watch.

Also, What a Piece of Work Man Is:  The scene by the van where we see Tig saying goodbye and Happy crying.  There is something heart wrenching in the moments through the series when  see Happy crying or upset.  I think it's because both, so often he is the comic relief and also he is such a hardened, cold person.  Seeing the contrast is even more devestating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 18:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After a few years in the industry if come to find out the ever elusive female craft brewer is a smoking hot ticket.  That's a job you have to be incredibly passionate about.  Educated and willing to do dirty work and get sweaty is also a must. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 05:27:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chicago! I lived there for nine months during  their second worst winter about 4 years ago,  would kill to move back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:19:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How... wait.... wha.... I just... I dunno </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 21:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only see some In white  and someone in blue....? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 19:21:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lady on the streets and a Sikh in the bed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Date Ideas </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 17:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have my first "first date" in a long, long time coming up.  I live in Plano and am accustomed to going out in east Dallas.   My date lives in McKinney near Frisco and I'm looking for a unique idea of where to take her near her area.  She's not much of a drinker and a vegetarian, providing a very slight challenge to my normal night out to the pub.  Does anyone have good ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-26 03:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww.....  I miss the 90's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-23 20:23:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome bike, what's your up, out, and rake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone else have problems sending videos? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-23 04:16:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-23 00:24:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, it's a lot of nothing until the last three seconds,  then BAM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 18:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I could hear in my head was, "3...2...1... WEEEEEEEEEEEEEE" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 17:06:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The amount of skill and control the person has over their knife is impressive. 7 years in kitchens and I've never seen that kind of control </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 07:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Highvolts, did you ever think when Bugs Bunny dressed up like a girl bunny,  that he was kind of hot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 07:13:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bad, saw the post of face book, chef friends were posting it there abs right redditv would enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mind Blown on cutting a Carrot </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-21 21:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Which apps do you use </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 22:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm having a hard time finding an app I like to keep track of my workout routine.  I just started working out and have an organized weekly schedule and routine for when I go in, but would to keep better track of weight, reps and sets. Using my phone would be nice.  Having a book and pen is one more thing to keep track of in the gym.  What does everyone here use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 01:35:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see the laptop pic, but where's the guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 01:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hands down my favorite Clyde moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 07:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed about agnostics.  I've dated atheists before,  it was a brick wall, never again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-14 02:06:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I call BS on your theory, they both drive POS cars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-14 02:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ELI5 why everyone talks to me like I'm an idiot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-14 02:04:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIL I must be God.  I cry, boobs appear AND I get fed!  I shit and someone else cleans it up.  Plus all of the big people place %100 of their focus on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-14 02:01:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not a tumor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-13 23:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It has been for me too.  But, if I were living in Chicago again where there's a Catholic Church in every neighborhood I would stress about it.  It's a little different here.   The number of Catholics in North Texas is reletively high per capita, but mostly due to a very aging population and immigrants coming from socially Catholic cultures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dating Challenges in the South </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-13 22:31:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know if this particular problem rears it's myopic head all over, but I've noticed this problem over the last few years here in the Great state of Texas.  I'm a proud Catholic and have grown up here.  We have our fair share of Catholics here in the Dallas area, but I am still in the protestant bible belt none the less.

Due to my commitment to my career and odd schedule, I've had to resort to online dating.  I don't limit myself to only dating Catholic Women, but practicing Christian or Jewish is a must.

One problem I consistently run into is the narrow mindedness against the Catholic Church.  The best and most recent example I can give occurred last night.  I had been taking to this wonderful woman for a few days now and she apparently missed me identifying myself as Catholic on my profile.   Her response when I told her what church I attend was one of shock.  

She asked if I was only supposed to be dating someone who was Catholic.  I responded no, and that I wished to be married in the Catholic Church and raise my own children Catholic,  but she wouldn't have to convert.  Her response was that,  "She wouldn't want that for her children because catholicism is too extreme"  

I wasn't going to fight it.  I wasnt going to get into a conversation on apologetics.

I'm not sure how to handle this.   Die anyone else feel the adult dating challenges.  It has interfered with a previous long term relationship.  How do y'all handle dating outside of your faith? 

TL;DR I'm catholic,  facing challenges of not having a large dating pool of Catholic Women.  I date protestants and it doesn't work due to narrow mindedness on their part.  What do I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 16:12:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And what ever sploosh is for men.  Which I guess is just sploosh....  But with semen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Was looking for a quote from hank on Google images and discovered this </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 17:05:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-08 07:02:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh please tell me this is going to /r/photoshopbattles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-08 03:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Global population control </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-08 03:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't so much in the beginning.   Her last two seasons when she started lying and causing problems I lost my likeness for her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-07 04:22:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lakewood Brewing Co. (Dallas, TX) The Temptress Imperial Milk Stout  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is a product that seems mousy people have, but when it comes down to it, is a scam? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-07 00:34:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems the more things advance,  the more stuff we have.   Anybody ever notice a household product that everyone owns that is really just a rip off or a scam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 12:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This thread section is why I love reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where is a good place to go for apps outside of the Google play store? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 19:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Android user here.  With all of the vast amounts of free information on them internets, the play store can't be the only place to go for content.   Any body have any good resources.  I'm not looking for anything specific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 19:17:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've actuary said,  "Young people's music sucks" and meant it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 06:45:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had the same thought, would wet myself if that was the case </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Police Officer Arrests Pizza Delivery Guy, then Delivers Pizza </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 06:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 14:08:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey look!  It's an old fat boy on an old Fat Boy......    sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 14:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm gonna dunk my balls in your mouth.  Your gonna gag, I'm gonna laugh, we'll be best friends forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 08:21:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck Zach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 08:10:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking Jenny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 07:50:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so out of the loop with whatever Jenny is on reddit.  A l8nk to the OP would be nice. 

But Amy Thompson is a fucking whore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 07:33:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The moment when suspicions are confirmed and you have proof your SO is cheating on you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 01:07:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I haven't changed pillows but I'm washing all of my pillow covers tonight, I also wear a beanie when it's cold and a ball cap at work, washing those tonight as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scalp is breaking out, any advice? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 00:23:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 16:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone know who's on the left? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-24 06:22:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's exactly how I read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 05:24:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He actually did, I would say best short trimmed beard of the 80's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 05:24:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And fast, as if it were on some sort of highway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-21 15:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kenny Loggins called....

Edit: Truth be told I'm a little jealous, my beard isn't that thick, keep it going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 22:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom used to do that with chicken, broccoli, and cheddar.  I never would have thought to make a sandwich with out of it.  Awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 20:32:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 20:31:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks.  I've been focusing there too.  I've cut the fast food first and foremost.  I also drank my emotions away all through the month of December.  After making an ass out of myself at a NYE party I decided to stop drinking, at least until I've showed myself I don't need it.  I recently took up a job at whole foods.  That has helped me keep focus on what goes into my body.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First Day of Disciplining my New Life </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 20:16:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Things got a little shitty for me this last year, but, at the risk of sounding cliche, today was my first new day.

Mid October I left home and moved across the country to be with my fiance'.  After moving to Arizona, giving up my promising job at one of the best new breweries in my area, and leaving all of my friends and family behind, I found my soon to be blushing bride not to be who  I thought she was.

Everything was wrong and I realized it 6 weeks into a new place.  I had found my fiance, the SheDevil as I now call her, sleeping with someone else.  As it turns out, she had been with him for the last five and a half years, and had been sleeping with him the duration of our two and a half year relationship.

I moved  home beaten down and alone.  I had given up my position at the brewery and my position had been filled.  But today I did something I hadn't done, but kept promising myself I'd do every day.  I got my ass up off the couch, did 15 push ups, 18 sit ups, and 18 squats.  I also ran 1.8 miles.

I know one day doesn't make a habit, neither does one week.  But realizing I can't commit to others who choose not to commit to me, I am now committing to myself instead.  Push ups, sit ups, squats and running every day.  

If I can do it depressed and 70 lbs. overweight, anyone can.  Keep pushing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 17:34:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't agree more.  Take it in to a local shop.  Ask other riders about good shops, maybe check out yelp.  I'd also recommend picking up a model and year correct service and parts manuals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 17:24:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I vote you just watch the site and make an opinion for yourself.  If you don't like it, quit watching, I you do, watch it.  Do yourself a favor and stay off the sub.  People will fuck with you here, like subtly referencing Tig's fate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 15:36:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so I out of the reddit loop, didn't know this was a thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where is everyone going to download since The Pirate Bay is down </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 04:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm getting itchy to download some new music and I don't want to forget what to download while waiting for them to get back up and running. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Head Shaving/Breaking out </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-17 16:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I recently made the choice to shave my head.  I'm going bald and pull off the bald and bearded look well.    I do however break out when I shave.  Most of it is on the site and behind the ears so visible to those around me.  When I don't shave I may have one or two if any pimples under my hair.  Any recommendations for a solution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> While we're on Ron Swanson Quotes... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-17 02:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-12 00:44:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meh, you can't expect much much more from someone who chose to be identified as "poopooslut" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 23:30:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bless his heart indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 23:08:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I *sobbing gasp* just wanted a *sobbing gasp* division *deep breath* chaaaaaampionshiiiiiiiiiiiiip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 23:06:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not disappointed in the Cowboys, quite the opposite.  I think they're growth this season was fantastic, including Jason Garrett's.  I'm disappointed in the calls, particularly the one, in today's game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 22:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *sniffles* sometimes its good to cry *sniffles* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 22:35:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But he called a catch complete on the field.  NY replay office ruled it incomplete </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 22:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every replay I saw, the ball never got the ground.  But f*** it.  Still proud of the cowboys this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> After the Dez Bryant incomplete call (xpost /r/Dallas) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 22:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Every Cowboys fan after the last Dez Bryant incomplete pass call </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 22:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 21:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's another app based program that is with looking into.  Is called 6 Weeks.  Its a conditioning program for push ups, sit ups, squats, dips, and pull ups.  Similar type of conditioning program as Couch to 5k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 15:59:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My ex has taken every single one of those photos, except you know, miss she's fat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 04:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good being the key word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 04:34:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is about the only way it happens.  Worked fur a dfw brewery for 2 years.  That's your only way in.  Be picky who you work for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 04:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And there we go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 04:04:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dawn of the Dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 03:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a sub for /r/accidentalswastica we should have one for accidental penis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 19:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.eyekandiart.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/07/green%20pearl%20w%20purple%20black%20edged%20flames%20harley%20davidson%20motorcycle%20custom%20paint%20set%20by%20eye%20kandi%20pic%202.jpg. Basic idea of the concept I mentioned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 19:42:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been in the craft beer business for a while.  I even worked for a brewery in Dallas for a few years.  The most aggravating thing was I had no coworkers who could just chill the f*"!k out on good, normal, well made craft beer.  Everyone had to have the biggest, rarest, most elaborate beer to find.  I love craft beer, and the industry.  Not everyone is a hipster, but unfortunately, they're there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 17:53:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want to get eye popping with it, keep the same purple, swap the black with a light metallic green with a lot of shine.  The two colors contrast well together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 15:30:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really just an excellent ploy to get beer nerds and hipsters to brag about having whale testicles in their mouth.  Way to go Iceland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 15:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In not, but I might, BBC has always been the most impartial news source imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 05:24:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As you so eloquently put, "you don't pneumonia from cold weather". However, a 67 year old man already had a suppressed immune system (fact, immune systems decline with age one past early adulthood years).  Also, cold weather does suppresses ones immune system (fact). The combination of the two would leave him more susceptible to the disease.  Also, I never stated it was fact.  I just said these were the two versions I've heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 03:10:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WE HAVE AN ANGER ROOM IN DALLAS !$ *!!-";%#+- #!!  Holy crap that's where it's going </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 23:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had an actual laugh out loud moment with this one. Thanks for sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 17:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's amazing.  That might be the must selfless thing I've ever heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 17:38:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was your biggest motivator over the 26 months and what was your final tipping point that inspired you to take action? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 15:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Troll 2 is the greatest bad movie ever made.  Easy to find on dvd online, and it may be in netflix.  Don't worry about seeing Troll first.  The two are unrelated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 14:11:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, it pulled me back enough to take my hand off the left grip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 02:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Come on...  Who wouldn't want a 13 year old television with a busted power button that takes up a ton of space and always has the closed captioning on...?  Its an awesome find </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 01:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy crap you're beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 00:41:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> None of them are absolute musts.  I just didn't know if their were any extraction apps.  Any other media sieves would be great.  It would also be nice if their are any apps to cast documents to the Tv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 00:39:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yikes, that tops mine.  I used to work on the Texas hill country in my very early 20's.  I decided to get a little sun while out riding on my day off and lost the shirt.  I was riding right next to the Guadalupe River and took a cicada going about 60mph.  It struck me about half an inch above the nipple.  Lesson learned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 23:10:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm looking to do a project build similar to this.  I'm interested on sine measurements.  What's the backbone stretch, front leg stretch, rake, and cup size? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 23:09:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can confirm that, except it was a cicada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 22:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Didn't want to go that rout but I think I may </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Must have apps? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 22:52:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just got my chrome cast in the mail today and getting my new TV in tomorrow.  Other than netflix, Pandora, and of course Chromecast itself, what are some apps that are must have or y'all would highly recommend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just shoot me a pm, here in the comments is fine too.  Remote doesn't work and CC is stuck on.  Its free, just pick it up.  If your going to just plug a DVD player or cable box into it, it works fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Free TV in Plano for pick up </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:31:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 02:05:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've heard two different versions of George Washington's death.  The first the he didn't die of pneumonia, but of syphilis contacted from his mistress.  The other was that he did due of pneumonia.  He was at his mistress' when her husband came home, George Washington peaped out the window nude, in fear of being caught.  He ran a considerable distance home in the snow in the bare, thus contracting pneumonia. 

Tl;dr. George Washington would have lived longer if he kept it in his pants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 20:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YES!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 18:45:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No worries, I'm a cowboys fan.  Jerry is a douche. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 18:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it just me?  Every time I see Clay Cooley, all I picture is what Will Farrel would look like if he spoofed a used car dealer or someone running for state comp troller? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 01:00:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What ever happens I hope the best for you.  I was madly in love with my best friend in college for 4 years.  I told her how I felt just to finally clear the site and lift the weight.  I knew what her response was going to be, but I manned up.  It got a little rocky for a bit, but soon enough, we were closer than we were before.  What ever happens, I hope happiness for you both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-04 02:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did a basic factory reset after T-mobile said that may be the issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-04 01:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, it's date night so I'll be spending a good amount of time tomorrow on this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 23:42:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I do.  The factory flas on the phone settings or the kind where I hook my phone up to my pc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 23:32:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool, I know almost nothing of what you said.  But excited someone had the same issue as me.  What was the solution, in plain terms, that a 12 year old could understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 23:05:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/MfHmRnR. Not that much actually... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 22:10:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did have to switch it, but no luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 22:09:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've done both, twice, no luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 22:09:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/l2NXRxc. Here is what I have space wise.  I've done a factory reset it just takes me back to when the phone updated to Lollipop, didn't fix the problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 19:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's the melodrama in the singer's voice.  I don't know how else to describe it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 19:14:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry, realized that after I hit submit.  I know "us" included peopel it wasn't supposed to.  I guess hwta I meant to type was, "People like Steve Harvey ruin the reputation of Christianity for those, including myself, who don't agree with his closed off, warped, sexist, homophobic and myopic views" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 19:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really want to believe this is a joke or a spoof, buuuuuut........ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 18:55:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> excellent, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 18:41:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think one of the biggest reasons to my understanding, was the Judea was expecting more of a more, for lack of a better word, epic Messiah.  I'm having a hard time finding the right words, but to my understanding, the expectation was to be more majestic showing of who the Messiah was.  The concept of a pour carpenter's son, who traveled by foot, and taught peace and patience was unexpected and a little too radical to be believable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 18:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no, I agree, there are others, I don't argue that.  But really, I can only speak for myself and the groups I run in.  Collectively, that's not a good representation of what all of us believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 18:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Upvote for the lyrical content and yeah, it certainly changes the mood.  But there's something about this song I can't get behind.  It's not yarling, but it's something in the vocals that kills it for me style wise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 18:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool, thank you.

So I'm completely ignorant on technological issues when it comes to this type of thing.  Step by step, what do I do.  Break it down like I'm 12 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 18:09:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This guy (Steve Harvey) seriously ruins Christianity for the rest of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 18:06:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (GRANTED I ONLY HAVE 1 SIDE OF THE STORY, I still felt compelled to share)  I (or a friend of mine) can reinforce his absolute horribleness.  A good, trusted friend of mine is a general contractor in the North Dallas area.  He got called to Steve Harvey's Dallas area home a few years back and nearly walked out on the job.  He claimed that Steve Harvey only communicated through yelling and screaming at people and had the inability to actually communicate anything like an actual adult.  He was screaming at the crew, his wife, and his children the second he walked in the door.  He said that when his children came home, ran in the door to great them, Harvey held his son by the nape of his neck and said I, "I don't even want to speak to your ass until you run up stairs and your home work is done."  Once again, it's a second hand account, but I trust this person fairly well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 17:53:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this the same as a factory reset?  I did one of those about 2 weeks after the update and all it did was reset it to when the phone updated to Lollipop, so not an actually factory reset, more like an update reset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Known problems of Google Nexus 5 not making or receiving calls after Lollipop update </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 17:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've posted this on /r/android and have gotten no luck.  Ever since the OS update late November, My cell phone has an extremely low amount of memory and isn't able to make or receive phone calls.  I have a minimal amount of photos on my phone, few unnecessary extra apps, and have removed all music and videos.

Here is what I have:
A Google Nexus 5 in good condition, purchased on Amazon.  
T-Mobile pay by the month account.  
I've done the whole sim card swap through T-Mobile.  
Only 2.1 Gig of available space (prior to the update I had a ton of music and photos and still had 12 gig of space left.).  
The ability to stream just about anything using LTE.  
Use of WiFi.  
Ability to make and receive text messages.  

What i don't have
Insurance on the phone (since purchased in full on amazon, learned my lesson there).  
The ability to make and receive phone calls.  

I've been to 3 different T-Mobile stores and no one's been able to help so far.  Does anyone have a definitive solution to this problem??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 21:52:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I spent about 45 seconds looking for the hidden vulgar message... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 14:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least there's the happy ending of Jax and Tara riding off into the sunset. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 14:10:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this thread really applies to hire the note was written.  The bite served its purpose well, but just sounded like an idiotic threat the way it was written </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 01:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's batshit crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 01:18:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buried in secrets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 22:31:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You seem very smart too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 07:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't imagine how bad it's going to hurry to pull those off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 06:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 05:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Forgot to mention, 30/m, I think it'd be fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 05:56:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be interested in Skyping... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 06:23:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still riding the stock 80' with a 4 speed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 21:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting.  I'd love to ride that configuration some time just to try it.  Nothing aggressive, I'm a big fella, don't know if I'd want to put my center of gravity that high </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 19:21:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More so than a springer seat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 17:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fantastic looking bike.  I've always wanted to know, what does the riding position feel like sitting so high on a posted seat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-25 05:42:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gew </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-25 04:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glad I could help. Merry Christmas (if you celebrate something else, Happy That) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-25 04:27:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elizabeth_Montgomery  Depends which husband you're talking about.  Not sure.  Very few men deserve a woman of that caliber though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-24 19:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed.  Not just beautiful but talented and classy.  Bewitched was my mother's favorite show as a child.  On late night Nick at night we would watch reruns when I was little.  Had a crush on her back then, rekindling that admiration now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I think I just redeveloped my childhood crush on Elizabeth Montgomery (pic from early 1960's) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-24 17:52:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-24 05:12:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Been creeping me the F*** out for 24 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 19:58:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe the proper term in, "Yowza!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-21 04:29:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I need that on a t shirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-21 01:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is this inappropriate for a 31 year old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 18:45:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That didn't take long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 18:23:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did I just motorboat Dickbutt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 15:51:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am excited about that, going to wait a month or for the price to drop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My first thoughts when anyone mentions American rights in regards to N Korea </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 05:37:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 05:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 04:10:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would be great for /r/creepy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 03:38:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Call me ignorant (I know my inbox is going to blow up for saying that) but what does "Ute" stand for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 03:32:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10/10 would hit.  Bikini girl wasn't bad either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 01:31:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Le sigh* oh vista </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 00:56:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, did his amp go up to 11? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-15 00:08:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe, at least they got a little cash and food from craft services for the month or so during filming.  At best, a permanent job skill and connections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL Part of Robin Williams' rider, a written list of demands to work on set, was that a certain number of people employed on set must be homeless. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-14 23:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-14 18:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus, just because TM gets sold doesn't mean he'd lose his job, plenty of businesses get sold with little or no staffing changes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-14 17:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I find it interesting (I really do, no judgment passed) that many people who posted on this thread who hate their children never wanted them.  It seems that the child did not much more than be a child, the parent hates them because they never wanted to be a parent in the first place.  It really has little to do with anything the child has done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 03:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where's the Tim Horton's? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 02:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any idea at all who the model is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Needs to be on /r/beer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was very much hoping it was a jot dog from Portillo's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 19:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed.  I've known 3 true 1%ers.  He fits the bill.  I'm so glad his character held true through the whole series.  Props to KS for writing his character true through the whole series.  And even more so to Emilio Rivera for executing him so well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 18:03:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good catch, you're right.  I completely forgot.  So he didn't give up his only son, but still has one son killed to make things even. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 14:39:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glad I'm not the only one who remembers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 18:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, going through the most recent events  in my life.  EAP is so correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 17:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Half Sack, "Hey look!  Its an old fat boy on an old fat boy.....  Sorry"

Juice, "Gemma knows every truth, behind every secret, inside of every lie.  She is the gate keeper" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 20:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So that's what I missed.  Made the same mistake.  Got a 96% and couldn't figure it what it was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 20:13:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was happy, you were right, which member want in the original 9? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 19:17:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Men of Meg have a boobs to ass ratio requirement, and sorry, but you didn't make the cut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 17:27:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This makes me very proud, I can't wait to move back home next week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 16:58:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I know what you mean, I hate it when my owner sticks her ass in my face too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 17:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We actually sat and talked for about 5 minutes.  I asked politely for a photo once he was done eating.  After that he asked where I was from/going.  We were in his restaurant and he pretty much asked me a customer service satisfaction survey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I met "The Demon" today. I couldn't help myself </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 04:59:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 17:00:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep going, stay strong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 16:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was really bummed when the gig cut off right before the second guy gets clocked with the bat.  You see it coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 20:48:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eh....  I try to avoid Instagram, cheating ex gf is a sociopath and make my life hell through it, even if I block she'll put up a new profile on their just to find me.  Its a Shane too, I was funding some awesome motorcycle parts through @chopperswapper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 18:36:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't be surprised if some how spoilers for next weeks episode show up through my scrolling on Tinder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 15:31:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the exact reason I went on media black out when I got home from work, no Facebook, twitter, reddit, any online articles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 12:02:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My only regret is that I can only up vote this statement once </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 11:55:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I second that.  I also ride. 70% of your stoping power is in your front break which is our right hand lever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 11:41:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When he said he was calling it in and she, in short, said she wouldn't go quietly, I was hoping for an epic suicide by cop scenario where Jax watched from a safe distance, they make eye contact, and he nods once as to say, "Now is the time".  Gemma opens fire and 7 or 8 state troopers take her down in a blaze of glory, as Jax watches from his bike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 09:32:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go out by Lake Lavon in Collin County, thats the best riding I've found so far.  
 If you want to make a half day trip out to see a pretty bad ass landmark, go to the Baker Hotel in Mineral Wells TX.  The ride is just okay, but the experience of playing around and taking pictures at a nearly 100 year old, abandoned haunted hotel is worth the ride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lollipop and Nexus 5 issues </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-02 20:10:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-02 13:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RHCP Blood Sugar Sex Magic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-02 02:42:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats to the top of the board.  Your friend Michael from Dallas, then Mesa AZ, and, unfortunately back to Dallas soon here to wish you Congrats on the whole trip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 06:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would be awesome in /r/unexpected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 06:22:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No lie, I immediately saw your pic and went "Hey, Bill Nye" then hung my head in my own wrong shameful ness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 05:55:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry I can only up vote that once </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Not working all together...? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 04:41:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I get when I try to load Bacon Reader is an error that says 410 UnAuthorized..  Anyone else having these problems.

Also, about 60% if not more of the time gif's don't work.  Does anyone know of any solutions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-30 21:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why the hell is every dessert "pudding"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-30 19:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BRILLIANT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [SPOILER]. Jimmy Smits spills the beans, sort of, and relationships in final 2 episodes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-30 05:28:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-28 23:13:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, that explains why Gemma is always...  Living on the edge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 19:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seen your bike here and love it.  Just a personal opinion, take it for whatever you want.  A front turn signal replication kit would move your signals down to the front forks and clean up those nice ape hangers a lot

Edit: but seriously, I love your street bob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 16:58:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jim Vs Dwight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 09:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm actually afraid to click the link, I don't want to be one of the last things I hear before bed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thank you so much, Facebook, for giving me another gem like this... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 09:28:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Uniform at work is a lack snap up chefs coat and a bandana. I took some liberties on my cake day and went cholo </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 09:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-26 22:32:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My story is a little odd but fitting.  I apparently had a sleep walking problem I never knew about until one particular night my junior year (maybe senior I can't remember) of high school.  

I woke up, shaving, in the shower.  I normally shaved in the shower to save time.  Half of my face was cleanly shaven, no Knicks or, finished my shower and dried off.  I realized I had no idea what time it was so I hurried.

I saw that it was 1:00 and freaked out thinking I over slept by hours and was afraid of getting in trouble.  I jumped into my clothes, grabbed my back pack and ran out the door.

It was dark out.  1am.  But hey, at least I was already dressed and shaved for the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 21:57:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree, grooved concrete is bad enough on a bike.  But a quick stop, downhill, possible wet, over a drain?  I'll find a different route on a bike </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 06:28:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Were there any clues in the final season to Tommy's identity before the reveal in the final scene?  Did I miss them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 04:13:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How so?  I've been in Harley sales.  When it comes down to it, your going to do one of 3 things after you buy the bike.  1) Your going to ride it and maintain it damning the cost 2) your going to ride it, not maintain it, not respect your machine and let it go to Shit, or 3) let it sit and rot in your garage.

Any hobby worth doing is going to get more expensive as you immerse yourself further into it.  Fact of life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 20:51:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All in all, if you do your own maintenance, expect to pay between 8-10k for the bike and expect  the same in parts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 19:07:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really I don't intend any disrespect in my response.  But if you're the type to ask "Is it worth the cost of  maintenance?" I suggest a different hobby.

Woodworking:  oh wait.  Saws have to be maintained and lumber isn't cheap.  Oh, and safety gear.

Maybe try hiking: but then you have trail fees, safety gear, books to buy, camping equipment if you get really into it.  Plus all the time you have to take off of work for trips.

Maybe canoeing or kayaking.  Your initial up front cost is a $1200 kayak if you want something new and versital.  Oh and the carrying rack on your car, stuff for day trips, fees to get into national parks.  Oh yeah and safety equipment like beacon lights and life preservers.  Don't forget paddles, they cost too.

Shit that's expensive too.

Everything you do is going to cost money.  Every easy to get your ass out and experience something is going to cost you.  Get educated, get prepared, then say fuck it and enjoy your self.  

But don't forget to but a helmet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 18:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good eye.  You do have to add in quite a bit for the 3imch BDL primary drive, that'll run you up.  If your not doing the work your self estimate a min. Of $60 an hour for labor.  Might get a better labor deal from a local bike shop than a Harley shop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 11:17:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could be retitled /r/momsofoldschoolcoolsubscribers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 11:13:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Da FUCK did I just read? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 11:09:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like he's replacing a list of talented pop Shit with talentless pop Shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 10:48:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Favorite MFC girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 10:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably the most hauntingly addictive random sub I've seen so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 10:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still cute though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My favorite Rocker and my favorite 5 head (Neil Fallon) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 10:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 10:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He looks better as a Tranny, is that weird? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 10:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worlds hottest 5 head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 10:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd believe it.  I went to Plano Senior High School.  When I graduated in 2002 we had 22 soda vending machines in the school cafeteria </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 09:47:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not cool dpenton, you shouldn't "Tug" on somebody's emotions like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 09:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bit Torrent it is then Walberg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 06:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have a good link to watch the shield online? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 06:17:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jax and Opie getting into some serious trouble as kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 06:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I concure, I've discovered some serious foreshadowing in a couple Monologs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 06:14:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you think Wendy will go out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 06:13:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't really think Sutter would have a problem writing her off in the last episode.  He's given her such av spotlight for so long what an epic ending for a character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 06:04:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jax, Nero and Juice took the whole episode, but Juice took it the most </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-22 09:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An eye for balancing books like Bobby...?  I see what you did there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-21 05:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What ever I can do to help ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 21:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's from Houton, they do that down there

EDIT: My bad, thought your comment was from a different post I had made earlier, that's what I get for day drinking while on reddit on my day off. 

I have no actual knowledge whether or not this kid is from Houston.

But.... Seriously...  Houston Sucks, fuck those guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 10:23:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your the kind if weirdo I want to be working next to in a kitchen all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 10:22:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A red neck kid pretending to be even more red neck.....  And he's way to young to have a belt hanging out from under his shirt...  He'll make for an awesome redditor one day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 09:33:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would Nero know the whole truth about JT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 09:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How about the basement of the Alamo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 09:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Poopflinger

That is all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 09:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, looks more like JT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 00:14:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure they had an old episode of Rescue 911 about this same scenario </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 00:08:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really didn't intend it to be that.  I grew up Catholic and my dad's step mother had that same type of voice just not as strong.  Everyone I hear Katy Sagal sing it just take me to that memory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 22:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what I thought, but I feel like there was more buzz on here about Tig being the rat than anyone else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> SPOILER The Rat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 20:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We've all be discussing who the rat is over the last several weeks.  At first I was annoyed at this topic being dominated by nothing but a bunch of fan theory, but I soon fell privy to it as well.

I've seen almost no discussion on the reveal of Borosky being the rat and anyone's opinion.  Anyone feel cheated at a weak reveal or let down it wasn't a member?  

"Trust me, in here, all I am is somebody's asshole" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 20:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't be surprised if it was just Sutter's way of being funny while extending the table </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 20:33:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed about the 4th wall.  I think that's my biggest problem with it.  

I also have stylistic issues.  Her sound is very mid 80's gospel country (that's not a shot, I promise). It doesn't really seem to fit the show.  

If she were the lady in the pew behind me at Sunday church I'd be amazed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 19:40:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the only thing that makes sense to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 19:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 18:45:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only thing I can guess is 1) people were offended at George RR Martin whipping it out in front of Butters and Scott Malcinson, and constantly taking to two other boys about penises 2). George RR Martin hearten to sue, or 3) crazy government conspiracy and the Fedb didn't want people seeing the biggest shopping day of the year portrayed in such a horrible light </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 18:40:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get most of these, I see why.  But Casa Bonita, why the hell would they remove that one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 18:15:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The part where you say the man beating another human about the had with a Knight stick was unarmed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 09:02:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is no Gemma, only Zuul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 09:01:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best line in the whole damn show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 06:55:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just not how to clean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 06:49:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seen this on I think 4 sub's now, 2 days till it hits face book.  I think more people will see the one dude's ass more than the Kardashian.  Think these guys may have really broken the internet.  And possibly one of my ribs from laughing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 03:47:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would be an awesome repost in /r/unexpected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 22:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a big fan of the basics.  18/10 stainless steel.  Get your pan hot (never rip on full high). Once your pan is hot, add a small amount of fat (clarified butter is best) wait it that to get hot, then sear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 18:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But can he make a decent cup of coffee? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 16:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its time to stop.... Now...  Mike? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 08:26:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She is the former wife of 2 founding members, but at the end of the day she is just an old lady, a very scary, (shudders) scary old lady </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 08:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it would be pretty gratifying seeing her alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 08:20:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, yes you are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 08:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Zoom in, there's a pasty.  You know, not that I looked or anything.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 08:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That never occurred to me.  Good observation, fits in with a lot of the theme of this episode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 08:15:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First time I thought it was since he (Venus) wasn't in make up and hair his masculine features shows and it freaked Tig out.  Getting through the episode and seeing their interaction changed that for me.

I think it was dealing with the guilt of Bobby and nerves over the show down at the AB compound.  Venus asks Tig if (s)he'll see him later and he replies, "yeah, maybe"

I think he was nervous about heading to a shoot out ambush where he knew he could have been killed.  Tig knows first hand (pardon the Bobby pun) Mark's guys aren't scrubs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 08:07:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In which case Jax goes to the Mayans club House and Alvarez is in a paper box fort, "You know ese, your authority is not recognized in Fort Kick Ass" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 07:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been thinking the same thing.  Juice wants back in, sons need an insider.  This is Juicey Boy's home now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 07:44:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was such a bad ass shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 07:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's pretty sad that you're being downvoted for being clever and using real quotes.  Someone quotes "Shenanigans" for the thousandth time in Reddit, and everyone loves it, but apparently there are dumbasses here who don't grasp the concept of repeater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 07:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4 peaks brewery for a pretty bad ass brunch on the weekends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It had plugins, toolbars and what not, but also a ton of viruses and malware </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably the only intense scene in the film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:32:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was going to say the Oakland Raider's fans buuuuuuut..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:27:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, but, the only reason he helps Gemma out and isn't involved with her on any deeper level is because it's unrequited on Gemma's end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 20:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would be 5 years since the show started given Abel's age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [SPOILER] The more I watch.. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 19:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The more in certain Ratboy is a fed plant.  Maybe not the rat, but FBI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 19:37:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't upvote this enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They were able to tell right away he was lying about the cutting.  The delivery at the end of the episode was very innocent. Jax knows Abel wants grandma to get in trouble, he'll put 2 and 2 together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We all thought it would be Juice who rats out Gemma... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 17:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 11:08:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same issue, right there with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 11:01:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was with you until "or there will ever be one" tonight was a good example of why not to expect anything or assume what will happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 10:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but the mirrored response was still pretty damn gratifying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 10:42:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck yeah it was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 09:09:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would be a good submission for /r/woahdude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 21:31:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If they are operating under a brewpub license they can sell, if not, if they are licensed as a self distributed or have a distributer such as favorite brands, BEK, or Andrews they are not allowed to sell for off premise consumption </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 20:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brewery or brewpub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 20:50:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was it purchased or free?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 19:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YES^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 19:05:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But for it comes with the refrigerator ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 16:32:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, if the are opening a straight production brewery, it is illegal to sell for off premise consumption.  Breweries cannot sell six packs or growler fills in the state of TX.  I just doesn't two years working at one.

And day they only let those who "donated" get growler fills, it'll be s customer service nightmare explaining to their regulars who didn't pitch in that they can't have growlers.  This just had bad idea written all over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 10:02:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any increase in your visibility? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 09:56:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recommended this to another redditors a few days ago and they like the idea.  Look up ChopperSwapper on Instagram,  give that a try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 23:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, as an  amateur with access to a cable television show, I'm certain I could do better in writing a 7 season series with developed characters and deep plots

EDIT: Wow either a lot of redditors didn't get the sarcasm or got it and didn't appreciate it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 23:11:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm trying to save up for a build project, its given me a lot of ideas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 05:55:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also a non reddit area: check out chopperswapper on Instagram. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 05:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The jizz of their enemies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 23:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not putting too much stock into this, and when I initially had the idea it was to just troll and insight a you in this sub.  Then I started thinking, and my idea became plausible.

What if Jax is the rat.  He's deep in hated for day the club has become and what is cost him.   No one had more knowledge of what goes on in the club and what will happen other than Jax.

Jax is so buried in the guilt of Tara's death, the death of members of his club, and the legacy of Clay's gun running he wants out.  He decides it'd be best for charming and his family to dissolve the club.  He goes out in a blaze of glory, stemming to kill the man who he think murdered his wife.  Mark's bring an Overijssel is just a convenient way to pay the club down so far it falls apart.  After the murder of Jury, no other charters will support SAMCRO.  Then once everything falls apart under Mark's wrath, the club dies forcing members into nomad or other charters.

We all know after season 3 Jax can play the long con.  Dissolving SAMCRO from the inside gives Jax a way to protect his family, his town, and keep other club members from violence or prison.

EDIT: Plus this would be one of the most unexpected things Kurt Sutter could do.  I don't think any one is expecting Jax to be an intentional down fall of the club.  Pulling this out of left field would take everyone for a ride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 17:14:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jax was the one who offered the patch over though.  The orient of the Grim Bastards was the one who was reluctant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 17:10:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I still am holding out that it's with Borosky or Ratboy though.  I do have a very unpopular third theory that I may or may not post on here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 12:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 12:37:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If Tig actually is the rat (I've both stores guessing AND caring) this is actually the only sound argument over heard on this sub in regards to the theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 01:57:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know... Most of the time people post pics of their family, and I support it cuz is family even though it might really not be, "old school cool". But that is actually a very cool photo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 21:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rat or not (it very well could be) I hope they're is a plant.  That's the one adversary SAMCRO have been up against yet.  Fed plants are something true MC's have dealt with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 20:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's been instances IRL of feds going under cover though and don't things far beyond wrong to keep their cover.  Donnie Brasco is probably one of the more known cases, but also Victoria Steele, is plausible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 19:20:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People on this sub have actually beaten to death the , "Tig is the rat" theory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New town, hiking questions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 21:28:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just moved here from Dallas.  I want to be healthier and more active.  I love being out doors and would like to go hiking in the hills out in the desert. 

Any good suggestions on where beginners should go.  I've been to superstition once while visiting a while ago. Where else is good for solo beginners?

I live in Mesa, so anything out this direction would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 11:18:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Simpsons did it... Wait no, I think that was done other show.... But which one...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 11:09:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love yo....  I mean, thanks for posting that gif.  We really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 11:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could be pissed for getting sold back to the Chinese by Clay days after getting out of prison (Season 1) That's when he must his fingers.  Could be playing the long con, gathering as much Intel as
Possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 11:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 11:03:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 09:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I appreciate it bitchwrangler.  It was a tough decision.  Basically have been saying I was going to do it for about a year, finally manned up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Goodnight Sweet Prince. Re-entering the kitchen works as a chef, has to make some changes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 08:40:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Someone once told me Balding is a condition, bald is a choice, What do y'all think of the change? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 08:35:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 15:19:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Queens, my bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 05:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Makes sense for Juice, when he was being pressed in season 4 you find out he's originally from Brooklyn.  The others I haven't noticed.  Jax on the other hand, I've heard Aussie, Brit, and Nor Cal , I think he's getting tired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 05:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are we don't this price is right style? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 02:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And let the face swapping begin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 20:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Marx forgave "Tig's debt" though when Jax turned over the fun business to him though.  Marx was no longer after The by the end of season 5.  Second to last episode of that season, but not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 16:01:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't mind being in her valley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 15:14:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tell it husband he's the first person I've ever seen to wear a sons costume and actually look like the person.  Cudos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 15:31:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with OP.  Its a possibility.  I've wrote off trying to predict what Sutter will do or assume he has rules of how a character will go out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 15:25:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In not sure I get the punch line?  Help me out, maybe put a finger on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 16:01:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Checks and balances </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 15:49:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm personally not taking too much stock in Sutter stating that 2 sons die.  It's possible, but seeing that Sutter likes to go the opposite direction in big episodes from what people think he'll do.....  I think saying that could have been a misdirection.   Plus, if it is true, Nero isn't a Son, neither is Gemma, the death toll could be far greater in the last 5 episode.  Plenty of time for folks to die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 06:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everything here mother was saying Jax took on as a direct reflection to himself.  The rent is punctuated by her saying something about a horrible father and a dead mother right before Jax puts a round through her head.  All foreshadowing Tara's death in a very sneaky way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 19:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thunder header 2 into 1 tailpipe is common amongst the bikes in Sons.  You see a lot of the sidekick seats as well.  Its a single piece 2 up seat.  HD diamond black grips.  Those are the big ones.  Chib's earlier bike had the fork tube boots, but I think with the fairing, the boots would clutter your front end too much.  

If you go with the thunder header (has a great sound) or any other full pipe you'll need to do a stage one air intake upgrade as well

Edit: also black lower front fork sliders and HD black magnum wheels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 19:09:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually very caught up, to the episode.  You didn't soil anything f for me.  Only takes 2 minutes to be considerate for other redditors though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 16:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank You!  I'm glad I'm not the only one who thinks it's Nero.  When he left the room when the sons saw what happen it looked a little suspect.  Then, when the focus was in him at the end and he says, "how could they not leave after what happen".  Clear foreshadowing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 16:22:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seen the episode already but still.  A spoiler alert tag, I'm sure, would have been much appreciated by some folks here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Season 6, EP: Sweet and Vaded </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 05:20:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go back and watch when Venus' mother rants at the kiddie porn studio.  Kurt Sutter drops some serious foreshadowing.  Bravo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 20:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Minception </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 06:55:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If have to go with the Piano Key Neck Tie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 06:22:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If your looking for which mods are on his bike I can let you know.  Used to work in custom accessories at a HD dealership in TX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 06:10:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No disrespect intended, but your mom is smoking hot.  If she were a dinosaur, she'd be a Babe-a-saurus Rex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 17:38:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some chick and dude meet on a boat, at the end ( SPOILER ALERT) a big rock gets dropped in the water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-26 07:34:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Added </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-26 06:59:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Serious case of MLA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-25 06:19:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haven't watched this episode yet but I'm saving it.  I miss tales from the dark side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 21:03:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blanch de Bruxelles, is Euro, but awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 19:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A kid called me an asshole, I told him I wasn't, he was convinced </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 15:10:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes....  Yes you are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-23 05:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't follow, what's the twist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-23 05:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Daaaaaaaamn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 18:57:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think he's permastuck in that expression </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 15:26:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Chump Chance" by Big Business </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-19 16:03:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My day just started and seeing this may be the coolest thing that happens all day, awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 17:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure at least 2 of those are photo shopped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 17:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Years ago I bought a legit bike jacket at a Wilson's leather outlet store,  Sturdy, warm, not a logo on it and 1/3 the price </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 13:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shiiiiiiiiiit, I got serious chills down my arm from that one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 16:53:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What year is that photo from?  Might be a good post for /r/oldschoolcool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 02:54:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who were the graduates and what year did they graduate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 02:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice, I was on my pop's Ultra, full size wind shield. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 23:40:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't imagine what it would look like without a wind screen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My beard once I got home from 100 mile is on my old man's Harley (x/post Harley) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My beard after returning home from 100 mile ride </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 21:15:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like you're not eating any....  Dry toast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 21:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its like ordering a sandwich on wheat, and your waiter brings it to you on rye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 01:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That you should of ate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 03:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *bobber* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Roommate paused Archer at just the right time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 05:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-28 05:53:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that escalated quickly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-28 05:21:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got a serious chill at the end, did not see that coming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take a motorcycle safety coarse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 09:44:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do what I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thank you face book for that one, live when this happens </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 09:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> VLC Media Player and Windows 8 support </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 03:45:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not tech savy, please be patient with me:
I downloaded VLC media player last week and every since I've had problems:

Netflix App wont work
I can't load videos on streaming sites like Coke and Popcorn or ProjectFree
I can't figure out how to get rid of the crap programs that come with VLC

How do I fix this?  I was also curious of people's opinions on the best spyware/malware and free virus protection as well.  Any help would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You can tell by the look on his face he's a pretty mean drunk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-21 18:54:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 01:41:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree totally with that.  Both probably made mistakes somewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 01:38:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rahr is bigger.  I believe they produce more barrelage per year than DEBC does.  I'm not totally sure, I havent checked the BA Forum letter recently.  But that is why I said "bigger than most"

I really doubt S S did what they are being accused of.  I know for a fact there are tap handles in that restaurant that local breweries didn't have to pay for.  That doesn't mean they didn't say what they are being accused of saying, but it doesn't help DEBC's case either.

As for serving Franconia over Deep Ellum, yeah, I don't get that either.  I want there, I dont know what happen.  Not serving there beer could be just an excuse for a deeper issue like you said.  One thing to keep in mind though, liking a certain brewery/style of beer/or individual brew is ALL subject to opinion.  There are some beers that most people in the Dallas scene love that I think are inferior.  There are also beers that I love other people think are shit.  Its all opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 01:20:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think they are a massive corporation.  But based on their distribution network, number of accounts, and total barrels sold, they are MUCH larger than most of the breweries in the area.  And by contrast, much larger than a single restaurant that's only been open or about 4 months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 01:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's trying to play up being the little guy, a small self distributed brewery.  It helps him look favorable as the victim.  He leads people to believe they're still a small operation, they don't have distribution, which they do, just not in this area.  There is absolutely nothing wrong with picking up a distributor in one area and not another.  But to tell people you don't have when to look like such a small operation when you actually do else where is misleading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 00:55:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the blog written about this John states that he's the little guy and the victim being bullied.  He stated that he is not distributed by Andrews or BEK which is only half true.  They are still self distributed in DFW, but distributed by BEK in the large southern cities in the state.  Is another good example if how he's misleading and petty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 15:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FOLLOW UP:  Replaced it with a new one last night from Autozone.  After taxes it was $250.  It took me about an hour and this was my first time making this repair on a vehicle.  The three places (one dealer and 2 national chains) I looked into to do the repair for me, each gave me estimates for $550-$600 for a one hour job.  Proof they're all out to gouge.  Moral of the story... I'm doing my own work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 15:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No sources, no references, and a weak looking site...?  Yeah, I'd believe it....  Why was this even posted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 15:19:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Going back through both Deep Ellum's post about this and Scotch and sausage's, and looking in the comments of the previous note our DEBC has had, is scary to see how much some of DEBC's fans have "drank the kool aide" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-10 00:08:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry. I meant to type the word "remember" not tendency.   Was trying to type at a red light and not paying attention.  Was meant to read, "do you remember the brand name?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-10 00:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> * remember* not tendency sorry. Was trying to type at a red light </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 23:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome.  Do you tendency the brand on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alternator Problems </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 23:32:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone have a good suggestion on a brand of alternator for an 06'?  My first one lasted 85k miles. In sitting in an NTB with a dead alternator that's 2 years old and Ford is showing me no love.

I'm looking for a suggestion in a quality product that will last more than 2 years.  Also, if there are any maintenance tips to make one last longer I'd appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sitting in a bar first Sunday of the season, with a bunch of friends who are fantasy football fanatics, and I'm not a football fan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-07 20:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 00:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They have similar style on Jpcycles.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL one of the heroes of my teenage years, Drew Carey spent quite a bit of time on the streets of Vegas, Homeless </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 17:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-27 20:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to sell for Harley and ride myself.  The biggest things are enjoying the ride, being comfortable, and controlling the bike.  HD has accessories and mods you can put on the Dyna series to help with all of those.  You can get things like "the reach seat" which is comfortable and moves you closer to your controls as well as curved handlebar riders that will bring your bars closer to you.  Get the bike you want and can afford then customize it to for you.  Do what you want man, is a Harley! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-27 04:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In guessing the frame is a 0 out 62 up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-27 04:01:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What you went through was incredibly unfortunate, but your Halloween must not go un wasted this year.  Take the new scar and run with it my friend.  Bond villains, classic horror monsters, the day will be your! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-27 00:54:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, your guests getting popped one in the face (in the not fun kind of way) usually isn't good for business </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Baseball playerJosh Hamilton relapsed in a Pub bathroom years ago. After years of support from his team and fans, he left the Texas Rangers, giving a big middle finger to his team and fans. This is now in the Sherlock's bathroom where he got drunk and banged a chick, who wasn't his wife. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 20:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 19:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah....  Its not doing well.  They get a lot of vagrants coming off the dart real running off customers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 19:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll never make someone for dealing with addiction. I see it a lot in my mine of work.  But I will make fun of someone for being a Dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Josh Hamilton Suite at Sherlock's Dallas (x/ Dallas) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 18:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 18:45:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, Park Lane and 75.  They put it up yesterday  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Welcome to the Josh Hamilton suite, Sherlock's Dallas </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 18:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 05:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy Hell. What's the size on that wheel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can any tell me the up/out/and rake on this frame? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 04:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Not a fan of taking selfies, but pretty proud of this one. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-11 05:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-09 02:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there a link to that specific clip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drop Request: Bob Sturm's birthday </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-09 01:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was wondering if anyone has a link to the drop WTDS for Sport Sturm's birthday.  It was a barrage of overlapping drops of Bob and other ticket members doing Bob impressions.  I think it ran for a little over a minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-08 19:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks great!  I like how you shaped a little lip on it with out going full bobtail.  Nice touch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 03:34:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I can say is wow.   The symbolism is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 08:28:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mesmerizing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 22:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Michael from Lakewood here.  The whole crew is pretty impressed and very proud of you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 21:02:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a buddy who rides an ultra and I busy his chops all the time just for fun.  He's 33.  Truth be told I'm jealous because he's riding and I'm not, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 00:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go for a straight forward traditional summer beer Czech/bohemian Pils are always a good choice.  Check for local ones NOT in green bottles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 23:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so glad this is in my life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 23:44:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. Topical humor and 16 years in the making.  There are people who are now turning 21 who can now go in there to drink who won't be old enough to get the reference. Still clever though, I must admit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-02 02:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a big fan of keeping it 200mm and under.  I actually prefer a 180mm.  I road the rocket custom when it first came out.  The stability in a straight run was phenomenal.  Turning was tough hard and sluggish.  It really depends what type of riding you want to do.  If you like a at straight haul go wide.  If you like a lot of twists and turns go narrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Allergy Specialist </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-20 15:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who here has an awesome allergy specialist they would recommend.  I took to google a found a few, but I'd like recommendations if possible.  It's getting to the point where I'm loosing A LOT of sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-28 02:54:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My vote's Frisco </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Girl gave me her number, actually texted her </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-25 03:28:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-24 03:06:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've tried it before, it fucking sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-19 23:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool,, have a membership, it's only 15 if you don't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-19 23:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 stop lights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Work out buddy. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-16 04:15:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just got a membership at Just fitness in Casa Linda.  Want a buddy, male or female, don't care, just want o have fun working out and someone I can push and who will push me.  I'm 29, male and training to loose some weight.  Cardio and weights and a little polymetrics/cross training would be ideal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-29 16:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sad thing is, I got more pivoted due to a type-o than I have posting anything else.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL That Steve McQueen was not only close friends with, and trained under, Bruce Lee, he was a pole bearer at his American Funeral </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-25 23:30:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-19 16:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Central Market on Lover's lane is the best place to go.  Or any of the whole foods.  Lakewood brewing has a couple bombers out right now and word is in the next couple of days they'll be releasing a bourbon aged version of their imperial milk stout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-18 21:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Put your cell phone in your pocket when getting into your car and don't rake it out till you're at your location, seriously. Don't use it while driving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-07 17:07:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well it's only 10am so........ session IPA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-07 07:15:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not Chinese, but I swear Ruang (sp?) Thai.  It's in the same parking lot as as the Albertsons at 15th and Custer.  Best Thai anywhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 23:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, no love for Santa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 23:00:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks btrlilwhtgrl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 18:15:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know right?  Where in the metropolis are you, the temp jumps are killing my body </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 17:31:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Marrying me?  You know, just sayin... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The brewery I work for throws a holiday bazaar. I dressed as Santa, the results were as expected. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 05:49:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dear redditors , when was the most you have ever felt conflicted with a life decision? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-02 22:04:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At what point in your life have you been the most lost and conflicted about making a personal decision.  How did you handle it and what were the outcomes.  If you had to go back, would you have done the same thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-17 23:15:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are seriously, CRAZY adorable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-13 16:19:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I've been into Neil Young for a while.  29 years old and have been into his stuff since early high school, very cool pic, thanks for sharing it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 22:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never knew he played on a V </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 21:59:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spot on and very beautiful, glad you got to live it up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 23:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha, I'm way too curious for that to be a deterrent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-08 23:48:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From Opie (SoA) to Dopey, sorry man, never shave again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 22:27:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah my whole plan is to treat it as a donor bike and throw as much as I can on a new rigid frame.  I did have a Honda shadow 750 ace.  Very reliable bike.  Only complaint is it was limited on customization and many parts on the baby that should have been metal were plastic or fiber glass.  Road like a champ though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 22:01:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the feedback, good knowledge for a HD TIL (no sarcasm intended)  I did find one auction site that sells everything from repo's to totalled out bikes.  Minimum bids start at about $200.  Don't have it saved on my phone but cam send a.link later if you're interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-30 00:53:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La piccolo buffalo in little Italy was Damn good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-30 00:52:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also went to high school with a Brandon, his wife is Caitlynn, there daughter is Braylynn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-30 00:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My girlfriend teaches third grade.  One of her students legal birth name's is La-a (pronounced Ladasha)  she's shown me the name while grading papers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-30 00:37:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-29 20:48:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe you're not allowed to do that awesome spin move to go from reverse to forward that Jason Statham does in every driving movie.  It is acceptable to do so in the afternoon though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-29 20:45:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very lovely, happy 21st </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-29 03:13:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the lead, but it looks like they only deal in metric.  I have friends into cb750 rebuilds, will forward them here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-28 22:42:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Pearl of the Stars" by Coheed and Cambria.  Not because of the content itself, but because of the emotional connection to that song and an ex.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-28 22:34:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hotel Palomar is nice too, being is awesome as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-28 22:30:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you wanted to use beer or wort product to get a starter going I recommend using whole, fresh, unacidulated and unused grain of your choice.  2 row is cheap, and spin it in a food processor untill it a fine flour, sift and start your starter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-28 22:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_Rock_Lake. We have our very own soppy wet prom date.  Its a great story, my aunts used to creep me out as a kid by telling me the story of The Lady of White Rock Lake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-28 21:44:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Last Call" is a great read.  Its everything you'd ever need or want to know about Prohibition in the United States.  It also has a lot of great knowledge of the long term and current effects from the fall out of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DFW Motorcycle grave yards </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-28 06:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone out there in internet land know of any motorcycle salvage yards in or near DFW, looking for a Harley build project </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-27 22:41:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, yes I do, very adorable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-25 22:24:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Johnny!  Kill one, fuck one, marry one.  Steve-O, Flo from the Progressive commercials, and the Bull from the rodeo see saw bit. GO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Woman Died from Doing Meth, Crawling into Her Freezer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-20 23:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Neograft knowledge </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-15 05:30:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone have any experience with receiving a neograft procedure.  Either the strip method or the FUE. method.  Almost 30 and looking quite a bit of hair up there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-12 07:20:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She is one of my favorite to fap to and have no info on her! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-12 03:01:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your question is invalid.  Everything I do naked is sexy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-08 06:07:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of shitty father (Or mother) lets his daughter dress like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-08 05:56:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Local honey, best with something mildly Spivey like a quality pepperoni  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-07 21:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-05 05:05:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hot Damn, looking good for any age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-26 02:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-25 22:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So he's homeless and caught up on new episodes of breaking bad, and shirtless but not tanned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-24 23:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, you're gold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-22 19:38:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Photoshop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-17 23:48:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kill One, Marry one Fuck one.  Joe Rogan, Seth Rogan, Seth MacFarlan, GO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-30 19:17:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slashed a tire on a girlfriends car right after we broke up when I found out she had cheated on me when we were together.  Got away with it, but didn't feel to good about myself afterwards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-16 20:12:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A beard as majestic as yours should never be ignored Sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-16 03:38:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who?  For the love of God who is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Unnecessary programs? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-12 21:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-11 16:23:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never canned it before, I either serve it immediately or cryo-vacced it and gave/sold it to friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-11 16:06:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2 celery stalk, 2 carrots and 1 LG red onion small dice lightly sauteed in 1/2C olive oil, when translucent add 2lg cans tomatoes puree and 1 small diced tomatoes.  Season with salt, black pepper and herbage to taste, simmer on low for as many hours as possible, puree and stain if you'd like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-08 20:55:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, it's just like dinner, whatever he doesn't want that's more for me ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-30 22:32:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You would do REALLY well in/ r/palegirls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-30 20:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the love of all things boobs, who is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-16 04:55:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wings with Dad while watching the homerun derby, not a bad way to celebrate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My one yeard anniversary </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-16 04:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-12 03:38:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, no welding experience, i didn't even think of that, i was more concerned with setting the petcoc and running a gas line </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-11 04:32:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never done a chop, used to work for HD at a dealership, in parts.  I have a pretty good starting knowledge but some things like gas tank set up and jetting carbs make me a little nervous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-09 23:19:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trying to plan ahead and budget, do this right even if it takes a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-01 22:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look close enough to Beiber's pants you'll get a new appreciation for the term dick face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-01 03:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know those story problems in jr. high math that are loaded down with A LOT of extra information that have nothing what so ever to do with the actual problem itself?  Yeah... that's the title for this joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Build Cost? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-01 02:42:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do ya'll think total cost would be, as many used parts as possible, to do a build like this, rigid frame, and perferably and 88"

http://www.americanclassicmotors.net/tonystblk1.JPG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-30 18:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go out to local brewery tours, they're usually fun and you get to have local stuff, which hopefully, is pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-30 18:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have a dough recipe, the one I have is a little spotty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-22 15:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing a can of spray paint couldn't fix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-18 00:37:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will you marry m....  I mean, that's a really good look for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-12 05:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who?  For the love of God, who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sony Alpha NEX repair </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 21:19:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My camera got dropped about 6 feet.  Everything works fine except the shutter button.  Any idea of how to repair it or anyone who will.  Sony wants $250 just to look at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-26 20:15:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just big big fans of our beer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-26 20:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We made sure not to serve before the ceremony,  afterward, well, different story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I work for one of the big Dallas breweries, we got to be a part of this tonight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-25 05:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I work at a brewery, this went down tonight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-25 01:47:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Transferring to a new computer? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-19 20:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My old compouter died in the worst of ways. I just got a new desktop, Windowsn 8 and downloaded the most recent version of Zune Market place.  I have a 32G Zune HD,  How do I get everything from my Zune to my desktop.  Apparently syncing it is enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-19 06:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God Bless Texas, where was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-13 06:57:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You ma'am, have the perfect pair! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-12 05:18:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best place I've found so far is Jerry's Woodfire Dogs in downtown Lakewood.  I actually have the Hot Doug's logo on my shin and spent plenty of time there, nothing here I've found has been that close </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Vehicle wrap Help </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-11 19:08:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have some scratches in the (what we hope) surface area of our skin wrap on our company's delivery truck.  Anyone have solid experience on how to buff out the scratches if it's possible?  Any solid links to information would be helpful too, google didn't do much for me on this search. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-28 18:37:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very Interested, I live near GWB and Custer, I work at The Lakewood Brewery at Jupiter and 635, very close by, I'm interested in what you guys may have to offer.  I know I won't be the first one, but I don't have an athletic bone in my body, would like to turn that around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-28 17:21:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> me gusta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crossfit Gym Shopping </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-28 17:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have any Dallas redditors shopped around different Crossfit gyms?  I was lookking for recommendations on price and quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-13 00:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pico de Gallo is pretty good, no seasoning other than salt and pepper, also If your more adventurous, small diced shrimp ceviche </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My 15yo Dalmatian Dixie Dog passed away this week, this is how the family remembers her </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 05:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 03:47:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's an awesome brewery too thanks.  See above comment for second half though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 03:47:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, still somewhat new to posting regularly, doing this on my phone so don't have a way to blur the name, (unless you know a way, then I'm open to info) but match isnt her last name, no worries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oh my god reddit, it might actually happen this time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 02:48:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 17:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Preferable standard american parts, not metric </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ground up step by step </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 17:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was wondering if anyone knows of any info out there, that breaks down a ground up build, step by step, with an explanation broken down as basically as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-30 19:23:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better than guitar center </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-30 19:22:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hope these aren't the same guys I'm thinking of.  Last Beer Week 3 guys claiming they were starting a cidery came into the bar I was working at (Jack Mac's) for the cask taping.  We caught them trying to steal beer off of the firkin.  Then they got so wasted 2 passed out at their table, then we caught them trying to walk their tab.  Hope its not the same guys, karma is a bad hangover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-25 08:28:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually have been loosing weight, see comments below.  I have a very physical job at a brewery, hauling kegs.  I've cut back on my drinking and have been making smarter food choices.  Next paycheck I'll be able to afford a membership to a gym already picked one out.  I also throw shot put during the spring (If we get one in TX this year) and will be loosing A LOT of weight during the summer at work whether I try or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-25 01:50:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah, I think that'll be the first step, I'm gonna start with the longest guard and work my way down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-25 01:44:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah...  he's actually a pretty slim guy, but I noticed that too when I first met him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-25 01:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah, i'm working on that, been steadily dropping actually, about 15lbs in 3 months was at about 270, I work at a brewery in TX so I know I'll be loosing a lot more this summer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-25 01:41:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have to respectfully look at the photo again, my hair is going pretty quickly now, it started when I was 21 and has been going exponentially recently, despite healthier decisions, you might want to look again.  But thanks for the encouragement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-25 01:39:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I'm gonna do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My friend Veronica is an awesome photographer, here's her husband's portraits </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 19:40:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My friend's wife shot his portrait, what do y'all think? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 18:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Be honest reddit, I'm 29, is it time to start shaving the heah? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 17:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hey reddit, what's your greatest small joy in life that brings you comfort? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-20 13:55:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me it has to be a full tank of gas and a new set of tires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-16 16:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last I heard snoop canceled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-16 16:02:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed, I can't speak for the turkey, haven't  had it, but Mr G's is awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:29:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should have been 21 plays of Tom Jone's What's New Pussycat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-21 03:45:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chris was actually a good friend of mine growing up but we kind of went separate ways around highschool, grew up in the same block, played baseball and did the whole "scouts" thing together.  He was an awesome guy and was always there for a laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-02 13:58:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How tall are you, I arrested losing my hair around 20 (28) but I'm just shy of 6'2" so most people don't notice, so I particularly am holding out a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First attempt at pretzel rolls, not too shabby </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-22 06:08:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-19 22:35:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do not reccomend using honey instead of sugar because it won't cook to the crystalyn state. Sugar will.  Try a very small (one jar) batch to see how it works.l, I may be wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-19 15:25:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make a tighter pesto, less oil, more basil and nuts, and spread it as a sauce a little thinker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-18 00:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He is a duck, he's a shady SOB, most of his payroll practices are illegal as well as his back of the house staff, I managed under him and his ex wife at the Allen location and it was a nightmare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-16 05:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My old boss finally made it big! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Neighbors seek boycott of Frisco restaurant owner </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-16 05:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-16 04:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grapefruit and/or orange marmalade with candied ginger.  You can also make and store an orange cure mix if you cure your own salmon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> one week shy of a 1/2 yeard </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-11 02:58:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-28 06:23:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out Lakewood Brewing instead.  It's the same price, you get to keep a Belgium style glass, and the lines are A LOT shorter.  They have the same music and food trucks, but it's a lot less pretentious and crowded.  Plus their beer is a lot better, if you're a beer knurd, also more consistent and true to form.  Big Fan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-28 06:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed!  Don't smoke the dips, smoke (some cold some hot, depends on the ingredient) the ingredients.  I also recommend pairing smoked queso with a good vienna style lager </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-25 15:24:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very fun x-mas album, big fan now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-21 03:26:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who is this???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-21 03:07:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe my immediate words, out loud, were, "Holy Shit" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-01 15:43:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome, thanks for the reference, best one so far,  once the paycheck comes in it's ordered.  And yeah, I'm looking for some help in my area, I've posted on craigslist and other subs to find a work out buddy, all my frends are industry people and I"m kind of on a 8-6 schedule </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-25 21:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lifting starter </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-25 20:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to start lifting, but not very familiar with proper form and safety.  Does anyone have tips, guidelines, or any good (preferably free) resources online.  I have a very physical job in a brewery and figured I might as well bulk up to make work easier as well as other things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> work out buddy needed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-18 21:14:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I really want to bulk up and get big.  Would like someone I can rely on as a spotter who has some experience power lifting.  I'm starting out at level 1 so I need someone who's patient.  I want a motiator and not a douchey gym rat.  I work at a brewery and have 3 very clear goal.

1)  Make my life lifting and moving kegs a lot easier

2)  Throw a shot put A LOT further.

3)  Make my cheating ex girlfriend sorry she left me for a stoner who works the register at a fast food joint.

I have a 24 hour fitness membership and will be working out probably after or around 8pm.  I'm motivated and committed but not knowledgeable in lifting, safety, form, all that good stuff.  If you're looking for a work out buddy, hit me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-18 21:05:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> price? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-28 08:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recommend skinning it.  Best to use a very sharp knife, about 6-8 inches long, take your time, go slow, you should be ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-15 05:25:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> best place for the top line for your beard is where the top of your ear actually meets your head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-15 05:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go For the Gibson! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-15 05:18:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> trim it short with an electric trimmer.  Keep staight, clean lines with a good straight edge razor, some even have a single blad on the reverse side for precise lines, that will give you a good groomed 5 o'clock look </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-15 05:13:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had good experiences with Wahl Hair trimmers.  I've bought cheap trimmers before and it seems like they pull hair more than clip it, in my experience, you get what you pay for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-15 05:09:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6 days a weeks I just wash it in the shower with soap with the rest of my face.  Saturday mornings I have a ritual of shampooing and conditioning with American Crew, it leaves it very soft,  I have a more curly facial hair type. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-15 05:07:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Submitting a pic of your face or chin would help, I myself and 2 1/2 months in on a full beard no trimming, feels very liberating, highly recommend it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Shampoo advice </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-15 05:03:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So unfortunately I've been using Garnier frucetice since I was a teen because that was always what was in the house.  I've found out recently  a combination of that, and my poor diet may have possibly lead to my hair loss and may be reversable to an extent?  Anyone have info on this, or even better, a good shampoo that will promote hair regrowth???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-15 04:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> can Vitamin B and Iron help grow back lost hair??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-12 04:06:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Soooooo......... should I upvote this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-09 17:57:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a clarinet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-09 17:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah, the entire joke is Dwight says "tweeter" ugh sigh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-08 07:17:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just curious, who's your favorite Batman villain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> About 2 months in </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-30 21:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-30 17:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Favorite one so far, face yould have been awesome, you have a pretty smile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> my buddy told me I should repost here, what do you think trees?  Coco chrispy treats with peanutbutter chips, nutella and pretzels </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-29 05:20:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-29 01:58:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The other gentlemen had fine beards indeed.  But you sir, got robbed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Coco Chrispy treats with extra marshmallow, pretzels, peanut butter chips topped off with Nutela </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-28 16:59:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-19 09:01:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well maybe, that's just like, your opinion...  man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-14 16:38:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> very pretty smile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-09 06:13:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> agreed.  it's also a major plus smelling the peppermint and menthol extracts early in the morning.  Better than a cup of coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-08 04:32:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the tip on "training" the hairs.  I started wax just so I could get away without trimming the lower ones.  I eventually want to compete on the local market for beards and stache.  If you come up with a recipe you like please send it my way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-08 04:30:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> please excuse my typo's, feelin lazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-08 04:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll have to give it a try.  I have some of their pommade and have had it for years, never had a reason to use it.  I use the american crew shampoo and conditionern on my beard once a week or before dates and my beard comes out sooooo soft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-08 04:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll check them out, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-08 04:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I was wondering about the American Crew pommade I've had some sitting around forever and don't have a reason to use it.  i do use their shampoo and conditioner for my beard and it comes out very, very soft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> grooming Q's? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-07 05:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm growing a pretty lengthy beard, with hopes in the future to compete.  My mustache is to the point to where I have to do something with it styling wise.  Are there any recommendations or waxing or styling products.  Went to CVS and picked up some Clubman's, didn't know if there were any othe rproducts worth looking at.

Also any good recommendations on good soaps or champoo's for the stache or beard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-04 19:22:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Barcadia on Henderson has giant jenga (jenga with giant pieces so the tower's 4 feet tall)  good place to drink and meet people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-04 19:21:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best new place: Jack Mac's Swill   Grill
Best nice but fine dinning place: Victor Tangos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-28 23:25:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> appreciate the help, I'll check it out when it's not so hot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-28 23:25:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks, I'll check soon, when it's not 103 outside </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Stereo help? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 16:37:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a 6 cylinder 2006 mustang.  The alternator went out (already fixed) but we tried jumping the battery before we knew it was the alternator.  When jumping my car, my girlfriends neighbor, being the jackass he is, put the jumper cables on his battery backwards.  We were lucky in that the only thing that died was the stereo.  Anyone know what it might be, I receive no power.  If it s a fuse, which one is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-21 00:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> really?  What kind of asshole is that kind of jerk to someone who's bummed out after they just put their dog down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-21 00:13:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dude, i'm just bummed out, don't be a dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 07:37:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dallas is not a hippie friendly city by any means </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-17 01:18:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I Love Bunk, wait... that sounds bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-16 23:22:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are freakin adorable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-16 23:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't know anyone, but I bet there's a lot of good tutorials for free (the best price) on youtube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-16 23:11:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and Dino's is pretty solid, best sandwich in the metroplex in my opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-16 23:10:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah, I'm not on that side of the Metorplex any more, but I love chilling out there when I can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-16 23:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's just a really cool unique bar, hadn't been in a while.  I used to work there when I turned 21.  Last time I hung out there it was pretty much a hipster joint.  Good drinks, pretty good beer list, and a great jukebox.  The patio outside is great too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-16 03:10:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're a hipster (or not but like to people watch and point and laugh at hipsters, i won't judge either way) check out the caves lounge.  Awesome lunch spot is Dino's subs, you can also go ice skating at the parks mall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-10 20:04:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Giant Jenga at Barcadia (knox henderson area) or at Goodfella's Pizza (Plano boardering frisco on Preston) is always fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-10 20:00:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The French Room, The Marquee Grill (used to be on the pastry team, it's awesome) Fearing's at The Ritz, Bolla at the Stoneleigh Hotel, Abacus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-05 23:36:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's a good place to order online: http://www.viennabeef.com/  I know how it feels.  I used to live in the East Village.  Have the Hot Doug's tattoo on my shin and everything.  I have not found a place yet though, but Angry Dog in Deep Ellum is supposed to be really good too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Soda Questions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-04 20:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I finally dipped my toe in the soda pool.  I made a mediocre ginger ale but an awesome Basil Mint Soda.  I used active dry yeast and it worked very well.  It did make the soda's muddy with yeast biproduct though.  Anyone know how to make a clear soda or possibly the same thign with much lest yeast biproduct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-04 18:30:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you REALLY want to...  Cold smoke it, plenty of info out there as to how to cold smoke if you haven't yet, let it rest at room temp for half an hour, season it and sear it or do what you will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-02 18:31:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anything off of Fishbone's "If you give  monkey a brain, he'll swear he's the center of the universe" album, Primarily 'Servitude' it's a pretty good song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-28 17:35:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can do macaroons, or, you also have the key ingredient for the best park of any meringue pie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-28 17:26:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It most certainly does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-28 17:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe not, but close, his last special that he produced on his website that he was selling downloads for sold $4.5 million, he produced himself.  I know much of that cash goes elsewhere, but without a production co. he's on the right path </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-28 07:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Louis CK: Millionare at the top of his career, the new "most influential" comedian
Joe Rogan: Reinvented himself, excelling in a new career field.

Carlos Mencia:  Hosting late night infomercials selling gym equiment and workout programs.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-26 14:23:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know he pulls content off of reddit, youtube, break, ebaums and a ton other sites, that's the whole concept of the show.  It's a show that makes fun of what is on the internet.  Just sayin it's a repost of something that's aired on national television </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-26 14:01:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uhhhh... Tosh.0 two seasons ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 19:59:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just as effective, works as well, we just got it to evaporation point and lit it to burn it off quicker for efficiency sake.  Not as safe, but in a controlled environment with professionals, much quicker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 18:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried several times in culinary school to make hollandaise, but I'd always crack under the pressure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 18:16:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seared or grilled salmon in a tomato water broth and roasted asparagus.  If your interested send me a message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 18:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you cook the whole thing, top to bottom?  If you did you should tail me the recipe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 18:03:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drugs are a bad, bad thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 18:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Combine it with enough tomato puree to make a chunky sauce, season accordingly and put over penne pasta.  It's a great "poor man's" meal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 17:58:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, it's all flare for the table side.  The only time I've seen an actualy function for it, is if you're making a sauce with a and you want the primary flavor to be a liquor (say a tequila based sauce) and you don't want the alcohol to dominate the tongue you burn it off. but ahead of time in the kitchen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-18 18:26:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only have a pump action shotgun.  It's an ok range for that, great if your shooting skeet.  Everyone I met there was nice for the most part, I wouldn't shoot range ammunition though, they carry the cheap stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-18 18:24:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check the big hotels, corporate hotels usually offer benefits to restaurant workers IF the restaurant is owned y the hotel, not just space leased out to the hotel.  I used to cook for Omni, it was a pretty good operation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-18 18:19:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this person may be able to help you, tell her you heard of her through me (Michael Burke) I'm friends with her dad.  https://www.facebook.com/BethABowers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-14 04:39:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> broken down step b step, like I'm 9, awesome! just what I was looking for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kegging? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-14 03:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friend and I have been homebrewing for a little while now.  We've been bottling and have found it to be a hassle.  We want to switch over to kegging but have no idea where to start.  Resources anyone???

Mucho Appreciado </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-30 08:01:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wise girl sounds like a hooker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-25 00:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I highly recommend Kayden DiGiovanni at the Skin Art Gallery in Addison.  Check him out at DallasTattoo.net  I have quite  bit of work done, the only 2 I wasn't satisfied with are the ones he did NOT do, and he still even helped me out with them (I've been going to him for 9 years)  Also chek him out at facebook.com/dallastattoo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-22 03:10:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But in London, they don't have Smokey the Bear, they have SMACKEY THE FROG! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-21 04:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow, really awesome, despite what ever kitchen you were in.  Are you in business or just do this for friends and family on the side? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-08 17:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was an awesome show! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 04:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very nice, never been out to that part of the country, can anyone visit the sound and go clam digging </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> SHU? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 08:50:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do any redditors out there have knowledge as how to practically calculate something on the scoville heat scale?  I'm working on a hot sauce and would like to know the actual SKU for bottling and marketing purposes.  Any information would help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 08:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ot me beat.  3lbs most I've done.  I was cooing in a restaurant going out of business and the last day we were open my Chef "cleaned out the walk in"  it was a race between myself and the food runner on a 3lb plate.  The volume was rough, but forcing it down fast was far worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-30 18:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know who you are.  I don't know who your friends are.  But that, that is amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-29 07:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nice, my buddies and I have worked with ghost peppers before.  We had a dick coworker who caused problems (we were all chefs in training) so we steeped ghost peppers in water and used that to make a dense gelatin and put his knives in it them set it in the cooler over night.  Highly recommend trying it some time.

But thanks, I'll have to check it out, I work right around the corner from there.  How many wings does one have to polish off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-28 20:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nice, that's the kind of stuff I'm looking for, what else do you guys have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-28 20:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks for the suggestion, but looking for local places, I could do BWW challenge anywhere, but thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Food Challenge? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-28 19:16:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any one out there in Dallas know of any good restaurants that have some sort of eating challenge.  I'm aware of the wing challenge at Pluckers.  Used to work there so I'm very aware.  Any others?  Would anyone be game to join up and start a group for it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-28 18:25:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Pearl Cup in the M Streets area is the best coffee I've had in Dallas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-28 18:22:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet, never thought I'd see this place on the net, especially reddit.  I live half a block from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-28 18:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah we do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-28 18:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Private message me, I'm interested and local </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-28 18:15:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bonnie Ruth's up in Allen has an awesome brunch buffet with every classic you can think of.  Dessert is was included too which we thought was really cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-21 09:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's amazing, how much time did it take you to piece it all together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-21 08:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tis is my first 4/20 on reddit....  I guess this pretty much sums it up...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-18 20:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> funny, they don't look asian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-15 09:57:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's sooooooo cool you're a Batman fan, not a lot of chicks are superhero fans let alone Batman fans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-13 01:24:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chubby is awesome, keep posting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-13 01:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good God, why can't I find any Ranger's fans like you in my neighborhood.  I"m on the wrong side of the metroplex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-11 06:07:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bet t was a "B" channel on the cable box </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-09 18:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "allow it" to happen for a while, put up remote surveillance camera's in your house that you can view from the web or your smart phone.  Use this to file for divorce, leaving her penniless.  Once he paper work is ready, hang onto it.  Wait for her to have her ex over one day.  While their sleeping in your bed together, sneak into your own house with another woman.  MAKE SURE SHE IS HOTTER THAN YOU PHILANDERING WIFE.  She could be an ex, some girl at the bar, a co-worker, a hooker, it doesn't matter.  Drop the paper work on the coffee table while being un-heard, then start going at it as rough and as loud as possible.

Really make it loud.  When your wife comes out with her ex, don't stop, just smile.  With one hand give a thumbs up, the other hold up divorce papers.

She'll get the point.  After a while there's not much that'll fill the void from being hurt by your ex, but bourbon will help.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-26 23:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have no words sir.  Touche </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-26 16:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any which way you cut it, you're still sucking a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-06 20:09:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go for a small dice and when you sautee your mire poix go for a darker carmelization (careful not to burn)  You should get a sweeter taste.  I like to use this in my marinare and pizza sauce.  2 carrots, 2 stalks of celery and 1 onion, 2 garlic cloves 1/2 cup olive oil, 2 16 oz cans of tomato puree and 1 small can of dice tomatoes.  Simmer the mire poix and garlic, add tomatoes and cook out for 2 hours, season.  For marinara leave be, for pizza sauce blend.  Pretty tasty, and if you blend she'll never know it's there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-04 23:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1-2-3, and 1-2-3, 1-2-3, really, you guys don't get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-04 06:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> prrreeeeeeetty sure (100%) I've seen her on craigs list singles page in my city </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-04 06:14:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sad thing is, I actually get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-14 03:38:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Join?....  I'd be president, secretary, and treasurer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-09 06:42:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I so very much enjoy your daily posts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-09 06:14:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My suggestion; post it on facebook and see if it gets taken down, your question will be answered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-06 04:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> got it, couldn't tell, big fun, love your confidence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-05 00:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> very excellent, what's the pattern on the socks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-02 17:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> very nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>