<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9036</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Protesters in Berkeley get naked to try to save trees </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:43:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 04:15:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.dailycal.org/2015/04/28/college-chemistry-buildings-experience-power-outage/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 20:20:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Salesforce Inc. is a global cloud computing company headquartered in San Francisco, California. 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Salesforce.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> From Daily Cal: Marc Benioff, Salesforce CEO, to deliver UC Berkeley's spring commencement address </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:36:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 22:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's no professor named Jacques Larue at Cal, this is fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 07:54:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Daily Cal wrote about it: http://www.dailycal.org/2014/12/10/protestors-break-peter-thiel-speaker-event-wheeler-hall/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Protesters disrupt Peter Thiel speaker event at UC Berkeley </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 07:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Live updates from the second day of ongoing protests in Berkeley </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 03:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Police fire tear gas at hundreds of protesters and students in Berkeley during Eric Garner protest </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 19:12:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 200 students occupy campus building at UC Berkeley over 28% tuition increase </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 23:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Letter alleges fraternity member drugged, sexually assaulted woman at Halloween party </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 02:27:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Watch the 2014 Berkeley election results live! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 06:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dirks "looks forward to welcoming" Bill Maher despite student opposition </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 22:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-17 01:04:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep in mind web archive removes some formatting and only really preserves images and text.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-06 06:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? You couldn't fuckin stick it out for two more days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> See the Holiday Assembly streamed LIVE! This Friday 12/21/12 @ 11:00am-12:30am  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-20 06:18:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-06 23:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fight Club. A twist doesn't make a movie good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-03 06:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's from UC Berkeley's SQUELCH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-10-20 05:32:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Leopard by Giuseppe di Lampedusa - fantastic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-10-02 01:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Campbell Hall doesn't exist at the moment, so in fact your method is quite difficult.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-28 23:44:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd guess it's about 50/50. I got in from number 23 I think last year but I don't know how many more people got in. I can't imagine a ton. Great class though. If you don't get in this semester, definitely try again next fall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some of the worst classes you took at Cal? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-02 22:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm wondering about electives mostly but also prereqs (although obviously there are a ton of shitty prereqs).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-07 04:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't you mean platypus bear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-18 05:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I was thinking Abe Lincoln </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-14 04:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you at Felix neck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-13 20:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a pretty cool Heat map </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-11 23:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One big answer?  Pages and pages of codes, regulations and laws, all using the English system.  They are unlikely to be changed because converting these values into metric is messy.  "This building code requires 2.74 meter high ceilings, and the stairs must each be 16 cm tall." or "Companies are allowed to dump, 30,564 liters of sewage into the neighboring stream."  There is a massive amount of regulation that needs to be taken into account.

Also there are dangers involved with changing the units people are familiar with. Imagine the height limit signs on bridges that prevent trucks who are too large from hitting the bridge. Mistakes would constantly be made during the transition period. It's just not worth it. 

The truth is, the metric system has replaced everything that matters. We use milligrams for our medication and most scientific research uses metric. NASA sure does. How we measure our drinks and weights really don't matter in the scheme of things, so we don't use metric. Metric's advantage is not important enough to replace the small stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> BCA #21 on America's Best High Schools 2012 (would have been much higher but for small AP offerings) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-21 07:55:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-20 06:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I completely disagree. Not to disregard your post, the creators have gone through much effort to maintain the physics of the world with the exception of bending which remains unexplained. (see: Function and mechanics of hot air balloons, submarines, gravity, properties of ice INCLUDING crystallization now in LoK) which mimics ours.  Air bisons are explained by bending (which remains unexplained but is not related to physics) and hence physics and the properties of every material up until this point are exactly the same as in our world. 

I would like to hear the countless examples which you speak have been different from our physics. So far you only mentioned platinum (which I think is laziness on the part of the new writing team) and air bison flight, which can be explained by airbending which we know is unexplained (or rather spiritually explained). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-20 05:20:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not knowing engineering is no excuse for laziness in preproduction. someone on the writing staff knew something about basic high school chemistry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 00:00:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reavers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 08:16:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so would I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-18 02:31:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> most of us arent even at BCA anymore. 

so go recruit!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-12-21 02:58:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get the book looked at and appraised before you have any work done on it. Often work done on an antique will lower its value.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Berkeley Alum wins Nobel Prize in Economics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-10 20:47:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-09-08 18:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> please for the love of god, learn to spell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>