<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3843</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Vulnerability in Microsoft Font Driver Could Allow Remote Code Execution (3079904) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Throw a flashbang, and look at the other team.  The players with white reflections on their faces are guarding whatever site.  I think it happened with c9 in the esl a few weeks back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:57:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Discrepancies between server and client.  They changed the way it worked to cut down on aimbots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 08:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You quoted half the sentence.  The explanation was in the half you left out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 05:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dota merch comes with codes for cases (whatever dota calls cases) that pay for themselves (roughly) on the steam market place.  CSGO merch costs an arm and a leg, and has no codes (apparently). 
  
Not that the in-game items matter all that much to me, its just crazy how differently valve treats their 2 most popular franchises.  CSGO has been paying the bills as of late, and we get expensive shirts back.

That being said.... in for one coffee mug.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Next time ask Pharrell if you can wear his hat and take a picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 03:05:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously, people are a little nuts.  Sure there are technical issues, but experience will fix that.  Sure the betting lines arent great, but who cares.  the teams and players need tournaments to survive, and the only way esports will grow is by spreading as much as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the group stages should have either been online, or more spread out over a couple days.  It was a ton of matches all overlapping.  If they spread it out they could have focused more on individual matches, afforded reasonable computers, and brought the quality way up.  12 odd hours of bo1's is ridiculous.  Now on day 2 its like they can return 75% of the rented computers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:00:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure if they could/if there was an easy way they would.  Sure they could take skins out of the game, or make every item account bound.  But that would be really bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 05:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus the speculation on him throwing a51 games for profit.  They had a couple really fishy losses right when csgolounge became a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 05:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember that case opening when him and his brother opened a knife, he/they were so damned happy.  Now he just burns knives 10 at a time.  Hopefully twitch stays viable for him.  Hopefully he plays cs one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:52:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yah Its pretty bad.  Id like to think it was the 50% off summer sale mixed with the last esl lan.  Smurfs tend to buy alts during sales and an influx of new players that tend to not care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 07:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last night my team was up something stupid like 13-2 going into ct side mirage.  Our bottom fragger was well above their top.  The rest of the game we bought mollys and mollied up our entire spawn, then we'd all start yelling stuff like "Rush through mollies , Push push push, gotta guard sites!"  We lost a few rounds because of it, but definitely worth it for a good laugh.  We also had one dude shoutcasting but telling us wrong spots for everyone, kept us on our toes when we all rush market while the terrorists are pushing out apps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 11:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd try to watch a couple pro games, just so you have some amount of map awareness.  Also play some casual, and a lot of deathmatch to work on learning maps and aim.  Don't stress if you die a lot in casual,  in comp mm they sort you by similar skill level and in casual I don't think they do.  Lots of hackers also hang out in casual.

  The thing that helped me the most was learning how to set my mouse dpi and sensitivity correctly, then learning how to move efficiently with a much lower dpi.  There plenty of youtube videos on that.

  If your team makes calls in a mm game don't be afraid to ask them if you don't know a nickname (Cat, Tetris, Jungle, etc etc).  You might get flamed a bit, but its just internet people.  You will learn and possibly never see them again.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would be a great location.  Right between Philly and Canada.  Or maybe I just want it to be close by.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 04:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and all this time I thought you were JW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 04:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha oh god, yea i meant sem. Long day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:10:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea same here.  I got 4 wins in a row as a LEM and then put on a team with a 4 queue.  All their names were "Sorry Im new".  They ran to mid every round and dropped weapons.  Then they kicked me.
Then I go on CEVO and people flame me for not putting in the time getting better on mm.  Sorry I cant get better playing people of the same skill level, certainly not good enough to carry a team of goof balls.

Edit: SEM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:02:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea, I see it being somewhat similar to making a call out loud and doing something completely different. If given an opportunity then why not.  If the organizers don't like it then they should be responsible for fixing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:56:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Intel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 11:46:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I played 120odd hours, I had fun most of them.  I did vog the week it was released.  At the end nothing dropped for anyone. Thought it was broken.  Went to find loot tables for raid rewards.  "Oh I guess there are none".  Haven't turned the game on since.

I was a wow raider, thought Destiny would scratch that itch.  Like an mmo-lite.  I don't care if I don't get a reward for doing the hardest content in the game.  In an mmo raids have loot tables, you certainly dont get something every time.  But someone in your party will.  An item worth coming back for every week to get.  An item that doesn't have the same low chance to drop off any mob in the whole game.

 Without raid specific gear whats the point of getting to end game.  Without pvp specific gear what's the point of pvping.

Sorry for my rant, incredibly off topic.  What im getting at is I got my moneys worth, I liked the game.  But dont see any point in going back.  Plus I dont own the dlc's.  $70 for the dlc+tk is too much overhead for me to come back. Shit I payed 60 for the game.  Essentially this is a really long "I agree". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:58:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One 980 should be fine if you're running 1440p.  2 980s would be better than 1 ti for 4k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get a 980 and an ssd, unless you are getting a crazy panel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:17:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's more a human reassurance type thing, even if they do read the rules.  Remember how scary your first build was.  If I had the internet during my first build I'm sure I would have been the same way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow I feel old, almost said they were fake.  Never knew they released highs. Been out if the game for too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 03:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 200+ fps doesn't matter on a 144hz screen.  Just play a few dms and you'll be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 06:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought the nacho cheese fountain was a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 04:05:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean I have that headset and fine talking game.  No-one ever complained it.  I definitely would use a headset mic for twitch broadcasting though.

Have tried updating your audio drivers?  Or go into Windows sound settings and raise the levels.  Just be careful, if you raise them too high it will get super pitchey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 01:56:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are trying do with the mic?  Are you just playing games and communicating, skype calling , or are you twitch streaming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 11:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah the last panel was that sketchy shenmue 3 kickstarter video that literally no one must have watched. Who would pay money for a 5 second clip where they re-used audio assets and had the worst voice actors of all time.  "Promise of a game coming out one day..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You also have to buy the $120.00 definitive edition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool thanks a lot, make sure you post future projects! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:38:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came out great!

What kind of machine do you use? I've been thinking about grabbing a cheap/mid priced machine but I'd like to dabble in denim.  Dont feel like ruining a cheap machine or wasting money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:58:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bet it all on a longshot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:01:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bungie and blizzard are both owned by activision.  Im shocked that activision didnt pay a couple blizz people to go over as contract workers.  Not that blizz has done everything right.  Bu at least they have experience with mmo content  additions and expansions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 19:21:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They have over 20 years experience developing pc games.  Their games also take over 5 years to develop.  Smart phones are still relatively new, They change dramatically even year to year.

 "Fuck android" isnt a good keynote for a press conference.  They arent a small indie studio, they can't be open about stuff.  They have a board of directors, and marketing people carefully selecting What any dev can say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 11:37:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's more the closed system thing.  On ios they are developing for 4 phones and x amount of ipads.  They know the exact details on every piece of hardware the game is running on.  It is much easier to optimize for less systems.

If a huge publisher like Bethesda puts out an android game and it hypothetically doesnt run on htc phones for some reason then they would get bad press and have their validity as a games developer questioned.  

Im pretty sure they just want to release a game that works  Hopefully it comes sooner rather than later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:02:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Afro samurai for the 360.  The worst ive played that I can recall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 05:36:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. It seems crazy, I'm not gonna be the one guy that doesn't vote to kick the afk guy, or the music mic guy, or the guy that throws the bomb out of the map.

 Pretty dont solo queue anymore. Guess it is what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 04:11:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I voted to kick one person each in 3 comp mm in a row.  Got a 3 hour.  Got back next game voted to kick and got a 24 hour. I didnt initiate any of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 23:02:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 09:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For a bit more you could get something high quality, like a ducky or a das keyboard.  For a bit less you could get something of equal quality. Like a corsair or a Razer non-rainbow.

You are paying premium for a keyboard with a Razer logo that has pretty lights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fallout shelter for android, more information to come. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 06:08:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 23:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's on sale for $60... That seems like regular price.  I don't need fake currency.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 06:09:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love my bitfenix case, they might be a little over budget.  They are worth it though.  Sick of mid towers that look to be designed by teenagers with crayons.

http://www.bitfenix.com/global/en/products/chassis/prodigy

http://www.bitfenix.com/global/en/products/chassis/phenom-micro-atx

http://www.bitfenix.com/global/en/products/chassis/pandora


Lian-li are also a solid choice.  I'm just not as familiar with their lineup.

Edit: absolutely check out the Pandora link.  Tiger direct for under 100 in brushed aluminum.  I'm considering a new case now haha
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 09:59:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The rank you are looking at is a temporary thing for the latest event.  You get an actual rank at 10 comp wins.

I consider myself new to the game.  I have ~300 hours played, and 60 odd comp wins.  You need to realize this is a game people have been playing in some form for 15 years or so, even the low rank people are going to be much better than you when you first start.  

Yes people hack and smurf, but generally people who play cs are good at cs.  Plus if people have a high degree of map awareness they are going to beat you even if you are possibly better at fps games than they are.

Stick with it though, it's a great game.  There's nowhere to go but up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:23:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The giveaways and sale are both great. A new free character vs free stash tab, happy either way.  A new pet and team up are great, I think those are coming?  But no event does kind of stink.  I'd even be happy if they just left mid-town madness running. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 07:42:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gonna be cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 20:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really solid build,  I'm not sure how processing heavy ableton is, but you could probably save a few if you got an i5 and 16gb of memory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 00:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally I'd wait.  The oculus doesn't come out until 2016, and the steam vr is unproven as of yet.  By the time they hit the market newer hardware will be out, and a vr ready pc will be cheaper to build </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 18:04:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It will work, it will be better than what you have.  The motherboard will be a bottleneck though.  That's a pcie 3.0 card, and you only have a 2.0 slot.  I don't remember the bandwidth difference off the top of my head.

There is no reason not to, that's a good price for the card.  Then you can plan a new build around it eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 07:35:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should be fine paying most modern games on high settings no problem.  streaming should be fine.  why a microatx motherboard in a full sized case? maybe check out the full sized d3h.

also you could consider an ssd, or a bigger psu if you were even thinking about running sli one day.

seems a very solid build though.

edit: streaming on high settings might be a little iffy in an i5,  but it should be workable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 02:00:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're fine, you will probably need a new psu if you do upgrade your video card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 09:46:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can get a grounding bracelet for less than $5.  If you can't come up with less than $5 then... Save up...

If you really don't want a grounding bracelet make sure you keep a hand on the case chassis, and don't stand on the carpet.

Also remember processors are zif(zero insertion force) if you are pushing down you did something wrong. Unless you got a p3 slot processor or older, then push real hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 09:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it a fresh windows install?  Sometimes if you do a new build using an old hard-drive driver stuff gets really wonky.

Did you try going back and using integrated graphics just to make sure it isn't crashing on you.
Check and make sure the ram is installed in slots 0 1, it will probably be the far right slot, and second from the left. (it probably isn't a memory issue if it wasn't crashing before the video card)

Are you using both 24pin and 8pin motherboard connectors? Is the power going to your gpu seated properly? I think its 8 and 6 pin pcie power, but i don't quite remember.

If you have access to a known good power supply you could try that, it would suck rma'ing another part that's good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha yahh once I had a hair fall in the dimm slot.. The slot melted, but the motherboard still worked, save that slot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My asus p4ps8x was doa. But the 9700pro I saved up for was baller at the time.  All in all it went better than some builds, worse than others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 03:15:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cleaning the heatsink and new thermal paste couldn't hurt, and it's a whole lot cheaper than new parts.  Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 02:56:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An r9 270x and an ssd would be a pretty good upgrade.  Or if you stretch a little over you could do a 970ti and ssd.

8gb of ram should be adequate for a while.  I guess long term you would be looking at a new cpu/mobo combo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 00:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The feature set and reviews are looking real good on the extreme 6.  I'll have to give it a closer look tonight.  Are you using that board?  Maybe I'm just old, but I always think of them as the early 2000s asrock which sold ghetto sketchy cheap boards.  Even though I know they improved across the board a whole lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 00:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sub 200 would be great. Closer to 150 would be better.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Build Help] Mid-range/budget motherboard advice. z97 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I have my build all put together, just staggered as normal when choosing the mobo.  Currently I have the GIGABYTE GA-Z97X-Gaming 5 in my cart.
I only need 2 usb 3.0 headers. I'm only planning on running a single gpu (at least for the next few years.)  Probably never going to use more than 4 sata ports.
I like the idea of having the m.2/sata express just in case.  They aren't essential, but a little more expandability never hurts.  Especially out of a budget board.
I love the Gigabyte dual bios switch, it saved me multiple times with my current ud5h/ivy-bridge combo. (apt to say dual bios chips are essential to me, but i guess if something great comes along I'd settle.)

Are there any better options in the price range?  Future things I'm not thinking about?

edit: ATX from factor.  I also generally don't overclock, at least not until it gets late enough in the life cycle where I need to start pushing my hardware's limits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The same week grand turismo 7 drops I bet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 18:03:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just noticed logitechs high end model is on sale for 50% off today.  I don't have any experience with it, but I figured it might be useful if your still looking in the $50 range.

http://www.amazon.com/Logitech-Webcam-Widescreen-Calling-Recording/dp/B006JH8T3S/ref=redir_mobile_desktop?ie=UTF8 pi=AC_SX110_SY165_QL70 qid=1431446366 ref_=mp_s_a_1_1 sr=1-1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 20:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use a logitech c310 it's pretty adequate, good under good lighting, not great under poor lighting.  If you have a digital camera you could see if there is any way to plug it in and use it as a webcam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 08:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm assuming you can speak well enough that people can understand you.

I don't see any issues,  if anything it could be a big self confidence boost.  So long as you don't mind periodic hecklers.  twitch chat isn't all that bad.  sure if you go into a room with 50k people there are going to be a ton of assholes, but when you first start you will gain followers that enjoy you and your content.  if you get big then you get a couple early followers/friends to moderate, and take it all in stride.

Good luck!  make sure you post if and when you start!  and good luck finding a comfy set if teeths! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 08:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> next level analytics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 03:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so pay 2 win, eyes give a clear advantage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 18:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not sure what it is.  it was at a local outdoor festival.  The owner had no idea, and I couldn't find any distinguishing markings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cast iron frame and wagon wheels. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 00:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 10:30:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> likewise, the shop I've been going to for years told me they couldn't cut a fork and tap in a star nut until mid-next week.  Pretty sure the shops are just super busy right now, I understand them taking care of people buying a new bike from them first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 00:43:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surprise teams, you guys are playing on a new engine. Hopefully we worked all the kinks out.

Nah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 20:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> campagnolo victory 1984-1989.

http://velobase.com/ViewComponent.aspx?ID=510c9c68-2312-4134-95f5-aeb828d2c1d8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:56:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those chain tensioners are brilliant.  Beautiful details.  Can't wait for build pics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:54:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How you liking the essors? Going back and forth between them, archetypes, and open pros. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 06:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mine is shipping :) Was really on the fence about going aluminum, but they seem solid for the price.  The lifetime warranty is pretty good to have as well.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 12:36:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cheap conversion.

Step 1 buy a cog.

Step 2 tighten the cog.

Done

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:02:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think modders should have options.  The games industry is risky,  What if they want a stable job and to make a little extra money here and there via mods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the press demo there was unique classes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 22:20:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree, I've been with ting for about 2 years.  I have 2 phones on my plan and my bill ranges between 40-60 a month.  Hopefully Google pricing will be competitive,   I might not switch but maybe they will drive tings prices further down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do you report without 100% certainty? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 20:54:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever I'm up against a player who is making incredibly weird shots or pre-firing corners that aren't normal corners I will usually report them.  It's just easier and less dramatic than trying to call them out in chat.   Should I rest assured knowing that if they are just really good they won't get banned?

How do you deal with a potential hacker?  I'd just feel horrible if someone got banned for being better than someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 00:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those crap cg Dragon babies tell me that they have no money for good animators.  I can't attest to anything past season 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 01:17:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thickslick makes sausages O.o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 17:58:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why is everyone still surprised when hbo go doesn't work on the premier of game of thrones.
servers are expensive and they can't use one night a year as a baseline or else they will be hemorrhaging money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> computer to vsx-824-k, youtube fullscreen briefly loses connection. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 11:22:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So i'm going computer to receiver to tv, and when I make a youtube video fullscreen it briefly gives me a black screen.  Seems like it temporarily loses connection.  I'm guessing it has to do with resolution variables, but its only through youtube.  Other online videos are fine, and youtube ad's are fine.  right when the ad finishes playing it goes black briefly.
  I never had this issue when plugged straight into my tv, and its fine when I use a monitor.  Its not the end of the world (it only lasts a few seconds)  I figure maybe there is some weird hdmi setting I'm missing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 00:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely not legit.  Read the footer, it says "powered by http://ray-europa.com"  if you go to ray europa you can see it was shut down for selling counterfeit ray-bans.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 09:10:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you play better at that res then why not.  The only issue is limited visibility, but if you play a position with the same group of people it shouldn't be bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 09:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love my rangers, but personally I'd probably get hiking boots.  If you are potentially walking hundreds of miles/thousands of miles you might want boots with treads on them.  Something more functional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 04:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What level is everyone stopping on or around? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 10:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got into dark souls late, and ds2 wasn't my cup of tea.  I want to get into the multiplayer this time around, so long as the servers start working one day.  Anyhow what is the "agreed" upon level to stop at?  I'm ~80 now and don't want to jump up too high.

Also, is there a "soul level" or err equivalent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 06:21:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 06:17:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think its a token so you can but his armor in the insight shop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 06:15:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Psn is down for me, maybe it will let you ring your bells but it's not actually connecting you.  Maybe try choosing and opening your games and double checking is online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 03:01:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's super weird, especially when he pulled the scythe back out mid attack.  Something similar happened when I fight martyr logarius,  not quite that bad though.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 01:39:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too, it was working fine a few hours ago.  Think it might be down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are there mandatory bosses in the chalice dungeon(s)? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 01:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've killed every boss I can find in every area (I've found), and have no idea where to go.  I haven't gone into a dungeon yet, so I'm guessing I should probably do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 10:07:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It happened 2 times in a row,  So I think it might have to do with the fact I spent 2 insight prior.  Especially if other people have been toying with that idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 09:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried summoning twice and didn't find anyone.  I think it went from 24 to 22.  So it could be possible of I hit the threshold just right.    I don't think it was glitched because it happened twice in a row.  The first time I was doing a lot of dodging in anticipation for his magic attacks, which never came.  The second time I just went right in his face from the get go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do bosses get nerfed after x amount of attempts? (Spoilers) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 09:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The past day or so I've had lots of problems with Logarius.  Figured I'd take time to grind levels, my health was low and he'd almost one shot me, absolutely 2 shot me.  

I cranked up my health a bit and went back.  He didn't do any aoe orbs or the big close range skull.  He did do the small skull missiles when I approached, and his melee attacks.  I pretty much backed him in the corner and stun locked him the entire fight.

I guess I could have been playing way too passive when I had low health, but he used to do the aoe balls as I approached him.  I guess a wins a win, but it was a bit underwhelming.  I didn't even get to use the blood flasks I ground prior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 01:01:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Practice parries on the cinder block guys, they are easy to learn on.  Skip the 2 big beasts on the bridge, they will wreck your shit early in the game.  

So long as you are enjoying your time with the mechanics you shouldn't worry about progressing quickly.  Obviously veterans of the series are going to get through quicker than you.  

You could also look up epicnamebro on youtube,  he helped me a ton in learning the ropes for ds1.  His bloodborne videos are coming along very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 00:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I gave up and summoned for his fight.  I'm extremely bad at human sized boss fights,  I can't read animations very well.  The first 2/3rd of the fight reminded me of the artorias of the abyss fight, which I hated.  I'm on my 6th boss right now, and nothing gave me problems like father g.

I didn't want to summon, but I tried for 6 hours...  I was also under leveled, and skipped the first boss by mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 00:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just going purely off one shotting bosses.  I haven't yet in bloodborne, and I did multiple times in ds2.  

I also play way too passively, so that's my own issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 23:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Assuming her husband is a ds veteran.  Also it's way harder than ds2.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Have you noticed the visuals in Grand Theft Auto V have recently gotten worse on ps4 and xbox one. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 22:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 04:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your husband week just got rougher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 05:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck a fireplace, let's warm up by this Ridley!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 19:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also have oroshi kirin if you need </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 19:30:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 45 1659 5694 2990 pw 3333 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 18:59:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just unlocked the 9* quest, but that would be great if you don't mind.  I have a 46 ruby basarios if you need it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 02:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe if you do c5* remobra remedy you get a lr quest, then he will show up in low rank expeditions.  I could be wrong though.  Kind of weird how rare they made him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 01:58:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is there a high rank Yian Garuga quest? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 01:50:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should I just give up on my purple hammer upgrade and start a new hammer?

Am I supposed to just be doing expeditions and hoping for the best? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 04:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait for oleds to go down.  Why get an early 4k tv when nothing is broadcasted in 4k.  Technology will get better and cheaper.

Isn't there only a select few programs that broadcast in 1080p, and sure Netflix says ya! 4k, but it's compressed as hell anyhow and absolutely not worth it.  Unless you are gaming in 4k and your screen breaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 10:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> May very well only be a handful of people with work places in here I suppose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 00:53:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Making sure I don't drink that death kool-aid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thirdworlds got blocked on my workplace network. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 23:26:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For reason: cult and occult.

Sounds about right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Konami and Kojima part ways on future metal gear games. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 18:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 08:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I doubt it will severely damage Tag Heuer.  But I do agree it will probably stay as a concept/beta project.  I just wonder what this price could/would be,  Tag prices don't exactly compete with the ~600 mark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tag Heuer Partners With Google and Intel To Create Luxury Apple Watch Rival </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 06:46:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 02:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn that's pretty killer,  I've been toying with the idea of getting a large format printer.  Err well my buddy's buying a print shop and I've been toying with the idea of him buying a large format printer and paying me.  

Keep up the good work! It's a killer piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:55:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good luck on the $$$!  Oh and what kind of press is your school using?  Assuming it's a digital ink jet type joint, really cool you can print on canvas in school!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 19:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The p ruins it for me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nintendo Just Made a Deal with the Mobile, Free-to-Play Devil </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 09:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 07:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Another t shirt comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 06:51:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Game publisher contacts youtube personality and pays them some amount of money for a steam recommendation.  

Now steam curators need to disclose if they were payed for their recommendation.  Essentially it's a way to make sure the customers are getting accurate and unbiased opinions of a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 06:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm guessing it's such a small amount of money it doesn't make much of a difference.  Offer x YouTuber a couple hundred dollars and a free game for a steam recommendation.

It isn't so much a marketing issue, and proper writers on big name games media sites already had policies to follow.

The weird thing is X youtuber can still get payed to make a YouTube video, they just can't give it a steam recommendation without disclosure.  Essentially what matters are how many people follow steam recommendations vs just watching their favorite youtube personalities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Premera Blue Cross Was Hacked -- And Took Months To Tell Anyone </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Verona is a Shakespearean sci-fi treasure hunt from the makers of Sine Mora </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 23:32:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 19:57:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea it could potentially be great,  in just not sure how big of an impact it will have, or how they can enforce it.  Thought it was interesting though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> All Steam users must now disclose paid recommendations </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 19:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 19:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pro: you get to play both consoles exclusive games.

Con: there aren't that many exclusive games to begin with.

I normally don't tell people to get a pc, but if your thinking about owning both consoles then money probably isn't a huge issue.  So a pc might be something worth looking into for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 11:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not going to make front page of iTunes, no one will discover it anyhow.  Unless they add featuring Taylor swift to the title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 11:37:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How long ago did you listen to system of a down, did you listen to anything in between system and the death grips, how old are you? So many questions.

A lot of people liked nirvana, it doesn't mean that every lead man's junkie girlfriend is going to kill them.  Or whatever happened to that guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 00:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe don't listen to the radio?  What artists do you like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 06:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lawyer is more than $450. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 06:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 500 is a lot of money.  Your insurance will take care of your car.  Being punished for doing nothing wrong is bullshit customer support.  Sony should give him his account and revert it to before the hack took place.  Sony doesn't take any losses,  they are digital purchases that can be removed from the account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 19:34:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best we could possibly hope for is free streaming of games we own on ps3 via psnow.  But I doubt that will ever happen.. They spent a lot of money on Gaikai </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 19:04:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, there is no backwards compatibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 09:46:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope,  it was a section of mobile games and apps.    Not incredibly popular, but it had plenty of fun little games in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sony Finally Shutting Down PlayStation Mobile </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 08:02:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:06:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A round or two of smash when you need a zelda break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-09 06:24:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No backwards compatibility.  There is the streaming service, and it has limited games.  I'm sure you could find an exact list somewhere.  There is no downloads for any old games, ps1,2, or 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-09 03:08:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dropped from 3Mb to 36Kb on mega as soon as it hit 60% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 07:35:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  man, all I remember is GRAAALLL JAILLL.  I'll definitely hop on at some point,  I didn't even realize it was still up and running </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 05:50:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you lack experience I doubt you would keep up even if you had the best bike there.  Don't blame your bike, just work harder and go back when you are ready.  Especially now that you know what to expect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 00:53:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeesh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An Updated List Of Studios EA Has Bought And Then Shut Down </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 00:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> EA Shuts Down SimCity Studio Maxis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 06:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I've been thinking about stretching my budget and getting the heritage, was hoping for a $400 set with head and fork.  Suppose I could hold off on new wheels, just feel weird about putting my dumpster depot retrospec wheels on a halfway decent frame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 23:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the heads up about blb,  Don't really need anything save the frame fork headset and wheels.  Picking up wheels from velomine, and if I only get a frame I'll be getting the fork at retro-gression.  So I'm hoping to find something at cg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 20:34:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea it's a great price for a solid frame, good luck with your beater build! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Metal Gear Solid V Will Be Out September 1 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 18:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 10:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you are dropping that much on parts and it's your first build make sure you don't forget the grease.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 10:10:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful contrast.  Keep it up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sub $400 cro-mo frameset from citygrounds. Advice? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 08:59:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey I got a gift card to citygrounds, and I'm looking for a cro-mo frameset, or frame.

I am never gonna ride track, and new England roads aren't good.  So I'm assuming aluminum wouldn't be my best best.  My only problem is their cromo selection isn't very good.  I'm not sure if it's just a weird time of year before the 2015s start coming in.

I really dig the blb lo-pro frameset, but they don't have any in my size.  I would buy the fuji feather complete but they don't ship.  The pake rumrunner seems to be my best option at the moment, but I'd rather get something double-butted.

Should I settle on the pake, wait, or does anyone have an opinion? Flexible on price, and I don't need anything immediately.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Divinity dev will announce two new RPGs "whenever they're ready" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 01:42:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Here's Video of Harmonix's Amplitude in Action, Including its New Team Play Mode </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 20:11:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 20:01:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I hate the fact that it's been in sale albeit in early access for what seems like almost 2 years, and it's still virtually unplayable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Feds Admit Stingrays Can Disrupt Cell Service of Bystanders </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 19:59:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DayZ creator Dean Hall working on "wild mass multiplayer ideas" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 19:33:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ikea Unveils Furniture That Charges your smartphone wirelessly </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hope so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dead Or Alive Community Leaders Soft Ban Sexy Costumes At Tournaments </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:14:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 19:13:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Samsungs is cheap because it's not worth it.  It has extremely limited applications bottlenecked by underpowered handheld devices.  Not to mention it has no head tracking opposed to stream vr/sony vr/Oculus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 17:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At this point it's like every big release, of which we really haven't gotten many new console exclusives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 17:32:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah, no confirmations yet.  Hoping it's under 300. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Valve|HTC VR headset comes with controllers. List of game devs. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 17:24:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rise of the Tomb Raider will be "pushing the boundaries" of the Xbox One </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 17:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> HTC Vive revealed as Valve's secret SteamVR headset | Wearables News </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 17:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 03:20:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wheelchair ass jimmy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 01:57:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Panforte looks super, thanks for the list. Awful lot of all-caps though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-26 23:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Currently at work in a print shop thinking "the printing press is my printing press.."  Good job to Wheeler though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-26 01:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More polygons are more polygons regardless of resolution.  There isn't much of a crazy difference, or a noticeable difference.  Unless you are playing the same game on ps4 and ps3 at the same time on tv's next to each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-25 00:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds good man,  yeah I haven't been home much the past few days so I haven't even seen the current state of the game, but I'll check it out tonight.  I have the same name on Skype, so feel free to use that and our pass it around if you have any artists that want to bounce around ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 19:59:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 86, probably Licensed to ill.

Not really into pre 90's rap though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-23 03:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let me know if you need any ui assets/menu pages.  Trying to build up a decent portfolio anyhow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-23 03:41:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We'll see, he earned it regardless.  Although I don't see him doing the label and avoiding being a feature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 05:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope, I could see a 1st person viewing camera for spectators at some point.  I don't see valve doing another tf, cs, or dota.  Their fan base just has way to much money invested in those games.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 02:03:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the concept,  But it gets a bit weird to read especially the u and v.  Did you think of maybe breaking the individual triangles into 3 smaller triangles so you would have a bit more placement options? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-18 20:19:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did you wind up in your mom's cousins roommate's basement?  And why did this person have games in the basement?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 01:47:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm would fall-out work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 07:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ps4 wasn't announced at e3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 01:49:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good find, trying to check out. super slow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> No Hook Gang - Andy Milonakis   Chief Keef prod by Chief Keef </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 01:03:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-13 09:26:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like to see naughty dog doing something new, all though at this point naughty dog isn't really even naughty dog anymore.  After all the devs that left last year at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> using slider to adjust room view. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 07:59:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used this tutorial series to make sliders for my interface ( https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vzIV_c81ovk ), and I want to somehow link my vertical slider to control scrolling the room up/down.  Essentially my background is 1280X1400, and my view/port is 1280X720.

I tried something along the lines of if x is at bottom of bar move_to_position(0,1400,spd)  just to see if I could get the screen to scroll at all.  Instead the slider sprite just hopped off the bar and went to that position.

any help would be greatly appreciated..

edit : not sure if I could if (X=50%  of slider position.  move_to_xview, 0, move_to_yview,1400, spd)
sorry new/bad at coding, and cant find anyone else that has done anything similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-10 00:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because he is extremely popular.  Just about anyone who has a passing interest in rap music knows Kanye.  If 50,000,000 have heard his music and 1,000,000 think he is a genius you will hear these peoples opinions more regularly than some underground guy that might only have 20k fans that all think he is a genius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-08 05:14:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice style for sure, but I'd chill with the floor boards.  Unless it's an integral part of the game.  Thinking Bastion where the world is shaping around the player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 11:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just maintain aspect ratio and run it 16:9 with black box's.  Don't see why they would allocate resources for something less than 1% of players want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-04 07:06:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 290 is pretty solid.  Personally I wouldn't go with an i3,  maybe look into an amd chip.  Not sure what your best bet is amd wise but they can be really solid and are generally much cheaper than Intel chips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-04 06:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you are remotely technically savvy I'd pay 4-500 for a pc.  If you want to strictly use your tv then you save on buying a monitor, and you can get a 360 wireless dongle which will support 4 players on wireless 360 controllers.  Plus buying games on steam will probably save you money in the long run.

Not to mention if you get used to putting computers together and trouble shooting after college you can reward yourself with baller computer parts.

Edit: a console isn't a bad option now a days if you don't feel like getting in over your head.  Both have their subscription plans with free games monthly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 05:58:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a beautiful case, and you are paying 2k for a beautiful custom case.  It's a solid computer, but not a $2000+ computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 05:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think this is the right demographic. Try /r/gaming maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 03:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.gamefaqs.com/vita/732136-monster-hunter-frontier-g/answers/377075-can-you-play-monster-hunter-frontier-g-ps-vita-in-the-us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 00:48:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Technically you could put the old break levers on the flats if you want it quick and cheap.  Riding drops might get a little scary though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-02 10:45:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heat is real bad about gun shots and quiet dialog, but I don't watch a ton of blu-rays so I can't attest to all of them. Figure I'd give a warning anyhow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-01 12:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depending on if op is talking about pleveling or just leveling.  Either way if you are killing mobs slowly in torment 1 it's more or less a judgement call on trying for torment only legendary items vs working up to efficient torment farming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-01 12:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are killing more mobs faster on master increasing the opportunity for good loot to drop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 10:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Microsoft should just force business owners into a subscription plan. (Kidding)

But really the company I work for has ~400 terminals with Windows xp.  I'm guessing that isn't an uncommon thing, they need to find a way to incentivize businesses to upgrade their software.

I think Apple as of the last few years is a crazy anomaly that hinges on consumers far to much.  I don't think either company is going away, they will probably even out in the coming years.  But man these past few years of witnessing the scrappy apple comeback has been crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 09:28:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A. Internet speed=/= net neutrality.

B.  Replace old switches, or better yet run fiber lines.  Congestion problems are gone, and everyone gets faster service.  They have no problem charging a ~$5.00 rental fee for a 10 year old docsis 1.0 modem for literally ever, and they can't spend a dime on improving their offered services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 06:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Couldn't you just play the mkv in your web browser and cast that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-23 10:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not my size, but good luck to entrants.  Thanks for the giveaway! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-21 06:10:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of pros that have been playing cs for years are probably used to playing in 4:3, plus everyone has a position and is watching each others backs.  So they don't need to be bothered looking at the edges. Then a minuscule performance bump.  If you are pugging I don't see any true benefit to playing 4:3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-16 19:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently one can never not survive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-16 19:49:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> meh, in that case hearthstone is pay to win.  Pay for a booster pack that might have something nice.  I'm sure they will balance it if people are getting crazy amounts of guns.

Granted I don't need another zombie survival bs game so it's whatever to me, hope it works out for the people who were waiting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-04 11:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.designsbytue.com/-ezp-5.html

In the about us section they state "Ran Ban" Sun glasses a whole lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 05:37:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw that video where he was Jesus once.  It was dumb as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-01 15:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> None </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 14:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An entire year? Really?

 Edit: Destiny released the first day of 2014 in Adelaide? Sure.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 03:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's a problem with your ssd.  I have a cheap 60gb Kingston from 3 years ago that hasn't had any of those problems..

Edit: you didn't format it did you?  Not that formatting one should cause that many redundancy errors.  Especially not for a decent modern ssd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 20:37:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Longer inseam, smaller leg opening.  But I wouldn't expect them to stay while being active. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 20:24:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neither of those pictures show someone riding a bike, or sitting.  You could try never bending your knees.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 06:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An expensive purse, individually hand made using top notch materials.  Generally loses value or maintains the same value once taken out of the store.

A knife made once and cloned however many times are deemed necessary.  Increases in value about 200% once taken out of the store.

I understand that they both serve a purpose, and are luxury items.  But any high fashion generally holds a value beyond supply and demand.  Such as materials and man hours.  (I don't know how many hours a designer puts into making a knife) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 05:39:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Learning to narrate what you are doing is a good skill to have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 03:27:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's $30 with the purchase of a ds4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 09:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Home/games/psplus/free games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 03:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Park avenue cap-toe, iron rangers, cdb's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-26 23:23:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of 2014..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-23 10:37:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Monaco is very fun.  It's also something like $12 for a 4 pack right now on steam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-23 09:57:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I'm old enough where I can say "sorry guys, I had no idea what I was getting into."  But some of the younger kids might just be to brazen or daft to realize they are way out of their league.

It would be nice if there was a place for lesser skilled players who are serious and want to improve.  But I guess that would just get ruined anyhow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-23 09:45:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went on cevo once,  I'm a silver and I hold my own in regular pugs.  I get sick of being queued with the one guy who's afk, one guy who's playing music, and one guy who is yelling in Russian.  I don't really care if I win or lose, but I like a good game.  Although winning is better.


I joined a cevo round because I figured maybe there would be more teamwork, people making calls, people who understand eco vs buy round, etc.  Long story short,  I got put in my place.  No one really treated me poorly, and I apologized for my 5 and 20.


I think lesser skilled players, especially ones with no friends that play cs like myself feel stuck pugging with brand new players, Russians, and general assholes.  Some people just want the full experience of what cs has to offer, experience the comradery team players and pros experience.


Sorry if we ruin your day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-23 05:55:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my blades </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 10:32:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Almost any other game I use a standard placement.  CS stresses me out so I decided to play 100% of the time like that, rather than switching back and forth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 10:15:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All about the unorthodox finger placement

http://imgur.com/rPzsVNO

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 06:53:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sunshine didn't sell GameCubes I doubt sunshine 2 would sell the Wii u. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-21 00:42:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> blam blam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-21 00:34:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's just remaining holiday balance that will be payed off next month.  90% of the time I don't have any balance.  The APR isn't a huge deal to me, just wondering how its all calculated.  I figure I'm getting a new card for X features, but having a lower apr would be a nice bonus for the few "oh crap, next month" moments.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-21 00:26:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I carry a balance once a year, during the holiday season.  Generally I have that balance payed off by Jan, and pay it in large chunks rather than minimum payments.  Wasn't aware that keeping a relatively small balance once a year would hinder me that much.  Thanks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> APR will be based on your creditworthiness? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-21 00:15:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got a form from Discover today, and was thinking about getting an it card anyhow (at the moment I only have my cap plat with no rewards and a high apr)
after a 14 month intro APR of 0% my APR will be 10.99% to 22.99% based on my creditworthiness.  Would that be determined based on my discover account, or numerous things including my discover account?  Is there any calculations I could do to estimate what my apr would actually be?  I have a mortgage with only about a 25k balance, roughly $200 balance on my cap card, and my credit score is ~725
Im just sick of my cap apr being about 24% and them refusing to drop it, despite being a customer for about 2 years, and never missing a payment. 10.99% sounds real good about now.
thanks if you can shine any light, or if you have any other cards I should consider getting other than the it card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-13 20:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean I do agree it isn't a true mmo,  But in a true mmo you are grinding gear for hours a night months on end.  The Destiny grind isn't that bad, but I can see it being perceived as bad to someone with no experience in the genre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People have never played an mmo I guess.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:52:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the whole idea is not to inform so players don't have currency saved up to be level cap the second it releases..  don't see a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 12:12:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3sixteens are a solid choice, love mine.  Those n f deals that pop up from time to time are hard to pass up on though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 01:55:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're worried about that she's not worth keeping around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 20:28:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fit is great, facial hair is rough though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 20:25:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At arena shows there's always good food backstage.  Generally lobster, steak, cereal, cake, and drinks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 12:16:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I got free backstage passes I'd go for the food and drinks then leave.  If I got free tickets I'd give them to my girlfriend and tell her to have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 10:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Elijah could make a second set of pants out of his hem trim.  Gotta be a 15" inseam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 02:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are all great but if you aren't to familiar with strategy based rpgs maybe start with mass effect.  Not too hard to get through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 02:54:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mans seen some stuff.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-06 03:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My first case was an awp asiimov.  Since then I've gotten a few $2-3 skins and a whole LOT of nothing.  The house got me hooked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-05 20:03:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See if the arcade sticks work on pc?  Depending on the games specifications it could save money if your group goes that route rather than buying ps4's, sticks, and games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 07:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Law and Order whatever subtitle.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-30 20:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depending on the specific skin.  Less desirable stay about even or raise by a few cents.  The more desirable they are the more potential they have in raising.  Ie if you got a 20 cent skin it's not going to make you rich in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-26 11:15:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sports games via there respective apps, or the are a few games designed for the chromecast like pirate dice..  you wouldn't want to send an actual game to the chromecast even if you could, the lag would be unbearable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-26 06:48:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends on your opinion of Microsoft exclusives.  The majority of games will come out on both.  I love my vita, but unless you really want remote play or have a long commute it might not be worth it.

Assuming you have psplus you are already involved in the sony ecosystem.  So an extra 2 games a month, plus remote play is a pretty good deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 23:02:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that plan sounds scary... To save $5 a month... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 05:57:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2-3 months isn't too young.  I soak my pants once a month just to keep the denim healthy and avoid blow outs.  Either way they will air out after a few wears anyhow if you're really against soaking.

If you do decide to soak, make sure the water is cold and your jeans are inside-out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 04:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Give em a soak and use some detergent.  Or just wash em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 20:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't doubt it.  Japan in general plays more fighting games, while the us plays more fps's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 04:22:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2hood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 10:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No pc gamer is going to buy a bioware rpg on console, and no console gamer reading a review on ign is going to run out and buy a high end pc because Dragon age looks good.  Clearly it was some sort of mistake, or it's how the game looked a week before the day one patch.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 03:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe the early build ign received was missing certain video settings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 02:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gradually.  If they are selvedge jeans make sure they taper the inseam.  If they are regular trousers then it shouldn't be a big deal however they normally taper.  Find a pair of jeans you really like and measure the foot hole, it will help to tell them how much you want the pants tapered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 18:01:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The GameCube version is the only version </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 04:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably going to get into some SG5109's after the jolly season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 04:00:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah sorry,  stuck at work on my phone so haven't got a chance to see the clip.  Just figured I'd throw in my 2 cents on twitch donations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 01:56:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a lot of scam artists on twitch that will make large donations, then contact their bank and cancel the payment.  It also takes the bank quite a while to notify the recipient that they are liable for the money+ fees.  So if they took the money out of PayPal and spent it it leaves them between a rock and a hard place.  I've heard it's actually quite common, which is why a lot of streamers won't accept donations or at least not abnormally large donations.

It's pretty sad and messed up especially leaving the streamer to take the blame.

Edit: source /r/twitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 05:33:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Illegal drugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 09:57:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your home wifi doesn't have a cap unless you set it.  Ie. Transferring data from one computer to another computer on your network wouldn't effect the data set by your isp. 

 If you are streaming on your phone from your wireless provider. The only way to send that to the chromecast would be to set up you're phone as a wireless access point and connect the chromecast to it that way.  The data used wouldn't be much different whether watching content on your phone or on the chromecast.  The easier way to do things would be to use wifi on your phone and you'd only be using data from your home data cap. Sending the data to your chromecast that way wouldn't effect your isp set data Cap at all, but if you have a really low cap then I'm not sure it's your best option.  

What is your home data Cap of you don't mind me asking,  it's really strange to see a lower cap on your home internet than on your cell.  Although I guess it depends on what country you live in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 05:43:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait. Your in home wifi has a data Cap, you're home internet has a data Cap, or your phone has a data cap? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 20:26:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The article is actually pretty interesting, and it seems to shine light on both sides of the argument.  That headline is rotten though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 20:05:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm assuming the fcc is going to throw Obama's statement in with the rest of the general public.  The only real difference is I'm assuming they will actually hear Obama's statement.  The fcc is a private organization, and in the end they can just do what's in their own best interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 20:00:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can sure as hell pay for a good one though.  Education fast lanes.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 01:16:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One pair of wide leg jnco pants.  I sure as hell don't wear them ever. Just to remind me how much and how fast things change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 19:05:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weird, I'm assuming a patch will clear up my problems.  Or maybe the hours I'm playing I'm getting put on west coast servers that are more populated, which could account for some lag on my end.  Glad to hear it's working well for most people though. On consoles at least haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 08:58:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Game runs bad but playable for me on ps4.  Freezes every few hours or so, random lag spikes.  I also think the ping reading is fake it jumps all over the place for no reason.  100/10MB internet and a wired ps4.  Not the best internet in the world but solid by us standards.  

No other ps4 multiplayer game has run this bad for me yet.  Again it is playable, just not great.  (Normally I play 12am-5am est so network congestion shouldn't be a problem) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 20:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dunno about that.. The nes version doesn't exactly hold up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 00:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jeans and a t-shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 20:36:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idle thumbs, player one podcast, no crisis yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 09:52:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can post the actual link, but I doubt it's a real game.  It has to be up to no good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> the browser game.... wtf. [NSFW] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 09:47:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 04:47:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doubt we'll see the price cut within the next few years.  Should/hopefully be a bundle at least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 03:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck the world baby we love furl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-01 01:00:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Short money for unsanf denim.  Anyone here try red cloud out before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 03:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahaha yah my thoughts exactly.  I think the watergate reference is so people from the outside will think it bares some sort of worldly importance.  I Guess we were all youths at one point.  Some of us just didn't have the luxury of growing up with the internet..heh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 03:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spark notes: game gate edition.

Some bullshit angsty youths came up with to make themselves feel better about threatening every woman in the games press. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 23:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True statement! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 00:59:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Activision won't listen.  I'm sure the devs at bungie would have loved another 5 years to work on the game, and make it perfect. Again it is all about the Benjamin's.  I like the game personally with 70 hours on I got my money's worth, and am anticipating the dlc/expansion.

I also hated halo.all of them.  And what I liked of halo was the crazy physics and multiplayer.  I wouldn't say the multiplayer was all that deep, but I guess sticking grenades to warthogs was pretty satisfying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Job interview at a boutique specializing in American made/workwear/raw denim. What would you wear? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 09:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>   I don't have an interview yet, but I'm thinking about applying to a few places around town.  Really I'm only looking for a few part-time hours a week,  I have a full time job.  

  I'd like to make a good impression, in general.  Especially if they really like me and happen to offer me something better than what I have going on right now.  In the past I have worked retail jobs, but never at a small boutique with a very clear demographic.  I feel a suit would be too much, plus I work in manufacturing at the moment.  Any suits I own were last minute funeral suits.  On the opposite side I'd feel really weird showing up about a job in denim regardless of how much I may spend on denim.  

  As a rule of thumb do you normally dress in clothes one step more formal than what the store generally sells, or how the current employees are dressed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 09:20:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I must have remembered wrong..  haven't used it in a bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just put in my US memory card, wont let me log in to my US account? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 08:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did something change? I used to be able to use my vita with my Japanese and US accounts so long as I changed my memory cards.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 00:40:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not always.  usually it's a mix of crappier stuff and last season store markdown type stuff.  Usually the actual good stuff is a small percentage, but it can be found. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-26 11:03:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously everyone I know is leaving the bay area..they make 40-60k a year and can't afford it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-26 03:15:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much, didn't wanna get my girlfriend jeans that look like capris. About your height. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-25 04:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks great, do you know what the inseam is by chance? Not listed on their site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-25 00:18:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take 2 years to train, and learn your limits.then you will be 18 and can rent a hotel room if needed. Camping with an injury 500+ miles away from home would be horrible.  You also can't ride on highways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-23 19:01:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those sufu kids are pretty shady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 08:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The left one controls the right side of your body.  Keep that in mind if you're right handed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 08:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with your idea, personally I could care less about resolution/fps (to an extent)  I would rather have a fun game.  I enjoy subjective reviews, having the ability to "get to know" the reviewer while consuming their media.

But 900p is worse than 1080P technically, 30 fps is worse than 60 fps technically.  There is nothing subjective about it.  

objectivegamereviews.com does a pretty good job at ironically objective game reviews.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 06:35:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vermont flannel co make great quality flannels for under $100.  I've done factory work in mine many days a week for the past 2 winters.  Make sure you size way down, this is an x-small..I'm 5'11 155 lbs

http://imgur.com/w3A2tjI  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 06:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Were they women you knew before and then after, or just recently met.  Sometimes a sudden complete change in looks can be a bit jarring for old friends.  If you just met them, don't worry about it.  Maybe they just like men that wear sandals with ae bootcuts, and you don't really want those types to be hanging around anyhow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 09:09:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is a game in this file/disc 10 out of 10.

900p minus 1 point.

30fps minus 1 point.

Consensus 8 out of 10.

Objective reviews are really fun to read right? 

Essentially, cosign! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-17 07:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They must have caught up on the 08-09 GPU failing class action lawsuit.  
edit:07-08 and it was an nvidia class action, my bad.  But here's a source from that if anyone was interested.

http://appleinsider.com/articles/10/09/29/07_08_macbook_pros_included_in_nvidia_class_action_settlement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-17 07:02:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These ones, but i mean those boxing ones are pretty damn hype.. heh
http://www.highsnobiety.com/files/2014/10/alexander-wang-hm-collection-39-960x640.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-17 06:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jusdan rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 23:11:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair point, didn't even think about the generational leap.  I like the idea of expansions mainly because if you have friends that don't buy them right away you can all still technically party together albeit on old content.

I would like to see their numbers though on what would sell to a higher % of the current user base.An expansion or a sequel.  I know people still haven't made the leap towards accepting a digital only purchase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 20:58:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An expansion is not a sequel.  Everquest has survived 16 years and is still making expansions.  Their sequel flopped horribly.  World of Warcraft has thrived for 10 years, and making world of warcraft 2 would be a mistake.

Obviously in an expansion you will use the characters you have right now, so why make a sequel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 20:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Confirmed? there has been a lot of hearsay but I hadn't heard any confirmation.  I don't see any reason to make a sequel, it will just fragment the community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 16:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those gloves look nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 06:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Resin in a crack pipe will probably get you possession if narcotics, especially if you are a common offender.  Plus if the bike was over $400 it's larceny, class A misdemeanor 3-5 years, I believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-11 01:57:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So when 40k people are trying to watch a world class dota2 tournament they will get sent to random small streamers?

  I don't care for a lot of the huge streamers (daily streamers) but telling people what they can and cannot watch is crazy.  Imagine if Comcast sent viewers of the breaking bad finale to pbs to spread viewers out more evenly, the internet would lose their shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 05:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I'd like to see more stuff like this in the community, really glad I got one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 05:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I'm really happy with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 19:49:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is only 1 game that is free on ps+ this month that is also offered on the psnow service.  I understand that their streaming technology probably costs them an insane amount of money, but offering that 1 game as a free to stream game from October 8 to November 5 wont bankrupt Sony.  They could put a countdown timer on the games icon, similar to the countdown on pre-loads.  "This game will expire on this date, if you want to keep playing you can rent it."

Offering this would also get people involved in the psnow ecosystem, if they play that one game for free and see that it works really well they are more likely to go in and spend money to rent things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 19:38:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha wow, didn't think I was being that illogical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 11:49:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would be nice if ps+ subscribers could stream it for free from the first wed in October until the first wed in November. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 11:17:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the ps4 controller better, and my ps4 is in my living room.  It would be nice if I could stream it there, rather than bringing my ps3 back and forth between rooms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 10:54:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Launch ps now, scroll down to the game that is currently on promotion on ps+ and instead of saying rent for 90 days for X-price it would say stream for free X days remain on promotion.
  
People would realize they were streaming the now version because they launched now to get the game.  Im pretty sure people are reasonably comfortable with launching the store and getting their free games for the month, so how much confusion would it cause.


Im not saying its the perfect solution, or that there is even a perfect solution.  But it would spread more good will towards their ps+ subscribers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 10:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> consistency across sony platforms is the key though.  It would be nice if ps+ subscribers could play the game via psnow for the duration of the ps+ promo.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 10:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they are both sony owned services, they should be able to control pricing on services they provide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 10:28:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would be cool if they would even let you play the game on ps now free for the duration of the psplus promotion.  If you are a psplus sub that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 10:24:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's free with PlayStation plus, which I have.If I want to play it on ps4 my only option is to rent it for 6.99. Just saying consistency across psnow and ps store would be pretty nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rainbow moon. buy it for free or rent it for $6.99 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 10:20:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 07:01:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 12, Camera was angled a hair so they look huge.  Wish they were smaller though. Heh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 07:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, the shoulders are a hair narrow but the rest is pretty spot on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Quinn selvedge supply popover came in today. Will update as it starts to fade. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 06:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 01:58:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 50 tops.  15 for the games, 30 for the nes, 5 for the accessories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 11:20:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd check and see if they have a dress code, and what it is.  Cap toe shoes/boots, or chukkah boots should be fine.  If you can get in wearing denim then go for the darkest blue denim you can find, go with slim or slim tapered.  You might feel weird if you are used to baggy denim, but you will look better.(so long as you really are slim, also depending on how tall you are).If jeans are a no go then try some slim chinos.  Personally I'd wear a slim cut button down, no tails so you don't have to keep it tucked in depending on if the rest of the crowd is tucked vs. Untucked.


Posting some shots of yourself will also help people guide you a bit better, and definitely check the dress code.You don't wanna be the one that keeps your group from getting in, unless you are rolling in with like 10 girls.then you might get in wearing your pajamas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 10:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good to hear, and another cheap security option.get an adt security sticker and put it on the door.  A petty thief probably won't risk calling your bluff when there are plenty of doors out there that don't say adt.  

My bike lives in my living room, but I have the luxury of living by myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New bars and stem day </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 10:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/Xi4uM
Managed to grab some 3t ergo drops and an angled origin stem for $20. Craigslist deal.  I've got big hands and got the hand numb thing every time I hit 15+ miles with the vintage 38cm drops (no flats).

  I know the aesthetic doesn't quite fit, but I plan on getting a new frame set this winter.  Something my size, and black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 09:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sucks.  You might want to show the receipt for your new bike to your building manager.  Don't be a dick, you don't wanna get on his bad side.  Maybe he will cut you a deal on rent.  At the very least he might consider improving basement security.  You could even try to get some of those fake security cameras.most petty criminals won't bother to risk stealing right in front if what looks to be a camera.

Best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 01:07:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been thinking about it, just for comfort.  Did you remove the lever so it's just the hood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 07:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Left leg faded, right leg brand new.  Classic look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 10:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dang, I'll be in Montreal the 11th-13th.  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 20:50:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Soldier of fortune 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-27 17:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mannn those combs
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-27 03:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The crotch is sagging about knee level </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-27 03:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wearing your pants that low is cheating.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 07:07:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had to get long reach tektro brakes in my recent conversion.  The arms can be set between 55-70 mm I believe.  And you will probably have to drill your fork for recessed bolts on modern brakes.  That's what happens when you go from 27 wheels to 700mm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 02:00:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Send em to self edge to get repaired XD. Never take the deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 23:12:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The men's stuff is hot garbage.  Gonna have to check out the woman's symmetrical and bootleg ass HARE tunnel neck sweaters in person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 10:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gap makes very durable, good looking windbreakers.  They might retail fairly high, but I picked one up off season for $8 on clearance.  You might want to check that out once the weather gets cold.  I figure your student might like wearing a jacket that is a similar material. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 02:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should have bought a ps3 and that version of Destiny and kept smoking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 02:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vermont flannel co.flannel,
3sixteen st, Brown cdb's.

Getting cold again finally
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 02:05:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found it comparable to kara or 10 man nax.  Certainly not end game progressing in wow.  The tricky part is the fact that the vast majority of people trying have never been involved in anything like it.
It's amazing that they managed to make a fun fps raid with a few relatively interesting mechanics. Been interesting stepping up to be somewhat of a raid leader dad and guiding people through mechanics though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 05:37:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The asteroids moved, they wouldn't burn in like Pac man where everything was stationary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why no bar tape? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-21 21:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been seeing a lot of people lately riding around with horns and drops that aren't taped.  Trying to understand why, lazy? Better road feel?  It just seems like it would be really uncomfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-21 21:28:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That Hodor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-21 21:23:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree, I think they have better fits than the gap solid color t's.  Im pretty partial to my jcrew v necks though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-21 03:50:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They scale it well and all drops are geared towards your level.might as well cut the player base in half right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-20 13:43:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a void rocket launcher but using that was hopeless, didn't even think of trying a large machine gun.it would probably speed things along, or at least it wouldn't hurt. Thanks for the advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-20 13:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've played about 50 hours and am in all legendary gear except for my boots.  Tonight is the first time I've even been in the crucible.  Personally I like learning patterns and killing bosses.  To be honest this is the first time I've ever played a competitive first person shooter on a console.  It would be another story if I could plug in a mouse and keyboard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> exotic bounties demote team play in crucible </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-20 13:01:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Limiting somebody to one specific type of damage, I find myself sitting in the corner with my void shotgun waiting for someone to run by to kill rather than being on the field helping my team.  I don't want to be in any danger because that makes my bounty slower to complete.  When I'm out of shotgun ammo rather than helping the team with another gun I'm running to find more special ammo, because kinetic kills are pointless.


I would rather do 100 strikes without dying than play one crucible match, not because I think the pvp is bad but because I don't like pvp in games.  I appreciate the fact that Bungie made exotic weapons bounties difficult to complete, they shouldn't be a cake walk but they have seperate pvp and pve vendors.  This means you should obviously specialize and primarily concentrate on one or the other aspect. Why not have separate pvp and pve exotic bounties?


I feel bad being in part of the game I don't want to be in riding the bottom of the leader boards, hopefully people are angry about this.  If someone was doing a strike with me stuck using only a shotgun I'd be pissed.
Sorry for this rant, but at this rate I'll be bringing down my team for over 500 matches... great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 00:06:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think everyone is instanced based on geographic locations.  Everyone I've met so far lives within an hour from me.  I don't much care for that, but it is what it is.
Edit.probably to help with latency </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 02:05:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tragedy khadafi and pharaoh monch. Shaped modern rap quite a bit in the late 80s.  Capone n noreaga did really interesting collab work in the mid 90s.   Ra the rugged man is really interesting, especially his work with biggie.  Cage's life story is out of control, his movies for the blind album might be worth digging into.  Oh and epmd before Capone and noreaga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 01:56:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm guessing amour is rarer at higher levels, because it's how you level up.  Special weapons vs other weapon drops is probably just bad rng </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 12:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of cs:go streamers will play cs for the majority of their time streaming, every now and again they will play a round or two of something else to kill time and or wait for someone who may be afk or whatever.  Don't really see a problem with stuff like that, although I havn't really experienced anything extremely flagrant or excessive.
Plus changing the name of your stream is usually really temperamental for me, it seems to say I'm playing whatever twitch wants me to be playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 04:06:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much will people willingly pay per month year round to watch a single tv show....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 02:02:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Xexyz was one of my favorites growing up, figure I'd throw it in because it isn't an obvious response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 00:44:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Run your game in a window, and stream just the game.rather than a whole desktop screen region.  A second monitor would be way more optimal though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 23:07:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ArmaniXchange=/= Armani </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 21:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you can guide this youth, and make sure he doesn't make the same mistake.  As for you... Don't wear sneakers to your wedding, in-laws hate that sort of thing. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 20:47:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just not to prom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 20:34:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cargo shorts and a tank top breh breh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 17:50:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Marketing, and adequate testing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 07:33:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Around 6th or 7th my school had a computer with sim ant.  Real rough life. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 07:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try http://www.reddit.com/r/frugalmalefashion/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 07:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Polygons... My grade school had black monitors with green text... :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 07:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Suspect website.  
Edit: they also wouldn't release that info the day before the ps4 version was released.  They want to sell more copies, not less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:39:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure thing, on vacation until tomorrow so I only have my phone.  Once I'm back by my computer I'll send you a pm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-07 17:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're gonna be in Boston let me know,I can throw you together a list depending on your style and budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-06 23:01:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 30 fps is acceptable in every game except for fighting and driving games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 13:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No open world.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 13:09:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No pools... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 10:50:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure about that,I do know that you can transfer all ps3 content to a ps4 if you were to buy the game on ps3 then eventually get a ps4.  So worse comes to worse he could just activate everything on ps3 then transfer to ps4 then start playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 10:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took public transport for a few years during college.  You just have to keep trying, eventually the motion sickness goes away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 23:06:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Resogun plat.  Sports friends and strider I played a whole lot of, don't know if they count because I bought them on release. But they are great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 20:21:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Play them on your phone.  If you really want then get a bluetooth controller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-30 03:57:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've played one character for 300 hours, might as well see the new season uniques.  If you don't wanna play season then don't.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-30 00:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It held attention in Diablo 2 for many many many years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-30 00:48:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Err misread a little thought I saw 2 weeks of wear.  Yah maybe exchange for a size down.  But yah they look like they will wind up looking like a ns type fit, which isn't necessarily a bad thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 23:26:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They look good at the block and calf the knees are a little baggy, you could try wearing them higherup on your waist.  They look a little low </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-28 00:04:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No reason not to.  At the end of the season your season character becomes a regular character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 23:43:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Account bound items </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 08:27:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean the wheelset will be $100 minimum, then you need a single speed crank which is about $45 for a cheap one, then you need to put pedals on the crank which will be about 50+ unless you go with $30 bmx pedals.  In order to put the new crankset on you will have to get a new bottom bracket for about $30-40, not to mention a new chain.  
Then if you want to start off riding with brakes you will have to get specialized brakes with long arms, because you will be putting 700mm wheels on a bike that once had 27 inch wheels, so the brakes currently on the bike wont reach the wheels.
Im not trying to get you down, just telling you the things I came across during my conversion.  What I though was going to be a sub $200 conversion turned into an almost $400 conversion real quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 08:17:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im just trying to say, an old conversion is probably more expensive than he thinks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:09:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your best bet would probably be a cheap fixie, like a retrospec.  You're looking at around 250 in that bike plus parts, vs 250 for something cheap and brand new.  I just got myself over my head with a similar rebuild, although the frame has sentimental value to me, so I guess in the long run it was worth it.  Maybe look into pure fix, retrospec, or critical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 02:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much! At work desperately trying to recall what they said.Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 01:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you can type with a controller.that would be great.right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 00:49:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When getting selvedge tapered you need to specify that they must taper the inseam.  You are probably out of luck, although your tailor did one of the best jobs at maintaining the selvedge line I've ever seen, it looks interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 2.1 hardcore s1, can you start in adventure mode? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-25 23:17:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember during the tavern talk they confirmed if you have unlocked adventure mode you can play through the new season starting in adventure, is that just softcore, or can you in hardcore as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> that sit shot </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 01:10:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-23 13:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clarks are pretty comfortable, and look good with jeans. Great with chinos as well.  Something like these maybe.  I don't have any experience with hush puppies, so just my 2 cents.

http://www.shoes.com/Mobile/ProductDetail.aspx?originalReferrer=direct p=EC1390151 pg=5220384 campaign=Clarks CMP=KNC-adwordspla cpc=adwordspla gclid=CJ-BwJyhqcACFSdk7AodrCkAJA k_clickid=42bbb3f1-abb0-2d69-eb5f-00006d7b9a8a KPID=5220384-EC1390151-12.0M partnerid=adwordspla

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-21 01:52:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll be in on one if you do a second run lmk.  Love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 20:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most avid pc gamers do have that hardware, true.but that won't keep a company afloat.  50-60 in a scene with nothing going on is not stable at all.  I agree with your last statement, but they released this video and now everyone thinks it's how games will look.  Ie darksouls and watchdogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 20:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 20:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unstable fps, 720p to display empty rooms with minimal lighting.  On a computer that most people don't have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 20:11:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's because it probably is a movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 12:01:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "In action"not much action going on there.nothing for the consumer will look like that, and the internet will be angry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 11:55:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First thing I noticed.  Can you change Keybinds at all?I couldn't find it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Stunning New Pokemon Project" To Be Announced </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 11:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 11:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a normal practice.the games aren't developed on xbox ones... They are developed on computers.  If something is wrong with the demo I'd rather them be able to go in and fix it really quick rather than pack up and go home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 11:50:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Size 12 normally, almost. 155lbs?  And I agree with charwinger21 you should get your true measurements and look for an unbranded sizing chart, unless you have a retail spot to try them on.ordering your first pair of raws can be tricky business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 04:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My size and height exactly, tapered vs skinny is more of a personal preference.if you don't own many jeans and aren't used to jeans then I'd probably recommend the tapered.they should look great, and will be more comfortable for daily use.  Good luck.  Be warned they will feel really tight for a couple weeks while they stretch out a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 01:43:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You take that back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 08:52:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also the blue jean bar by Fenway park,I believe they have railcar.Not sure what else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 08:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Forgot about ball and buck, is pretty new. I think they only carry tellason but check out out anyhow for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 06:21:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Barneys of new York has apc raleigh n f, the wilderness workshop underneath the tannery has 3sixteen. The tannery in Harvard square carries baldwin amongst other brands, and it's next door to concepts which sometimes gets nice stock. Riccardi on newbury st is fun to browse if you have cash to burn, real high end type stuff.

Kaze shabu in Chinatown does a great hot pot.  Santarpios in east Boston does the best pizza in town, especially their anchovy (trust me).  If your looking for pasteries go to bovvas or modern, do yourself a favor and skip the hype lines at Mike's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:57:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sneaky peaky like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-06 01:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Half life 3 confirmed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-05 20:57:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> @feltraiger is good for workwear menswear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 08:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 00:30:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks anyhow, good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 20:58:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usually on 12am to 5am est </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 20:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Silver 2 looking to pug less.I'm not the best, but not bad.never played with a team and tried actual strats, but I have decent aim and good map sense.

If you ever need a fill in add me @ entangel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 05:35:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta look for the rb etching in the bottom corner of the right? Lense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 12:03:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's actually quite comfortable to ride, just need to sacrifice aesthetics and keep the saddle low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 08:26:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, yah I know. But the frame has sentimental value to me, so figure I'll ride it until I save enough for a new daily rider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 08:54:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some cheap retrospec wheels and crank, but I wanted to get back to riding before the summer is over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My new/old ad-s build. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 08:53:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 00:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gg deal on injustice for ps4. 8.44. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 06:05:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 
What brake setup is that? Working on an old austro daimler and can't make up my mind on a lever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 01:54:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Infamous looks the best, but wolfenstein is probably your best bet for a great game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-11 20:47:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pardon my ignorance, but what's the difference between surround speakers and regular bookshelf speakers?  I was looking at this setup. http://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B009ZTGZOC?cache=bdf832dc73551381a6cc7b381b79eb7a#ref=s9_simh_gw_d0_g23_i2 pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER pf_rd_s=mobile-1 pf_rd_r=1NAKFZFDP8HYMSZJT9BC pf_rd_t=101 pf_rd_p=1634797062 pf_rd_i=507846

And was wondering if I eventually get towers if I could just use the surround speakers as rears.
Edit: also I'm mostly gaming how are the fluances for generated audio rather than acoustic/reproduction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-11 05:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 5 HDMI inputs are not a deal breaker, but they are looking very good.  Bluetooth I can take or leave, it would be nice but my chromecast works just as well.

I've been told that Yamaha receivers have the least amount of technical problems, as well as the least amount of features.  Opposed to Denon with the most technical problems, but the most extra features.  Apparently Pioneer falls right in the middle.  (who knows how accurate my source was on that one though)
Thanks for the input, I'm waiting for the towers to go on sale so I guess I will still keep shopping around on the best receiver to fit my needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sub $500 stereo setup, opinions? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-11 01:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thinking about getting the new denon avr.s500bt with the Andrew Jones towers.  I need something under $500 that will sound good enough and will be worth expending into a 5.1 setup when I get more money.  I like the Denon, because it has 5xHdmi inputs and Bluetooth.  But I'm a little worried getting the lowest end model from any brand, are there any other receivers I should look into before pulling the trigger? And or any other comparable towers? 
Thanks in advance.

Edit: I'm not an audiophile by any means,I just don't have great hearing and my tv speakers are starting to sound a bit tinny at higher volumes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-28 02:00:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Diablo series always worked for me.enough of the mmo hooks with not nearly the grind or attention needed, or even give path of exile a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I heard Dota2 passed LoL in viewers, I didn't expect quite a large margin though.. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 10:46:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 10:14:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Comme des fuck on op... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 07:57:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, Yah I was completely unaware.  First time buyer, thought these things were pretty much set in stone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 06:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, really the money wasn't the issue.  I was hoping asking for a ridiculous amount of money would push the seller to just leave on the 24th.  I don't care if the seller is homeless for 2 days, it's better than me being homeless for 2 days.  If I have no grounds to ask for money and the seller just says no then I just look like an asshole and nothing changes.  I suppose putting together an itemized list would be more professional, and probably work out better in the end.
Thanks again for your time and advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 06:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two days is a big deal when now I need to rent a moving truck for 3 days instead of 1 just to store my stuff, I also need a place to store the moving truck because I wont have a driveway.  I also need to get hotel rooms for me and my mother.  Plus I need to pay a fee for canceling on my kitchen contractor with less than a weeks notice.  Also I have to take a docked day off of work as well because I'm giving less than 2 weeks notice.

Normally the agent has been very clear with me about everything, and explained document.  If he had any questions or needed to make any changes he gave me advanced notice as to what was happening next.  He sent me this last email with a subject stating "sign and return asap" and no body text.  Since emailing him back and saying "no" I have yet to hear from him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seller wants to push closing date back less than a week before closing. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 06:33:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am buying a condo,  the terms of closing date were set about 3 months ago when we agreed upon a price.  Closing is supposed to be on Tuesday the 24th.  On Friday the 20th I received an email from the sellers agent with no explanation, just a docusign document trying to change the close date from the 24th to the 26th.  I'm guessing he was hoping I would sign without reading.  I sent him an email back saying I wouldn't sign, and when I talked to the bank lawyer about signing my closing documents I was told that the seller wasn't prepared to leave and needed to push the date back a few days.

I can understand that things happen, and if I was nicely asked rather than trying to trick me (the way I see it) I probably wouldn't be so miffed.  Do I have any ground to stand on in making demands?  If I were to say "I want the price to drop 1k for every day after the 24th" is that reasonable?

Sorry if this seems a little bit like a rant, but my childhood house is sold, my mother is moving across the country, and I'm stressed out enough as it is.  This was the last sort of stress I needed less than a week moving into my new place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 01:54:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For 360-400 you can get a video card for a gaming pc.If that is your budget then get a ps4.If you have 1000+ to burn then get a gaming pc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-21 21:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Devin the Dude, Cage (at one point, I havnt seen him since Hells Winter),  The Clipse was real fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-21 07:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I expected them to start testing payment models, but 2.99-4.99 for 4 hours. That's crazy.  I might, pay that price for a week.  It would price up with renting a video game from a video rental store.  Hopefully if no-one pays they will realize, it is beta after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-19 20:02:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [minimal sketch-book](http://imgur.com/QGRHTGg) bored work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-19 19:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [print, laminate, cut and bind.. every day](http://imgur.com/a/d35BE)
Also a random design I'm finishing up.  Seriously need to find a way out of the factory life.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-19 03:07:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How does Dwayne suck so many dicks in one day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-18 19:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Constitution is great, tucked out of the way and generally pretty quiet.  The playground and basketball courts are nice if you're the having family sort.  Granted I haven't been there in a few years, for all I know it could be all pavement by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-16 06:13:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hippies... ancient Egyptians didn't have work boots.if I had to work construction and could only wear sandals I'd probably wear socks as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-15 08:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look great, not often enough seeing interesting denim in Boston. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-15 06:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whatever console your friends are playing it on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-15 06:15:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She didn't get the memo.female assassins are too hard to animate, therefore they don't exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 07:37:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always looked at fashion boards as an extended group of friends.  If you are around a certain group long enough you begin to act, dress, and like the things the group as a whole likes.  Every board had their select few individualists, sometimes they are the creative's, or industry people, or even just the ones with the most money and they tend to spark trends in the community.the only way to get "beyond"the group is to leave that specific group.
I'm a hypebeast person from 06, when I joined wdywt consisted of evisu, and red monkey jeans, bape hoodies, and dunks.  User/blogger Neek was the first to start posting fits of 501stf,wtaps/cukkas, and solid colored tshirts.  at first it wasn't well regarded "too sufu" a month later and it was the biggest entire forum paradigm shift I ever remember seeing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 06:47:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> idk. god of carts..  or cart of war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-11 17:29:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a fitted hat for the winter, it can be bought at lids in the winter... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-11 16:43:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that possibly herringbone fishtail parka is real tight.

and this whole fit is something special. http://fuckingyoung.es/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/CIVILIZED_fw14_lookbook_fy4.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 19:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> real intrigued </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 09:00:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://theworldsoriginalface.bigcartel.com/products </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 02:06:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> War of the roses, if you don't mind only multi player.the sword pay is super rewarding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-09 09:18:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> build a cheap pc, get 4 wireless 360 controllers and do the steam streaming thing.  All the couch co-op and cheap steam games you need.

Buy a ps4 if and when there are exclusives you want to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-01 23:57:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> solid jeans,I love mine.They're really soft.although I ripped a belt loop off of mine last week...in Montreal.thanks for the giveaway, and someone enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-30 06:48:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> game, depending on what time/where.  Maybe we could have it in Copley square, and if it rains we could move into the prudential food court or something.
Seems easily accessible for someone unfamiliar with the city, and not in the middle of the commons if it starts raining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-29 08:25:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/biBHoPG

I can say they fit similar, we have very similar bodies, and I happen to be a person that has worn many different brands of T-shirts.  Sorry I don't own white T-shirts so a black one will have to do in this compare and contrast picture I have taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-29 02:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gap tees fit very similarly, the necks aren't quite that large though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-22 20:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worked adequately on my 660ti. Wired pi, wireless ac300 pc.it's how I beat dmc, dark souls wasnt a great experience though.  My only problem was getting my 360 dongle to work with the pi, wound up just leaving the dongle on my pc.and bringing the controller to another room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-19 07:45:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yah I got the opacity mask working just fine.meant to work in rgb anyhow, habitually work in cmyk due to work.but thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-19 00:40:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> argh, thankyou... Forgot to work in rgb, clipping masks dont like cmyk gradients for some reason.  But ya Got it sorted out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-18 23:50:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Can't make a compound path. All objects in a compound path must be paths, and they cannot be brushed or part of an object." heh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-18 23:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to cut the circle out of the mesh, "minus from front/back"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-18 23:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to minus a circle from that mesh, am I out of luck?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> can I subtract from a gradient mesh? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-18 23:22:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-13 20:54:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a graphic designer who currently works in print production.I've always wanted to get into ui/menu design.  Really,I just don't know where to start.do you know of any indie devs around the city who would be looking to give a guy a chance and get free work in return.either that or any indie designers who would want to take on an apprentice?  Thanks for all your work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can I transfer credit history, from an old to a new card? Same bank. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-13 08:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry if this is a dumb question, anyhow.
My first credit card was a CapitalOne Platinum card, It was just about the only card I could get with very little credit history.  After a year or so my credit score is ~700, and I was pre-approved for the Cap quicksilver card.
If I have 2 cards in my wallet, one with a higher APR and no rewards and the other the opposite I don't see myself using the platinum card any more.  I don't want to close my platinum card, and lose all the history I built with it.  I also don't want to keep it unused and have that go against my credit score, as little as it may actually effect it.

I'm also planning on applying for the Discover it card, and don't really care to keep track of 3 credit cards.  I'm very responsible with credit, and 90% of the time I don't carry a balance from month to month unless I'm hit with a last minute emergency in which I clear it off as quickly as possible.  I'm just not the most organized person in the world, so the thought of carrying around 3 cards scares me.

Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-29 01:48:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Getting more money for mk vs dcu than for bf3 it's bonkers, nobody could be looking for that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-20 19:22:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "George Bush doesn't care about black people" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ARM, vs Fixed rate? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-20 07:39:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am planning on buying a condo in the next month, I will be taking a 30-year mortgage and am not sure whether to go with an adjustable or fixed rate.
I'm accounting for my finances with no over-time at work, and I will be fine making payments with either loan.  I'm planning on paying the loan back within 10 years.  For the moment going with an ARM would save me on monthly payments for when I am not getting over-time.  (its slow season now)  For 2/3rds of the year I am planning on making double/triple payments.
Would I be wise to stick with the best % fixed rate mortgage?

I have about enough finances saved up to pay it off in full if things get bad, but I would rather build more credit.  I also don't want to buy a cheap condo in full and have no just-in-case money left.

PS. thanks to everyone who helped me out in my rent vs buy topic from a couple days ago.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-18 07:14:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dracut, lowell, haverhill. Depending what you consider around. 25-35 minutes away is close enough for me. I work out of Chelmsford ma. The cheapest I've found near the city proper is Malden, but the cheap cheap end was like 130k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 06:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot, I'm going to have to look into a buying agent and see what I come up with.  Glad to hear you made out well on your condo!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 06:35:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely atleast 5 years.
The place I have my eye on currently, well one of many.  The one I'm waiting to hear back from has been on the market for about half a year, and has already lowered their price about 10k.  It isn't a very convenient area, it just happens to be very very convenient to the place I work.  I do need to have it seriously checked out though, if I get serious on this one.  Because that length of time tends to make me nervous.
Thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 06:30:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot, I would have absolutely overlooked that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 06:29:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I promised my mom I would before she moves to Florida, I'm staying in the Boston area.  The last thing I need is for her to be worrying about me, when she needs to be worrying about herself.
Figure there is no harm in meeting with the guy once and seeing how I feel.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 06:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I will have to look into that.
At the moment I'm looking for a one bedroom, in hopes that my girlfriend will move in when she is ready.  For now I want to prove i can be fully independent, and if she moves in we would be making about 100k in total together and could pay it of quick, and or live like king/queen.
I went into more detail why she can't at the moment a little further up, but ya after dealing with roomates for years I don't know if i can go back to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 06:21:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, average in my area is only about $150.  A few im looking at are around $250 with gas heat included.  When I was renting, during the winter my gas bills were around $250 alone.  So at that price it seems to even out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 06:19:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me and my girlfriend are pretty serious, but at the moment I need to do whats best for me.  Since moving back home I have an hour commute to her, and a 45 minute commute to work.  The places I am looking to live would be within 25 minutes from her, and 10-odd minutes to work. ~200 a month in gas in my civic is getting old.
She doesn't have a car, She moved to the states when she was 16 and has had Boston public transportation ever since.  Wherever I look at I anticipate bringing her, and value her opinion.  But for the moment I want to prove that I can be completely independent by myself, and hopefully she will move in with me eventually.  I can't afford to live walking distance from the subway by myself, and need to be safe if anything happens between us.
Just to clarify, she makes more money than me.  She doesn't drive because she never needed to drive, but she's working on it. (I don't want anyone thinking poorly of my lady ;))
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 06:09:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't want land, I grew up in suburban NH and have plenty of land.  I hated every minute of any yard work, and shoveling I've ever had to do.  I would love to get a townhouse maybe, but its out of my budget at this moment, and will likely be for the next 5-10 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 20:57:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the input. I have 65k is saved up.so even after a dp I have some wiggle room.have an appointment next week with a financial advisor.is there anything you would recommend asking or telling an advisor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Should I buy a condo, or rent? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 19:32:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 28 years old and was renting for a few years.  My father passed away last year and I moved back in with my mother. (not trolling for sympathy, just giving context).
My childhood house is going on the market, and I need to come up with something to do soon/within the next few months.  Condo's in my area are in the 75-100k range, and I have enough money saved where I could comfortably put in a 30% dp.  If anything goes completely awry I have enough saved where I could probably buy it outright.  
I make about 40k, and am happy at my job and don't intend on leaving it or my area any time soon.  It also works out with the loan I'd be taking plus average hoa fees in my area that I could live in a nicer condo for cheaper than renting.

I strongly oppose going back to having roomates, and I don't want a house (after maintaining my current home over the past year).

edit: also I know this isn't the reality sub, but if anyhow knows about how firm condo prices are it would be appreciated.  I don't want to offer 65k on an 80k condo, planning to settle between 70-75 and have my offer seem like a slap in the face only to not hear back.  (I don't know if condo's are like houses, and owners expect an offer, or if they expect to get the asking price.)

Any opinions or advice would be greatly appreciated, hopefully y'all can help me from giving myself more headaches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-08 01:41:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crazy Titch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-11 06:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> are you sure its your videochip? do you have windows 7/8 32 bit or 64 bit?  32 bit isn't supported and could lead to some of those same problems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-07 19:56:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shoe goo works wonders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-01 21:43:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure there are more tv addicts out there than gamers, but thats old news. Gaming is still relatively newer, and still has weird stigmas attached to it. Personally gaming is more addicting to me because it is more engaging than those other things.

Edit: Also when you finish a show you are done, you have to wait for next week. Same with a book.  With mmo's and mobas, things that people are generally addicted to there is no end. You can keep playing forever with no real reason to stop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-28 20:48:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Strange, ya sometimes if things are too close to a Wi-Fi source they won't connect.maybe try using the cable and getting all the system updates, if you haven't tried that yet.if that doesn't work you might have to contact support.heh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-28 02:19:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you try moving the ps4 further away? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-26 19:16:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree, permanent.  If they aren't friends at first it wont take too long before they have some sort of chemistry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Konami cuts price on MGS V Ground Zeroes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-25 19:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 05:04:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rakim ran shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 01:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2, just because the blazer in the first picture looks crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 01:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> might be good to include your price range. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-22 03:57:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you can program a game using the Commodore, you can't on the arari or the coleco.in the most basic sense I guess every console is technically a computer, but not really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-22 03:08:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Search, then post... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-22 03:07:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The commodore was a computer, and no one ever took sides with the colecovision.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Itunes account was hacked. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-20 06:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I received an email stating that my account info was changed.  For some reason there is no button in the email to say no it wasn't.  All of my information was changed, so i can't retrieve my account.
I had no credit card info stored, and 10 dollars in my "wallet".  My library is all backed up.
Is it worth calling customer support? is there anything they can do? should i just bite the bullet and make a new account? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-20 01:51:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Madvillainy then mmmfood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-19 10:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jimmy boi is aiight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-19 04:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rayman will last twice as long(if not more), and strider is half the price.  They are both great games, rayman is arguably better.  But i haven't had as much experience with strider.

essentially either way is a pretty good bet
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Strider demo wont launch? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-19 04:25:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> anyone else having this issue? Seems like it's trying to launch the full game. Giving me the error "you don't own the licensing"
baffled



Solved. If anyone else has this issue go to settings/psn/restore licenses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-15 23:10:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-13 10:23:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tmtm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-10 05:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot less work than making 14k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-09 08:14:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> people have been predicting these things every day for the last 10-odd years. lets take a break for the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-09 07:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try soaking them more often.they will fade slower, but the denim will stay more healthy and less prone to crotch blowout. I almost never wear these because of all the holes, and am kicking myself for not soaking em more often.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-09 07:34:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Atleast you don't have to worry about indigo bleed ruining your shoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-08 02:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started off with Venomancer, was pretty good too me. Lots of aoe and dots, can hold down a lane pretty well
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-07 15:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> raw denims been becoming mainstream for a long time.  Similar to how street wear used to be exclusive to small boutiques, and now its available at zumies.


5 years ago you saw Raw denim at high-end stores/some boutiques, now you can get it at urban outfitters and macy's.

Not that there's anything wrong with that.

The niche market likes it, the famous people start wearing it, the rest of the world wants it. It is what it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-06 08:43:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> APC NS, roughly 1.5 years. 1 soak 1 wash.
http://imgur.com/a/bYUEq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-06 06:58:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ack, thanks for the info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Comcast, issue in adding digital voice and internet blast service. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-05 23:48:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just last week I upgraded my service to a triple play deal, because it worked out to be cheaper than my current tv and internet separate bill.  along with upgrading my internet from performance (25MBps) to 50*.
Today I go outside and find a box from comcast, inside was a technicolor TC8305C MONSTROSITY.  I called comcast to say I did not want it, only to find out I had a tech coming to my house in 2 days, I had no idea about this.
Currently I have a asus RT-AC68R, and a Motorola SB6121.  Am I going to need this outrageous technicolor box to add digital voice to my package?  Or is there an inline solution they can do.  I dont want another 2.4GHz device mucking up my signal (I have a pretty large house, and have a few devices stuck on 2.4 still)
Is my best bet to pay comcast for a phone line that I don't use, and continue paying AT T for my phone service? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-01 06:27:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> February is probably a safe bet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-31 19:47:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True, the other day I got my jcrew selvedge chambray stuck between some pressing rollers at work.rather than being smart and turning off my machine I instinctively ripped my shirt out. I lost a button, and was amazed it didn't get torn at the stitching.if their quality starts to diminish I'll just have to go elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-29 06:30:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the summer, sometimes.also depending on the cut of my pants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Retrospec crank, will I need a bottom bracket? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-25 09:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.retrospecbicycles.com/cranksets.html
I have a 197X austro daimler AD S, which im trying to convert as cheaply as possible, hence why i'm looking at retrospec.
Just getting back into cycling, and don't want to drop a lot in case its just a passing phase.
Also if anyone has recommendations on quality budget cranksets/wheels I would love to hear. (as quality as budget can be) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [H] Deus Ex Collection, Zeno Clash, $3.48 wallet. [W] Might   magic X Legacy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-25 09:47:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deus Ex collection includes (Augmented edition of Human Revolution, and invisible war) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-23 18:58:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Online sales are also not taken into account </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-20 19:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably a Tucker Blair belt, but i cant find that specific model though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-16 13:59:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea throw em his way! Hope this one works better. Many many community respects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-16 07:00:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dunno about those whiskers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 06:22:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> beautiful, should be front page any minute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-13 09:28:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe new in box, the name zelda sells units.the more units sold means the less valuable it will be in the long run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-13 09:16:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 25 seems reasonable. 10 for the console,5 for the joystick,10 for the games.unless there's some crazy valuable game in the stack, because zelda is a 50 cent game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-07 20:50:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you go up to NH at all you could check out myriad games and double midnight comics.both great gaming spots about 45 mins north of boston </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 10:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no hackers on the stand alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-30 19:13:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dunno about raws. "Here's a pair of really expensive denim." "Wtf they are stiff, uncomfortable, and I want to wash them." "Naw man it's cool just wear them for the next three months...trust me".

I mean I love me some raw denim,I just don't think they are great for someone who doesn't care.  Personally I'd say a pair off dark washed denim,jcrew or something of the sort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-29 19:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nintendo needs to give up the virtual skoal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-29 06:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea they opened a store in boston recently too, dropped in today and the sale was pretty great.seemed it was 50-75% off everything except a small section of next seasons line.

Pretty sure it's gonna be my new between season go to spot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-29 06:45:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea my thoughts exactly, I wouldn't hold my breath. but it would be a great surprise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Initial d perfect shift, online. 3ds. Hopefully U.S. one day. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-28 08:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-27 18:02:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sports cap and normal attire.  if its really cold i'll wear a sports beanie and normal attire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-27 10:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> faux fur isn't "pretty much the same thing" as coyote fur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-26 10:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is that good at factory.jcrew as well? probably your best bet. :D Super cute though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-26 10:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solid chinos, and they sometimes drop around that price between seasons.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-26 10:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [gap GQ collaboration](http://www.gap.com/products/gap-gq.jsp)  has alot of solid pieces, really depends what your looking for.  Some of those Baldwin denim pieces look really nice though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-26 10:16:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you have a couple extra bucks, these would be a solid pick-up for sure.
[selvedge denim](http://www.ae.com/web/browse/product.jsp?productId=0118_2957)
Edit: didn't notice the lack of sizes.... could be good if your real skinny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-26 02:07:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Def the tassels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-25 22:14:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Girl got me a Jcrew [rucksack](http://i.imgur.com/zgmS5iV.jpg)  and bro got me a load of Jcrew vnecks.
pretty happy with it :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Overcoat sub $150? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-18 07:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looking for something decent, and as cheap as possible. New England funeral, so it'll be cold.leaning towards functionality over looks, but I'd rather get both. No time for my tailor and I suppose no time to be picky. Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-17 02:28:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you don't have to pay 60 for the full release.potentially. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-17 02:26:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From what I saw at the pax east panel the interface was a lot more user friendly and intuitive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-16 04:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So the parents who are just trying to be holiday hero's all deserve to be scammed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-11 04:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> arma 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-11 01:20:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  if you wind up parting it out send me a message. interested in gpu and psu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-06 18:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  the boots are completely different, beyond color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-05 09:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  the hurricane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-05 07:02:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> originoo gunn clappaz, tradgedy khadafi,  unless I missed anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-01 04:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would actually recommend watching a bit of a few "let's play's" not enough to see the whole game, but to see what and how experienced players grapple with the beginning quandaries that leave newcomers stuck. essentially get a feel for the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 17:32:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if you are in the new england area, bullmoose records as well.
http://www.bullmoose.com/p/15400409/ps4ac-psn-12-month-subscription-card </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 17:26:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and or just take a pair of jeans you like, and do all the measurements and compare them to measurement guides of jeans you are looking at.  If you cant find a fit guide, dont shy away from sending emails to customer support. Nothings worse than having 150$+ jeans that you dont like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 17:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sized down n f skinny guys work well for me, im 6'/145 lbs. just size down once or twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-24 20:50:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> rick ross </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-23 11:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A PENTIUM.  yah sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-23 11:02:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2 write </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 11:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  omega virus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 07:31:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  tried it once, looked like a  flat-top. I guess I could use like a whole can of pomade  every day, but ain't no-one got time for that.
edit: my hair it's brillo pad curly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 06:53:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> " THE HAIRCUT ALL MEN SHOULD GET"  except for the curly haired freaks :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-19 10:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  maybe check on frugal male fashion advice as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-19 10:12:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  headache setup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-18 05:58:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  not the cable torn, the whole hdmi port got torn out of the ps.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-17 23:47:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  God damn, that's horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-17 23:45:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  too casual for anything classy. but I guess it depends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 20:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Valkyria Chronicles of your into that sort of thing, and the infamous  games are good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 19:40:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you forgot about a horn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 12:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  like a horn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 12:42:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  it has as much DRM as any other console, it's the only one that's region locked, and the cost is not that low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 12:36:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Yea I honestly thought I needed to upgrade to a ps4 ps+ or something. way too big, way too much, way too everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 08:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  dang. update went super smooth for me. after that I anticipated just logging right in. but nope.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 07:16:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  happening to me when wired to Ethernet connection. when I try wireless it's "please wait..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:20:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FF XII </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 17:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  height is a little too big, width is way too big. you also look young, so cheap glasses are more than fine. it would suck to buy $100+ glasses only to outgrow then in a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 17:01:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> vamp ass hoes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 10:32:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  top right 3/4 view actually looks pretty good. top pair are better. but concur way to large </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 08:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  no offence, honestly interested in why you would get a v-neck  t shirt tailored. why not just get a better fitting t. unless you have a really really strange build.I mean even great quality t shirts have a finite number of wears before they are no good anymore. unless you just have a real solid income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 06:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  np hope it works out.I swear finding good fitting shirts off the rack is like an at form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 05:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  if you have a Brooks brothers near you try and check them out.  especially if your near an outlet store they have great deals.  I'm 6 even and 160lbs,jcrew slims fit me great, but Brooks tend to be a little too big for me. they'd probably for your build better.  you could also check out jcrew chambrays, more of a classic/ loose cut than their ocbd's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-09 19:36:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> morte ruled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-07 00:54:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dayz? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 19:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wonder if current ps+ users that keep their reoccurring payment going well be grandfathered into the old price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 10:22:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neeks fits from 06-07 era hypebeast.  First person I remember bringing street wear from crazy ass all-over prints and evisu jeans to minimal slim cut raw denim, and chukkas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-02 20:13:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> krs-one, I got next. tragedy, saga of a hoodlum. cnn the war report. are pretty much what got me in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-30 22:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nujubes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-21 04:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> co-sign jc2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-17 08:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-16 07:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm don't generally like supras, but those aren't bad.  Really minimal as far as supras usually go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-16 07:31:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dress nicer than the average factory fare.  Granted my specific job is less grungy than most other factory jobs.
workwear look m-f.  Every season shift I tend to bring in nicer/old weekend pieces into my usual week wear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-10 02:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  still lookin for crunchy black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-09 20:31:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> garbo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-07 01:39:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha must be pretty nice, but ya i'd give them a shot figure its worth a try if it isnt too out of your way.  I also know theres a uniqlo in SF if you felt like going on a long ride for some shorts haha.
gluck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-07 01:29:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm pretty sure they do, maybe not in the off season though. although i dont really know what the off season is like in LA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-06 19:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> american apparel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-05 20:04:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heltah Skeltah - The Art Of Disrespekinazation 
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0MbL8bwxhzo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-05 20:02:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dont forget about the nighthawks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 07:10:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  my character has been created and I've had him for about 40 hours. I'm absolutely not golden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-02 17:53:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  offer 100. 160 seems high imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-02 03:54:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> shoe goo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-27 19:50:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought both the new consoles were supposed to be able to output at 4k.  how about we just wait and see about the framerate. not to mention 4k tvs/monitors  probably won't be in the average consumers houses for another 4-5 years anyhow.

 and if we're talking about the far off ps5 future I'm sure tech will evolve so as to create solutions keeping costs about at standard price. last gen was a much bigger advancement making the jump from 4:3  to 16:9  imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-24 17:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every GTA game has come out on PC eventually, why is everyone so down like this one wont.

I'm not saying it will be soon, but it will likely happen eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-23 20:31:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  my computer has also been hooked up to my tv for 8 years or so. so I guess I might not be the target demographic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-23 20:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  most of the games I pay are in the steam eco-system. but not all of them, that sort of worries me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-22 19:10:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're trying to get in shape, and new to denim I would absolutely go sub 200. Probably even cheaper.
A. make sure you actually like wearing raw denim.
B. It would suck spending a considerable amount of money on denim then losing weight.  Personally I would wait until you are happy with your weight and arent going to fluctuate much before spending big money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-22 06:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  buying multiple pairs of sub $200 denim rather than one pair of higher quality denim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-22 06:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  rogue didn't cost 270 million dollars to make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 11:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dreamcast  had a killer lineup.  jet grind, sonic 3d, shenmue, alot of other weird obscure imports. not to mention you can burn games on cds without modding  if your info that.
 the rest I'm impartial to, they are all good bets, but Saturn games might be a tad on the pricey side, if that matters to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-09 10:12:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2 out of 5 are free.  the rest combined are probably cheaper than this pack costs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 20:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Somewhat interested in picking up a ps3. What are you looking for before I bother you for pics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-02 09:26:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My thoughts exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-24 22:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like they are working on it though. 

"The game isn't running on my Windows 8 machine. What do I do?We're sorry to say that Rogue Legacy is not officially supported by Windows 8. Some people have successfully managed to get the game running in that OS, but we can't provide support for those versions. We will be releasing an official version for Windows 8 along with the Mac and Linux versions." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-24 21:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rogue legacy doesn't support win8. Maybe you could try running in xp compatibility mode. But not sure if there's any way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-24 21:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have windows8? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 22:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trying something radically different than my usual slim fitting work wear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WIWT jcrew/dockers/clarks </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 22:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 18:43:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> normally don't care for pocket stitching, but those are absolutely beautiful.  Love the details.  Would love a fit pic when you get a chance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 18:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not to mention, no matter how fast your network is you would have more latency streaming it to your pc than plugging your console into a monitor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 10:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> suspect ass mw3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 07:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> shin megami tensei IV, Animal Crossing, Monster hunter III/IV. 
If you are in the market for a handheld system then its absolutely the way to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-22 18:55:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It will look alot better on a smaller 3ds screen, and pokemon games have never looked particularly good.  They are fun and charming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-22 07:26:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> co-sign, maybe I'm just getting old. But I'd rather just pay per month than having nonsense multiple currency forms and feeling bullied into paying potentially more than $15 a month on silly micro-transactions.  

 "wink-wink nudge-nudge, you could be doing this faster if you pay $5" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-22 06:55:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> beautiful
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-21 19:13:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because nintendo wouldn't and shouldn't give us the opportunity to fund anything, least of all being pokemon on a tv.
If they thought it was a good idea im pretty sure it would have happened 10 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-21 18:08:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 24 hour codes dont work with the free game promotion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-19 01:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> UB201's.  they wont have the metal pocket rivets, but they don't have pocket stitching.
If you dont mind pocket stitching then the levi's would work fine and probably be even a little cheaper.
http://theunbrandedbrand.com/collections/all/products/ub201-tapered-fit-indigo-selvedge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-15 19:07:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> steam
 @ entangel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-15 09:32:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 28k modem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-15 09:16:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> measure a pair of your own pants that you like the fit of, and compare.  Just buy the one that most closely matches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-15 09:12:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> making this post implies that you are still alive. in which case you should probably have enough time to finish downloading all of them.  How is this a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-13 09:25:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> in store as well.  Went in and picked up the faded twilight microdot today.
I believe it was off any full priced shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-13 09:19:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/malehairadvice

might be of more help, maybe a portrait as well as your 3/4th view picture would help as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-13 09:09:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tidy up/shave beard, remove earring.  If you want fashion advice don't post from shoulders up.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-08 18:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has anyone worn andrew marc shoes? never owned a pair of chelsea boots and figure if the price is right i might as well give em a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> anyone try Andrew Marc Chelsea boots? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-08 18:48:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-08 06:32:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they have a button bar at the top with a search box, and they have panels... same as most websites.
greenmangaming fits right in the middle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I miss Filene's Basement :( haha

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having a good time (vita) took a few hours before I was able to concentrate on my character with everything else going on. I still get lost from time to time, but its not too bad.
About 4 hours in myself, waiting to unlock multi-play.
absolutely recommend on vita, cant attest to ps3 but im sure its great as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-27 08:52:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention OCBD's might not work depending on what he does for a living.
absolutely plain tee's, maybe try out a colored denim chambray. (personally think its a bit more casual than an ocbd) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-27 06:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want the 5 panel style, but don't need the brand behind it check out the ASOS brand. They are around $20, I haven't had any experience with them but for that price i recon its worth a gamble.
http://us.asos.com/search/5-panel?hrd=1 q=5+panel
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-27 06:12:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they've been 35-50ish for years.  roughly the same price as a 5950 authentic fitted cap.
the price will vary dependent on brand, and no they probably arent worth 25% of the construction/material price.  How would a company, particularly small brands make money if they were closer in actual vs retail pricing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Former Blizzard, SOE, Relic devs form AAA online game company </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 18:58:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> er. f2p pacman runner. what has he become. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 10:03:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 09:58:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But we already lost Lincoln, JFK, and Hendrix... Wasn't that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 09:38:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fffff.... a lot... soz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 09:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Getting an awesome computer.... To play f2p games and minecraft.  You could save alot of money by buying a less awesome computer...

Real talk though, you could check out the stalker series.  Probably be able to pick them up for cheap, and the modding community is great.  It might not look great vanilla, but it will make a modern computer chug with some of the graphical overhauls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 06:09:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mine have been holding pretty strong, although I wouldn't have got em if it wasn't for $30 nordstrom rack deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-23 16:25:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.amazon.com/Madden-Mens-M-Gamer-Boat-Shoe/dp/B005MWN5C6
Got these last month, rarely take em off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-23 08:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 75% off everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-23 06:49:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> site looks real shady, anyone have any experience with em? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Arma III just keeping it real. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-11 18:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-09 18:53:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> people are really standing up for kanye, this blows my mind.

http://images.freshnessmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/nike-sportswear-kanye-west-air-yeezy-black-570x453.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-09 07:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont care how he dresses. Im guessing based upon the things he has designed in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 17:57:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because everything the man has ever done is tacky as fuck. He probably wanted to do a tiger print warp but touitou wouldnt let him go that far. Plus werent the air yeezies green and pink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 04:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pink and neon green tiger print weft inc. Gonna be more pointless than n f's gimmicky jeans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-02 19:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> steam summer sales are always tuesday, its always cut in the midweek madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 08:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cheers, exactly the sort of info I'm looking for :)  I'll def check it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 08:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not looking for a single $1000 item, I'm looking to go shopping in Paris with $1000 for clothes which I believe is fairly frugal.
I thought quite a bit on where to post it, and took a shot. But im guessing in /r/expensivemalefashion they would tell me i'm being unrealistic and frugal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 08:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because I'm not asking how to dress myself properly,  I'm asking for places to shop at under a budget. Perhaps local insight, if there are any French users. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Paris ~$1000 for clothes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 07:42:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anywhere I should check out, looking to get a few interesting key pieces.  I know I could easily spend way more than $1000 on clothes in Paris, and am looking to make it stretch as much as possible.
Normally I'd consider myself to dress in the grey area between street wear and high fashion.  APC's/naked and famouse/Jcrew/and all sorts of different boots.
Also am specifically looking for things that would be hard to come by in the US.  I'm in Boston, so average high fashion is readily available (barneys, saks, neiman, riccardi)  Maybe some interesting mid-range french brands. The best example I can think of would be Supreme NYC, not that I would normally wear supreme but when im in NYC I go there because its such a hassle to get supreme outside of nyc.
Sorry to ramble on, and thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 07:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.dsw.com/shoe/aston+grey+rockcastle+2+boot?prodId=280808 productRef=SEARCH

Sorry been away a few days, I'd recommend going into the retail store if you buy them.  Normally I wear a 12, and had to size down to 10.5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 17:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks for the input guys, and yes the left pair is navy blue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 11:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wore the same pair of apc's to work atleast 4 days a week for about a year.  The only reason I stopped was because they developed some noticeable holes, and I didnt want people to ask why I never changed my pants.
Granted I work in a factory, so im guessing this is much more acceptable than day to day office wear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 11:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "There are always the people who get a coat and they just look like pedo's."
priceless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 11:04:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> personally i'd go with a 5 panel cap if your gonna go with a cap at all.  Granted I guess it depends on your style.
HUF, Stussy, if your on a budget asos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> shoe advice, meeting the parents.. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 10:50:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meeting girls parents, normally this wouldn't frighten me but she's graduating and i'm going to be spending apparently a significant amount of time with them alone. (college, not highschool)
Its an outdoor graduation, and its gonna be about 85 degrees F.  So i'll be wearing dark slim chinos and either a jcrew popover, or ocbd.
narrowed it down to these 4 pairs. http://i.imgur.com/bzUNAPj.jpg 

Normally wear boots for work, so the rogue wingtips wont bother me in the heat if you think they would work well.

personally was leaning toward the left pair, but not sure if they aren't casual enough for the occasion.  Never really dealt with this graduating stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 09:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/CXMFzTr.jpg rockcastles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 09:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A tank that says mastermind shouldn't be labeled as a "mastermind tank" unless its a tank top made by mastermind.
change that. unless your targeting the legal knock-off grey area market demographic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 09:06:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> chukkas or desert boots maybe.  Normally I dont care for toms, but i think matched with that shirt something interesting could be made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-29 10:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean top notch celebs always wore high fashion, but fashion itself evolves over time. Rappers normally wore hood shit, there was alot of evisu and red monkey jeans. 
Streetwear itself started in the mid-late 70's/ early 80's.  brands like stussy and 10deep were specifically geared towards surfers.
Groups like Pharell and the clipse were the main reasons street wear blew up, they started wearing bape, supreme, and pharell started bbc.
I don't remember much more than that, its about when I got into clothing. Pharell came out in dem bapes and i was like I DONT KNOW WHAT THOSE ARE BUT I WANT THEM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-29 10:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there once was a time when streetwear wasn't mainstream.  These things go in waves. Give it 5 years and there will be something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-29 09:57:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you could also check out sites like gilt, myhabit, and jackthreads.  Depending on you're area find outlet stores, nordstrom rack, saks fifth off fifth, etc.
but yah a job is pretty key, and don't get discouraged.  The amount you make is never enough, same for most everybody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-29 07:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that second link is proper sketchy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-28 03:06:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're in the north-east you could check out barneys new york, and the tannery in Boston.  There's probably more, but those i'm 100% of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-21 17:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pinroll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-16 19:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "reputable tailors in your city"?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-16 18:19:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> great idea for a thread, but maybe change the title. A little misleading. But yah hope this comes through. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-16 18:17:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks, yah im hoping they stretch a bit. not as much as my past experience with apc. but they are a tad bit tighter than i'd normally wear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-16 18:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for retail price they are better than I expected, and for sub $100 they far exceed my expectations.  and thanks! might shorten em a little, but figured i'd give big ass cuffs a shot.  mixed opinions on reddit and in real life haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-16 18:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sweet, i was a little worried. out of the box they are one of the roughest pairs ive had.  was expecting the twill to be much lighter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-16 18:11:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> meh, they are for the ALS association. best friends dad just got diagnosed with it. made a donation and figured i'd wear the bracelets.  Normally i'd agree, but yah. circumstances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> N F skinny guy broken twill (day 1 fit pics) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-16 08:46:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/tzmh8#0
Told myself I'd never get a pair.  Always thought I was too old for n f, thought their label was too tacky, and they had way too many gimmicks.  Found the skinny guys on karmaloop for ~$70 and figured i might as well give em a shot, seeing as how my apcs were about ready to become retired.
Sorry for the grainy quality, decent camera was too far away, and ms paint cropping.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-11 06:48:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes they do, But if you only wear them on the weekends then just don't wash them at all.  Not because your a denim head, but because you don't want them to fade.  Hang em up and spray febreze on them every sunday night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-02 06:30:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only way their customer service could be better is if they would ship their offices to Boston so I could visit. ;)
cant wait for my kickstarter UH's and launch slims as well :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-18 19:24:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks like monster hunter 3, and only showed more than 4 people on screen in a brief clip at the very end.  
I am very excited if it happens, but something screams skeptical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 18:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Selvedge certainly does have to do with longevity. the extra stitching goes throughout making the denim itself more dense and durable.  It just happens to also ensure the edge of the denim doesn't fray (finishing edge).
realistically if your levis have lasted years then I would expect apcs to be the same, it all depends on how hard you wear them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 19:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe the originals should be shipping this month (end of last month), and other fabrics will be shipping over the next 2 months.  Personally awaiting the Super heavy's which are slated for may shipment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-18 01:40:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> like Athosicus said... pretty much just hurdles, and high jump. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'll raise your X in 1 game cart. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-17 21:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-17 15:42:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> indigo paint. fixem' right up... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-17 15:38:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "curvy", "friction from walking" lol... Try a denim skirt... not much friction there... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-14 03:48:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> keys on belt loop, everything else in shirt pockets.  If you don't have shirt pockets, then make shirt pockets.  Oh and put your eraser in the backpack, don't need dem shirts be disappearing up infront da honnies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-14 03:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 30 isn't that old, and you can still pull off streetwear without looking weird.
Streetwear unlike most sects of fashion has a huge range, spanning from skater to hip-hop to high fashion esque.  Sure a 30 year old man might not want to wear a pink camo bape hoodie, and ballin ass evisu jeans.  That would look pretty weird.  
Essentially what i'm getting at is just toning down a little bit.  Maybe pick up some 501's or other straight leg jeans, somewhere between baggy and slim.  Personally i'm even a fan of krew chinos if you want to go with a slightly more mature look.
Rather than wearing hoodies every day you could try out some LRG or mishka button ups.  Even just pick up some plain 'ole crewnecks. 
Replacing a whole sneaker rotation I dont see as being a problem, depending on your line of work.  Most grown men wear sneakers now adays.  Plus buying lots of shoes can get expensive.  But if you have the cash maybe check out some clarks desert boots.  They are more "adult" than sneakers in general, yet still look very young and hip.

Sorry to drone on, but i'm 27 and went through the same thing a few months ago.  I wore strictly streetwear for 5+ years, and am trying to move in a more mature direction.  But you always can mix in a few street staples to make a look come through.
gluck mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-14 03:24:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If streetwear is just a trend then its a long lived trend.... I mean Stussy, 10deep, and vans alone have been around for 25-30 years individually.  Sure in the last 5 years the "streetwear" market has grown substantially, and I see that slowing down.  Imo it has stood the test of time, and it will always have a place in the fashion industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-13 23:19:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ACK, was ~4:00 am before work. I done goofed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Emo guy Sebastion. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-13 11:01:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-27 05:17:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yah dishonored was really good.  Its just strange that these developers are all like, "need a name".  "OH I KNOW, lets pick something silly that starts with a C!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-27 05:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dead space 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> all these characters with C names are really getting to me. all of them. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-26 23:07:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-26 17:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> boots, and general wear should do the trick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-26 17:44:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aston Grey Rockcastle's.  Got em at DSW, I'd try and get into a DSW and try em on if you're thinking about buying.  They run huge, I had to size down 1.5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-26 17:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks, I sized 1 down.  Tried on 2 sizes down, and was really paranoid about crotch blow before they got a chance to stretch.  They are a little too big on my waist now, so i just wear an undershirt and tuck it in + belt.

Im on the same boat. Thinking of trying japan blue, or 3sixteen.  They seem to be the most comparable in value/quality.  Also hanging in to see if Gustin releases info on their 18.4oz selvedge indigo they talked about on here.  Although i'm not in a huge rush, still loving my apc's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-26 11:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not sure exactly to be honest.  I spill chemicals on them at work from time to time, along with general wear and tear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-26 10:48:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I washed them once, and I work in a factory where I wear them daily. Im guessing thats why I have significant wear around my thighs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-26 06:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yea, essentially taking the sides in.  Giving the body a more flattering look.
Although even that might be tricky considering the pocket placement is really close to the side seam.  But i'm no tailor so it could be a non-issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-26 06:19:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> be wary of breaking them in then deciding you want them hemmed.  Im guessing you meant try them on, and make up your mind. You just dont wanna start getting fades then make the fades look unnatural by hemming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-26 06:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it was an in the moment type picture
http://imgur.com/a/wiwvn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In response to raleigh model pic. apc ns 6months, 1 wash. factory worn daily. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-26 04:08:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-26 03:27:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not an expert, but the shoulders and arm holes look too big.  Probably not worth tailoring costs.  You could get it tapered, and maybe try it with a casual look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-25 02:12:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good lookin out, but yahh. Boston to SF is a long ways to go for a shirt. :(  Although I could deal with not being in -3 degree weather right now. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-25 01:02:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks for the quick response. Ya i'm pretty skinny. ~6'/150lbs, So I will probably hold out.  My local shops havn't gotten them in yet, i'm hoping they do eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-25 00:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mainly has anyone tried the fit. I need slim shirts, and they don't seem to make it in slim.
elbow honeycombs would be killer I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> anyone have any experience? (J.crew - Selvedge indigo denim shirt) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-25 00:43:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-22 11:17:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> planetside 2... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-21 10:55:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> give it 15-40 wears, they will size up to about a ~36.  From the waist to the bottom of your knees will stretch substantially.  So don't fret if they feel too tight.  If you like the tight look maybe check out the ns petit slims.  Can't say much for rescues, never owned a pair.
Also be careful until they do stretch.  Dont wanna blow the crotch out on a fresh pair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-17 06:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> scr8 up out da han dynasty? L Bu'in it an all dat? Teachin dem numbers? word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-17 06:23:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the type on back is done beautifully. stencil, and spray? or by hand/ruler? Either way I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-14 18:31:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my thoughts exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> found this gem in the back of my bookshelf. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-14 18:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> steam box/big picture. whats the point? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-09 10:31:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am and have always been primarily a PC gamer, and I love steam for what it is.  I just want to get other peoples opinions on what the big deal is with steam box/big picture mode.
I've had a living-room computer since the x800AIW card, which at the time was a really niche market.  But seriously. Most budget computers have hdmi out, and will be able to run more games and at a better quality than the "steambox".  Atleast with the given specs as of now, not to mention at a fraction of the cost.
A computer with HDMI out will also let you run your choice of OS whilst regular old steam at the same time.  The big picture mode web browser seems really clunky. The library section is also horrible when you have a descent sized game collection.
The lan party aspect of the steam box is intriguing, but in the same light for ~$1000 you could get a solid m-atx gaming rig with a lan case.  It wouldnt be as small, but atleast it could run AAA games decently.  Plus the steam box is marketed as a console killer, hence nix lan parties unless you are replacing your big computer with a small computer an a big TV.
Not trying to be a hater, just genuinely interested in other peoples opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-09 06:30:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I foresee a horrible ending.. . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-03 09:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> legend of grimrock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-12 15:26:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> install a seatbelt on your racing simulator.  
Don't wear your seatbelt.
Damn thats realistic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-10-30 17:59:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you only have $10 to spend why not DS 1 2. most bang for your buck atleast.
havnt played any fear since the original, but either dead space game is better than rage or dead rising 2 imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-12 10:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm gonna brag about all these services I have, and i'm still gonna beg for ms points..
And how is this game related? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-30 10:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The World Ends With You. is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-29 06:43:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thx, real not repost.  They are done and belong to my friend though. Just thought /r/gaming might like too see :)
http://imgur.com/usTg2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In anticipation of "Jet Set Radio HD" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-29 02:59:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-26 19:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Terry Crews is pissed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-22 07:20:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thx was wondering this myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-18 10:11:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dark Souls pre-purchase.  I work hard for the money I use to buy games.  Therefore I buy games I deem very worthy of my money.  I feel dark souls would be worth my money, although with speculation of it being a crumby port job I'm not sure if I can swing it with my budget.
Im not sure if you can gift pre-purchases, either way I appreciate what you're doing. Great morale boost for the community as a whole :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-18 09:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :D Yah I stumbled across it there when I was looking for the same case myself.  Great case, great price, and ncix has great service/fast shipping.  Hope you enjoy
PS Depending on what aftermarket cooler you go with make sure you check the depth specs. my Cooler master 212 evo has about a quarter/eighth inch of clearance from the case side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-17 19:15:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NCIX sells kits for around 20 bucks with a different colored logo/mesh.
http://ncix.com/products/?sku=74187 vpn=GRLM manufacture=Bundle%20Deals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-16 19:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best indie pack yet, imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-16 08:28:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From what I understand they do stay forever.  Although individual server admins have the power to wipe their servers at any given point.  Essentially clear the world and start fresh.  Mainly wipes happen if the world gets over encumbered by tents/barbed wire/sandbags/etc, and or hacks.  So there isn't exactly periodic flashes, and technically given really bad luck your tent could be wiped the next day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-14 20:06:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> right on, didn't mean to cause a stir.  Thanks for clearing that up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-14 19:21:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> .. Ys origin's normal price is 11.99, not 19.99.  Flash deal price should be like ~5..  Bare in mind I just woke up and could be not thinking straight.
http://i.imgur.com/MmTvW.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>