<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5807</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Individuals Who Believe in the Paranormal Develop More Causal Illusions than Nonbelievers in the Laboratory </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:32:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> People who claim to be experts in a topic are more likely to fall for made up facts on that topic. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 19:37:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Analysis shows that pesticide residues in food are at levels far below those that would pose any health concern. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Failure to attain a high school degree is associated with a higher risk of premature death. The researchers suggest that a lack of education leads to the adoption of unhealthy behaviors. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 21:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Top scientists are reporting signs of life on comet 67P. "I am here to make a prediction: this claim will vanish, never to be heard from again." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:58:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers have found the first evidence for STDs in honeybees. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:06:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pre-crastination: Why the opposite of procrastination can be just as bad. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:56:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> KFC Plagued By Urban Legends Fueled by Psychology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:25:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Primatologists have recorded the first spontaneous case of a chimpanzee drumming in a way that resembles music. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 15:30:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Online communication as a window to conspiracist worldviews </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:54:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is there a limit to temperature? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:17:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers envision Earth as a giant computer, determine its storage capacity and power by calculating the total amount of DNA and the overall rate of DNA transcription. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:47:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 21:57:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure I'm buying Kate Mara as Johanssen. Hopefully she'll prove me wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Creationism can be used in science classes to teach the scientific method. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 21:54:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Creationism Belongs in Science Class: A professor teaches creationism in her classes in order to have students debunk it with the scientific method. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 21:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Insect Mating Behavior Has Lessons for Drones </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 01:15:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 21:43:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Link to journal article: http://journals.aps.org/prl/abstract/10.1103/PhysRevLett.114.215001 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists move one step closer to mimicking gamma-ray bursts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 21:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New discovery could lead to sunscreen in pill form. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 04:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Study links infections to a decrease in cognitive ability. The researchers found that the more times a subject was hospitalized for an infection throughout his life, the lower he scored on a test of cognitive ability. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:34:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:29:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry! I've posted a link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:28:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Link to Study: http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate2631.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Exposure of US population to extreme heat could quadruple by mid-century </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:37:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There's a particle accelerator in the Louvre. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:13:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New analysis finds that if the world built nuclear power at a similar rate to Sweden or France, all fossil fuel electricity could be displaced in 25-34 years, reducing carbon emissions by half. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:14:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First-born siblings show better second language skills than later born siblings </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:20:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that flossing is not supported by scientific evidence. It offers little to no benefits over daily toothbrushing alone. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Computer scientists find that 1980 music had the lowest stylistic diversity of any other decade. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:05:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Targeted antibiotic treatment plans could be used to reduce antibiotic resistant genotypes in bacteria. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 01:57:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For the first time, astronomers have detected visible light directly from an exoplanet. The effort is a proof of concept for a new way to detect exoplanets. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:22:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Review finds that intake of vitamin and mineral supplements are generally associated with an increased risk of cancer and heart disease. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 17:31:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chimpanzees from a troop in Senegal make and use spears. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:42:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have captured the first MRI video of a joint cracking, finally resolving that the "pop" is caused by a bubble forming in the joint's synovial fluid. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Smiling makes you look older. Smiling people were perceived as 1-2 years older than when they had a neutral expression. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 15:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 07:01:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bottled water is one of those uniquely American enterprises that's a mx of marketing genius and questionably legal tactics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A study of university faculty members finds that they are more likely to hire a woman over a man as an assistant professor in engineering, psychology, or biology by a margin of 2 to 1. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 21:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If marijuana is a schedule 1 drug, caffeine should definitely be one, too. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 04:48:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New study finds an association between eating out at restaurants and high blood pressure. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 00:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Science Behind the Perfect French Fry </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 01:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But graphene glitter. GRAPHENE glitter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers take another step toward functional nanobots. They outfitted bacterial spores with tiny flecks of graphene armor capable of activating electrodes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 15:41:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> After using search engines, people overestimate their ability to explain ideas. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We Should Have a Better Condom by Now. Heres Why We Dont. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:01:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fast food is just as effective as exercise supplements at helping athletes recover after a workout. In a study, there were no differences in muscle glycogen levels and subsequent performance. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 15:37:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A glimpse inside a macroscopic quantum state: Researchers detect particle entanglement in a beam of squeezed light </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 00:47:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Simple Messages Help Set the Record Straight about Scientific Agreement on Human-Caused Climate Change: The Results of Two Experiments </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 04:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Neurofeedback training could potentially be used as a treatment for criminal psychopaths. In a new study, psychopaths who used it experienced reductions in aggression and impulsivity. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 14:43:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Contrary to popular belief that regular pornography use can give men erectile dysfunction in partner situations, a new study finds no link between the two. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists make breakthrough in understanding how to control intense heat bursts in fusion experiments </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:43:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in 2005 a thirty-foot-high trash avalanche at a Landfill in Indonesia killed 143 people and destroyed 71 houses. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> That's not God you just spoke to; it was a dream. "All humans are endowed with brains innately primed to daily generate god concepts in dreaming." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 15:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers have used stem cells to create custom red blood cells tailored to individual patients. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-09 21:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Psychology retractions have quadrupled since 1989 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-09 04:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A quantum effect helps protect plants during photosynthesis. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 17:47:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Intimate partners with low self-esteem stay in unhappy relationships </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 20:09:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-25 21:02:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is clearly satire, just to make that fact plain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Terrible, Horrifying, Painful Truth About All Those Corporate Scientist   Science Writer Shills </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-25 21:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Computer games can be used to watch for early signs of cognitive decline in the elderly. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-25 03:25:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Incarceration has little effect on crime rates. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-14 05:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When scientific findings challenge a person's social identity, they are more likely to try to attack or discredit the science. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 16:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Cannabis use in patients with a psychotic disorder has a long-lasting negative effect on illness outcome, particularly when persistent. Treatment should focus on discouraging cannabis use. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-07 01:11:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Athletic performance fluctuates based on circadian rhythms. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 02:47:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Study finds that NFL players who started football before the age of 12 are more likely to have thinking and memory problems as adults, regardless of the time they actually spent playing. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 18:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> On the Existence of Low-Mass Dark Matter and its Direct Detection </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 04:51:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is glass a true solid? New research suggests it is. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 19:31:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chewing a piece of gum removes up to 100 million bacteria from your mouth, a similar amount to flossing. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 19:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If models bear out, the average child of the next generation will live for over 100 years. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-21 20:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new study shows that the incidence of lung cancer is lower at higher elevations. "For every 1,000 m rise in elevation, lung cancer incidence decreased by 7.23 cases per 100,000 individuals." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-16 00:40:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-15 21:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good to see Hai exercising; I've been worried about his health. Hopefully Balls will get him to hit the weights, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A review finds that prison inmates suffer from deficits in executive cognitive functions. The researchers suggest that the prison environment may deteriorate those functions, potentially making inmates more prone to future criminality. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-15 21:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why do we breathe oxygen and not some other gas? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-14 17:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You Have More Musical Talent Than You Think. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 20:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cold is contagious: In a new study, when subjects looked at someone dipping their hands into ice water, their own hands actually grew colder. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 23:31:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fast-food consumption in children linked to poorer academic outcomes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 21:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NASA Study Proposes Airships, Cloud Cities for Venus Exploration </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-20 02:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Most Radioactive Places on Earth </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 21:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Biggest Junk Science of 2014. A familiar face to /r/skeptic earned the top spot. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 17:53:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 10 Ways That Brain Myths Are Harmful </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 18:55:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For the first time, researchers have tallied the number of microorganisms that Americans unintentionally consume every day. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 17:35:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Analysis of comet water from the Rosetta mission contradicts the theory that water on Earth had a cometary origin. Instead it's now more likely that Earth got its water from asteroids. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 17:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 19:13:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Original for good measure! 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4sT99Y4AnmA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 19:10:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello, my baby. Hello, my honey. Hello, my ragtime gal.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4sT99Y4AnmA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How One Woman's Discovery Shook the Foundations of Geology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 19:09:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "83% of the Psychology/Education articles with four or more experiments that were published in Science (20052012) have an excess of success, which suggests that their results are too good to be true." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-06 01:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A study conducted in Chicago found that giving disadvantaged, minority youths 8-week summer jobs reduced their violent crime rates compared to controls by 43% over a year after the program ended. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-04 20:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hype around cannabis as a treatment for cancer is undeserved </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 04:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have used carbonate to boost silver's antimicrobial activity 1000x. The change could make it much easier to spread clean drinking water throughout the third world. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-26 22:57:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obesity-attributable absenteeism among US workers costs the nation more than $8 billion annually </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 00:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists get the first, up-close look at what a nuclear meltdown looks like. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-21 19:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Many Possible Melodies Are There? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-21 18:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 6 Tests for Evaluating Conspiracy Theories </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 16:20:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists switch off molecule that grows new blood vessels for prostate cancer cells, effectively halting the spread of tumors. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As many as half of the stars in the universe may be outside galaxies, according to a new study. These previously unknown stars were likely ejected from their home galaxies during galaxy collisions. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 20:11:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL Before the widespread use of artificial light, most people didn't sleep in a single block. Instead, they likely went to bed shortly after dusk, slept for four or five hours, awakened for an hour or two, then would go back to sleep until sunrise. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 00:30:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 18:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it's not. The article is from Scientific Reports, which is open-access. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Effectiveness of the Electronic Cigarette on Smoking Reduction: "Remarkable eight-month reductions in, or complete abstinence from tobacco smoking was achieved with the e-cig in almost half (44%) of the participants." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 18:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can We Predict the Unpredictable? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 18:04:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Austrian Gaming Expert Who Has a Collection of 40,000 Video Games </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 03:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A win for science and the public! "More than half of all peer-reviewed research articles published from 2007 to 2012 are now free to download." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-23 17:16:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ego depletion fails to replicate in a new study. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-23 17:13:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL humans usually get the urge to pee when the bladder is just 1/3 full. But in zero gravity, the urge doesn't kick in till the bladder is almost completely full. When John Glenn orbited the Earth, his only urination was 27 ounces, seven ounces more than the capacity of the avg human bladder. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 02:42:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Expensive Engagement Rings Linked to Higher Divorce Rates </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:47:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Neil deGrasse Tyson was recently asked whether or not he believes in God. Here's his answer. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 22:41:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reading the Daily Mail causes mental judgement problems and may give you cancer. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 22:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Viruses convert their DNA from solid to liquid form in order to infect cells. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 21:58:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> States with More Religious or Conservative Populations Search More for Sexual Content on Google </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 20:01:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 22:36:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry. Missed that earlier one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The video game Portal 2 improves cognitive skills more than the "brain-training" app Lumosity. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 18:58:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Do People Drink Shampoo? Our brains may be getting fooled. Viewing non-food products with packaging that imitates food products elicits the same brain patterns associated with viewing or tasting appetizing foods. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 22:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Couples who met online three times more likely to divorce </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-27 06:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Large study gets the down and dirty on dating and hooking-up in college. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 20:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Titillating Science of Sexsomnia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 22:38:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Well-Loved Music Robustly Relieves Pain: A Randomized, Controlled Trial </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 17:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:24:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should also monitor your mental health status. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Study finds plants are able to germinate and grow with no added nutrients in simulated Mars and lunar soils. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 20:53:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drink Responsibly Messages in Alcohol Ads Promote Products, Not Public Health </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 04:42:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Psychology Behind Why It's So Hard to Change the Toilet Paper Roll </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 15:58:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Highlights from 25 Years of Cold Fusion Research </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-30 05:39:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Power of Two: Why Sharing Is Better </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 18:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> People Think Experiences Bring Happiness, Still Opt For Things </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-25 03:03:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 01:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's true. . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-21 21:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That collection is... beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-21 21:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The "no shit" comments are certainly warranted. But this fact needs to be reiterated and supported by analytical measurements. It's the only way FIFA will finally get their heads out of their asses and make a change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new analysis finds that Qatar's summer weather will not be "appropriate" for World Cup fans. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-21 19:10:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nurses who are motivated primarily by the desire to help others are more likely to burn out. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-21 16:10:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 17:16:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the link to the paper referenced in the article:

http://www.daysyn.com/Morrot.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The original study that called out wine tasting as BS also revealed a fascinating insight into human perception. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 17:15:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sharkageddon may be the worst Shark Week show *ever* </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 20:46:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 8,000-year-old mutation key to human life at high altitudes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-17 20:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An Atheists Guide to Spirituality </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-15 17:12:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NASA scientists have identified the first interstellar dust particles brought back to earth. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 20:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Astronomers recently discovered a faint, mysterious signal. They theorize that it could be a dark matter particle, the sterile neutrino. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 03:44:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What Would Aliens Actually Look Like? Seven Experts Respond. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 01:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 01:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard this incredible story first on This American Life. Here's the [link](http://www.thisamericanlife.org/radio-archives/episode/522/tarred-and-feathered?act=2#play) for anyone who'd rather listen than read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New study finds that antiperspirant deodorants alter your armpit bacteria and may actually worsen body odor as a result. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-11 18:04:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Physicists create water tractor beam </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-10 23:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When Neil deGrasse Tyson was asked for his thoughts on GMO foods, he responded with this brilliant answer. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 05:52:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For a "Boring Billion" years of Earth's history, evolution basically stopped and life consisted of slime. 3 recent studies try to explain why. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 15:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Stanford researchers achieve a stable lithium anode, a tremendous advance in battery technology. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 00:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How should men pee? Study examines the "urodynamics" of sitting versus standing. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 21:21:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 30% of U.S. clinical trials do not have their results publicly disclosed within four years. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 17:08:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is the vehicle that astronauts will use on Mars. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-19 01:18:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tractor Beam Created Using Water Waves </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 18:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientific review of randomized, controlled studies finds that weight loss from low-carb diets is almost entirely from caloric restriction. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-14 22:40:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A first direct glimpse of photosynthesis in action. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-14 02:46:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Large study finds organic produce contains significantly higher levels of antioxidants than conventional produce, contrary to prior research. But there may be methodological flaws and selection bias. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 03:12:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Environmentalists Almost Killed My Friend </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-10 17:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does the Mind Affect Quantum Mechanics? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-10 16:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Many zoos have elephants paint as an "enrichment" activity and often sell the art to the public. But a new study finds little evidence that painting reduces stress behaviors or benefits the animals. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-10 16:13:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-07 15:43:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So true. He has that big (mostly) liberal blind spot on GMOs and vaccines. I watch his show every week and bite my tongue when he goes on one of those rants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Comedy vs. Anti-Science: Comedians are using humor to combat everything from climate denial to anti-vaccine BS. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-07 03:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New study finds that most people don't enjoy sitting and thinking quietly by themselves. Some actually prefer receiving electric shocks. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-03 20:18:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-03 20:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The full scene is much longer. The build-up is like 3-4 minutes. It's perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-02 17:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me, probably The Ring.

One of the best constructed horror scenes came from [Exorcist III](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zH8ynu0jRvY), however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New study finds that half of pet cats in Europe are infested with a parasite. Parasites were most prevalent on cats in Italy. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-02 17:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> People Who Wear Glasses Really Are Smarter </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-30 04:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3 big problems with the new paper showing that pesticides are linked to autism. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-27 17:08:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Casual sex is commonly considered negative, but a new study shows that amongst people who like it, casual sex is linked to higher self-esteem and life satisfaction as well as lower depression and anxiety. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-20 21:17:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 10 Reasons Why You Can't Live Without a Particle Accelerator </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-13 22:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Doses of the hormone oxytocin cause old rats to regenerate muscle at levels comparable to young ones. Researchers suggest oxytocin could be used to prevent age-related muscle loss in humans. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 17:26:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One out of every eight American children are maltreated by the time they are 18, not one in 100, as has previously been reported. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-09 22:29:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The first vertebrate sexual organs evolved as an extra pair of legs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-09 05:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NASA funds feasibility studies for 12 futuristic proposals, including a submarine to explore the methane lakes of Titan. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-07 03:27:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 8 Common Health Tips That Aren't Supported by Scientific Evidence </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-05 18:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Even if you travel at the speed of light, there are some galaxies you can never reach. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-04 22:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers identify a new type of procrastination: sleep procrastination. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-04 15:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Astronomers Find a New Type of Planet: The "Mega-Earth" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-02 19:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists can alter primates' preferences by stimulating the ventral tegmental area of their brains. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-29 22:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Learning Early in Life May Help Keep Brain Cells Alive," new study in young rats suggests. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-27 23:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New review article concludes that there really wasn't anything anatomically special about Einstein's brain. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-27 21:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chemists find a way to turn a troubling contaminant into a harmless sugar. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-24 05:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "How did the Universe begin?" A beautiful answer to a complex question. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-24 03:58:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Science writer Peter Gwynne wrote the now-famous global cooling article in Newsweek in 1975. He's now urging people to stop citing it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-23 00:14:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-21 05:55:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like it could be a quality movie, but I don't think I'll never be able to accept Michael C. Hall as any character but Dexter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drunk fish convince sober ones to follow them around. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 08:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-19 06:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for letting me know. Looks like it was published in Nature Photonics.

Link from the bottom of the article:

http://www.nature.com/nphoton/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nphoton.2014.95.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists discover how to turn light into matter after 80-year quest </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-18 21:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-14 18:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adorable. I wonder if she also stepped around Mrs. Peabody's azaleas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gluten intolerance may not exist: A double-blinded, placebo-controlled study and a scientific review find insufficient evidence to support non-celiac gluten sensitivity. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-14 15:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Archaeologists think they've found the wreck of Christopher Columbus' flagship, the Santa Maria. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-13 15:57:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers induce lucid dreaming in subjects by applying electrical current to their brains. The technique could potentially be adapted to allow PTSD sufferers to control frequent nightmares. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-12 15:35:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New research explains why Antarctica is not warming as much as the other continents. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-11 21:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New species of metal-eating plant discovered in the Philippines </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-10 00:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new analysis in PLoS ONE finds that female genitalia in the animal kingdom are massively understudied, which likely stems from aged sexual stereotypes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 16:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers image the spread of pesticides in snails and shrimp in order to understand how they are affecting these aquatic species. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 18:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Public science funding generates substantial returns to the private sector, a new report claims. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-07 01:54:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are You Really Gluten-Intolerant? Maybe Not. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-06 17:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chiropractors' spine-chilling warnings about computers, phones and pancakes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-02 20:20:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A review of archaeological records shows that Neanderthals were just as advanced as humans, making it increasingly likely that they were assimilated into our species through interbreeding, not driven to extinction. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-30 23:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New study shows the first functional replacement of muscle tissue in humans. Surgeons implanted extracellular matrix derived from pig bladder into wounds. Over time, muscle grew around it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-30 23:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have built an 'off switch' for the brain. Their technique uses light sensitive proteins to shut down neurons. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-28 16:29:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Birds in areas with high radiation contamination around Chernobyl produce more antioxidants. It's the first known example of wild animals adapting to chronic radiation exposure. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-25 20:59:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-23 01:04:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see your point and raise you a "shit ton."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have long wondered why our atmosphere has so little of the noble gas Xenon. They've just found a whole bunch of it in Earth's core. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-22 21:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Arecibo Observatory Detects Mysterious, Energetic Radio Burst </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-21 17:33:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-21 16:36:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks like the link is at the bottom of the article: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature13027.html

The research is in Nature, so it's paywalled, obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A possible cure for ebola virus infection has been discovered. A molecule called BCX4430 rescued 17 of 18 monkeys after they were infected with the virus. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-21 15:40:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Another reason not to use Apple Maps... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-21 02:13:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-19 23:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure thing! Sorry, I didn't read the new rules. Whoops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ten things you might not know about particle accelerators </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-19 17:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Would You Have Sex with a Total Stranger? An Inside Look at the Study That Found Out. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-19 15:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have shown they can rapidly produce large quantities of graphene using a bath of inorganic salts and an electric current. It's a step towards mass production of the wonder material. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-19 15:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Intravenously Administered Ketamine Shown to Reduce Symptoms of Chronic Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-18 21:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cannabis use is quantitatively associated with nucleus accumbens and amygdala abnormalities in young adult recreational users. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-18 21:08:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Astronomers Find First Earth-Sized Exoplanet in Habitable Zone </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 20:03:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Men's beard fashions may be guided by Darwinian selection. Both beards and clean-shaven faces become more appealing when they are rare. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 18:25:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Positron emission tomography, a type of brain scan, could help predict if patients will wake from a vegetative state. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 03:32:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> By tracking brain activity when an animal stops to look around its environment, neuroscientists at Johns Hopkins University believe they can mark the birth of a memory. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-14 23:06:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For a Happy Marriage, Stay Well Fed: Low blood glucose levels correlate to greater levels of aggression and anger between spouses. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-14 21:23:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Two research teams have unveiled a quantum-information analogue of the transistor, a major step towards the development of practical quantum computers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-12 04:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If he looks stupid, he probably is: In a new study, both males and females were able to accurately evaluate the intelligence of men simply by viewing photos of their faces. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-11 16:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Positive Association of Video Game Playing with Left Frontal Cortical Thickness in Adolescents </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-10 23:54:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 69% of respondents support extending disability protections to obese individuals, according to a new survey. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-10 20:08:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New study reveals the power and scale of Earth's cataclysmic collision with a 30-mile-wide object some 3.26 billion years ago. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-09 19:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 10 of the Greatest Myths in Psychology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-07 16:34:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new study highlights that people are often mistaken in how spending our money might benefit our lives. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-07 04:36:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New study identifies key cells in touch sensation and gleans how these cells, located just beneath the skin surface, enable us to feel fine details and textures. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-07 01:40:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientist finds the worst places to get stung by a bee by experimenting on himself. In order, it's the nostril, lip, and penis. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-05 16:18:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-05 16:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seemed to me like the author did a decent job of summing up the research and then applying a critical, skeptical mindset to the results, which any decent science journalist should do.

Any scientific research is limited in scope in some fashion, but the point of comparing a one-off study like this to prior research is to give perspective. Sure, maybe the prior research had some limitations, but a whole lot of it also seemed to have reached the opposite conclusion as the current study, which is very important to know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New study finds that the benefits of infant male circumcision to health exceed the risks by over 100 to 1. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-05 05:23:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are The Mafia Psychopaths? A new study finds that members of Cosa Nostra in Italy have lower psychopathic traits than other criminals. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-04 21:41:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The study that found a vegetarian diet to be associated with poorer health has a "host of inescapable limitations" and goes against prior evidence. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-04 18:36:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Eating harder foods leads to a 13% reduction in caloric intake. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-03 22:10:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> CrossFit Almost Definitely Won't Kill You </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-02 16:44:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Well this is intriguing: DARPA is launching a biotechnology office. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-02 15:53:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists announce a new theory on why zebras have stripes. Zebras have them to prevent bites from flies, not predation by lions. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-01 17:35:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Health Check: four myths about vitamin supplements </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-31 20:04:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Video Gaming Doesn't Replace Player Social Lives, It Expands Them </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 19:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MIT Engineers design "living materials," which combine bacterial cells with nonliving elements that can conduct electricity or emit light </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-23 23:30:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gravitational waves explained with a towel and an apple </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-20 05:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is the best explainer I've read on the discovery of gravitational waves from moments after the Big Bang. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-18 16:27:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MIT researchers have created a "bionic" plant by augmenting it with nanomaterials. The plant can now capture 30% more light energy. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-17 14:48:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The planet Mercury has been shrinking ever since it formed roughly 4.6 billion years ago. A new report finds that its radius has shrunk by as much as 7 kilometers. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-16 20:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Study highlights the prospect that global civilization could collapse in coming decades due to unsustainable resource exploitation and increasingly unequal wealth distribution. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-15 04:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reduced-Gliadin Wheat Bread: An Alternative to the Gluten-Free Diet for Consumers Suffering Gluten-Related Pathologies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-15 00:07:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A team of researchers has identified multiple genes linked to musical aptitude, providing further evidence that musical ability is heritable. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 14:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Ross Sea, a major, biologically productive Antarctic ecosystem, "clearly will be extensively modified by future climate change" in the coming decades. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 06:05:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Changes in the suns energy output may have led to marked natural climate change in Europe over the last 1000 years. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-11 23:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A research team has discovered a group of molecules in the blood that can predict with 90% accuracy whether older people will develop Alzheimer's over the course of 2 to 3 years. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-10 00:29:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-07 16:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The results of this study really aren't surprising. If teens start using nicotine before adulthood, they're more likely to crave nicotine throughout their lives. Prior research has demonstrated that brain development is altered with nicotine use. 

A major limitation of the study to keep in mind: "The studys cross-sectional nature didnt allow the researchers to identify whether most youths initiated with conventional cigarettes or e-cigarettes."

That's a pretty big drawback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Male fruit flies restricted to monogamy show reduced cognitive and learning abilities. "Sexual competition may drive the evolution of intelligence..." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-07 15:56:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-07 06:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fooled a lot of people:

"That is so dope but did you filter that or something? Looks almost too good haha"

"Sweet car man, New York?"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A 28-square-kilometer living coral reef has been found in the coastal waters of Iraq. Until now, it wasn't thought that Iraq's waters could support a reef. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-06 19:39:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-06 18:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> People who copy their friend's drinking behaviour will deny that their decision has been influenced, researchers at the University of Liverpool have shown. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-05 06:14:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have discovered a 30,000-year-old virus in the Siberian permafrost. It's one of three viruses that are as large as bacteria and it's still infectious. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-03 21:39:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Physicists have measured how the surfaces of glassy materials flow like a liquid, even when they should be solid. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-03 16:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-01 00:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Taco Bell... breakfast, lunch, and dinner.

But in all honesty, [this](http://www.gastro.org/patient-center/digestive-conditions/gas-in-the-digestive-tract#Foods%20 %20Gas) guide from the American Gastroenterological Association lists foods like cauliflower, brussels sprouts, dried beans, broccoli, cabbage, bran, dairy, and fructose. Sounds like a lot of vegetarian diets are probably high-flatulogenic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-28 21:05:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're right to be skeptical. The picture the article paints is somewhat bleak. But there's a tinge of hopefulness at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The New Yorker goes behind the scenes at ITER, the international fusion reactor being built in France. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-28 18:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In two new papers, researchers correlated three types of gut bacteria with the frequency of "anal gas evacuations" and found that a "low-flatulogenic" diet can reduce farting by up to 54%. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-28 16:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NASA's Kepler mission has announced the discovery of 715 new planets, doubling the exoplanet count. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-28 04:36:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Since most of the gases our body and gut bacteria produce are lighter than air, do you weigh less if you're incredibly bloated? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-27 18:55:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Adverse psychological side-effects of anti-depressants are more widespread than is commonly thought. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-27 17:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have discovered what created a 6 million-year-old fossilized whale graveyard. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-26 01:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-24 22:58:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Studies like these prompt a lot of boneheaded, insensitive comments, which attract the ~~sharks~~ amazing and awesome mods. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new study links believing in hell, and perhaps even thinking about it, with lower levels of happiness and satisfaction in life. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-24 18:48:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The people who are "disengaged" from science are the most likely to think that it creates more problems than it solves and that we should depend more on faith. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-24 18:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New data confirms that Earths crust first formed at least 4.4 billion years ago, strengthening the theory of a cool early Earth, where temperatures were low enough for liquid water. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-24 01:19:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Serpent-Handling Pastor Killed by Snake: Where Was God? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-21 20:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NASA Researcher Finds Planet-Sized Space Weather Explosions at Venus </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-21 02:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Binge drinking after working out significantly reduces muscle protein synthesis, and may impair muscle growth and subsequent athletic performance. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-21 00:26:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Schizophrenics are more likely to get autoimmune diseases, suggesting a potential genetic link between schizophrenia and diseases such as type 1 diabetes and MS. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-17 02:56:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Psychologists examined Internet trolls and found that they are narcissistic, psychopathic, and sadistic. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-15 04:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-12 22:50:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Sochi, stray puppies find you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 10 Problems With How We Think </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-12 22:48:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists explain the "munchies." THC fits into receptors in the brain's olfactory bulb, significantly increasing the ability to smell and taste food. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-10 04:53:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A species of bumblebee can fly to heights of 29,500 feet. That's higher than Mount Everest. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-07 17:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The capacity of working memory is defined by quality, not quantity. "We try to memorize all relevant objects, but the quality of these recollections... gets worse as we have to remember more. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-07 16:56:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-07 06:29:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All cars should have something like this. It would probably reduce road rage precipitously! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Jehol Biota, a famous collection of fossils from the Cretaceous, was preserved by volcanic flows just like Pompeii. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 19:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 07:20:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For everyone curious about the research team's methods, particularly in regards to word graphing, the full paper is open access and available here:

http://www.nature.com/srep/2014/140115/srep03691/full/srep03691.html

The authors' description of the technique is a doozy, at least to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 06:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Department of Defense is primarily a jobs program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 06:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is the dog dressed as Snow White? I can't tell... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The word patterns a person uses when describing a dream can distinguish between schizophrenia and bipolar disorder. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-03 23:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In a comprehensive study of bad dreams, men were more likely to have nightmares about catastrophes while women dreamt about relationships. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-03 03:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In a study of congenitally blind children who underwent surgery to restore vision, researchers have found that the brain can learn to "see" much later in life than previously thought. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-03 03:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NASA is planning to create the coldest spot in the known universe onboard the ISS (video). </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-31 04:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Differences in Oral Sexual Behaviors by Gender, Age, and Race Explain Observed Differences in Prevalence of Oral HPV Infection </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-27 06:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> From one cell to many: How did multicellularity evolve? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-26 07:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just 60 seconds of viewing models alters women's perceptions of attractiveness in regards to weight. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-23 16:29:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-23 16:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whoops. My mistake. Damn Phys.org republishing old press releases... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Snow days do not impact student learning. In fact, keeping schools open during a storm is more detrimental to learning than a closure. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-22 15:57:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Functioning biological cell created from plastic </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-20 04:29:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers discover how a common form of irregular heartbeat occurs. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-20 01:17:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mathematical model describes how to survive a nuclear explosion. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-18 04:45:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tiktaalik roseae fossil analysis provides new details on the origin of vertebrate legs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-13 20:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Placebo effect provides pain relief to migraine sufferers even when they know they're taking a sugar pill. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-13 03:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dr. Oz has described 16 weight loss "miracles" on his show. None of them has cured obesity yet. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-11 01:12:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For the first time, scientists confirm that sea stars have vision. The eyes at the end of their arms can produce images of about 200 pixels. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-11 00:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-10 02:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently, drinking 3-6 cups of coffee each day can be just as hydrating as water, provided you're already a recreational caffeine addict.

[Source](http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0084154?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fish swallows bird in flight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-10 02:13:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Odor receptors discovered in lungs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 23:29:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Astronomers use the Hubble Telescope to reveal cloudy weather on a "super-Earth" exoplanet. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-31 23:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reading a gripping book results in heightened connectivity in the brain that lasts for five days. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-30 06:06:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Forest cutting and impacts on carbon in the eastern United States </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-21 01:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 5 Simple Tips for Denying Scientific Consensus </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-20 16:48:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New findings hint at diamond deposits in Antarctica </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-17 22:25:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-16 02:30:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha. I wonder if that's actually true? MOAR RESEARCH PLZ, SCIENTISTS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> No Two People Smell the Same: With nearly a million variations on 400 smell receptors, everyone senses smell differently </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-15 21:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-11 17:39:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for adding that! I can see how my title could be misconstrued. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Top 10 Junk Science/Bullshit Stories of 2013 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-11 17:03:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Material can capture mechanical energy from walking, driving, or even the wind using the triboelectric effect. A square meter of the stuff can now produce as much as 300 watts. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-11 00:34:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Life on Earth may have developed below rather than above ground. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-09 05:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The FDA Stifles the Advance of Modern Molecular Medicine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-09 04:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-07 02:37:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Before clicking, I thought this was going to be one of those "that's terrible but kinda funny" posts but this is actually heart-wrenching. You have to feel for Vin Diesel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have recovered the oldest human DNA to date, beating the old record by 300,000 years. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 19:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For the first time, scientists have succeeded in transforming human stem cells into functional lung and airway cells. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-02 20:26:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-23 07:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's one fiiiiiiiiiiine piece of [forced perspective](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Forced_perspective) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-22 18:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For a laugh, go to the video section and watch the spokesperson try to talk up the machine while on it -- you can barely understand him because his voice is shaking in and out.

I'd wager this might impart small boosts to bone density, but as far as increasing aerobic capacity or losing weight, the effects will most likely be negligible. 

Source: http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/whole-body-vibration/AN01598 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 20:59:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 20 Tips for Analyzing Claims of a Scientific Study </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 23:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-18 18:02:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Found a terrific study in PubMed:

**Lifetime exercise and disk degeneration: an MRI study of monozygotic twins.**

Study: "...the effects of power sports were investigated in 12 discordant [twin] pairs (2,300 vs 200 h of weightlifting). The age range of the twins was from 35 to 69 yr.

Finding: Increased power sport participation was associated with slightly greater disk degeneration in the lower thoracic spine, but not in the lumbar spine.

Link: http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/9346167 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drinking or eating caffeine even six hours before bedtime could reduce sleep by more than one hour. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-18 00:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There's a large volcano forming under Antarctic Ice, and it's going to erupt. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-17 21:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 21:57:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This press release is terribly written.

Something to remember: Not all fat is created equal. Visceral fat, which coats internal organs in the abdominal cavity, is far more dangerous than subcutaneous fat, which is stored just underneath the skin. It doesn't look like the study made any effort to differentiate the two.

Addition: Yowzers. Nobody seems to like this comment. Here's information to back up what I'm saying. From the Harvard Medical School:

"Abdominal, or visceral, fat is of particular concern because its a key player in a variety of health problems  much more so than subcutaneous fat, the kind you can grasp with your hand. Visceral fat, on the other hand, lies out of reach, deep within the abdominal cavity, where it pads the spaces between our abdominal organs."

Link: http://www.health.harvard.edu/fhg/updates/Abdominal-fat-and-what-to-do-about-it.shtml
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 5 million acres of land set aside for conservation - more than Yellowstone, Everglades and Yosemite National Parks combined - have vanished and been planted with corn to make Ethanol. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-13 17:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 01:59:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do I assign flair to this? I don't see a bright yellow box under the submission... (Browser = Firefox)

Update: Looks like somebody else did. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As little as 20 minutes of moderate exercise three times per week during pregnancy enhances the newborn child's brain development </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 01:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 'Freakish' asteroid discovered that resembles rotating lawn sprinkler. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-07 18:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 22:55:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My girlfriend lost about twenty hair ties to my roommate's orange tabby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Male nursery spiders initiate mating by presenting the female with a "gift"  an insect prey wrapped in silk. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 20:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-03 17:38:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TL;DR

http://www.realclearscience.com/journal_club/2013/10/16/why_do_we_elect_attractive_politicians_106724.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-01 16:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. We've always known that muscles atrophy after disuse -- muscle is physiologically expensive for the body to maintain. What's incredible is how fast the body does away with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-01 16:21:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Precisely. I don't think people have to worry about wasting away from just days off at the gym. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Have you ever had to get a cast? A new study shows you lose a fair amount of muscle after just five days! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-01 06:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's an interesting new study:

"Substantial skeletal muscle loss occurs during only 5 days of disuse."
http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24168489

What did the researchers do?

"Twenty-four healthy, young (231 y) males were subjected to either 5 (n=12) or 14 (n=12) days of one-legged knee immobilization using a full leg cast."

What did they find?

"Quadriceps muscle CSA declined from baseline by 3.50.5 (P0.0001) and 8.42.8% (P0.0001), leg lean mass was reduced by 1.40.7 (P=0.07) and 3.10.7% (P0.01), and strength decreased by 9.02.3 (P0.0001) and 22.92.6% (P0.0001) following 5 and 14 days of immobilization, respectively."

The takeaway: It's amazing how fast muscles atrophy after only five days of total disuse! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New compound battles type 2 diabetes and promotes weight loss. It does this in smaller doses compared to current drugs and with minimal side effects. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-30 19:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Eye-tracking study shows that everyone ogles women's bodies. "Both sexes fixed their gaze more on women's chests and waists and less on faces" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-30 00:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Brain training improves memory, but it does not boost intelligence. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-28 06:00:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-23 05:37:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 58% approval is nothing to scoff at, though. Polls never reached anywhere near that in the 60s, as far as I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> US Support for Marijuana Legalization at Its Highest Yet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-23 02:45:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Interactively exercising with music can make your muscles work more efficiently and reduce strain. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-16 23:36:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> These government-made public health and safety posters from the 1930s are terrific. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-16 20:07:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-14 20:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RealClearScience actually interviewed the author of the paper. (Link: http://www.realclearscience.com/blog/2013/10/40-years-of-government-nutrition-data-may-be-flawed.html)

Here's what he said about the Coca-Cola funding: "Archer explained that it's an unrestricted research grant. In other words, the soft drink maker contractually has no input or say in what he researches or publishes."

I actually think that Coca-Cola wouldn't like the findings of the paper, because it's actually saying that people eat MORE calories than they think. Hmm now I wonder where those calories come from... soda maybe?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Love actually tastes sweet. Psychologists have found that thoughts of love cause people to rate the taste of plain water as sweeter. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-10 16:51:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-10 16:48:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For all those people eating paleo diets thinking to themselves that calories in vs. calories out doesn't matter, this study reported that obese people UNDERESTIMATED their intake by about 800 calories a day. So the largest individuals in society are actually eating a lot more. Thus -- if true -- the results of this study seem to further reinforce the USDA's general stance on obesity, that we just need to eat less and exercise more.

Study is here, btw: http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0076632 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-06 08:08:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glitch Gaming, an organization at the University of Minnesota, did this at the local BWWs on campus for the LCS Championship. The joint was actually at capacity, with 90% of the people there to watch the LCS. It was a blast!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-02 18:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks to Tom Clancy's Hunt for Red October, Sean Connery played a Lithuanian submarine captain -- Marko Ramius -- resulting in the best accent mash up of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A nearby alien planet six times the size of the Earth is covered with a water-rich atmosphere that includes a strange "plasma form" of water. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-02 17:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A massive review of the scientific literature has found that genetically modified crops pose no significant hazards to consumers or the environment. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 17:11:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers have discovered the first physical evidence of structural brain differences that distinguish early risers from people who like to stay up late. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 08:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Stereotyping isn't always morally wrong. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-30 06:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-26 21:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surprised to see that my hometown TV station made it on r/science. The last time they made worldwide news was for their drunk anchor. http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2071669/Annie-Stensrud-Was-bumbling-news-anchor-drunk-air-Female-presenter-slurs-words-bizarre-broadcast.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> South Park: "Chef, what would a priest want to stick up our butts?" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-22 20:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-20 17:47:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's he doing at a World Wrestling Entertainment event? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-20 17:45:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One has to wonder about the multitude of ways that sports subtly affect our psyches and actions. The article mentioned that sports defeats also boost chances of traffic fatalities and domestic violence... eeek!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Football fans eat fattier foods and 10% more calories than usual the day after their team loses. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-20 17:37:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-20 16:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100% positive feedback: sounds like a responsible mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to extract better work out of misbehaving employees: guilt them. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-19 18:48:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-18 23:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So rigid, methodical, and uninspired... but enough about the current state of scientific publishing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers have demonstrated that if the language processing areas of the brain become damaged, language function can switch to the non-dominant hemisphere. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-18 23:30:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The human sense of touch is far more sensitive than originally thought. New research shows that we can detect deformations on the nanoscale. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-13 19:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists don't "believe" in evolution, they accept the evidence for it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 17:25:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-02 17:04:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So many people carry around hatred and contempt after being wronged. The accompanying worry and anxiety must feel like a 20lb weight on each shoulder. You don't have to forget -- justice should be done in those circumstances. But forgiveness is the true liberation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Power of Forgiveness: Forgiving linked to mental and physical health. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-02 07:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-29 20:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Technically correct. Though with male animals, vets almost always remove the testicles: simple, cheap, effective.

The downside is that your male cat won't be cooling its balls on the base of toilets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mini-brains with separate working regions have been grown using stem cells in the lab for the first time. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-29 16:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-26 23:00:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If fusion reactions don't become self-sustaining, how do you explain stars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-26 20:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NIF began focused on achieving fusion ignition and it still is. But they've missed so many deadlines over there that it seems they're starting to "diversify their research portfolio," so to speak -- taking on all sorts of projects.

I mean, that HUGE laser has to be used for something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-26 20:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NIF's biggest problem is being able to sustain and control the fusion reaction. Judging by the article it doesn't seem that fusion ignition occurred, where the reaction actually becomes self-sustaining. In other words, I'm guessing that they didn't reach the break even point, if they did, that would be the headline.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-26 04:40:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We like to have fun in Madison.

http://www.southparkstudios.com/clips/402323/we-like-to-have-fun-here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists uncover the remains of Leedsichthys problematicus, the world's largest fish. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-26 04:37:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New device uses electromagnetic waves from TV broadcasts and cell phone and wireless Internet signals and converts them to power </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-24 16:26:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-24 05:47:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This study was released almost two months ago and already appeared on /r/science. I love how Scientific American simply slapped on a misleading headline and republished it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oh hai, Giant Russian Military Hovercraft. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 06:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-21 01:03:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like they compared the subjects' final fitness scores/metrics to baseline metrics taken at the beginning of the program. Not sure if sedentary controls are really needed for a study of this design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First scientific study on CrossFit finds that it significantly improves body composition and aerobic capacity across all fitness levels. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-20 23:03:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Unrealistic comparative optimism: Why we always think the other guy is going to get hit by a truck. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-19 05:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The deep-sea footprint of the Deepwater Horizon oil spill. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-17 03:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-17 00:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> STUNNER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Ugliest Churches in the World </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-17 00:50:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Subtle thoughts and primes of death increase alcohol consumption </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-15 20:39:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-13 16:43:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's a link to the research that I think the author is referencing:
http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23759244

Psychobiotics: A Novel Class of Psychotropic.

Abstract: Here, we define a psychobiotic as a live organism that, when ingested in adequate amounts, produces a health benefit in patients suffering from psychiatric illness. As a class of probiotic, these bacteria are capable of producing and delivering neuroactive substances such as gamma-aminobutyric acid and serotonin, which act on the brain-gut axis. Preclinical evaluation in rodents suggests that certain psychobiotics possess antidepressant or anxiolytic activity... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 'Psychobiotic' Bacteria Affect Our Mood </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-13 16:42:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Woman murders a talking hot dog in a classic public service announcement about the dangers of LSD. The horror! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-09 00:29:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-08 06:47:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One time I ripped my boxers deadlifting and mistook it for an anal blowout. For the thirty minutes before I noticed that they were ripped, I was scared shitless that my colon would start leaking out of my arsehole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL the first and only transplanted human penis was cut off after two weeks "because of the wife's psychological rejection as well as the swollen shape." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-07 20:42:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 00:05:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whoops, damn my brain. A billion billion is still less than 10^32, though! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-30 23:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only a billion years? Pffft. The proton can live for up to 10^32 years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Exosomes derived from stem cells could cause the brain to regenerate itself after trauma, and may one day be used to treat Alzheimer's </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-30 23:39:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 16:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This study is interesting in that people commonly perceive cities as more dangerous due to higher crime and homicide rates -- we fear what we can't control. But in reality, the risk of injury death is higher outside of cities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Major cities are often the safest places in the U.S. The "overall risk of injury death is lower in urban areas compared to outside of cities." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 16:17:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 16:09:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One findings that was surprising about this study was that people were least likely to intervene when the conflict was between a man and a woman. Those fights are often of a different nature, I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-23 18:07:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, here are a couple.

Lesbian parents (PDF): "...although children from lesbian families were more likely to explore same-sex relationships, the large majority of children who grew up in lesbian families identified themselves as heterosexual."
http://www.silveroakcasino.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/3.pdf

Gay Parents: "More than 90% of sons whose sexual orientations could be rated were heterosexual."
http://psycnet.apa.org/journals/dev/31/1/124/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Homosexuality is not contagious: Same-sex attraction does not spread in adolescent social networks. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-23 16:26:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sperm Whales   Giant Squids may do battle as many as 3.6 million times per day. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-22 20:05:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-17 00:24:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This article gives a pretty good explanation of the study:

http://www.realclearscience.com/blog/2013/06/low-doses-of-psilocybin-help-extinguish-conditioned-fear.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 18:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Re-posted to correct misspelling in title. Here's the original paper: http://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/am401956s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New film created for checking whether bootleg liquor is made from ethanol (good) or methanol (bad), just in case you ever wanted to drink some strange dude's moonshine. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 18:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 17:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, and here's the original paper: http://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/am401956s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 17:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Misspelling in title: There should be a "try" between "to" and "some." But your brain probably filled in the gap anyways. Isn't that crazy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Missing Energy Found In Warming Deep Oceans </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-14 00:10:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Decapitated Worms Regrow Heads with Memories Still Inside </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-12 20:08:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The George Zimmerman trial is almost over. Finally. Now let's discuss why people are so obsessed with watching court trials. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-12 17:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A staffer for a Republican congressman argues that the GOP should accept climate change and put forth a conservative solution. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-10 19:06:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 23:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meh, I'd let the mods decide. Cheers, mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 21:17:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with a lot of what you're saying, but one thing to also keep in mind is that the experts that you contact will also likely have "agendas and biases," especially if you speak with competing scientists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 20:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's also a great article here when this paper was originally linked to Reddit in June:

http://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/1fslo3/low_doses_of_psilocybin_speed_the_removal_of/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 18:30:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure the subjects only did it once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 18:05:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TL;DR of the study:

http://www.realclearscience.com/journal_club/2013/07/06/violent_video_games_dont_make_you_mean_106583.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 17:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. The study was also conducted in vitro, so that could also affect the results. 

What's really interesting here is that short-term exercise produced the hormonal changes with inhibitory effects on cancer cell growth. A previous study showed long-term exercise to have such an effect: http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/11490320.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A mere 60 minutes of aerobic exercise could inhibit growth of prostate cancer cells. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 17:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New PLoS study describes a hipster toad with a weaponized mustache. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 04:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Killing Cancer With Salt </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-04 08:38:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-27 06:14:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the actual paper. It's open-access over at Scientific Reports: http://www.nature.com/srep/2013/130625/srep02066/full/srep02066.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have designed what is effectively an electronic dildo for collecting semen from male parrots. It's a vast improvement over the old method, "rhythmically massaging" the cloaca, and should greatly boost conservation efforts. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-27 06:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Economists link poor numerical abilities with mortgage default and delinquency. They suggest that poor math skills may have contributed to the mortgage crisis that fueled the Great Recession. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 23:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have engineered a sensor to detect melanoma by the odors emitted from human skin cells. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 17:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do morbidly obese people have sex? And can someone be too fat to fornicate? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-18 17:35:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers may have discovered the cause of bad hair days: traces of copper from metal piping. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-17 05:17:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 1 Could Americans handle drug legalization? "I simply dont buy arguments for drug legalization premised on liberty and freedom, when those drugs by their very nature take away liberty and freedom." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 04:11:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 04:06:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The piece is based on a recent study from the Scripps Research Institute that looked at cocaine addiction in a rat model. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could Americans handle drug legalization? "I simply dont buy arguments for drug legalization premised on liberty and freedom, when those drugs by their very nature take away liberty and freedom." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 04:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-14 03:49:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't put much stock in computer simulations, but this is quite a provocative theory that makes some intuitive sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Did men create menopause by chasing after younger women? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-14 03:48:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-06 19:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. And according the the article, the researchers were working with low doses of psilocybin in a controlled environment. Self-medicating in an uncontrolled environment with higher doses may not be effective at all, and may instead be deleterious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Low doses of psilocybin speed the removal of conditioned fear, meaning the psychedelic could be a potential treatment of Post Traumatic Stress Disorder. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-06 17:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do dark-matter discs envelop galaxies? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-04 07:04:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Religious Fundamentalism Is a "Mental Illness" That Could Soon Be "Cured" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-03 04:58:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-01 03:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep! I'm super pumped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-31 21:49:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In general, science television today is but a shadow of a shadow of its former self. There are a few bright spots of course, like Planet Earth, Mythbusters, and Bill Nye, but for the most part, anything on Science Channel or Animal Planet is garbage.

I just finished watching Carl Sagan's Cosmos for the first time and was blown away.

If you wish to make an apple pie from scratch, you  must first invent the Universe.

-Carl Sagan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 04:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The paper is open-access and available over at PNAS:

 http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2013/05/16/1305923110.full.pdf+html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New, powerful immune system discovered in mucus. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 04:34:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-24 03:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The researchers found that when they deactivated the macrophages, the salamanders healed in the same way other animals do: scabs and scars, but no new limbs

Thus, by process of elimination, they've found that macrophages are key to regeneration. It will be even trickier to find out why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A 9-year-old border collie has been trained to understand grammar elements and comprehend sentences. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-21 21:43:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is cold fusion for real? New study takes a look at the E-CAT reactor and discerns intriguing results. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-20 19:41:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>