<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3651</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Comb jellies, close cousins of jellyfish, once had skeletons </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Original Study: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2015/07/15/1504467112 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fossil fuel emissions will make carbon dating less reliable. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:12:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:24:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One interesting possibility is that trans teens will be less depressed if they know it's not a case of being in the "wrong body". From the conclusion:
Transgender youth are aware of the incongruence between their internal gender identity and their assigned sex at early ages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Transgender youth have sex hormone levels that match the gender they were assigned at birth, according to a new study </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:41:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When Angelina Jolie tested positive for BRCA1 (a gene involved in breast cancer), the publicity influenced other women to seek out genetic testing, a new study finds. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:35:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gut worms protect babies' brains from inflammation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:24:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the animals...they're trying to tell us something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that cheetahs cannot roar. Instead, they chirp like birds. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:07:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robots pass the classic "wise-men puzzle", showing a new degreee of self-awareness. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:07:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Coaches can be a strong influence in preventing football injuries, new study finds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dairy products boost effectiveness of probiotics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:06:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that girding your loins is pretty easy. It involves lifting the hem of your tunic and then tucking it into your belt or tying it in a knotbasically turning a dress into a pair of shorts. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:01:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:01:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The study is mansplaining combat, and it's wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:01:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fun fact: Spanish speakers actually modified the Aztec word "ahuacatl" to "avocado" because the former sounded too much like "abogado", the Spanish word for lawyer. TLDR: Avocado=Testicles=Lawyers. The Aztecs http://www.smithsonianmag.com/arts-culture/why-the-avocado-should-have-gone-the-way-of-the-dodo-4976527/?no-ist
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:56:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are only ~172 million water buffalo in the world. 95.8% of them reside in Asia. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Water_buffalo#Distribution_of_populations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:53:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Implying Christians do not *already* like anal sex and bestiality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> False.

http://m.snopes.com/man-arrested-for-alligator-sex/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that is an incredibly interesting insight into a blessing that always bothered me a bit. Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Incidentally, all of those Talmudic cases also have very practical, law-based applications. For instance, the section on breast size is trying to determine at what age a woman is considered an adult for the purpose of court prosecution, especially in capital cases. 

In the US, once you're 18 you are an adultregardless of your personal development. Even though we know some 15 year olds can consent to sex and make their own decisions, we call them children. And even though we know some 20 year olds can barely consent and are easily swayed by peer-pressure, we consider them adults. 

The Talmud tries to avoid these pitfalls by defining adulthood for the purposes of consent and prosecution by physical development...the onset of puberty...at which point, the Talmud needs to define puberty.

Fascinating...not ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL Russia has a larger surface area than Pluto. Russia has a surface area of 17 million km2, compared with 16.6 million km2 for Pluto. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:20:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:10:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you've ever met someone with colorectal cancer or Crohn's Disease, this actually makes a lot of sense. I think it's sort of awesome that they thank god for something that actually matters...the physiological processes that make our bodies work. Sure beats those hymns thanking god for mountains and forgiveness and stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Curiosity rover finds evidence of Mars' primitive continental crust </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL warm-blooded fish exist. Opah (or Moonfish) use their warm bodies to thrive even in frigid ocean depths. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nah, that was me. sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL cats only meow at humans. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:24:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Shark attack incidents have fallen by over 91% since 1950, due to public information campaignsnot culling </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:37:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When the paper is live, it'll be here: http://www.wiley.com/WileyCDA/PressRelease/pressReleaseId-119242,descCd-release_additional_material.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cancer survivors face potentially discriminatory challenges when trying to adopt children, new study shows </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's a link to the paper...but it's entirely behind a paywall (even the abstract...)

http://pediatrics.aappublications.org/content/early/recent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nixon's healthcare plan shared some common ground (and much rhetoric) with Obama's Affordable Care Act according to a new study published in the journal Pediatrics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:33:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 14:23:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't know how to read. Let me help:
The scientists ran an in-depth statistical analysis to find out whether pesticides, human land use or other factors may have contributed to declining bumblebee populations over the past century. And the answer is clearly nowe checked this carefully, Pindar says. They are impacted by climate change and these effects are already very large and widespread.

That's a quote in this article, from the lead author on the new study, published in the most prestigious scientific journal in the world. They confirmed through statistical analyses that climate change and NOT pesticides or land use were to blame.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> u/mesopotamiae: not the bee keeper we deserve, but the beekeeper we need right now.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:33:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah...not according to the *real* scientists (nice try, though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:32:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Monsanto isn't a vague boogie monster? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:22:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed. The study was literally published in the top scientific journal in the world (give or take "Nature" journals). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:35:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bumblebee drones don't have feelings anyway. Also, drones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Giant pandas are only able to survive on bamboo shoots because they move slowly and conserve energy. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:32:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New jumping soft robot combines the advantages of hard robotics with the more malleable properties of soft robotics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:30:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bumblebees are clearly liberals, looking for excuses to tax the rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists confirm that worldwide bumblebee populations are dying out due to climate change </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers identify new spectrum disorder: ALPIM Syndrome. The disorder helps explain some of the physical symptoms behind certain kinds of panic attacks. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:41:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lake Erie is in trouble. NOAA report warns that the impending algae bloom could be so severe that it'll pose risks to swimmers and boaters. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:02:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> People are wiling to take the stairsbut only when the escalator is at least 100% farther away, new study shows. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:59:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New online genetic research tool transforms huge DNA and RNA datasets into a free, open-source data mining project. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:27:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Brawling badgers age faster. New study shows the stress of fighting tooth and nail may shorten the lives of particularly aggressive badgers. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:22:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:04:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if she might harm her immunocompromised patients? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Freakin Typhoid Mary... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "There is an unspoken understanding that you probably should be on your deathbed if you are calling in sick, one anonymous emergency room physician commented on the open-ended essay section of the survey. and [it] makes me look bad to do so (like I am weak or something). It is much, much less stressful to suck it up and come in sick than call out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:37:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good point. Although some of the quotes from the physicians really got me. The idea that they'll risk a patient's life so they won't "look weak" is a big problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Doctors refuse to take sick days, even when they know it puts their patients at risk. In a recent survey, 95% said they believed working while sick could cause harm. But 83% said they do it anyway. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:25:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:17:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Original Study: http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0117259 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIFU by inviting over my coworkers' dead father. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:20:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obligatory: this happened just now and I'm still wallowing in shame, but not badly enough to wait until it wears off to write a post

I keep a bunch of dinosaur toys on my desk at work. There's a triceratops and a stegosaurus. I expect every intelligent person to know the difference between the two but, just in case you don't [here's a handy explanation](http://dinosaurs.findthedata.com/compare/255-278/Stegosaurus-vs-Triceratops). Right. So my desk-mate pointed to the triceratops this morning and asked if it was a stegosaurus. Rather than smacking him for not being a paleontologist, I gave a super dank explanation: 

"No," said I. "It's a tricerotops. Cuz it's got tri, three, ceras on its tops!". So witty. So cool. That's why I'm the king of the workplace.

Meanwhile, another coworker walked by. He said, hey, thats what my Dad used to say when he was describing tricerotops. Now, a social adept person would have heard the phrase what my Dad used to say and figured there might be more to the story. Not me. 

Hey!" said I. "Thats awesome. Your Dad is awesome. Lets invite him to the office! Why has he never been here before? Cant wait to meet your dad!! He rocks. 

My coworker just stared at me sadly and walked away. Turns out his Dad is dead, and the triceratops thing was a fond childhood memory, not an invitation to remind him of his loss. Oops.

TL;DR Invited coworkers dead father to the office. Ruined a happy childhood memory involving dinosaurs. Clarified stegosaurus vs triceratops once and for all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:58:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Relevant video](http://www.vocativ.com/video/culture/science/junk-science-mouse-trials-are-meaningless/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slappity-Bumpies sounds like a 90s board game. And I would play it with ALL participants of ANY gender. 

Cuz even in the 90s, I was progressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:13:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP is most definitely not with the FBI.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://nature.com/articles/doi:10.1038/ncomms8346

Abstract:
"Evaporation is a ubiquitous phenomenon in the natural environment and a dominant form of energy transfer in the Earths climate. Engineered systems rarely, if ever, use evaporation as a source of energy, despite myriad examples of such adaptations in the biological world. Here, we report evaporation-driven engines that can power common tasks like locomotion and electricity generation. These engines start and run autonomously when placed at airwater interfaces. They generate rotary and piston-like linear motion using specially designed, biologically based artificial muscles responsive to moisture fluctuations. Using these engines, we demonstrate an electricity generator that rests on water while harvesting its evaporation to power a light source, and a miniature car (weighing 0.1kg) that moves forward as the water in the car evaporates. Evaporation-driven engines may find applications in powering robotic systems, sensors, devices and machinery that function in the natural environment." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:20:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can anyone find the original paper for this? It's supposed to be in Nature Methods, but I don't see it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can flying fish fly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the abstract from [the original study](http://www.nature.com/srep/2015/150611/srep10768/full/srep10768.html):
"Microscale soft-robots hold great promise as safe handlers of delicate micro-objects but their wider adoption requires micro-actuators with greater efficiency and ease-of-fabrication. Here we present an elastomeric microtube-based pneumatic actuator that can be extended into a microrobotic tentacle. We establish a new, direct peeling-based technique for building long and thin, highly deformable microtubes and a semi-analytical model for their shape-engineering. Using them in combination, we amplify the microtubes pneumatically-driven bending into multi-turn inward spiraling. The resulting micro-tentacle exhibit spiraling with the final radius as small as ~185 m and grabbing force of ~0.78 mN, rendering itself ideal for non-damaging manipulation of soft, fragile micro-objects. This spiraling tentacle-based grabbing modality, the direct peeling-enabled elastomeric microtube fabrication technique, and the concept of microtube shape-engineering are all unprecedented and will enrich the field of soft-robotics."

EDIT: Here's the full study (no paywall): http://www.nature.com/srep/2015/150611/srep10768/pdf/srep10768.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As long as the peanut supporters keep the hate to their own subreddit and don't harass those with allergies on imgur, I think it'll be fine.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Babies at risk for autism may demonstrate superior visual perception. In a study of over 100 infants, scientists found that babies who were quicker to glance at inconsistencies in simple diagrams were more likely to develop autism later on. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:09:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those people are allergic to longevity. Study says so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:53:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure, but it looks like all the popular reports are emphasizing NOT peanut butter. Anyone know why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Eating for two" during pregnancy might be a bad idea. Research has shown that gaining too much weight during pregnancy increases the risk of gestational diabetes, high blood pressure, large babies, and delivery by C-section caesarean section. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:44:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:43:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Original study: http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/add.12962/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Children's exposure to secondhand smoke in England has dropped 80% since 1998 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://www.nature.com/srep/2015/150611/srep11123/full/srep11123.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:39:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://ije.oxfordjournals.org/content/early/2015/05/26/ije.dyv039.short?rss=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Peanuts reduce risk of cancer, dementia, heart attacks and diabetes, according to a new study. People who ate 10g of nuts per day were less likely to die from major diseases, including respiratory disease, neurodegenerative disease, diabetes, cancer and cardiovascular disease. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:37:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://mdfoodsystemmap.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/06/Baltimore-Food-Environment-Report-2015-1.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One in four Baltimore residents live in a food desert, defined as an area more than 1/4 mile from a supermarket, where median household income is at or below 185% of the federal poverty level. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:33:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:27:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://js.sagamorepub.com/jlr/article/view/5682 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:37:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Original study: http://psycnet.apa.org/? fa=main.doiLanding doi=10.1037/hea0000240 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get your own Karma, OP.

http://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/387j03/children_from_poor_families_tend_to_be_more/ (same story, from 8 days ago) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Five major corporations control more than half of all scientific research. New study shows Reed-Elsevier, Springer, Wiley-Blackwell, Taylor   Francis, and Sage now publish more than 50% of academic articles. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:56:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:23:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, you quit using Reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://www.nature.com/srep/2015/150609/srep11202/full/srep11202.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://www.hydrol-earth-syst-sci-discuss.net/12/1437/2015/hessd-12-1437-2015.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Original Study: http://www.nature.com/neuro/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nn.4035.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:16:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's a link to the abstract: http://qje.oxfordjournals.org/content/130/2/759.abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Juvenile incarceration yields less schooling, more crime </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Teens who use social media to quit smoking are twice as successful as those who use a more traditional method, according to a new study </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drought, heat and insects have been responsible for the death of more than 12 million trees in California. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I don't think US should *support* them. I just don't think US should be trying so hard to stop them. Seems likely ISIS will lose anyway. Worst case scenario, ISIS wins and wipes out the Syrian government, the Iranian government and a few terrorist groups. As for the civilians, they're utterly screwed under both the status quo and ISIS, so we're not doing them any favors either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> right, so those are bad things. But, like, everyone they're at war with is equally bad, and a bunch are actually kind of worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 21:48:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the USA should join Team ISIS.

Think about it. ISIS is trying to overthrow the Syrian government (that would be Bashar al-Assad's government, the one that used chemical weapons on its civilians). Meanwhile, ISIS is also at war with: Iran (the ones with the rogue nukes), Hezbollah (the ones with the rogue rocket strikes) and basically every failed state and terrorist organization in the region. Why are we trying to stop them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:03:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One of Starbucks' new frappuccino flavors contains 102 grams of sugar. Thats 4x the recommended daily allowance, and roughly equivalent to drinking an entire one-liter bottle of coke or scarfing down about thirty sugar cubes all at once. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:35:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's an abstract from [the full study:](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2015/150609/ncomms8352/full/ncomms8352.html)
Exceptionally preserved organic remains are known throughout the vertebrate fossil record, and recently, evidence has emerged that such soft tissue might contain original components. We examined samples from eight Cretaceous dinosaur bones using nano-analytical techniques; the bones are not exceptionally preserved and show no external indication of soft tissue. In one sample, we observe structures consistent with endogenous collagen fibre remains displaying ~67nm banding, indicating the possible preservation of the original quaternary structure. Using ToF-SIMS, we identify amino-acid fragments typical of collagen fibrils. Furthermore, we observe structures consistent with putative erythrocyte remains that exhibit mass spectra similar to emu whole blood. Using advanced material characterization approaches, we find that these putative biological structures can be well preserved over geological timescales, and their preservation is more common than previously thought. The preservation of protein over geological timescales offers the opportunity to investigate relationships, physiology and behaviour of long extinct animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Death To Paywalls!! Here's a bootleg copy of the complete study: http://docdro.id/12xxp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fifty hospitals in the US are overcharging the uninsured by 1000%, according to a new study from Johns Hopkins. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:31:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Less than seven hours of sleep is "inadequate to sustain health and safety in adults," according to a new study. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> At least 55 diseases correlate with when you're born. Overall, people born in May have the lowest lifetime disease risk, and those born in October have the highest. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Non-profit workers are dirty donut thieves, according to a 2006 study on altruism and anonymous donut sales. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:56:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 19:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> huh. that's a good point. we should really say "newly discovered species". A newly discovered species really can't be THAT new...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 16:21:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or reproduction in general has occurred in sync with El Nino Rabbis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 16:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By the way, here's the complete study (no paywall): https://peerj.com/articles/1011/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:35:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Original study: http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0033589415000368 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rabbits have reproduced in sync with El Nino weather patterns across the past 10,000 years. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seven new miniature frog species were just discovered in Brazil </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:32:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Original study: http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0091743515001668 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Most Americans, including gun owners, now support stronger gun control policies. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Social class influences music tastes. Poorer, less-educated people tend to like country, disco, easy listening, golden oldies, heavy metal and rap. Wealthier and better-educated people tend to like classical, blues, jazz, opera, choral, pop, reggae, rock, world and musical theatre. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:15:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously, though, we need an astrophysicist to help us. Any volunteers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0925231215004725 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:01:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/pirs.12163/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> College grads in the 90s moved to cities with fast-growing "smart" industries like tech. But now, US college grads choose cities with the biggest labor markets and the best chances of landing literally any job. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://rspb.royalsocietypublishing.org/content/282/1809/20150229 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chimpanzees have the cognitive power to cook their own food. Like humans, chimps prefer cooked food over raw food, understand the transformation of raw food into cooked food and often transport food over long distances. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original paper: http://iopscience.iop.org/0004-637X/803/2/80/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Astronomers can now "weigh" the Milky Way Galaxy, using approximate measurements streams produced by dissolving globular clusters. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 23:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha! That explains my altruism...but does it explain my autonomic nervous system?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 20:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the abstract from the [original study](http://www.nature.com/neuro/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nn.4035.html):
"Independent evidence associates -amyloid pathology with both non-rapid eye movement (NREM) sleep disruption and memory impairment in older adults. However, whether the influence of -amyloid pathology on hippocampus-dependent memory is, in part, driven by impairments of NREM slow wave activity (SWA) and associated overnight memory consolidation is unknown. Here we show that -amyloid burden in medial prefrontal cortex (mPFC) correlates significantly with the severity of impairment in NREM SWA generation. Moreover, reduced NREM SWA generation was further associated with impaired overnight memory consolidation and impoverished hippocampal-neocortical memory transformation. Furthermore, structural equation models revealed that the association between mPFC -amyloid pathology and impaired hippocampus-dependent memory consolidation was not direct, but instead statistically depended on the intermediary factor of diminished NREM SWA. By linking -amyloid pathology with impaired NREM SWA, these data implicate sleep disruption as a mechanistic pathway through which -amyloid pathology may contribute to hippocampus-dependent cognitive decline in the elderly." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 18:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.docdroid.net/1293f/psychological-science-2015-miller-0956797615578476.pdf.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 18:26:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't like when science is behind a paywall. Here's the full study: http://www.docdroid.net/1293f/psychological-science-2015-miller-0956797615578476.pdf.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 16:19:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's sort of interesting is that the study also links altruism to "autonomic flexibility"...which is some sort of biological thing I don't understand. 

Can anyone explain it to me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Poland will kill off about 5,800 pigs to prevent the spread of African swine fever. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 16:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Children from poor families tend to be more altruistic and more willing to make personal sacrifices for others. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thousands of UK patients with gonorrhea were prescribed outdated antibiotics. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:17:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 13:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the abstract from the [original paper](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0019103515002079)
"Relatively recent cometary impacts at the Moon could leave unique traces of their origins: high impact velocities and volatile abundances, combined with the presence of a dust- and ice-laden coma, may thermally and mechanically process the lunar surface in ways distinct from the impact of an asteroid. Here we analytically and numerically assess the consequences of a cometary impact at the Moon by considering the combined effects of a collision by the nucleus and inner coma. Our results show that cometary impacts entrain the finest fraction of lunar soil grains (10 m) over regional scales (1001000 km), produce large masses of vaporized material, and likely generate transient magnetic fields that could exceed the Earths surface field strength by a factor of 104. This combination of processes is consistent with a mechanism to generate lunar swirls: the diffuse, meandering disturbances in brightness and regolith texture that curl across much of the lunar far-side and are also commonly (but not exclusively) associated with magnetic anomalies. Previous observations of swirl features indicate that bright regions also possess a peculiar, altered regolith structure, which can be produced by the removal of fine soil grains. Regional scouring by an impacting comet explains both the structure and albedo variations: large dynamic pressures entrain the smallest grains within a near-surface flow of dusty plasma, disrupting the backscattering, fairy-castle structure of lunar soils in equilibrium with the airless environment. The resulting surface is brightened by compaction of the previously open, porous macrostructure. Darker lanes observed within swirl regions are interpreted as possible melt and/or vapor deposits. Finally, the intense magnetic fields generated during high-speed cometary impacts provide an explanation for correlations between swirl locations and magnetic anomalies." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lunar swirls, those wispy bright regions scattered along the moon's surface, were likely created by comet collisions. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 13:25:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Neuroscientists can now activate opoid receptors with light, potentially paving the way for painkillers that rely on light instead of dangerous, addictive opioids drugs. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 18:03:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chilli peppers hold promise of preventing liver damage and progression </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 15:17:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never trust people who do yoga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 17:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...and they've believed no studies since then. I'm not optimistic either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 17:07:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the [original study](http://jama.jamanetwork.com/article.aspx?articleid=2275444) published today in JAMA. Excerpt:
"A retrospective cohort study using an administrative claims database associated with a large commercial health plan. Participants included children continuously enrolled in the health plan from birth to at least 5 years of age during 2001-2012 who also had an older sibling continuously enrolled for at least 6 months between 1997 and 2012...In this large sample of privately insured children with older siblings, receipt of the MMR vaccine was not associated with increased risk of ASD, regardless of whether older siblings had ASD. These findings indicate no harmful association between MMR vaccine receipt and ASD even among children already at higher risk for ASD." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Study of 95,000 children finds no link between MMR vaccines and autism, even within high-risk populations </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 17:01:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cannabis consumers show greater susceptibility to false memories </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:33:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 15:29:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Original Source:
"Case 1: An Amputation Cover-Up. The Treatment: A new stem cell therapy that promises to restore blood flow in damaged legs. The Claim: All 26 patients in the study reported no significant clinical changes in either of their legs, beyond those caused by the stem cell treatment. The Fraud: FDA documents show that one of the patients had an entire foot amputated two weeks into the study. Thats a pretty serious omission, and it definitely constitutes a significant clinical change in the leg. No one bothered to correct or retract the faulty study, and the trial was considered a success.

[Stem Cell Trial](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22079876):
"This phase II clinical trial shows that the use of a combination cell therapy is safe and effective in increasing blood flow in the ischemic legs of patients with limb ischemia."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 16:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sort of. But not entirely.  
Our results demonstrate that the GNSS and INS navigational sensors built into consumer devices such as smartphones are capable of detecting surface displacements from moderate and larger earthquakes.

...what we generally call "cell phone GPS" is really a Global Navigation Satellite System (GNSS...one type GNSS is GPS) plus Inertial Navigation Systems (INS). So the thing that most people think of as "GPS" include INS. In your cell phone, INS gets its position and velocity from the GPS satellite receiver and then calculates its own position based on motion sensors.


TL;DR: "Smartphone GPS"= GPS + INS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 16:19:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the abstract from the [original study](http://www.vocativ.com/culture/science/early-earthquake-warnings-smartphones-gps/):
Earthquake early warning (EEW) can reduce harm to people and infrastructure from earthquakes and tsunamis, but it has not been implemented in most high earthquake-risk regions because of prohibitive cost. Common consumer devices such as smartphones contain low-cost versions of the sensors used in EEW. Although less accurate than scientific-grade instruments, these sensors are globally ubiquitous. Through controlled tests of consumer devices, simulation of an Mw (moment magnitude) 7 earthquake on Californias Hayward fault, and real data from the Mw 9 Tohoku-oki earthquake, we demonstrate that EEW could be achieved via crowdsourcing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Brontosaurus is officially a dinosaur again. New study shows that Brontosaurus is a distinct genus from Apatosaurus </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 13:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 13:08:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, a lot of what you just said is wrong.
 
*Tidally locked*: No. Atmospheres can keep a planet twirling. Source: http://www.popularmechanics.com/space/deep-space/a33/earth-like-exoplanets-around-dwarf-stars/

*Strong magnetic fields*: This is often claimed alongside the 'fact' that Red Dwarfs also have more violent reactions. But both are only true for young Red Dwarfs. And those stars last for an incredibly long time, compared to our own star. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 12:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Goddamit!!! I confused browser tabs and accidentally deleted this post when it had 1,000 upvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> On average, every star in the Milky Way Galaxy has 1 to 3 planets in the 'habitable-zone' that could support liquid water, says new astrophysics study on Kepler planet hunting data. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 12:32:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Humans killed at least 2.8 million whales in the 20th century. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 12:08:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Worlds first successful penis transplant announced by surgeons - another nine underway! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 18:14:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Rarest Wild Cats in the World. Heres a collection of little-seen scientific videos of them (most of which you've never even heard of). </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 13:40:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 23:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's gone down 0.1 pH. It's now 7.9 to 8.2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 22:02:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is one right answer. It is this one. ^

*pronounced Ehn-Cel-Lay-Dee-Ans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 21:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We can't know with just Cassini. When Cassini was sent out the idea that Enceladus of all places would look even marginally interesting (life-wise) was laughable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Enceladus, Saturn's 6th largest moon, has a warm ocean with hydrothermal vents. This is the first ever discovered outside of Earth, and makes for the most habitable off-world environment ever found. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 19:06:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Police lineups cause false accusations up to 60% of the time. But now scientists are exploring "nose-witness testimony" in a new study that suggests victims may be able to identify their attackers based on body odor. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-06 13:35:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 19:06:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like it would look like some sort of cross between Lucy and Homo habilis... so sorta ape plus caveman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 21:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough.

And when you tally how much money every Star Trek movie grossed collectively since 1979 (without correcting for inflation, we admit), its only slightly more than that one Transformers movie made at the box office.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-08 17:02:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a good point...the mirror test has some flaws. 

But note, rhesus monkeys have never passed the mirror test before. The study is interesting because these monkeys, which do not intrinsically understand mirrors, could *learn* to use them. That's promising, especially when you think of neurologic conditions that cause humans to fail the mirror test. If mirror recognition can be taught, perhaps therapy can help these people in the future.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-15 20:53:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...says the biologist :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:40:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those Alberta servers are clearly not made to handle Redditors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 15:59:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It turns out that cowbirds gauge their risk of death-by-truck based on distance, not speed.

So yeah, basically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 18:03:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Robert Seyfarth, a psychology professor at the University of Pennsylvania and pioneer in the fields of animal behavior and learning, wrote in an e-mail. This is the first time that a professional linguist has tackled the data on call combinations in wild monkeys.

So at least from a research standpoint, it means that we may want to start examining animal calls through the lens of linguistics. That's a sort of revolutionary idea, since we tend to think of animals noises as "calls", rather than a language or a dialect with logic-based rules. It's an interesting new avenue for research.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists translate monkey sounds into English, and develop linguistic rules for different primate dialects. Their research is published in the journal Linguistics and Philosophy. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 17:11:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 20:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always think it's ironic that Greens cite scientific consensus for climate change, but ignore the equally compelling evidence that GMOs are safe. 

If you're on the side of science, stick with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 20:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WELL...the DoE lightbulb thing and the EXIM ban were honestly a bit draconian. It's one thing to charge companies extra for choosing the less environmentally friendly option, or to add taxes or incentives. But these were outright bans on investing in incandescent lightbulbs and coal-fired power plants. And the DoT light rail thing just shuts down current projects (the same senators who pushed for that rider are also working on new light rail projects as we speak).

The only thing that I see on your list that looks purely spiteful and "villain level" is the UN Climate Fund. Why the hell can't we let the poor guy fulfill his pledge to save the world?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 19:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even small farmers are notoriously bad for the environment. They all need to make money, especially the small ones, and so they often let their cash crops mess up normal crop cycles.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 19:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, the good news is that these sorts of things can be easily reversed next year. They won't be...but they could be. Every year when it comes time to figure out appropriations, it's another opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 19:28:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It made the farmers pretty happy. It's strange, you usually think of farmers as being lovers of the land and pro-Earth etc...and then you take a look at the politics of it all, and notice that farmers are usually the ones pushing hardest against climate and land protection. Strange times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 18:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pres. Obama is not allowed to fulfill his pledge to give $3 billion to the United Nations Green Climate Fund, designed to spur other countries to respond to global warming.

...that can't be a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 17:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...but nobody lost quite as spectacularly as the sage grouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 16:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TBH, I haven't read all 178 pages yet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 16:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of those documents were actually declassified in 1977. Here you go: http://www.nytimes.com/packages/pdf/national/13inmate_ProjectMKULTRA.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 15:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hm. Decent point. Maybe we should. If the private sector would agree to fund the research, I can definitely see why we'd be better off without linking science to government money.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 15:26:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For more than two weeks many American scientists couldnt share their findings with the international scientific community or participate in joint research projects abroad. Government shutdown not only stifled U.S. researchit set back our foreign collaborators, too.

That's why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 14:34:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Losing two weeks of data collection during a critical research period or two weeks of a key experiment that took months or years to set up will have repercussions for years

...And I thought shutting off the National Zoo's panda cam was bad.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 15:32:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's crazy that a guy like Culberson can be so into NASA and yet so ignorant when it comes to environmental science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL Paul Simon once invited a fan on stage to play "Duncan" at a concert, after she shouted from the audience that she had learned to play guitar on that song. She was nervous, but Simon kept saying "Go on, Go on!" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 21:52:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 16:30:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like a story about gecko-inspired gloves comes out every month. But apparently this one actually works (!). Crazy video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 00:18:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wonder how this impacts studies of video game violence. Does COD teach violence *faster* than, say a violent television show? Interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Science in a Republican Senate: "If Republicans win the Senate, James Inhofe will likely take charge of Environment and Public Works. That would be disastrous for science." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 17:58:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MIT scientists built microscopic tumbling beads that mimic bacteria to navigate cell surfaces. These early findings, which could have future applications in drug delivery, are published in Physics Review Letters. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 16:14:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists uncover the origins of HIV in Africa and track the genetic differences that allowed the "M group" to spread farther and faster than any other strain. Their findings are published today in the journal Science. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 20:01:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 19:55:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "We look at these old Archaean crusts, for instance, and we dont see the features that characterize subduction," Rey says.

It's a model that confirms physical evidence. Read the article (and the study, for that matter).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A tobacco plant has been genetically engineered with turbocharged photosynthetic enzymes from a bacteria. The first step toward 35-60% better GMO crop production  UK and American biologists report in the journal Nature. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 19:49:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers have sequenced the genome of the coffee tree. After comparing coffee genes with those of other caffeine producers, they conclude that the ability to make caffeine arose independently at least twice. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 20:02:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 18:03:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup. The NASA Centennial Challenge might help them fix that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Solar-powered blimps can now carry satellites and telescopes above the clouds, into the stratosphere. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 15:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists publish thousands of blog posts and even start their own social network in China to find out firsthand how the government censors content online. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-21 20:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 20:21:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll never begin to understand the people in those comments. Even the direst homophobes shouldn't want a portion of the population not to get healthcare. It boggles the mind how people can hate so strongly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dr. Demetre Daskalakis is a Harvard-educated physician who traded the laboratory for the nightclub, in an effort to bring public health services to NYC's underserved gay population. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 15:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First complete map of Mars since 1987, released by the USGS. The extensive, detailed map shows that ancient rock exists in many more locations on the Martian surface than previously thought. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 17:24:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We believe the HBP is not a well conceived or implemented project and that it is ill suited to be the centerpiece of European neuroscience.

Ouch. Wonder how that'll affect the US Brain Project...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alcohol is responsible for 10% of deaths among 20-65 year olds in the U.S., according to a recent CDC study. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-08 15:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 22:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...in 2012. Love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 16:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scumbag BICEP team. Getting us all excited over nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 15:59:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's amazing that these robots are realistic and detailed enough to "fool" real animals. In a way, this is also a victory for materials science...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Another victory for the Standard Model of Physics. A study published today in Nature Physics further confirms the existence of the Higgs Boson, by proving for the first time that it breaks down into fermions. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-22 20:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-16 17:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIL: Curiosity was in fact the first rover to ever die from cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-16 17:03:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait, I thought all cosmic radiation was EM radiation. This is going to suck for Mars One.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-30 16:11:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the original scientific paper: http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24724938 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The First Family Tree of Beer: A Team of Geneticists is creating the Beer Yeast Genome Project, which will allow researchers to breed new brewing yeasts in spite consumer resistance to GMOs. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-30 16:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Climate Change may bring rising tides and storm surges to New York City. This architect re-imagines the city with permeable streets and barrier islands. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-30 19:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New Computer Program Could Help Solve Arson Cases. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-27 14:58:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that some Sunscreens are Flammable, so every now and then someone applies sunscreen, only to burst into flames when they get too close to the BBQ. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-27 14:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> HIV is slowly adapting to its human hosts, according to a study published yesterday in PLOS Genetics. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-27 14:49:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New study of the physics behind fruit flies' sharp, banked turns could change how we build flying micro-robots, according to a paper published today in Science. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-11 16:07:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that mosquitoes prefer certain blood types, and people with the "O" blood type are more likely to get bitten. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-24 20:48:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>