<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7994</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Number of U.S. Children Living in Poverty Spikes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:39:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All hail The State Authority! Thank you Comrade Warren </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair point, but then they aren't the link in the chain that is working for free. That money paid to the doctors is coming from some elses paycheck in the form of wages that they can't keep for themselves because the government is making a claim on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could make that argument for anything then. If we all chip-in in taxes, then whatever the majority says so, gets paid for through the tax system via the State Authority, and therefore is a "right". I view rights as something you are free to pursue, but cannot be one persons claim on some one elses labor. But I see your argument clockworkgirl21.  Edit: sorry I realized later that I was arguing another point about healthcare being a "right". Not about the smaller paycheck versus taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently people think when the majority "says so", that makes something a right. But it's not a right to be provide free healthcare. That would mean that someone in the chain is forced to work for free. Who would you suggest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:07:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not a right to be provide free healthcare. That would mean that someone in the chain is forced to work for free. Who would you suggest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:04:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a great idea that young workers would get smaller paychecks to pay for the Healthcare of people they don't even know. Or as most people would call it "Single Payer". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:17:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You realize the recent government debacle known as the Affordable Care Act does nothing to change the opaque price structure of the US healthcare.. It simply forced young healthy people to overpay for their insurance so others can pay less. The problem is health providers (not insurance companies) don't have any open pricing policies that the consumer shop, and that problem sure wasn't fixed 5 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Democrat Party, with a wink-and-a-nod, flooding the US with low skilled illegal workers drives down average American wages. Maybe that's what resonates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:25:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bill Clinton says..."What I'm really saying is...lets let these drug pushing criminals back into the African-American communities, after all, I don't live there and have to deal with the consequences". Uh..OK..thanks Bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alternate headline. Thanks to the ACA, average woman has other working people paying $255 for her birth control pills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:05:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She doesn't really hate America. She hates those little insignificant people who work in places like bakeries and restaurants. Ewe, those icky unwashed masses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:23:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe it's because illegals are willing to work "under-the-table" for fifty bucks a day when Americans actually abide by the minimum wage laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 18:39:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The "for profit" part is meaningless. They all pay their administrators and staff with the wheel-barrows of cash student borrowers bring in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 23:33:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This one is awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 04:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My cat is missing a top fang and his mouth does that same thing. I wonder if this cat is missing an upper fang too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 03:58:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok. This is stupid. A Reddit description that doesn't even remotely apply to some dumb random photo of a "person".....whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 04:26:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Memorial Day has nothing to do with the founding of the United States.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:49:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I missed the paragraph in the "social contract" where I end up paying for the electricity someone else uses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 04:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And how many kids don't bother to finish "free" K-12. Why is this a smart idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 16:55:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The vote was about late term abortions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 00:41:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I'm there about four time a week which means 200 times per year. I'm prepared! He he </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My car storage box is a Taco Bell condiment station </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 23:45:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 04:48:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can catch a cold over a telephone call. I like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 03:19:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've already jumped ship back to Firefox. I push the save button and I can't figure out the exact location of where it saved, nor could I change the location of the "save" where I wanted it to go. The big and blocky "manage bookmarks" blows, because I just want simple functions like "edit name" and easy to understand "drag to folder" functions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 01:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got two today. I was excited. I need to get a life. I hope they keep them around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:26:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is always a point when I'm looking through "Mildly Interesting" when I physically laugh out loud because it is the perfect three way intersection of:

1. Me realizing I need to get an actual life. 
2. The mind numbing randomness of this whole subreddit. 
3. Then seeing a great post like this one and saying to myself "hey, that's pretty cool".

And all is right with the universe once again. This was that post. (And the dryness of the title is the trigger). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw Shaq at The Mall at Millenia last week in Orlando. His size attracts lots of attention. (look at her face) He is a friendly guy to everyone. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 04:09:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 03:42:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which one's normal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 04:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did anyone kick you out of their stores...anyone at all? I didn't think so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 05:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I lost interest when Ramsey went irrational over his kid. But I lean towards being a cynical jerk anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 16:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By her reaction, it wasn't on purpose. Funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 04:25:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think I would have ever guessed that one without the comment section </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:33:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently, the only criminal activity back then were slaves running away. Glad we've got that sorted out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 02:42:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yup...fits with the mildyinteresting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 01:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That didn't look too bad. Almost like her foot scooped him squarely in his torso. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 00:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really a Burns quote, but I liked when they thought Mr. Burns stole a trillion dollar bill and the government was using satellite imagery of Mr. Burns compound to locate the bill. The government guy says, "Using this advanced satellite imagery, we can tell he's not hiding the bill on the roof".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 03:31:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's funny
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 03:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad there are people skeptical to this nonsense and aren't afraid to post it. Yeah to the o.p. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 15:23:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I'm glad you admit the validity of my original comment in that Obama didn't actually stand up for the revolutionaries in Iran, although I don't agree with you that he did nothing because he feared for the safety of the dissidents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 14:38:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obama said it was "up to the Iranians to choose their government, but sometimes their governments acts poorly". That was Obama's way of staying away from the Green Revolution controversy but claiming he was taking a stance, That is a joke. Those words had no different impact than if he really would have said "trust your Mullahs" (which he didn't). But explain exactly how Obama's mild lip-service was anything but a tacit support of the status quo in Iran.
http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/article/318891#.T0xSqdSGBFs.facebook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 03:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Were you allergic to nuts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 03:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> President Obama didn't support the Green Revolution in Iran at all in 2009. He sided with the Mullah's and told the people they should listen to and respect their supreme leaders. That was a blown opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 00:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That picture and headline made me laugh big time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 02:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I demand an explanation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 03:50:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's funny you put the nickle there because I was not actually getting it until my brain processed the coin. Very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-08 04:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fry's dog turned into Dolomite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 03:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All that did was make me hungry for Pop Tarts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 03:44:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was that a $600 iPhone that he dropped into the water? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 01:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was trying to be funny..tee hee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So cool. Is this in New Jersey? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 03:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's dumb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 04:24:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first one with the baby was great. The Trump one made me laugh too. They were all good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 01:56:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a staging area for transportation. Boat or truck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-07 17:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How could the President have missed the last 500 years of history? The point is, Christians had a reformation and no longer are violent. His statement is dumbfounding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:04:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People who wear jeans and sandals. They're trying too hard for the laid back image. Bunch'a d!ckheads if you ask me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 20:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't that the point at being a punk band? Your supposed to be angry. I say good job Governor for tweaking them back into their "sub-culture-ish" attitude of being ticked-off at the man...... about something, or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 02:25:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do they own 50% of the cars. Eat 50% of the food? Utilize 50% of the medicine? Do they buy and hoard any of these? If these 80 people died tomorrow and their money erased it would have zero impact on the remaining 6 billion of us in the world. I could care less how many zeros are on there Merrill Lynch bank statements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-20 02:53:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a terrible argument. Do these 1% own proportionally more houses? More cars than us? Do they use more medicine than us? More food? 

My point is that they do not "hoard" physical assets. Their wealth is merely extra zeros on a bank statement. The well being of us bottom dwellers has nothing to do with how many zero are on THEIR Swiss bank accounts. I don't believe taking up pitchforks and hangman's noose's on the rich will effect one ounce of my prosperity. My livelihood is from the roofing business.  If I charge my neighbor $1,800 to re-shingle their roof and I spend it how I choose, how does that have any relationship with Mark Zuckerburg and his wealth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-18 03:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is why I like Reddit. A perfectly pointless posting that actually amuses me greatly. Well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-23 04:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought they had to have a legitimate value added (at least one they could attempt to explain) as part of their business. For example, part of Amway's value is the claimed value of physically distributing product. Another one, an energy drink pyramid company, distributes the energy drink but most, if not all, of their money doesn't come from the drink sales and distribution, but from the big checks just for "sign ups" below them in the pyramid. That is more questionable than Amway in my opinion. But they claim it's the legitimate drink sales.  Then, the total illegal scams are one's with zero product but just get sign-ups (or money) from down the pyramid. Legit MLM have to have an explainable value added and the government and lawsuits become involved in making the determination if these business "value added" claims are legit..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 03:25:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> look at that skinny-mini in the white tank top. Super nice looking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-21 17:05:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sebastian Buemi at the Shanghai GP in 2010.
 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7En1Q6zuAl4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 17:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>