<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1280</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Local ISP refuses to provide High Speed Internet. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So a friend of mine built his house just on the edge of town and for over a year now local ISP (Eastlink and Bell) refuse to hook him up with high speed internet.
The issue arises from the fact that currently the house across the street (less than 100 ft away) has access to high speed. However, the ISP says they would have to run additional cables to allow my friend to be connected. The kicker...they want him to pay for their infrastructure.
I've got a home being build next door to my friend, even closer to the house with high speed access and doubt I'll be able to have access to it.
We've both been told, "You will be able to have access to our Rural connection, good luck."
Now, considering their current high speed connnectiong is 50 down/ 5 up and their rural is 1.5 down / 0.5 up.... there is literally no way in hell I can handel that bad of a bandwidth. And to top it all off the ISP is going to put a 15 GB data cap on their Rural connectiom starting in the fall.

Tl;dr - Fuck ISP's in rural Nova Scotia, they don't give a shit about their customers or the service they provide, and only care about their bottom line.
It ain't  only comcast that screws people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:45:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watching u/sips_ play this on stream sends my dick into the dark depths of the universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How I feel about Zilien Support... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:39:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 14:04:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maritimes also has bagged milk.
Nova Scotian, can confirm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 04:43:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wellington beefed her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 16:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Shriek is Love, Shriek is Life"
You can assume how it would go... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 12:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "The Reaper is always one step behind me..."
Shadow - FFVI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> $20 Steam Card from Pixel Flashback! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:15:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 02:15:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Always tell people they are " Whale cum" after they thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Shining Force - Review from Pixel Flashback </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 17:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> To all the cute dog couples...Let's rep some cute kitty couples! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 03:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 03:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By donating it to a new, struggling teacher who can't find a permanent job due to cuts to education by an idiotic government?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 04:25:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stone, first man to lose hand from slash and regrow it shortly after to continue playing and throw some punches at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 13:12:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His passive proc will help him out.
Shield based on Max mana and increased burst to spells. 
Makes playing Ryze more of a timing game and less of a spam all the buttons one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 04:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *in the black </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 04:31:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 01:46:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The sound track though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you understand probabilities you will be less frustrated.
Example: If you have a steal rate of 5% for a particular item, thats a 1 in 20 chance  (not great but not terrible), the issue arises when you fail to consider that consecutive steal attempts do not increase the odds of getting the item. Every attempt is still only 5%, it's a common phalicy to believe independent events alter probabilities.
So my advice...be patient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're doing it on an emulator, I'd get a prepatched version from www.fantasyanime.com 
You'll get better translations and just some bug fixes overall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 15:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I find VI to be a very great game that takes a lot of what the series has done and improves upon it (like a long standing series should do).
I would go with IV first just because its a little shorter and a great playthrough.
VI will give you great bang for the time spent playing. Personally, my favorite in the franchise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 02:20:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup.
Was split between plant bio, genetics, ecology and cellular bio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 02:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Introductory college/university level Biology courses usually do a good job laying the ground work for deeper, more focused study.
I found my biology experience in high school didn't give me any kind of advantage for an intro bio course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also live in Snowva Scotia...this winter has sucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-08 00:22:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buy Phantom Dancers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 06:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like to hear Sips talk about old school turn based JRPGs. What's your opinion? Did you play them in your youth? What were somenof you favorites? Any games today that compare to what I'd consider the best genre of games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "We just like to cuddle" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 00:50:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 03:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> D...is for Degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-31 07:52:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you ever smelled mothballs?
How'd you ever get his little legs apart? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-31 03:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hai rekts on Zed....gg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-31 02:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Got Lustboy into better position to bubble -- Kill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 22:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone ranged from 24-26.
Photographers idea on that pose.
Got better ones if anyone cares.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Happy 1st Anniversary to my Wife! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 14:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 01:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Social convention. 
People can't handle things thay go against "social norms". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 01:45:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I too can attest to this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Religious Headwear topic of controversy at DMV for driver's photograph. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-15 00:52:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 21:37:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.barringtonmunicipality.com

Barrington, NS. Canada.
Lobster captial of Canada.
(Nova Scotia I believe is one of the largest [if not the largest] exporter of these delicious crustaciens).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-12 01:53:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is usually the funny ones that have internal struggles that no one knows of.
Can't believe it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Look at these snuggly bastards! (X-post from /catpics) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-09 00:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Look at these snuggly bastards! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-09 00:51:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 00:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either method will yield the same result. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-06 03:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like people who aren't teachers have improper perspective on the job itself. Where as people who are teachers have a "holier than thou" attitude. (Soley based on these posts).

I myself am a high school teacher.
Graduated 3rd (of 115) from my high school and was on the dean's list throughout 4 years while pursuing a BSc (double major in Biology and Psychology,  minor in Earth Science).
I'd like to think I am a relatively intellegent person, who went on to become a teacher. 

That being said, I agree that teaching isnt the toughest job in the world. My wife is an ICU Nurse...and I'd never be able to deal with the shit she does (ie. Shift work and people who could die at the drop of a hat). However,  as she has informed me, she'd never want to do what I do. Stand onfront of (on average) 120 15-17 year old kids and try to teach them things, prepare lessons that are engaging as well ad informative,  handle classroom management (such as that ine kid who just jumped out a window...or that other kid that just full on bitch smacked another kid).
My point is ever job has its difficulties and its easy portions, however until you have 1st hand experience (such that you have got the training, degrees, and job) don't knock it based on preconceived notions and shit experiences you've had with someone who was clearly not good at their job.

For me to get my current postion, I underwent an interview that 14 other applicants also took...but I managed to come out on top. This was after applying for a total of 12 other positions that individuals more experienced than myself recieved. Yes it's true that places are crying for teachers...but the government isn't putting money into education departments to allow for them to come in.


Tl:dr 
I'm was top of my class both in high school and university and became a teacher. My wife's an ICU nurse, I'd never fucking want that job and visa versa. All jobs have pros and cons, don't knock it unless you've actually done the job yourself. I've never smoked marijuana, but I dont condemn people who do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-05 01:20:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best option ever. I was in the same boat.
Rom hacks = OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 22:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahri.... no explanation needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 19:00:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried this for hours...finally managed to get 0:0:0.....only to realize I hit it right on and need to get below that time.  
Most infuriating elixer I ever recieved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 18:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 7-9 summoning s are pretty sweet. Making sure you get all the hidden ones is key! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Meet our new kittens: Belle and Prince </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 13:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 18:16:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sabin is a bit OP early game.
But, with proper esper equipped leveling you can make any and every character OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 18:05:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can get an early Genji Glove when you enter The Returners Hideout.
When Banon askes you to be their "last hope" say "no" three times. Before you leave the hideout a random underling will pop up and give you one of the best relics in the game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Minecraft Quakecraft! Check out one of the better game modes created online! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-02 23:19:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 21:48:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tales of Phantasia plx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fight It Out! Playing some MMX2! Watch us put out Flame Stag and squash Morph Moth! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 01:01:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-01 17:28:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Team name : EWreckShen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-01 17:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All the agreement.  Even having them as custom games would make life more enjoyable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TMNT: TIT Finale! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-21 23:32:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Loadout! Come watch us kill ourselves! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-16 01:35:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We're Back! Another Episode of TMNT: Turtle in Time! This time, with more suckage from Saul! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-14 23:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-13 11:29:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Appologizes for the lack of 720p. 
I blame Saul. This was the first video I let him edit...and he obviously screwed it. 
Privileges revoked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MMX Let's Play! Ep 12, Killing Bosses and Taking Names! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-10 04:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Our First Look At Loadout! Love Dat Arena Shooter! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-09 00:24:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mega Man X - Storm Eagle (plus secrets) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-31 22:20:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mega Man X Opening Stage Guitar Cover! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-30 23:31:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mega Man X Play through! FIght It Out! Come watch a couple Canadians try their hand at Mega Man X! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-16 23:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fight It Out! Couple of Crazy Canucks playing obscure video games! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-04 17:08:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New YouTube Channel!?! Fight It Out! A couple of crazy Canucks playing obscure video games! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-04 15:59:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New YouTube Channel! Couple of Crazy Canucks Playing Obscure Video Games! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 12:21:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New YouTube Channel?! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-01 20:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>