<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5096</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What actors do you want to do famous roles? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:25:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I selfishly made this because the guy from person of interest would make a great James bond.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:25:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't get why feminists don't go after stuff that is genuine inequality like female genital mutilation or even something like not being able to drive. But that doesn't affect them so they find stuff that might potentially affect them in their first world country. I'd be 100% behind the movement if they focused on actual issues but none of those issues affect them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:07:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bad timing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow OK I can't think of a way to say this without getting ripped on and down voted to hell and I know this was just for fun. But how has nobody here considered the cumulative time you've wasted of all the people you've done this to after pulling them over?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:57:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 19:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did they get the battery to last five momths]? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 09:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Half the movie is in Chinese and the subtitles are in arabic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 09:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think its out on DVD yet so it would just be some shaky shitty quality video of a theater screen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 10:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Talking to a cop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 08:54:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So without knowing anything, you've accused me of committing a traffic violation, said I'm a bad driver and ruined someone's day. BTW she slammed the brakes on the highway because of a plastic bag and said that to insurance. /r/protectandserve at its normal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 08:25:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup theres the blame shifting I've come to expect from p s. Don't get me wrong, other subs would still blame me but because I talked to a cop when I didn't need to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 07:57:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I saw something on king5 last week about some podunk in Washington buying military heavy vehicles. So yeah... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why not just ask mercer island for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just got a ticket after getting in my first accident. I felt like shit about the damage to my car and then up walks a cop who I mistakenly talk to. Next thing I know, I'm handed a $200 ticket. Why? Just to add insult to injury? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 07:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm from Wyoming and whenever I get jealous about their free apartments I just about their what their  great grandfathers went through and I kinda undersrand. But I'm still jealous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where on 5th street is that? Or is that the viaduct in the background? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:58:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have a brand of choice? I've heard long lasting kind has more dextro dxm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 09:24:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh a nipple that looks like a dick. I was thinking dick that looks a nipple. This makes more sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 11:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because this bugging me. Look up my history and check out the post titled "I cheated on my bitch." I saw the joke a mile away its just not original or funny so I ignored it. About the other stuff, I don't see any point in talking to someone so close minded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 10:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 07:48:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I think they're just cops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 07:46:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow that kid looked scared shirtless at the end when the thug was punching him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:54:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boy you sure told me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:14:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I'm not allowed to call a random asshole on the internet an asshole just because he's a cop? Oh and I also noticed similarities between the downvote brigade and the blue wall of silence. 

You just want drama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:43:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What? Who are you? Why did you write me a condescending paragraph? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 08:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. You have a good night too

Edit:  Even this got down voted too? Blue wall of silence knows no bounds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 08:03:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OK I think we're done. Thanks for your input </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 07:52:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So just be grateful for what we have and don't complain?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 07:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just bored but think down voting someone you don't agree with is asystematic to our problem of bully police and the blue wall of silence that protects them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 06:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Since we're being honest I'm affaid for my country when the blue wall of silence condemns someone who thinks that cussing out a softball ref isnt funny and silences my feelings on that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 05:13:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it crazy or are you being sarcastic? I can't tell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 04:30:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People lie on the internet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 04:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean MLB where you're in the stands. If you think its OK to cuss out a ref to his face then you're just an asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 03:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I meant the swearing at a ref part. If it was baseball I might understand, but softball? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sound like someone I never want to run into. Scary to think you have a gun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 01:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about dogs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:52:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You just say that because you have princes who fight dragons and evil wizards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-21 07:13:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he's like Stephen Colbert  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 07:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first thirty seconds of this and the first thirty seconds of his 9/11 show are exactly the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:51:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its funny that's what I think about so I don't cum early </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 04:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can't OD on shrooma but saying so does make the cop who can't take down someone tripping on shrooms more heroic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 22:54:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well at least nobodys gonna get shot over this... Right...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 07:07:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hide money in books. Check ur books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 06:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once when I was arrested I asked the cop if he ever smoked weed when he was young, he said he never got caught and laughed as he pushed me into his backseat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can someone please help me do math. Which is cheaper per volume/alcohol content- a handle of vodka costing $18 or 24oz steel reserves costing 1.50? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 05:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The vodka handle costs $10, the rest is Washington state tax btw

And the steelies are 8% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 03:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to think that I invented egg drop soup by dropping an egg in top ramen. Turns out some Asian did it before me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 07:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn. ur a genius  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 17:24:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I keep my Gameboy in my bathroom and only have pokemon yellow. I play pokemon whenever I have to shit, I call it poopoo pokemon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 16:59:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nice try but I forget </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:48:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He looks like a down syndrome kid that got recalled to the manufacturer and came back normal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah he seems like a genuine nice guy. I forgot to say that was part 1. here's part 2
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DZjbQPhduVk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 'Freeway' Rick Ross on the Jim Norton show (starts at 10 minute mark) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 17:40:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 09:14:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why would you let it live? it's your civic duty to kill those things before they multiply </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 08:12:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hobbits gettin karma for isengard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 02:32:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always wondered what's the point of recording a cop if they can just delete it. is there an app that sends video to a server? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so compare to number of postal workers who kill dogs instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:23:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a better statistic to judge the misconduct of police is how many dogs US police kill compared to UK police. the UK probably haven't killed any, hard to do with a baton, while there's a whole subreddit to US police killing dogs /r/puppycide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 15:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone assumes reedit is so anti police that any sentiment close to that is immediately disregarded  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 15:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What I want to know is how many dogs US cops kill compared to how many dogs UK cops kill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 13:41:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that was my point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 09:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Detective Patrick Cherry has been removed from the departments elite Joint Terrorism Task Force and will be doing desk duty until he is officially transferred out of the prestigious division."

your title makes it sound like he was fired, he wasn't. he was transferred. no justice at all here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 09:22:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Detective Patrick Cherry has been removed from the departments elite Joint Terrorism Task Force and will be doing desk duty until he is officially transferred out of the prestigious division."

your title makes it sound like he was fired. he wasn't fired at all, just transferred.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 11:22:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who the fuck do you think you are? You a fucking lawyer? Dont get smart with me, boy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 18:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a minute ago I watched a video on r/videos of a party girl who passed out in her car on the freeway. everyone in the comments gave her the benefit of the doubt, but he's homeless so fuck him right. it's on the front page of r/videos right now btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 17:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what makes you think he was drunk? looking for half a cigarette in the ashtray is something all homeless who smoke do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 17:09:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's called premeditated assault... he knew he was gonna have to mess with the guy's bleeding unconscious body  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 17:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that interviewer was pretty good guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 17:28:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> took me way too long to realize skiing isn't some Slovenian word and she's not a queen. not even high </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 08:22:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> joking aside, why would any cop be against this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:46:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm no animal fucker, but I think that's a cow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 07:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah sucks stargate got canceled  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 06:42:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they get too much hype and are pretty weak. try heroin instead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 18:51:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what's the single best episode, if i don't have time because i have a meeting and children to pick up n shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 09:22:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you can hear the sound of the bell some stores make when you open the door. doesn't make sense for a house and we never heard that before, but that shittily let's you know the door was opened. but maybe the cops were waiting inside the house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 09:02:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've watched that ending a dozen times and his face doesn't change at all. the only thing to give a hint is the sound of boots on pavement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> question about the ending of The Drop. spoilers maybe. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 05:14:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so the woman says she'll go get her jacket and he's waiting there. and then we hear really loud footsteps sounding like running. did she go to the cops?

aquarion, blassreiter, gankutsuou, gad guard, kite, md geist, now and then, shigurui, slayers, xxxholic, 009 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 23:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it fell less than a foot. I bet he plays soccer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 09:51:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how did you try to do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 13:00:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's because it's rare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 07:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when I was in middle school our DARE officer got suspended for using cocaine. I've cheated so many drug tests during high school and i'm sure that cops get more leeway than I did. these guys must be retarded

just tape the synthetic piss it to your thigh because they make you hike up your pants to your knees, and also pee on the outside of the bottle because sometimes they smell it. and make sure to follow the directions to have it at the right temperature. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'd give her a night. I have no standards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really want know what she said just after the video ended. "the fact that women have been shut out of dangerous..." 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i give up trying to make an alright pirate deck. can someone please share theirs with me? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 21:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 14:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I call bullshit. not that you did this, only that alcohol is solely to blame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 07:27:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't get me wrong, fuck republicans and all that. but if this senator was republican this post would be on the front page with 3000 comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 03:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant wait to be outraged by the verdict that they're too young to know that stabbing someone causes death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 01:59:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. hope you have a nice day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what's the name of that subreddit where some guy posts random sequences of numbers and theres a conspiracy theory about it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 01:51:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 21:50:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live near seattle and i'm pretty sure I've had this beer before. it came in a golden or yellow 24oz can and was really good. too expensive for me though (around $3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 17:50:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nope, I can't. well actually I can get one but not two </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:16:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> did anyone actually think that putting any kind of smoke in your lungs is healthy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 12:44:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> was he still on dope then? he looks pinnned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-09 20:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the driver is a Saudi so he'll probably beat the worker too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 11:44:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. hope you didn't do that on my account. too bad shroom season is still a few months off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 11:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you don't happen to know what episode that was do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 06:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no, death for yelling and screaming the morning after new years on the train. completely justified in my opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 10:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I had to punch you and knock you out because I was concerned for your health because you might have been smoking marijuana" 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 10:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a handle or a fifth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-01 17:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because a shaman is a great authority on western culture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 22:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a hard reset is always holding down all the buttons at once. usually fixes most problems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 06:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well, that's the job he took </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 04:07:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no doug Stanhope?

edit: no doug stanhope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 12:35:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> actually while I was off on the shoulder, two other crashes occurred. I think a presidential candidate was in town 

but is that your way of saying giving a ticket to someone who just crashed their car is justified? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 09:47:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I forget, there was an unlit underpass and traffic was going smooth up until then where traffic stopped. completely my fault as I told the cop. traffic was about 50mph until the unlit overpass where traffic was stopped. my fault  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 09:07:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "this guy is making too much sense, better downvote him rather than talk to him" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 08:43:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I gathered that. I also got a ticket after I was in an accident. 

don't just ignore an opinion you don't agree with or so you can meet your quota without feeling bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 08:33:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> driver got in an accident, give him a ticket too. and you wonder why people hate cops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 01:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> can the other guy see when i'm fucking about with the features on the board? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 00:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 22:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you don't have siblings. i'm kinda in the same boat and Christmas was hell. seriously I have never wanted to kill myself more than during holidays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 06:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you know, you're probably right and I can't find where it was mentioned before. probably just a conspiracy theory or something. but i'm sure i'm read something bout it on reddit. anyways thanks for being cool about me being wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 04:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just look at any of the times it was posted on reddit. usually one of the highest comments explains it. how I heard it was fake was on reddit so i'm sure you can find it if you look </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 03:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> anyone know if this is fake like the American south episode or if it's real this time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 00:56:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably empty and in the trash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 15:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't make it that far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 11:23:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how many dogs have UPS, FedEx and Postal worker killed combined? FUCKING ZERO. cops are pussies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 09:45:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my problem with feminism is that feminists never focus on actual problems but instead only stuff they think affects them. there are plenty of problems concerning women in the middle east and i'd be 100 percent behind any feminist who addresses them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-18 08:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "police officers don't meet the same consequences that the general public would experience in the same scenario"

how many dogs have UPS or FedEx or USPS drivers killed? zero. cops? too many to count. i was a seasonal driver helper and got bitten by a dog. didn't even report it. there should be a cowardice test along with the other ones

if a post office worker kicked a dog that was biting him, he would lose his job. but a cop shooting a golden retriever? guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-18 05:27:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yea, never realized until now how autistic George costanza was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 18:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's not that. just that once hard a was allowed to be sold in grocery stores liquor stores couldn't compete.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 17:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I once tried to have a civilized conversation with someone there, but it was like talking with a cop... oh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 17:14:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> washington </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 08:02:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not that much drinking in either of them. but thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 07:48:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish my state still had liquor stores. just bought a ten dollar handle of vodka that cost me almost twenty with tax. and had to wait in line with judgmental assholes. I worked an overnight shift you cunts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 07:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my buddy was the first legal weed bike dealer in Washington state. his pack consists of weed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 06:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's because those states have already legalized medical marijuana for awhile now. nobody is going to buy a $40 gram if they can get a $10 gram or $15 dollar (medical) of same shit. 

two things I hate about this subreddit - people just can't connect two simple dots. and this post has 200 upvotes but only 10 comments. people think upvoting a post within this little subreddit of people who already smoke weed is helping the cause </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> looking for anime with lots of drug use or heavy drinking </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 06:47:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's gotta be English dubbed. and preferably action with cool fight scenes. thanks

on a side note, also looking for action anime with art style similar to afro samurai or redline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> looking for a dubbed anime with lots of drug use and or heavy drinking. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 04:30:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pretty much any anime with drug use fits the bill but action is a bonus. i'm looking for something where drinking is more than just a quirk like eating a lot or sleeping a lot and defines the character. or really any anime where drug use is common </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 00:05:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4 steps on how to use a dildo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-06 06:44:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you write really well. write the next game of thrones. George r martin probably gets hella bitches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anime with lots of drug use or heavy drinking </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 15:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> looking for any anime with lots of drug use </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 15:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 06:20:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah I've worked UPS driver helper a couple seasons and at the start of a day when the truck is fully loaded, some packages will get stepped on to get to ones in the back. it can't be helped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 19:02:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is the zoo decklist he posted the best one? is there a better zoo deck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 02:00:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol that's the definition of the word, retard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 01:22:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was right.  http://www.ushistory.org/franklin/philadelphia/fire.htm

I won't bother to call you a retard, but why do foreigners always care so much about America anyways? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 00:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> didn't benjamin franklin invent firefighters? what did the rest of the world do before, just watch shit burn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 19:00:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what does getting shot feel like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 06:14:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the art and the that title "master of disguise" sounds badass

also its just 1 health off from being a yeti but its special is really useful when I get a 8/3 bloodsail raider (which is a 2 drop) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 05:02:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just got from rank 20 to 16 today with just this deck. I played a few hours today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 04:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't have those and I really want to enchant my first legendary, but yeah I really want a blade furry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 04:24:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> give it a shot man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 08:54:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> does the producer have tits?

DN episode 9 next </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 06:17:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he broke through the autism spectrum into infrared colors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 12:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there's a weakened version of 211? that seems unbelievable because it would be more expensive to dilute the shit than change the label on the cans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 09:35:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the alcohol tax in washingoton state forces me to. i'm not made out of money, cutie. I drink steel reserves like a champ. i'd rather drink whiskey but I can't afford it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 06:50:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I corrected the I;m to I'm  so now everyone should be be on the same page :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 05:00:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I fessed up when I went in for cigs today and she said "no beer tonight?" in hindsight I should have stocked up on more booze so it wasn't suspicious. she acted like she was cool with it, but I could tell she was hurt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I cheated on my bitch last night </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:25:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it was after midnight and i was more than a few beers deep but didn't have any more in the house. so i went to the only store open, I'm sorry. i didn't mean to cheat on you but you were closed. i still love you and value our relationship. i made a mistake and hate myself for it, but lets just move on ok honey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 04:08:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> congrats man. i'm saving up for a dualsport because i'm right at where you were on my fourth steel reserve tallboy right now. I need one so I don't drink so much and feel better about myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 05:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm playing a lot of hearthstone now. my account is Dionysus#1697 in the Americas if anyone else plays hearthstone add me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-27 18:45:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> obviously never played slime-grenade wars, put firecrackers on slugs and throw them at each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 15:58:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> widespread panic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 15:31:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah add me if im not too late ! Dionysus#1697

anybody add me and we'll play eventually whenever i'm on, just ask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Light] At the movie theater I chose to sit far away from a black couple because I thought they might talk a lot during the movie </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 23:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> At the movie theater, I chose to sit far away from a black couple because I was worried they would talk a lot during the movie. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 04:48:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 07:25:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't drink a couple days ago for the whole day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 07:24:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fried cheese. just place on a pan until crispy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-31 20:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nobody has ever said that about anyone who has dependents or children. and nobody has ever said that about opiates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-31 10:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you, that actually helps a lot. but whats the difference between decks used for tournaments and normal decks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-31 08:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know you could right click them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> where can I see deck lists that really good people use? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-30 10:07:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 00:36:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> jesus Christ that's disgusting, just use tissues like a normal person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-27 22:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> shamalongadingdong

also, cheez-its are the shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-27 07:37:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> in highschool I had to do a two page presentation on if I was for against the death penalty, my whole presentation was about batman. batman doesn't kill people and he's my role model so I think death penalty is wrong, for my research I listed comic books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 10:08:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I knew someone here could help me out. thanks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 09:48:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no i didn't intend for that to happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 07:58:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alright, thanks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I accidentally drank out the bottle I put my cigarettes out in yesterday, and now everything tastes sour and shitty and I cant get the taste out my mouth no matter how many times I've brushed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 06:12:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-05 08:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> will you marry me? I can be gay  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 21:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sounds like someone has a case of the Republicans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-02 12:12:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why do other countries have such a fascination with America? we're a country too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> LPT: use crushed ice when you want a drink to get cold fast and cubed ice when you want a drink to stay cold for awhile </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 09:36:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because surface area and shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 01:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how did you get the paperwork? and how much was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 09:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lucky there's video to back him up, could have seriously fucked his life up if those passengers were "witnesses" against him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 01:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't get how someone can claim to be poor but then it comes out that they have 15 family members... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 02:01:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I put weed in my soda cup when a cop stopped me one time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 13:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> go for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 23:31:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he looks like a down syndrome kid that got recalled to the manufacturer and came back normal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 13:06:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> too late motherfucker I got my answers. better luck next time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-20 04:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so about 6 feet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-20 04:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I meant how high would the building have to be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-20 04:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> widespread panic! unfortunately, youtube is lacking in album recordings. but they are one of the best concert bands so its ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love their fries. but everything else they serve is nasty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:23:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hahahahahahahahaha that makes me feel a little better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 13:46:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what does it mean when poo is green? lack of protein or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what's the worst thing you've tasted? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 13:18:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:56:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> awesome!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> looking for someone chill to play with! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my game name is Dionysus#1697 in the Americas

I've never played against a friend before and i really want to. don't worry, i disenchanted all my priest, shaman, and druid cards so i could make a pirate deck.. i mean a deck that has 5 pirates in it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:16:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey i'm looking for someone to play with. except i don't know how to do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what does miracle mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:12:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey man let's play a game! i'm definitely casual because i disenchanted all my priest, druid, and shaman cards so i could make a pirate deck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:11:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also want to know this because i disenchanted all my priest, shaman, and druid cards so i could do a pirate deck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-17 11:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I interviewed for a dishwashing job at whole foods. I made the mistake of cracking a couple jokes during the group interview. got a call saying I didn't get the job because I didn't take it seriously enough. I responded by apologizing profusely and promised I take washing dishes very seriously, they changed their mind and offered me the job. I refused </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-17 09:11:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when he stressed equal weight of butter and flour, does volume vs weight really make that much of a difference?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-15 09:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh cool, thanks. I heard something like 64,000 peopleattended </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-15 09:42:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's really fucking cool. goodwill is on olive st right? i'll have to check that out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-15 09:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> did Dempsey or that other sounders defender play in the game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-14 02:40:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry about your balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 12:49:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm sorry that people downvoted this. some people don't care for it much, that's cool idk people be hating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 11:01:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when I needed money I sold my car and bought a motorcycle. I should learn about food stamps, I'm sure I qualify. its pretty ridiculous that someone with two cars can get food stamps, she learned how to abuse the system and wrote an article about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-28 22:40:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha thanks buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-28 22:10:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah it has a carb. and i'm using a glass screen. i just stuck a stem down the stem and thats working ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-28 22:09:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> using a glass screen, doesnt help. but thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-24 08:58:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> friend's house got broken into and his xbox was stolen. the police told him they had a suspect in mind and that this suspect had a record. friend knew i had a criminal record (marijuana) so he calls my house phone and accused me of stealing his xbox. my dad beat me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 20:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe you spilt booze on it and there's a heating vent under your dresser? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-05 04:27:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she forgot her purse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> in anticipation of Godzilla, i had to watch Monsters again. what are some other good movies that not many people know about? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-26 20:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> monster or apocolypse movies would be great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-25 23:57:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my buddy has a wifi stealer. it's like an antennae that steals wifi from like a mile away. he takes it when he goes on road trips too. its a little expensive but its a 1 time cost and lasts for life. i'm thinking about getting one when i get my motorcycle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-25 22:32:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't really get how some alchies can have such interested lives. i buy bulk liquor and cheap beer and drink at home while i swear at my playstation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> looking for a dogfighting anime. or any anime about the frontlines of war (hopefully realistic warfare) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-25 22:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> really really want a realistic dogfighting anime (not mecha)

edit: first my post gets removed because it didn't have a body, then my post was almost removed because i forgot flair. why does this subreddit have to be so difficult? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 11:05:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> please don't let me keep you up because of me. really, i'm sorry if i'm keeping you awake. if you want to, tell me your highlights. anything that stick out in your memory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 10:55:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and you say you can't get easy pussy... lol. just figure out a good segway like say your still in the music business and tell these stories. you will get aids and die a happy man lol;. 

i have a lot of questions but they might by after you met the bands:
1. i heard that Spoonman was still somewhat homeless after his fame with soundgarden, do you know what they paid him?
2. do you know why layne staley left alice in chains to go to mad season? granted mad season would have been huge if they made more than one album </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 10:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you're so lucky. i really want to know more about him but don't want to waste your time, so my second question is why you punched curt cobain did you really knock him out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 10:26:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn sounds like you had an awesome experience. please don't let me keep you awake or refresh reddit- but my first question is about layne staley- what was he like? what point in his career did you meet him? what do you know about his downward spiral? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 10:15:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just got an idea while i was pissing- do your AMA in r/seattle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 10:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you have to do an AMA right fucking now! i have so many questions but there may be things i forget to ask that other people with think of. please. maybe a CA AMA if you dont want to get flooded with messages?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 09:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well i would still love to hear about your time hangin out with those bands. maybe you could do an AMA sometime or something like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 09:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do you still live in seattle? i linked you to a Mad Season song before i saw that you hung out with alice in chains. i did my college essay on Spoonman. if you're still in seattle lets grab a few drinks sometime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 09:12:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey op - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fm72DPJCX58

mad season - river of deceit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 08:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do to but only when I camp. But I did steal someone's hub cap one time to use as a base so I didnt start a forest fire. I put it on the roof of their car in the morning burnt and charred. Feel bad about that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 07:24:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn, thanks i had no idea that was possible. i was thinking about making them out of skateboard wheels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 03:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Mexican officials late Saturday said he was apprehended with a man identified as Carlos Manuel Hoo Ramirez, contradicting earlier reports that he was arrested with a woman."

#REKT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 03:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he posted it to a different subreddit each time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 03:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i like your other video too. any damage to the motorcycle? i wonder if i should put sliders on my supermoto after i get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-21 05:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> school security guard put a boot on my car so i took off the tire, took the boot off, put tire back on and was driving away when he came out. he pulled me out of my car and searched my car without permission (later he said i gave him permission) and found a bb gun i forgot about. when i went to jail i spilt some hot ham juice on my foot and got a huge blister bubble (hot ham juice is the most dangerous weapon in jail, that shit was over 100 degrees) but aside from that jail was pretty cool. just watched family guy and played cards and read all day, got 3 meals a day and could take a shower whenever i wanted. i kinda want to go back to jail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-21 05:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they chose that job so they could abuse their authority and go on power trips, that's what appealed to them and made them go after those jobs. nobody wants to look closely at people's assholes but i guess domination over other people outweighed the downside for them. i hope none of the reddit mods decide to be prison guards, that's a scary thought </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-20 05:05:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if i ever cried i would die of dehydration. i'm like the people in Dune  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-20 04:54:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my piss tastes like Rainier or Rainier tastes like my piss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-20 04:52:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 
"yeah me and my playstation are gonna have a wild night." i might also try to finish that movie i have watched every night this week but only remember a few more minutes of it everytime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-20 04:42:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i've lived in seattle my whole life and never done any of the cool stuff on that site. never even been to the spaceneedle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-17 07:44:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> jpepe is a poop name. unless your last name is pepe then i'm sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-10 05:24:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> light has energy, when it encounters an object it pushes it a little bit so you weigh more when the lights are on NASA has to account for light when it goes on long missions. chicago weighs 300 pounds more when its sunny, faggot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-10 05:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm have to remember that line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-05 23:57:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not for OP's friend now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 21:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> starring that one black girl in that movie where she overcomes adversity and hardship, while being oppressed into having to attend school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 07:58:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i guess i shouldn't of pissed on my laptop. but maybe the fucker deserved it, i don't remember </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 07:52:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what is Grain belt? i'm a washingtonian and love my craft beers too, especially when i go down to oregon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 07:50:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i keep a beer koozie in my shower so i can hawaiin hotbox and drink cold beers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-24 23:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look on the bright side, you might just have parkinsons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-19 02:28:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Widespread panic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-10 05:35:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I sleep good. When I used to sleep sober I'd hum the cat-dog cartoon song to sleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-09 04:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something just downloaded onto my phone when I clicked that link. Better not have a fucking penis on my phone now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-05 23:49:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're shoes will be fine. You don't want to know what my wallets been throu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-05 23:42:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's disgusting I would smell like piss for weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 03:47:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you please shoot a video of like a dozen guys titty fucking an obese woman with different parts of fat on her body? Please. And then link to me after?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 03:46:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really want to watch a video of like a dozen guys titty fucking an obese woman with different parts of fat on her body. Sadly no such video exists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 03:23:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I had the shower running so nobody would hear the lotion and to get the water hot. But I came too fast the water was cold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 03:21:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone know if a video exists of like a dozen guys titty fucking an obese woman at the same time but with different parts of fat on her body? I need this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 02:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We accept him! We accept him! One of us! One of us! Gooble gobble! Gooble gobble! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 02:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just tasted my cum too! Parents wanted to Skype with relatives so I took a shower and unrolled the hose. I was on my back and meant to cum on my shirt but came too hard. Fuckin Jenni lee... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 03:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i asked my dad for a zip (an ounce of weed) when i meant to ask my friend dave. i then told him a zip meant a full tank of gas because i panicked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-24 18:35:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "if marriage didn't exist would you invent it? would you say to your girlfriend, 'hey baby. this shit's so good let's get the government in on it. i love you so much let's get lawyers and judges involved'" - doug stanhope (paraphrased) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-24 02:31:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $10,000 bail = $1,000 bond. his family left him in there because they didn't want to lose $1,000? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-23 05:44:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i would rather have someone who does drugs in congress than someone who never has or sucked at using drugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-22 22:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pterodactyl   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-19 22:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm sure you can find the whole thing on reddit in 5 minute clips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-17 21:17:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> men can't be raped you faggot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-17 20:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i didn't ask to be circumcised  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-17 19:41:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so since it doesn't go through my stomach would i still piss myself? or would i piss out my asshole? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 02:44:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wasn't expecting that. have some of [this](http://31.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lryu9iTeb31r3bm2co1_500.jpg) and some of [this!](http://31.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ls3scfgKRT1qjcf0do1_500.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 02:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's what i've been doing for awhile but doesn't seem to work. i tried swishing hydrogen peroxide around in my mouth but that always gets me close to puking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 02:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow thank you. thanks a lot. how much toothpaste should i put in though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 02:33:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i usually only smoke when i drink. and average 1.5 cups of coffee a day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 02:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "In this moment, I am euphoric. Not because of any phony god's blessing. But because, I am enlightened by my intelligence."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 02:29:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fighting ninjas in the backyard and using pine cones as grenades. no wonder they gave me special education </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> do whitening strips work? is there a cheaper way to whiten teeth? i smoke and drink too much coffee </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-16 02:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 04:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i would dress as a hobo and hold a sign that says "single mother, please help. god bless" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 04:06:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i drank my piss when i thought it was beer. it tasted kinda like oxygenated beer so i took another sip, then i realized. i also drank chewing tobacco spit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 04:03:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Joe Camel](http://eppy7890.files.wordpress.com/2009/06/joe_camel.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 06:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> these fucking assholes call them munchies and they put pretzels in them. what kind of sick bastard would do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 03:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fuck munchies. who the fuck thought it would be a good idea to put pretzels in them? i give the pretzels to my dog so he'll drink beer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 02:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my mom stole my weed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 02:04:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i was forced to go to NA awhile ago. i think that if you want to stop drinking then you should go. why wouldn't you go if there's a small chance it will help you reach your goal? yes it's extremely religious but that only takes up a few minutes of it, the rest is about hearing other talk openly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-13 20:19:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i want to, i just don't know where or how to start </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-13 20:18:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how do i go about learning more about a PC? the audio on my laptop stopped working so i learned how to uninstall the audio driver and then restore my laptop to how it is when you first buy it. but that's all i know how to do know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 21:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do you have the one of the dog with the smile? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 03:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i understand why the US gives so many billions of dollars to Israel, but at some point it's like we're financing terrorism... again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 16:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i hope he gets compensation for this happening to him and i really hope those officers lose their jobs, but any money he receives comes from tax payers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-31 07:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you're old enough to shoot people and get shot at for your country but not old enough to smoke a cigarette? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-24 07:56:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> remember to stay hydrated buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-22 20:34:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i guess there's a benefit that all japanese teenagers never leave their room </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-22 06:43:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how did he only shoot 3 people? does he have parkinson's disease? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-19 15:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i just watched Person of Interest and thought that guy would make the perfect batman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-19 13:41:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't know. i'd rather not have a job and still get paid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-17 17:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well i guess it's ok as long as it's on purpose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> looking for an anime where the main character is an alcoholic or drug addict. or any anime where drug use is prevalent. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-16 03:19:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> do people get sucked out of a plane if there's a hole in the plane? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-05 06:53:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 11:43:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think so too because i've heard dogs try to run when they sleep. can dogs talk to other dogs like humans talk?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 11:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> from an economic standpoint, in a world without countries the currency would be the same. so we would be better able to help the sick the sick and poor right? 

thank you obliging my stupid mind. i would love to have a discussion about this but i'm pretty drunk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:55:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do you think that dogs have dreams when they sleep? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:52:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nothing that communistic. i was just thinking of either

1. countries without borders: which might make the rich richer and the poor poorer but would help the desperate. 

2. a unified world: which has the potential for disaster or peace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:48:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do dogs dream? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:36:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't know but if the love of my life looks through my stuff she will see people like me and will contact me and we will meet and then she will be grossed out but not before i smell her and take some of her hair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:31:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i just delete my posts that get bad karma. except the ones i think are funny even if no one else does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> would the world be better off without borders or countries? what would be the most humane way to do this? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:29:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> without borders everyone could be happy but there's a chance that everyone could be sad. with borders some people are happy and some are sad and the happy people want to separate themselves from the sad people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:17:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how does this affect me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 07:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i liked the story. don't worry about about knives it'll be ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 07:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> awesome! my mom works for the IRS and we're going to the movies tomorrow now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> (request) i want an anime with with lots awesome action and not much filler please. maybe something like the second season of full metal panic </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-30 09:44:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-30 07:19:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's been awhile but i think i just didn't like their design. it reminded me of that old game Space Invaders  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-30 05:47:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mainly i didn't like the new enemy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-30 03:53:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i keep thinking about gurran lagann because i dropped it after it jumped ahead in time. i wonder how it ends, but i don't really want to watch it anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-27 01:30:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can't believe i'm the only one wondering why they don't just clean the bathrooms and kitchens? are all of them just waiting for someone else to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-26 04:10:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't like it when that woman talks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-24 02:07:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can't get food stamps because my parents claim me as a dependant, but don't feed me enough. where's my government assistance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-24 01:47:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Darker than Black maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-21 01:37:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> more like BUTTom lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 23:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no its not. try it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 22:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> evan williams   sriracha sauce. thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> try putting a little sriracha sauce or any chili sauce in your beer and let me know what you think. i'm liking it a lot </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 22:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its good in whiskey too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-10 11:42:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you just told two girls (who i assume are friends because you have liked both for 3 years) that you like them both? fuck man. please keep updating this journal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-07 01:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there should be Underground Olympics. 

stealing - it can be an art and if you get caught, it can also be exercise. put the athletes in any store with any security measures and judge them on how cleanly they get away and what they steal. 

assassination - give the athletes a target and paintball guns

graffiti - judge on the art and the lengths it took to tag that shit

cop chases - think ghost rider  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-06 20:09:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> last night i was swinging a chair around because i heard that that badass ancient warriors worked out by swinging a heavy mace around. the chair broke but luckily nothing else did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-06 20:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> go rob a church. unless you believe in god. then don't do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-06 19:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when you truly don't give a fuck you would say "i would fuck buffy the vampire so hard she pees" instead of "i don't give a fuck" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 16:52:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RIP Mexico City council </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-04 18:49:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is why I always carry hot sauce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-02 18:33:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> aren't you a little young and skinny for a bike like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-31 05:13:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think the scooby doo shapes taste better than plain old noodle shapes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-30 23:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe i'm a lightweight but it would take me over a week to drink all that icewater </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-30 21:56:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i just wanted tissues
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-29 00:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm looking at KLR650's as my first bike... what's this doohickey mod?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-25 05:47:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm in the same boat as you OP. i actually fit your description too. i've been looking at KLR 650s and DR650s so far. they seem to be pretty cheap and durable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-20 21:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what's farkle mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-20 04:37:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what's a valve? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-19 10:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats a good one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-16 05:28:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you for this, helps a lot. money is my main concern so i think i'm getting a KLR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-16 05:05:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah i would like a DRZ more but it's a lot more expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-16 05:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm missing something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i can't decide between a klr650 and a drz400sm for my first bike. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-16 03:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> which is better for a 6 foot 3 tall person? 

which is easier for a beginner to ride? 

which is more durable/long lasting? needs less maintenance?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-16 03:38:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why flatten the tires? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> About how much would it cost to make a dirt bike street legal? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 05:06:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:43:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how did the photographer get in the stall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 12:58:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wheelie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-21 11:17:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. Which one were you talking about though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-20 19:41:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what's the difference between a dual sport and supermoto? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-16 15:52:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i loaned $500 to a "friend" and now she's ignoring my calls and texts except for when i call from a different phone, then she hangs up. i have no way to get the money back because she moved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-16 07:14:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but now what are they going to rape? oh yeahh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 04:12:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 18:19:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i took speech therapy for about 3-4 years (elementary and middle school) and that only made my problem and anxiety worse because it was always on my mind. and that was when my parents paid for it, i can't afford it now anyways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 18:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but then i would have to piss ten times before i get a buzz going </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 16:43:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i won't remember. but thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 16:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm friends with most of the cashiers and they don't check my ID. i'll bring it up next time i go in but i don't want to cost anyone their job even if he was a dick. fucking effort went into this grammar. hope you appreciate all my spellchecks haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Having a speech impediment sucks. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 15:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never been able to pronounce the letter R. Speech therapy didn't help so i'm stuck with it and with my stutter, and i've always been pretty embarrassed about it so i don't talk much. I just got off work, i work overnights (9pm to 6am) and went to go buy a couple steel reserves at one of my usual stores. Some new guy was working and after the pleasantries and he took my ID, he said he wouldn't sell me the beer because i'm slurring my words. i told him that i have a speech impediment and i can't pronounce the letter R, and that i just got off work so i can't be drunk yet. then he changed his mind and started ringing me up again, but i couldn't help myself and muttered something like "this is fucking nuts." he asked what i said so i said it again, and then he changed his mind again and wouldn't ring me up. 

i had to go across town to get my beer and am drinking pretty heavily now. i only wanted a couple beers but now i'm getting shitfaced because i don't want to face that i'm always going to sound like a fucking cartoon character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 04:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just curious, what would be a good price for it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-04 13:11:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want that bike for my first bike too but craigslist isn't helping me out. Where did you get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-01 06:25:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks, that clears things up. i'm thinking a supermoto would be a better first bike then. but which would be better suited for a really tall person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what's the difference between a supermoto and a dual sport? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-01 06:11:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-01 04:52:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> didnt mean to sound like a dick my bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-01 04:49:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if it's the one off of the highway by Outback steakhouse then make your employees wear some fucking hair nets. shits disgusting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-01 04:45:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm confused. you talk about having money problems but you have a shrink. doesn't make sense man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-25 02:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i work overnight shifts and so i usually buy most my alcohol around 6 or 7am. i always get weird looks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-25 00:07:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what are the main things to look at when buying my first (used) bike? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-22 00:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what does the MSF course consist of? i'm looking to take it sometime next month and don't want to go in with no information beforehand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-14 18:07:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm glad those people weren't redditors or they would have kidnapped the fox cub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-11 17:20:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> new rider here, is there an exact speed that i should from counter-steering to steering normally? i mean if i'm certain to crash, should i steer normally or counter-steer at.. 11, 12, 13mph? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-11 15:15:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i got to watch the finale for the time twice because i was blackout drunk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> can someone please explain countersteering to someone who has never ridden? i don't doubt it, but just have questions in the comments </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 16:49:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> at what speed to you go from steering normally to counter steering? i mean if i was lane splitting at 10mph and can't make any mistake, should i steer normally to get into a lane or counter steer? 20mph? 

i assume counter steering at higher speeds comes naturally once i take my test, so i guess that's my only question. but i'm still curious of the balance between counter steering and leaning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 16:03:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i want a tortoise so he can play peek a boo with my cat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 16:01:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> egg cartons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-28 13:07:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> love the art, but can i please can you please share where you got this information.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-26 16:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i am a felon because i forgot i had my bb gun in my car and parked illegally at school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-23 14:36:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fried cheese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-21 23:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't you think its kind of inconsiderate to ask him for a picture with a crying baby. maybe it's just me but i can't think of a worse sound than a crying baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-21 21:53:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i would look at her from a distance so hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> to open a can of beer silently, open it slightly by pulling on the tab then tap the lid down </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-18 16:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-17 04:49:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> overnight stocking and shipment receiving at Home Depot. i work during nights and sleep during the day, so i start my drinking at 7am. cashiers think i'm a crazy alcoholic who never sleeps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-15 19:10:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alcohol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-15 05:57:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i need to stop clicking on these links. it's sad that i knew what this was going to be about before i even clicked on it. i even knew that the women wouldn't be charged, all before ever clicking the link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-15 03:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i wish my cat loved me that much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-08 15:09:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she won't get punished more than the guy she accused would have. they never do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-08 15:06:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> at college i tried to go to my old dorm instead of my new one. key didn't work so i climbed in through the window. that's all i remember. woke up in a drunk tank surrounded by snoring native americans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-07 19:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> get a hammock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-05 16:02:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's awesome. i bet that saves a ton of weight and space in your pack. where is this DIY gear supply you speak of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-02 09:30:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if you want to listen to the police scanner: 
http://tunein.com/radio/Seattle-Police-Fire-and-EMS-s145392/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-28 00:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i hate what this subreddit has become </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-24 05:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because old people. fuck old people. and also because these kids are retarded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-23 18:26:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i love how little kids don't know the "roll down the window" sign because they've only seen power windows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i have the best pubic region of all other straight men because i pick my pubes when i'm sitting alone high on meth. i don't mean to pick at my pubes, it's just a habit. but girls have said they like my pubes because it's thinned out and not like a bush. it's way better then picking at my face </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-23 08:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-23 03:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i've never had that much fun at walmart. i want meth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-23 00:23:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is that what a front ass is called? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-20 18:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is it just me, or would hundreds of angry protesters decrease the chance of the police in india getting the right guy in favor of just someone who doesn't have an alibi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-17 03:31:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a sociopath evil genius designs a house to torture and cause pain on the people in the house. 

Saw and Home Alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-14 05:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i found my cat sort of playing with a dead bird so i impaled it on a stick and played with my cat. the bird fell off the stick a few times so i kept stabbing it to put it back on the stick so i could play with my cat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-14 02:02:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i want to put something up my ass and stimulate my prostate but i'm too much of a pussy to do this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-13 19:46:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the piss covered boxers and shorts. also somehow i got some of the piss into a cup. i'm a blackout drunk and sometimes i pee in my sleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-11 06:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1,000th comment in this thread! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 23:27:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i thought zelda was a guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 01:24:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's craigslist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-09 06:19:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the dealer requires $2000 to test ride. i'm going to sell my car to buy my bike </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-09 06:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can't afford a new one and i need the money to test ride. but i'm going to sell my car to buy the bike so i can't test ride it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-09 04:39:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks for your input. i won't forget you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-09 03:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 250R because it would be my first bike ever. there's a forum just for ninja 250 riders and some people my height own them and love them, but i just want a second and third opinion. because i can't test drive it before i hand over the $2000 and i don't have that yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-09 02:37:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm 6 foot 3 inches or maybe taller, would a kawasaki ninja be too small for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 07:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> awesome keep recommending sliders when you stumble across one of the many "new rider, need advice" threads. i made post to raise awareness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 06:44:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nope. but i'll go back and check the threads i saved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 06:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i heard that for a beginner, one day at the track improves your riding as much as six months on the road </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sliders - i've been browsing rideit a lot this past month, especially posts from people buying their first bike (there's a lot of those) and not once has anyone mentioned to get sliders. but on youtube everyone says you should get them right away </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 05:52:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i guess my point is i just wanted to bring this to the attention of other beginners </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:34:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i should say that i've never ridden a motorcycle but am about to get one. i just don't understand how someone knows when to counter-steer at low speeds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but i don't want to be one of those people. i like living </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:17:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but at what speed does counter-steering take over? say i decide to lane split and have only one direction to go (right), should i counter-steer to go right or turn the bars right? at what speed does this change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so anything above 10 mph i should counter-steer? i don't get how someone would know if they should steer "normally" or counter-steer. say i'm lane splitting and going 10 to 15-20 mph and want to turn, which way should i turn the bars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> how did you get into the habit of counter-steering? i mean besides just practicing. i feel if i have to swerve back to back to back, my brain just won't remember quick enough. or like if i have to make a split second decision i'll forget about counter steering. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 06:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> also at what speed does it change from normal steering to counter-steering? how would i know if i should steer right to go right, or to counter-steer before it's too late? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> how do i get my first bike home? i would have to go on the highway </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 03:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 01:21:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i also want to know if i can sit on a bike without it tipping over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 16:00:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i hate deer more than any other animal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 21:22:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry im drunk. made me chuckle to myself. didn't mean it tho i'll detele it now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 19:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> did you have to wear one of those sheets that muslim women wear? 

edit: i thought this was a valid question  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 19:04:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> starting a mold garden. like a regular garden except with cups of moldy juice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 21:49:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> vice city </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 21:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> consciousness
parades - efterklang
the residents - not available
mew - and the glass handed kites
broken social scene
childish gambino - culdesac
man of aran - british sea power
ken - by request only
joy division - unknown pleasures
alice in chains - facelift
slaraffenland-private cinema
Titus Andronicus - The Monitor
hundred waters
orgy - candyass
monk solo - it might be the sun
mount eerie - the microphones
welcome to the new age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 18:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and in another thread... first time offender and father of three gets 25 years for selling marijuana to a friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 06:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks for the advice and link. i got ahead of myself because i'm too excited, of course i need to try a bike before i buy it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 06:10:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah thanks, that's pretty much what everyone in this thread has told me. i guess i'm getting ahead of myself. i just can't fucking wait and i'm too excited  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 06:09:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah thanks, that's pretty much what everyone in this thread has told me. of course i'm going to ride it before i buy it. i guess i'm getting ahead of myself. i just can't fucking wait and i'm too excited  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 06:07:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah thanks, that's pretty much what everyone in this thread has told me. i guess i'm getting ahead of myself. i just can't fucking wait and i'm too excited  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 04:51:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. i'm sorry but i have one more question. you've already been so helpful so i apologize. 

i'm 6 foot 2 inches, so i'm worried about how how a sport bike like the ninja 250 would fit me. would a standard or cruiser bike be better for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 04:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. i'm sorry but i have one more question. you've already been so helpful so i apologize. 

i'm 6 foot 2 inches, so i'm worried about how how a sport bike like the ninja 250 would fit me. would a standard or cruiser bike be better for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 04:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. i'm sorry but i have one more question. you've already been so helpful so i apologize. 

i'm 6 foot 2 inches, so i'm worried about how how a sport bike like the ninja 250 would fit me. would a standard or cruiser bike be better for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 04:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. i'm sorry but i have one more question. you've already been so helpful so i apologize. 

i'm 6 foot 2 inches, so i'm worried about how how a sport bike like the ninja 250 would fit me. would a standard or cruiser bike be better for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 04:50:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. i'm sorry but i have one more question. you've already been so helpful so i apologize. 

i'm 6 foot 2 inches, so i'm worried about how how a sport bike like the ninja 250 would fit me. would a standard or cruiser bike be better for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 04:50:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. i'm sorry but i have one more question. you've already been so helpful so i apologize. 

i'm 6 foot 2 inches, so i'm worried about how how a sport bike like the ninja 250 would fit me. would a standard or cruiser bike be better for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 00:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> keep reading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah i get that. it took me awhile to drive stick shift perfectly. 
other people in this thread already convinced me to take the lessons. especially when one guy said it pays for my license and saves on insurance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks i'll check it out. i found it in a pdf file, here's the link if you want it.
http://tinymicros.com/mediawiki/images/c/cd/Twist_Of_The_Wrist_I.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> really i didn't know it pays for my license and saves on insurance. that's great. thank you. you guys are pretty friendly in this subreddit, i like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha yeah that's a good point. thanks, i appreciate you taking the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well i would have to buy the bike before i take the license test anyways, but yeah i think you guys convinced me, thanks all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:17:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah i forgot that bit, i put it in the comments section straight away. 250. no way i would get a liter bike for my first one. also i'm cheap so this would save gas right? 

i think you guys convinced me, i'll take some lessons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i honestly feel that i know everything there is to know for a beginner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:01:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh ok. how much were your lessons?

edit: i meant to say over a dozen. i can't spell today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> did you pay for any motorcycle lessons when you first started riding? also is a kawasaki ninja a good choice for a beginner? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 22:57:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ninja 250 i meant to say

i've seen at least dozen of youtube videos, so i don't know if i need to take lessons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 20:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ctrl + f ghost in the shell, wasn't disappointed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 19:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why are they shouting at admiral ackbar from star wars?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 19:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a few days ago my cat was pawing at my stream of urine. it was the funniest thing in the world. i couldn't stop peeing and he just kept swatting my pee. so there's an idea for a comic. if you make it i'd love to see it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> please ignore. i had to wipe my computer so don't have word anymore. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 08:16:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> from a /mu/ thread, i want to listen to later

glass handed kites
broken social scene
childish gambino - culdesac
man of aran - british sea power
ken - by request only
joy division - unknown pleasures
alice in chains - facelift
slaraffenland-private cinema
Titus Andronicus - The Monitor
hundred waters
monk solo - it might be the sun
mount eerie - the microphones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 06:46:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can't pronounce the letter R... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 08:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how can batman be dangerous if he doesn't kill anyone? why do criminals fear him when they know he doesn't kill anyone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 04:14:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> waking up in a drunk tank surrounded by a bunch of natives and not knowing why i'm there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is there anything i can do to make my bladder bigger? like bladder kegels? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-27 01:43:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-26 22:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GIVE ME BACK MY CAT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-26 12:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why do you have a hammock and a tent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-26 06:26:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i pre-ordered bioshock at gamestop, how long do i have to buy it before my $5 goes away? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 03:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> please don't say get an eye patch and a parrot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 01:28:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks i appreciate you taking the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 01:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks. i appreciate you taking the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> my xbox360 got wet and won't read discs. after some research, cleaning a lens is supposed to be my best bet. but where is this lens and how do i get to it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 01:25:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 01:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't know what that is. honestly i'd be surprised if i find out how to open my xbox without taking a hammer to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 01:24:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> horizontally. also the disc tray had a few tiny drops of water on it when i opened it. also my fallout game was soaking wet. i learned my lesson about drinking too much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 01:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah probably but it's worth a shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 01:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i got blackout drunk. i woke up to it being unplugged, on the ground, with the bottom wet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 01:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 01:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks. i can't believe i didn't think of youtube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-23 16:07:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't get why people want signatures and pictures of celebs. it just doesn't make sense to me, and i'm sure he didn't want to be in a picture with you but he didn't want to be rude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-23 01:26:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i've been looking into ecigs. what do you think about this one http://www.vapedojo.com/collections/kits/products/katana-kit ?

yesterday was the first day i didn't smoke in probably like 8 years, so this is working for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-22 06:13:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good luck on not getting raped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-22 06:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this reminds me, i need to look into getting food stamps. anyone know how i go about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-21 21:35:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what songing is playing in the background? this is really bugging me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-21 05:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> which, as you said, is just a plot of land </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-21 05:21:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so is nationalism just basically "my government governs me less shitty than your government governs you"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-21 05:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so is nationalism just basically "my government governs me less shitty than your government governs you"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-20 05:37:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if my dad says comments on my drinking, hide my drinking from him that day and the next day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-20 04:57:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh my fucking god thank you. "i'm trying to save you a bullet" lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-19 21:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i asked my dad for a zip (an ounce of weed). then said that a zip is slang for a full tank of gas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-16 19:06:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> trip wrong? there's no wrong way to trip. providing a nice setting is a good idea but it's not wrong if you don't do that. think of a trip as a trip. you're going someplace new on an adventure, but you get stuck in traffic. could you have avoided the traffic? no because you're someplace new </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-09 09:48:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> at least the one in front looks like it has limbs. what is the bunny equivalent of arms called? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-03 14:09:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> liar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-17 07:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do you have steam? i'll gift you a game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-17 06:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i did it once. it was good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-17 06:57:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damnit i forgot that my audio stopped working. does anyone know how to fix audio on a laptop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-17 06:56:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't know anything about computers. how do i do that? thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> the audio on my laptop stopped working. i can't turn the volume up because when i try a text box pops up and says "your audio device isn't functioning properly" no shit </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-17 06:39:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-16 22:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i sprayed warhead sour spray on all the food in my highschool's cafeteria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-15 20:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he dead? nooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-15 20:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whenever i drive with my gay friend i have him yell "faggot" at people in his gayest voice. it's hilarious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-15 06:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i like how he managed to get his longboard in every shot. i'm that that wasn't planned  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-12 04:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> asians are horrible people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 06:32:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks. are you a cop, lawyer, or have heard of a similar story? it was weed and ecstasy by the way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 06:30:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a friend forgot a backpack in another friend's car. that friend consented to a search of the car because he didn't know the backpack was there. just some weed and ecstasy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-07 20:10:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> at least they weren't black </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-07 04:03:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why didn't you just surround the place with treadmills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-05 19:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> girls think my stutter is cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-05 06:52:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what is SC GOP? and where do i sign up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-03 23:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damnit man i had a boner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what happened to the basketball trampoline league/show that was on tv a decade ago? what was it called? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-03 05:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it was basketball but with trampolines and pads. that was the shit. what's it called? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> is it possible to turn humans into delicious bacon? if you cut right section and the meat thin enough would it taste like bacon? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-01 10:14:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-31 03:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you sound exactly like i do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-24 01:00:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> will your show get better? i gave it a shot, should i stick with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-21 11:40:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i loaned a "friend" 700 dollars, how do i prove that money exchanged hands? i have no proof </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-14 04:53:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-14 04:49:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so where is mercer island? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-14 02:07:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm looking for a longterm solution though. that helps for a few minutes.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-14 01:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm kinda pissed that doctors are taking pictures of him instead of helping hm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-14 01:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how many MCG's of vitamin B do you take a day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-14 01:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how many MCG's of B12 do you take a day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-13 22:41:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks a lot. so that's all i need to know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i don't know anything about pirating, how do i do it? and how do i not get a virus? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-13 22:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-13 20:50:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what is the name of that first song? and the other songs too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-13 14:01:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you... you funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-13 14:00:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i just bought some and cleaned the fuck out of my room :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-12 20:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alright thanks i'll look into vitamin D and fish oil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> do B vitamins really help with depression and... laziness, for lack of a better word? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-12 19:47:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-11 07:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i hate you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-11 07:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol this woman is retarded lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-10 23:14:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but i already know this... it's not fast enough tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-10 23:13:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my pillow is too hard, giving me a headache </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-10 23:13:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm trying to lucid dream tho so i stopped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i need a hangover cure.. anyone have a good one? please help </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-10 23:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-10 23:00:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-03 00:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> home alone - human centipede - saw   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-31 02:48:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alright thanks. looks like i need a college education. reading books that don't cost a couple hundred bucks can only get you so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-31 00:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's just as cool. do you have any special qualifications that gave you an advantage over other applicants for the job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-30 23:27:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have always wanted to work at a library? how did you end up there? any special training or education? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-26 16:03:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because then you couldnt have this circlejerk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-25 23:40:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that fucking asian cunt. i would fuck her up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-20 08:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats definitely it thank you so much my brother will love this christmas gift i'm sure. although i might have waited too long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-20 04:35:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> asian women drivers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-20 04:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sent a picture of my balls to a friend i don't like, he stopped talking to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-18 19:08:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i was at a party and this cute girl openly said she only came to fuck me. i pretended not to overhear. i'm so fucking pathetic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-18 18:30:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> your ex-wife shoots up heroin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-18 10:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you really don't care that you could have ruined someones life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-17 11:00:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you're genuinely a really awful person. you show no remorse for seducing a married man and you actually seem to be bragging about it. i hope somewhere down the line you look back and realize just what a terrible person you are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-11 22:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you i'll look into that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-10 08:59:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the doors - lsd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-06 22:57:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alright thanks. GTA 4 isn't as good as those? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-06 22:57:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> san andreas it is then, thanks. is GTA 4 not good at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-29 06:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> would vegetable oil work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-29 06:40:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> does the bowl need to have steep sides? what did you use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-29 06:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't think i have vinegar but thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-14 17:57:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good point from a good movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-10-29 08:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DMT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do I reduce the redness of a badly popped zit? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-30 00:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-01 16:30:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm completely new to this... what's a torrent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i have never pirated anything before, how do i do it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-01 16:26:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-27 04:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> too bad about the fake tits, she's still beautiful though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-19 08:39:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> commenting so i can return to this later. for science </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-19 08:35:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> commenting so i can come back to this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-19 08:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> commenting so i can come back to this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> LSA - should i get morning glory or HBWR seeds? how do i get the bad chemical shit off the seeds? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-12 01:34:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 10:44:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nice try, troll. or are you just dumb enough to think that shooting another human being is the only thing guns are used for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 10:32:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> solitude. those rare moments when everyone else on my timezone is asleep and i walk through the park </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 10:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i may not be as bad as you, i like hanging out with one friend at a time. whenever someone calls me up i make sure it's only us two kicking it. i stutter and can't pronounce the letter R, i think this is why i'm so quiet around groups of people. i only have one friend now because my other good friends got addicted to shooting up heroin and are no longer the same people i became friends with, so i ignore their calls and texts. i feel awful every time they call and i ignore it. and my other not so good friends, i finally realized only called me because they needed something like for me to drive them around. i guess i needed someone to vent to, thank you stranger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 09:22:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i was thinking about buying a fleshlight (those flashlight vagina things) and told a story about how i bought mine. i was sitting in my car on the street outside my apartment building in seattle, smoking a cigarette. it was raining and a homeless woman carrying a baby walked by and i asked her if she wanted a cigarette and get warm in my car for a minute. she accepted. her face actually lit up because i treated her like a person. we get to talking and it's obvious from her face and teeth that she does a lot of hardcore drugs. i point out where i live and offer to take care of her baby for her. she gratefully but remorsefully accepts, and i give her 40 bucks so she'll get out of my car and go buy drugs before she stinks it up. she hugs and kisses her crack-dumpster baby and cries as she walks to the food shelter. i lied to her about where i live and i just got a fleshlight, but now i'm thinking about getting one that doesn't cry and need to be fed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 09:14:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the scar on my leg i got from fighting tigers as a child prince in asia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 09:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i said "hi." 

then she said "hey how are you?" 

then i said "good. how are you?"

then she said "good." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 09:07:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> provenance, merlot, napa valley, 2005 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 09:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have been so closed off and reclusive for so long that it's impossible for me to change. i want to change, but everyone i know will know that this new person is not the real me. i want to be outgoing but this would require a new surrounding with people i don't know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 09:00:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how much change does two weeks worth make? that's a lot of money for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 02:15:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you for all the help. i just have a couple more questions if thats ok. for the acid, do you mean squeezing a little orange juices into the bowl? how do i get the ground up seeds out of the water, or do you mean to drink this mix?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 00:23:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what's a water soak? or is it just exactly what it sounds like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-27 00:22:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what should i wash them with? alcohol? would water work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-26 07:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you will need a backpack and stuff to put in it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-26 06:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what do you mean i'm funny? you mean the way i talk? funny how?  I mean funny like I'm a clown? I amuse you? I make you laugh, I'm here to fuckin' amuse you? What do you mean funny? Funny how? How am I funny? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-26 06:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nice try troll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-26 06:38:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you'll have to quit drinking alcohol for a little while too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-26 03:17:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what seeds did you take? how many? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-26 03:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't think i'm going to wash them, just grind them into a pb j sandwich. i fully expect to get sick but i'm ok with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-26 03:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what seeds did you use? how many? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-26 03:14:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what seeds did you use? how many?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-25 06:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when you jack off do you only use one finger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> has anyone tripped on LSA? i know about erowid, but i want to talk directly to someone who's tried it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-25 03:55:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-25 03:52:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you for replying, i was sure it wasn't well known enough to find anyone but i just thought i'd try my luck. did you extract the LSA from the seeds or just swallow/grind them? would you do it again? any open eye visuals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-25 03:47:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow i actually didn't think i would get this lucky! did you extract the LSA from the seeds or just swallow/grind them? what seeds did you use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> has anybody tripped on LSA? i know about erowid, i just want to talk directly with someone who's done it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-25 03:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> don't mind me. just compiling some music i might forget about </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-24 21:02:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> youth - daughter

fatlip

battleme

phish

massive attack

portishead

Smoking Spore - Toad Patrol

tycho

dj shadow - midnight in a perfect world

bonobo -recurring

a perfect circle - judith

cannibal ox - pigeon

If I Had a Heart - Fever Ray (Fuck Buttons Remix)

Gonjasufi - Blaksuit

fun - all alone

kip moore

Arkasia - Pandemonium

mos def - mathematics

aesop rock

Nas -memory lane - illmatic album

CunninLynguists - a piece of strange album

Tangerine Dream - Ricochet

Jonathan Coulton - re: your brains   still alive

devin townsend

funki porcini - purrfect

Mt Eden Dubstep - Still Alive

One Day/Reckoning Song (Wankelmut Remix) - Asaf Avidan   the Mojos

9 Lazy 9

DJ Food

Cold cut

Crystal Stilts - Frost Inside The Asylums

the tallest man on earth - the dreamer

MF Doom - Vomitspit

Mos Def Talib Kweli ft. Common - Respiration

minus the bear

hopsin

woodkid - iron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-22 09:30:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank balls. my day's getting better thanks to you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-22 09:28:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hopefully this will make sense in the morning. thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-22 09:27:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so would the lower number be cheaper or higher number be cheaper? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-22 09:24:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i just bought a rifle at a gun show without a background check or any waiting period </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-21 05:29:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mos Def Talib Kweli ft. Common - Respiration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-21 05:29:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> MF Doom - Vomitspit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-21 05:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the tallest man on earth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-20 10:56:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i got cold when it was warm outside. then i realized i haven't smoked crack in awhile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 22:04:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crystal Stilts - Frost Inside The Asylums </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 22:03:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nine Lazy Nine

DJ Food

Coldcut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 22:01:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One Day/Reckoning Song (Wankelmut Remix) - Asaf Avidan   the Mojos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 22:00:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mt Eden Dubstep - Still Alive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 21:58:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> funki porcini - purrfect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 21:56:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Devin Townsend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 21:49:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jonathan Coulton - re: your brains   still alive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 21:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tangerine Dream - Ricochet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 21:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CunninLynguists - a piece of strange album </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 21:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nas -memory lane - illmatic album </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 21:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> aesop rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 21:32:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mos def - mathematics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 21:30:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Arkasia - Pandemonium </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 21:21:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> christina hendricks sexy

beggars and choosers 

undressed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-19 10:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> kip moore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-18 08:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fun - all alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-17 22:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gonjasufi - Blaksuit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-17 21:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I Had a Heart - Fever Ray (Fuck Buttons Remix) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-17 21:49:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cannibal ox - pigeon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-17 21:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bonobo -recurring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-17 21:48:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a perfect circle - judith </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-16 01:43:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tycho

dj shadow - midnight in a perfect world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i woke up the instant i realized that i was dreaming. how do i avoid this next time? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-13 20:30:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what made me realize i was dreaming was when a dog meowed like a cat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Hey." "Hey." "How's it going?" "Good. You?" "Good." WHATS NEXT??? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 20:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 19:24:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. one more thing if you don't mind, which number in the picture in this link should the tip of my tongue almost touch? http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alveolar_ridge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 19:22:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you very much. one more thing if you don't mind, which number in the picture on this page should the tip of my tongue nearly touch? http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alveolar_ridge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 19:21:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. on the picture in this link, which number should the front of my tongue go towards? http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alveolar_ridge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 06:36:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i won $300 at a casino, then spent most of it at a strip club </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 06:35:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i was always running away from something and my legs would feel really heavy, and i wouldn't be able to run fast enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 06:29:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. i still have some research to do but now i have a starting point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 06:14:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what's the name of waldo's evil twin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 06:13:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so CO2 emissions cause greenhouse gasses which reflects some radiation back towards earth? and radiation is the same as light. do i have the jist of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 05:42:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so then why are you at the mall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 05:36:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so the earth has always been getting warmer since it was created? what is infrared radiation? which way is the radiation ejected, back towards earth?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 05:34:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why is earth's climate getting warmer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> my dad said global warming isn't real and i don't know enough to correct him. explain it to me please </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 05:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 04:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 04:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I KEPT SAYING "STOP" BUT SHE WOULDN'T. even when tears streamed down my face, she wouldn't just let me run away and lock myself in the bathroom. i think she craved my humiliation, she loved being stronger then me. she loved being on top and dominating me until i couldn't take it any longer and peed my pants. she just wouldn't stop tickling me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 04:42:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ross's is hardly noticeable, i sound like a cartoon character. that's a good idea though, thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 04:41:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> already have it memorized, that's how nervous i am. and actually if i think about what i'm going to say before i say it then i'm more likely to stutter. english is my first language, speech therapy didn't do shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 03:51:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i was thinking about saying my nickname was "boston joe" on the first day of class, but didn't because of shyness and not knowing anything about boston </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 03:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is it just me or does everyone with down's syndrome look like twins? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 03:14:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i say these whenever i'm home alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 03:13:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what? that is the opposite of how i was taught. i was taught to curl my tongue backwards. i just tried your way and i can't do that either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 03:11:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm 21 and i've had this problem all my life. i used to go to speech therapy for years until i just gave up (also have a stutter). it didn't do shit. 

how far back should i curl my tongue? was there anything specific that really helped you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-04 23:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok thank you. i'll have to go buy a mouse so i can do that. this isn't my computer i'm on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-04 23:54:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok i'll try that, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-04 23:53:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks. what's a driver and how do i re-install it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-04 23:24:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-04 23:21:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nope. i thought of that, not an 80 year old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-04 06:41:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yup. testicular trauma its called </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-03 23:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THE DOCTOR SAID HE WOULDN'T TELL MY PARENTS ANYTHING WITHOUT MY PERMISSION, HE LIED. one of my balls (actually the ballsack) is a lot bigger than the other because i rode my bicycle into an oncoming car. when my mom comes back in the room. he draws my genitals on his notepad and shows my mom. he then says what size my balls are on a scale of one to ten, and then goes on to tell us what size his balls are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-02 03:14:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> shit. i guess i should have waited for an answer. thanks for looking this up, you went above and beyond </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-25 05:28:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nosleep. that's it, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-25 05:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's a good idea but my friend is fishing in alaska so i don't know where to get weed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-25 04:41:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nothing to do with you if that's what you mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-25 04:35:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do you know the name of that thread for creepy stories? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-25 04:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok thank you. i've never done this and i can see how this would be helpful. thanks a lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-25 04:32:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hmm i'll try that, thanks. your comment might actually be helpful for a change. i like to write strange fiction but i'll give this a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-25 04:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> two problems with that: i only have one friend and he's kind of permafried, and i'm too self conscious for that anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-25 04:30:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my problem is that i can't get my ideas onto paper. i can't even write for 15 minutes without getting frustrated and needing a smoke break </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-25 04:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm too self conscious for that. maybe i'll put some of my stories on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 20:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the only drink i've ever ordered at a bar is manny's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 07:06:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 06:19:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what sorry? i think i've heard of tonic water. away to google i goooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 01:49:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 01:48:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what is tonic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 01:37:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> double just means twice as much alcohol right? non clear rum means it was stored in barrels right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 01:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 01:32:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> really? can is better then bottle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-23 01:31:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i knew someone would say this but i didn't think it would be the very first comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-21 04:53:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i hate all the women on the daily show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-21 04:49:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its just that i'm terrified of my parents smelling lotion on me or hearing the noise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-21 04:46:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i masturbate without lotion or lube or anything like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-20 15:22:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no but last week i started a new job and the day after my first day of work i dreamed that i would walk out of the store and somehow would wind up right back in it. this kept happening until a security guard came up to me and asked to talk. then out of nowhere another security guard comes up behind me and grabs my balls. i don't fight back but it hurts bad. i wake up and think this dream means that society finally has me by the balls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-19 10:33:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't buy it. delusional kids are easy meals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-08 04:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't take investment advice from strangers seriously. best thing you could do is put it in the bank. maybe look at cars once a week  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-06 12:38:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do you have a piece of gum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-06 12:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i paid $600 for a vet to hook my my cat up to an I.V. overnight. the vet knew my cat was dehydrated right away but still half the bill was for running tests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-06 12:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wishing i was caught up in a bank robbery. i would close my eyes and put my hands over my ears so there's no need for them to kill me. the robbers would be so impressed that they would give me money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 13:21:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why do Scotsmen wear kilts?

because sheep can hear zippers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 13:12:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> rock paper scissors. the trick is, after awhile people usually forget about one of the choices and if you keep track of what they do then you will beat them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 13:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the ability to slide on anything, regardless of gravity and friction. all i would need is a running start and i would be able to slide along the side of buildings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 13:06:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> we share 99% of our DNA with apes. so apes are 1% less smart then us. so imagine the species that is 1% smarter then us. they can make whatever drug they damn well please. so far DMT is the only drug we have made purely for recreational use, and that is some intense shit. our brains would not be able to handle the drugs these advanced aliens use  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 12:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> every sailor has at least one blow up doll (most are male because they are in the navy) and when they take gun fire they deflate them and fill them with helium so they float. they then tie them to the ship and the ship is unsinkable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 12:06:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i put my dog down when he was unable to stand by himself. i tried holding him up so he could pee but he was too proud for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 12:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't have to go back in time but i would ask emma watson to blow me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 11:53:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i got poop on my dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 11:48:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i wouldn't remember it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 11:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but when it's nice out it's fucking perfect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 11:46:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i potato </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 11:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can't compare it to anything else. some people say it doesn't rain much but it rains hard, some people say it rains a lot but not that heavy. it just fucking rains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 11:40:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> seattle: i guess i'm normal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 11:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WHO THE FUCK DOWNVOTED THIS! THIS IS HILARIOUS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 11:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> work out everyday and you will feel better instantly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 11:24:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i love you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 11:18:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> looks like i'm the first one to call bullshit. if two things compete against each other for long enough, one will eventually dominate the other. men have the choice of the litter and women will have to settle- whether it be for money or security or whatever they will have to settle while we can get what we want if we work for it. fat women stand no chance at getting an alpha male and will have to settle for beta, while fat men can provide things other then looks. i'm drunk and will delete this comment tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 11:14:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i introduced my friend to 4chan and reddit. he is failing all his classes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 07:24:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> one of my balls is a lot bigger then the other. it's from riding my bicycle into a car.

edit: wait, i thought these were supposed to be 100% true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 07:16:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't be THAT GUY. just chill and have a good time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 05:57:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why do people (i mean women) care so much about their own birthday and get so upset if it doesn't go perfectly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 05:47:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i just wrote this in another thread. one time at a high school party i overheard a cute girl say she only came out tonight to have sex with me. i pretended not to hear because i was a shy virgin at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 05:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> google it. don't downvote because you're too retarded to believe something that seems unlikely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 05:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i bought my friend in the hospital a e-cig and it broke the next day. and i couldn't find the receipt/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 05:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there's a type of jellyfish that never dies of old age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 05:04:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i blacked out and woke up in detox in wyoming surrounded by drunk natives and not knowing where i was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-04 14:31:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's pretty interesting about the emperor. i wonder then if nuking a non populated area really would have worked the same. 

actually over 400,000 japanese died. half vaporized, half died later from fallout and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-04 14:10:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i wish i never started smoking cigarettes. now i can't stop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-04 14:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok, speech therapist is right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-04 13:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks. what's a logoped? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-04 13:53:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can't pronounce the letter R and i have a stutter. this really makes my life hell. i've almost given up making new friends and no one will hire me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-04 06:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> based on your comment history, you are going to get stabbed. enjoy death asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-04 06:00:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> since you paid for him, legally he belongs to you. take this cunt's ass to small claims court and you'll definitely win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-04 05:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when is mothers day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-03 05:31:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SO YOU'RE THE ASSHOLE WHO DOESN'T TIP ME! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-03 05:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow i can't wait. thank you, doesn't sound too crazy so i'm not so nervous anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-03 05:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm getting some soon and just want to know what i'm in for. i've tried shrooms a few times and some super weak acid once. 

what can i expect my trip to be like? i mean what was yours like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-03 05:11:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> aww fuck yeah . awesome thank you. i'm getting some soon and i want to know what i'm in for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-03 05:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> shit. i meant to put "AMA request" in the title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 13:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i would smoke a lot more weed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 13:20:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh yeah i forgot about that thing. but i'm talking about on a much larger scale. like a fire extinguisher that you can use on wild animals to get them high so you can catch them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 13:18:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> now that i'm thinking about it, after i payed and picked him up they showed me how they knew he was dehydrated. something with his eyes and the skin on his neck didn't go right back into place if they pulled on it. and they still ran a buttload of tests even though they knew what was wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 13:12:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the tests they ran accounted for most of the bill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 13:06:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ooh thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 13:06:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 12:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you also have my ideas. my first idea is a weed gun. it's like a fire extinguisher but it blows out weed smoke. you can get animals high so you can catch them.

my second idea is jeans with velvet on the insides.

i have more ideas but i forget them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 12:07:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how do you find a prostitute? i want one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 12:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> say someone who doesn't know anyone in the tv show/movie industry writes a pilot episode or something, what does he do from there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 11:52:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "What the fuck?" I say aloud as i frantically search my brain for clues as to how i wound up in the middle of a dense forest. As I take in the absurdity of my situation I think back on the previous day. I didn't drink and I only left the house to get a pack of cigarettes. 
"Oh fuck yeah, cigarettes." 
As i take my first drag I approach my situation with a new sense of calm. I hear running water so i make my way towards that. 
I don't remember falling asleep but that's not new. I don't think I'm dreaming but I've never been able to have a lucid dream before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 11:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how did you do that? that must have taken some effort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 11:33:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i would pay a pilot to fly me around the state so i can drop bags of weed attached to parachutes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 11:14:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's weird. you lose a lot of water when you sleep so maybe you just got dehydrated. alright then i'll quit talking to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 11:09:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have insomnia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 11:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she self serves when we play hacky sack... and misses... again and again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 11:01:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i live in seattle... so no. it was only a drop or two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 10:55:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> jack off twice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what's the strangest thing you have ever smoked? (not a drug) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 10:55:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i smoked my piss once. i peed out my window and jiggled my dick to get all the piss out and some of it landed in a packed bowl. my last bowl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 10:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i blew a smoke ring and turned it into a heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 10:47:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> would a lesbian be aroused by her own boobs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 06:31:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pyramid apricot ale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 06:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i got the big scar on my leg from fighting tigers in asia as a child warrior prince </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-01 06:21:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah especially since my name is charles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-30 10:38:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i also want to be a stand up comedian but i stutter and can't pronounce the letter R that well. i feel for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-30 08:21:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i wish i could give you more then one upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-30 07:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-30 07:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> women aren't funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-30 07:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i turned on the tv right when my dad came home and there were two guys having gay sex. we watched it together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>