<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1529</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ISIS Transforming Into Functioning State That Uses Terror as Tool </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ISIS Transforming Into Functioning State That Uses Terror as Tool </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> US officials target social media, encryption after Chattanooga shooting: Did "IS" propaganda inspire the Chattanooga shooter? There's no evidence to back the claim, but some officials are already calling for access to encrypted messages and social media monitoring. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:47:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> US officials target social media, encryption after Chattanooga shooting: Did "IS" propaganda inspire the Chattanooga shooter? There's no evidence to back the claim, but some officials are already calling for access to encrypted messages and social media monitoring. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Senator Lindsey Graham will probably have to change his cellphone number. Thats because Donald J. Trump...brandished a card showing the South Carolina senators phone number from the stage at a speech on Tuesday afternoon, reading the digits aloud and encouraging people to dial. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:47:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Senator Lindsey Graham will probably have to change his cellphone number. Thats because Donald J. Trump...brandished a card showing the South Carolina senators phone number from the stage at a speech on Tuesday afternoon, reading the digits aloud and encouraging people to dial. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Don't Forget About the New BRICS Bank: The New Development Bank, which opened today in Shanghai, has been overshadowed recently by the AIIB. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:44:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scores of Native American demonstrators protested at the US Capitol on Tuesday against a proposed $6bn copper mine in Arizona at a site that members of the Apache tribe say is sacred. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:44:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Simulations lead to design of near-frictionless material </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:40:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A scientific research team spent seven years tracking the movements of skyscraper-high waves in the South China Sea. Scientists are trying to understand how these waves, which rarely break the ocean surface, develop, move and dissipate underwater. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:37:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Facebook Inc cannot challenge search warrants New York prosecutors used to get information from its site on hundreds of users suspected of Social Security fraud, a state appeals court said on Tuesday, in a decision likely making it harder for New Yorkers to keep their digital lives private. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:34:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> With Tuesdays Speech, Donald Trump Continues to Blow Up the 2016 GOP Primary Field </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:31:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Senate Republicans Said to Mull New Tactic for Easing Dodd-Frank </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:28:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:24:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Press release from conference with abstracts](https://www.alz.org/aaic/_downloads/tues-8am-women-risk.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Older women with mild memory impairment worsened about twice as fast as men, researchers reported Tuesday, part of an effort to unravel why women are especially hard-hit by Alzheimer's. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The European Court of Human Rights condemned Italy on Tuesday for failing to provide legal recognition to same-sex couples and said the country should introduce some form of civil union for gay couples. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:21:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The European Court of Human Rights condemned Italy on Tuesday for failing to provide legal recognition to same-sex couples and said the country should introduce some form of civil union for gay couples. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:21:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The bullies who run Kosovo: Hashim Thai and the rest of the Kosovar political elite are frustrating investigations into murder, kidnapping, and trafficking in human organs. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obama on Iran deal critics: They were wrong on Iraq too: The administration has presented the negotiations with Iran as a choice between peacefully preventing a nuclear Iran and going to war with the Islamic Republic. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obama on Iran deal critics: They were wrong on Iraq too: The administration has presented the negotiations with Iran as a choice between peacefully preventing a nuclear Iran and going to war with the Islamic Republic. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:19:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new report on child welfare that found more U.S. children living in poverty than before the Great Recession belies the fanfare of the nations economic turnaround. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new report on child welfare that found more U.S. children living in poverty than before the Great Recession belies the fanfare of the nations economic turnaround. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:07:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Republicans chose different path when John Kerry's war record was questioned: As the presidential candidates defend John McCain and other US veterans, the 2004 attacks on secretary of states war record tells another story </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Republicans chose different path when John Kerry's war record was questioned: As the presidential candidates defend John McCain and other US veterans, the 2004 attacks on secretary of states war record tells another story </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:06:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> George Clooney seeks to expose those who fund and profit from wars in Africa: The Oscar winner has launched a project with US human rights activist John Prendergast to investigate the flow of money in and out of conflict zones </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:05:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The EU fell short Monday of an agreed target for the relocation of 40,000 asylum-seekers across Europe. Interior and justice ministers secured pledges from member countries to take about 32,000 refugees and pushed a deadline for completing the pact until the end of the year. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The U.N. Security Council on Monday backed Iran's nuclear agreement with world powers but the Islamic Republic's Revolutionary Guards attacked the resolution, underlining powerful opposition to the deal. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:59:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The House will take up a bill this week blocking funding for so-called "sanctuary cities" that resist turning over immigrants to federal authorities. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:54:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Israeli Ambassador Courts Black Lawmakers Ahead of Iran Vote </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:50:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ukraine cant survive on its own: The United States could provide the help they need. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:49:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Los Angeles County public housing agency and two Mojave Desert cities have reached a $2 million settlement to resolve allegations they discriminated against black people by discouraging them from living in their communities, the Department of Justice announced Monday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:49:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP GOD DAMN IT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:50:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean they miss the very best and the very worst... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 07:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah well sorry about that, hope it didn't reflect poorly on LGBT as a whole. There are some thirsty-ass creepers I've dealt with too. Really sad, most of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Israels ongoing opposition to the nuclear deal signed with Iran has put it at odds with almost the entire international community and the tension was clear to see during yesterdays meeting in Jerusalem between prime minister Binyamin Netanyahu and visiting British foreign secretary Phillip Hammond </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 02:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hungary plans to close its permanent refugee shelters in towns and cities and set up temporary camps outside urban areas instead, the latest response to a surge in migrants crossing its borders. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hungary plans to close its permanent refugee shelters in towns and cities and set up temporary camps outside urban areas instead, the latest response to a surge in migrants crossing its borders. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:47:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> France Foils Plot To Attack Army Base and Behead Senior Officer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:41:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> America's best program for the poor may be even better than we thought </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:13:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 2016 fundraising shows power tilting to groups backed by wealthy elite </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Protesters wave Confederate flags as first black president drives by in a motorcade </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:10:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "A trove of thousands of Saudi documents recently released by WikiLeaks reveals in surprising detail how [Saudi Arabia's] goal in recent years was not just to spread its strict version of Sunni Islam  though that was a priority  but also to undermine its primary adversary: Shiite Iran." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:08:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 11 Planes Struck by Lasers Approaching Newark Airport </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rudeness in the workplace isnt just unpleasant: its also contagious. Encountering rude behavior at work makes people more likely to perceive rudeness in later interactions, a study shows. That perception makes them more likely to be impolite in return, spreading rudeness like a virus. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:02:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe on Thursday pushed through legislation in the lower house of parliament that could see troops sent to fight abroad for the first time since World War Two, despite thousands of protesters overnight chanting and holding up placards reading "No War, No Killing." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 2016's Campaign War Chests Are Just Jewelry Boxes Next To The Super PACs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Russian President Vladimir Putin said on Thursday calls for a U.N. tribunal to be set up to prosecute suspects in the downing of a Malaysian airliner in a rebel-held part of Ukraine were counterproductive and premature. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Russian President Vladimir Putin said on Thursday calls for a U.N. tribunal to be set up to prosecute suspects in the downing of a Malaysian airliner in a rebel-held part of Ukraine were counterproductive and premature. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:00:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Europes dirty little secret is Greece will never pay back its debt </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Netflix CEO tells subscribers to brace for higher-priced plans in the future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obama Turns to U.N. to Outmaneuver Congress: Washington is working on a new Security Council resolution making the nuclear deal legally binding on the next president. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:50:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obama Turns to U.N. to Outmaneuver Congress: Washington is working on a new Security Council resolution making the nuclear deal legally binding on the next president. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:49:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> U.S. authorities working with law enforcement officials abroad have shut down the Darkode online forum used by cybercriminals around the world and charged 12 people linked to the site, the Justice Department said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:47:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> U.S. authorities working with law enforcement officials abroad have shut down the Darkode online forum used by cybercriminals around the world and charged 12 people linked to the site, the Justice Department said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Phone app can identify behaviors linked to depression, study shows: The average daily phone use for depressed people was about 68 minutes and about 17 minutes for non-depressed individuals </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:46:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Phone app can identify behaviors linked to depression, study shows: The average daily phone use for depressed people was about 68 minutes and about 17 minutes for non-depressed individuals </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:45:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Italy takes step toward legalizing pot: Even members of Prime Minister Matteo Renzi's party voted for the measure, a first step toward full legalization. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Greek Parliament accepts austerity; protests erupt on Athens' streets </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:44:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Slovenia turned itself around: Another Balkan country didnt need an EU bailout to get its crisis-ridden economy back on track. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Slovenia turned itself around: Another Balkan country didnt need an EU bailout to get its crisis-ridden economy back on track. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> California Gov. Jerry Brown has approved legislation recognizing the states professional cheerleaders as employees who are entitled to minimum wage and overtime, following high-profile lawsuits alleging labor violations in California and elsewhere around the country. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:43:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good golly, brah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jeb Bush says never make nuclear deals with dictators. His brother and father both did. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:59:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obama: $80 billion spent on incarceration could eliminate tuition at public universities </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:58:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obama: $80 billion spent on incarceration could eliminate tuition at public universities </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Middle East Allies See Heightened Peril in Newly Empowered Tehran </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kids expecting aggression from others become aggressive themselves: Children taught to be vigilant for hostility from others are prone to aggressive behavior </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:53:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Republican leaders delayed a House vote Tuesday on a bill raising money for breast cancer research over anger that some of the funds would go to a group that has worked with the Planned Parenthood Federation of America, which supports abortion rights. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:50:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Republican leaders delayed a House vote Tuesday on a bill raising money for breast cancer research over anger that some of the funds would go to a group that has worked with the Planned Parenthood Federation of America, which supports abortion rights. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:49:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Numbers Behind Hillary Clintons Economic Vision </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:48:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The European Commission is frowning on Hungarys project to build a fence on its border with Serbia to quell a spike in refugee crossings, but doesnt plan to stop it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:45:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok so then explain to me what FWIW means? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:15:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know there was a stove business... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:11:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you should pop over to /r/gaybrosgonewild in that case...haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 06:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly ashamed this still goes on in a supposedly "civilized" Internet forum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:53:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What use are reading comprehension skills? The curtains are just fucking blue, why can't you people study something useful like STEM?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What Jeb Bush has right  and terribly wrong  about worker productivity: Some workers need more hours, but that's partly because others are working too many. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:27:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Central Intelligence Agencys health professionals repeatedly criticized the agencys post-Sept. 11 interrogation program, but their protests were rebuffed by prominent outside psychologists who lent credibility to the program, according to a sweeping new report. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:17:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Central Intelligence Agencys health professionals repeatedly criticized the agencys post-Sept. 11 interrogation program, but their protests were rebuffed by prominent outside psychologists who lent credibility to the program, according to a sweeping new report. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:16:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Philadelphia police investigate violent arrest after video of beating emerges: Video depicts as many as 26 officers kicking and punching Tyree Caroll, 22, who was initially stopped for riding his bike the wrong way down his street </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:13:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For the second time this year, the House used overwhelming bipartisan unity Friday to approve health legislation, this time voting to bolster biomedical research and streamline how the government approves drugs and medical devices. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For the second time this year, the House used overwhelming bipartisan unity Friday to approve health legislation, this time voting to bolster biomedical research and streamline how the government approves drugs and medical devices. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:08:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China and Russia Lay Foundation for Massive Economic Cooperation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China and Russia Lay Foundation for Massive Economic Cooperation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:06:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Federal Reserve chairwoman Janet Yellen has repeated her view that the central bank is likely to start raising interest rates this year. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Senate introduced a bipartisan bill on Thursday that would prevent criminal prosecution as well as liability and asset forfeiture for banks that do business with a state-sanctioned marijuana business. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:03:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Immigrants who were detained at a suburban Denver facility while they awaited deportation proceedings are suing the private company that held them, alleging they were paid $1 a day to do janitorial work, sometimes under threat of solitary confinement. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> German authorities are set to officially recognize as "genocide" the colonial-era crackdown in Namibia by German troops more than a century ago in which over 65,000 ethnic Hereros were killed. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> German authorities are set to officially recognize as "genocide" the colonial-era crackdown in Namibia by German troops more than a century ago in which over 65,000 ethnic Hereros were killed. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:01:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jeb Bush's Super PAC announced Thursday that it raised over $103 million in the first half of this year  a massive haul that makes Bush's operation by far the best-funded of any presidential candidate, Republican or Democrat. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:00:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jeb Bush's Super PAC announced Thursday that it raised over $103 million in the first half of this year  a massive haul that makes Bush's operation by far the best-funded of any presidential candidate, Republican or Democrat. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:00:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Judge pushes to speed up release of force feeding videos at Guantnamo Bay: Judge Gladys Kessler accuses Obama administration of launching baseless legal challenges to delay court-ordered release of tapes showing shocking treatment </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:56:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Japan Seeks To Export its New Sub-Hunting Plane: Tokyo has ambitions to become a global supplier of military hardware. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:54:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Three Senate Republicans, including vulnerable incumbent Mark Kirk of Illinois, helped Democrats advance a repeal of the so-called global gag rule that restricts U.S. funding to humanitarian organizations that provide abortions. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kremlin critics say a climate of fear is growing in Russia after the upper house of parliament drew up a list of "undesirable" civil rights organizations and two similar groups decided to close. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:48:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Morocco Is Running Out of Time: Unemployment and stagnation are fueling extremism  and the king's gradual reforms aren't cutting it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:44:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hackers stole Social Security numbers and other personal data for about 21.5 million people in breaches of the U.S. governments personnel office, the Obama administration said. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:41:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bumblebees being crushed by climate change </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:40:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Russia is top threat to national security, US general says </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:38:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Florida's congressional districts rejected as gerrymandered: GOP accused of ignoring constitutional requirements approved by voters in 2010, possibly affecting 22 of 27 districts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Florida's congressional districts rejected as gerrymandered: GOP accused of ignoring constitutional requirements approved by voters in 2010, possibly affecting 22 of 27 districts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obamacare has saved women more than $1 billion on birth control </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:55:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Two senior senators  one Republican, one Democrat  proposed on Wednesday that the government largely end the taxation of United States corporate profits overseas, but with a mandatory, one-time tax on such profits to pay for an expansive highway and infrastructure program. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Baltimore police chief fired in wake of scathing report on Freddie Gray protests: The report cited evidence that Anthony Batts had instructed officers to refrain from arresting rioters involved in looting during the April demonstrations </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:49:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new study estimates the number of deaths that can be linked to differences in education, and finds that variation in the risk of death across education levels has widened considerably. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Delays in efforts to form a coalition government in Turkey are buying time for President Tayyip Erdogan, heightening the chances of a snap election which could see his AK Party regain its majority and leaving the opposition floundering. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crowdsourcing brain data with hundreds of adults in a short period of time could be a new frontier in neuroscience and lead to new insights about the brain, neuroscientists have shown. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The U.S. National Security Agency tapped phone calls involving German Chancellor Angela Merkel and her closest advisers for years and spied on the staff of her predecessors, WikiLeaks said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The U.S. National Security Agency tapped phone calls involving German Chancellor Angela Merkel and her closest advisers for years and spied on the staff of her predecessors, WikiLeaks said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hillary Clinton's campaign is telegraphing that it is "worried" about an insurgent Bernie Sanders. But should it be? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Right Way to Buoy Chinas Stock Markets: Rather than relying on its own companies to expand investments, China should welcome more foreigners. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:40:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obama said to put odds of an Iran deal at less than 50-50 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obama said to put odds of an Iran deal at less than 50-50 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Former Italian PM Silvio Berlusconi has been found guilty of bribing a senator in 2006 in an attempt to bring down the then centre-left government. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Former Italian PM Silvio Berlusconi has been found guilty of bribing a senator in 2006 in an attempt to bring down the then centre-left government. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:35:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Record-breaking heavy rainfall events increased under global warming </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> all-inorganic molecular nanowires successfully compounded </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Russia has vetoed a United Nations Security Council resolution that would have described the Srebrenica massacre as "genocide". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:40:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 5 Reasons the Eurozone Could be Stronger Without Greece </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:36:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New York City officials announced a plan on Wednesday to change bail requirements for some low-level offenders in an effort to keep thousands of people out of the troubled Rikers Island jail complex. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> After months of fighting, the European Parliament voted to back a compromise on the most controversial piece in Europes evolving free trade pact with the U.S., while also giving its blessing to the future of the talks. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> FBI Chief Wants "Backdoor Access" to Encrypted Communications to Fight ISIS </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:28:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sanders Among the Least Wealthy Presidential Candidates </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:21:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China's Navy Just Got Better at Detecting and Taking Out Submarines </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:18:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Greek Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras won a commitment to seek a last-minute rescue at an emergency euro zone summit on Tuesday, before his country's banks run out of money. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 00:17:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:32:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Increasing the workload for users who voluntarily supply content doesn't seem like a good way to do things. 

I don't mind having conversations like this, because I enjoy telling moderators when they're fucking up the sub with asinine rules that filter out quality submissions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:21:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great so I created an album with both big-ass topical maps, and automod deleted it because you only allow single-image posts. That seems like such an arbitrary rule, do you want people to spam with multiple maps regarding the same topic because they can't submit an album? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mapped: The Islamic States Territorial Losses and the Beginning of a United Kurdistan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mapped: The Islamic States Territorial Losses and the Beginning of a United Kurdistan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mapped: The Islamic States Territorial Losses and the Beginning of a United Kurdistan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:17:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:09:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah an article about the huge-ass map that's embedded. Fine, I'll resubmit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The biggest and most disruptive layoffs in America are coming from the military: The Army has already discharged 80,000 troops. The next 40,000 will be harder, especially for the communities that depend on them. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:08:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Obama administration hopes to make solar power more accessible for low- and middle-income Americans. It's announcing a series of moves, including installing more solar energy units in federally subsidized housing, low cost loans for homeowners and a program to help renters. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The biggest and most disruptive layoffs in America are coming from the military: The Army has already discharged 80,000 troops. The next 40,000 will be harder, especially for the communities that depend on them. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:03:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mapped: The Islamic States Territorial Losses and the Beginning of a United Kurdistan [2166x1270] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How much a child's pupil dilates in response to seeing an emotional image can predict his or her risk of depression over the next two years, according to new research from Binghamton University. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:55:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Heroin Use Surges, Especially Among Women And Whites </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Obama administration hopes to make solar power more accessible for low- and middle-income Americans. It's announcing a series of moves, including installing more solar energy units in federally subsidized housing, low cost loans for homeowners and a program to help renters. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:51:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Obama administration hopes to make solar power more accessible for low- and middle-income Americans. It's announcing a series of moves, including installing more solar energy units in federally subsidized housing, low cost loans for homeowners and a program to help renters. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:50:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A three-quarters of a century old ban on government contractors donating money to political campaigns was upheld by a key federal appeals court Tuesday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WHO gets failing grade for Ebola response: An Independent panel urges big changes to "re-establish ... pre-eminence" of the global health body. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Philippines argued at a closed hearing Tuesday that an international court should intervene in its dispute with China over the right to exploit natural resources and fish in the South China Sea. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:43:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How a Chaotic Grexit Could Wipe Out $1.4 Trillion in Global M A </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:42:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The U.S. Just Botched Yet Another Chance to Press for Human Rights in China </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:39:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> While the United States celebrated Independence Day, two pairs of Russian bombers flew off the coast of California and Alaska -- forcing the Air Force to scramble fighter jets to intercept both flights </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hillary Clintons Team Is Wary as Bernie Sanders Finds Footing in Iowa </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:48:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> These maps show the vastly separate worlds of the rich and poor </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:47:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why hardly anyone sponsored the most-watched soccer match in U.S. history </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:45:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> These maps show the vastly separate worlds of the rich and poor </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why hardly anyone sponsored the most-watched soccer match in U.S. history </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:31:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> U.N. Report Highlights Surprising Global Progress On Poverty Goals </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:30:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A 9-year-old boy has died after his mothers boyfriend beat him for eating a piece of birthday cake without permission, police said. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:29:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> With Corruption Rampant, Good Cops Go Bad In Texas' Rio Grande Valley </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:24:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Donald Trump, 'Wrestling A Pig,' And The GOP's Struggle To Reform </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:22:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Obama administration says it cannot support either the Senate or the House versions of bills being considered this week to update the No Child Left Behind education law. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Saudi-led coalition targeting rebels in Yemen launched a massive airstrike on Monday that hit a populated marketplace, killing more than 45 civilians, according to security officials and eyewitnesses. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The European Central Bank decided Monday to keep emergency assistance to Greek banks at its current frozen level but made it slightly more difficult for the countrys lenders to obtain the funds they need. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:14:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Greeces growing political and economic problems have its small neighbor Macedonia sensing an opportunity to push hard for joining NATO, a move that has been stalled for years thanks to Athens opposition because of disputes over Macedonias name. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:14:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Greeces growing political and economic problems have its small neighbor Macedonia sensing an opportunity to push hard for joining NATO, a move that has been stalled for years thanks to Athens opposition because of disputes over Macedonias name. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:13:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> European Parliament President Martin Schulz is under fire from members of his own party who say his statements on the Greek referendum have been too combative, too focused on national politics and often unexpected. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:13:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Russian father-and-son businessmen Alexander and Evgeny Lebedev have sunk more than 100 million (140 million) into their British media interests since 2009, including the Evening Standard and Independent newspapers, according to company accounts. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 03:17:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kind of weird you used his full title, but I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 00:52:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Government so small it can fit in your bedroom" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's the future of polar bears? Studies say they may soon be extinct: A new US government report has found that if greenhouse gas emissions continue at their current rate, polar bear populations will start to rapidly decline as early as 2025. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China is suing Samsung over bloatware after finding 47 pre-installed apps </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:27:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Colorados Push Against Teenage Pregnancies Is a Startling Success </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:21:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Colorados Push Against Teenage Pregnancies Is a Startling Success </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As Bernie Sanders' popularity surges, Democrats question socialist label </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Europe and India, Testing New Delhis New Diplomacy: An underperforming relationship could benefit from some Indian reforms. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:19:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Discovery points to a new path toward a universal flu vaccine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cancer survivors who smoke report fewer negative opinions about smoking, have more barriers to quitting, and are around other smokers more often than survivors who had quit before or after their diagnosis, according to a new study appearing in Psycho-Oncology. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:17:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> On nervous border, Turks welcome army but fear incursion into Syria </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:17:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Egypts military launched air strikes and ground operations that killed 63 Islamist militants in North Sinai on Sunday, security sources said, as the country grapples with an increasingly ambitious insurgency based in the region. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:16:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Tsipras and Syriza have won big in the referendum, strengthening their hand for whatever comes next. But theyre not the only winners: I would argue that Europe, and the European idea, just won big  at least in the sense of dodging a bullet." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:15:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The U.S. Navy is tripling the amount of paid maternity leave that female sailors and Marines can take after the birth of a child, and will now provide a total of 18 weeks off. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:13:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Federal Election Commission has fined a political action committee associated with Democratic presidential candidate Bernie Sanders for missing financial reporting deadlines. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:11:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Egypts Coming Chaos: The assassination of a top official and a brazen attack by an Islamic State affiliate this week herald a prolonged period of bloodshed. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could China Save Greece from Financial Ruin? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could China Save Greece from Financial Ruin? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:10:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The GOP May Regret Its Lasting Battle Against Gay Marriage </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:09:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Case for Talking With Terrorists </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:07:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 19:04:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Showing support for what? We don't know why she was fired. You mean showing support for better communication by the admin to the mods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:33:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You really ought to have included "per capita" in the title, OP. Unnecessary confusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kaptan - Anywhere We Go [indie] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 09:35:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> CNN Worldwide's Errol Barnett is a beautiful man. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 07:27:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The discussion of this over at /r/hiphopheads is disgusting, if anyone is interested in seeing white guys justify hateful language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Online Fund Started To Raise Money For Greece's Debt </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:56:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:52:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This doesn't make sense... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Latest: Massive Militant Attack Kills 64 Egyptian Troops </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:49:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:46:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love how the simplest comments can be so sexy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 07:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This looks like an alien abduction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:03:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I've risen to convert your children to the gayness! MWAHAHAHAA" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The DOMA ruling was two years ago today :) This is one of my favorite political cartoons ever. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 18:15:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hi </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 01:48:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hi </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 01:47:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hi </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 01:47:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The head of NATO said on Wednesday the alliance would not be forced into a new arms race with Russia but said what he called Moscow's aggression in Ukraine had compelled it to strengthen its defenses. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:22:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The head of NATO said on Wednesday the alliance would not be forced into a new arms race with Russia but said what he called Moscow's aggression in Ukraine had compelled it to strengthen its defenses. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:21:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The U.S. economy contracted in the first quarter but less than previously estimated as it struggled with bad weather, a strong dollar, spending cuts in the energy sector and disruptions at West Coast ports. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:21:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Number of US homeowners reaches 20-year low: As homeownership rates drop to historic lows, low-income, middle-class and minority Americans feel the pinch of steadily increasing rents </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Number of US homeowners reaches 20-year low: As homeownership rates drop to historic lows, low-income, middle-class and minority Americans feel the pinch of steadily increasing rents </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dozens of senior Colombian army officers implicated in the killing of 3,000 civilians falsely claimed to be rebels a decade ago have risen through the ranks and are escaping punishment for their roles in one of Latin America's worst atrocities, Human Rights Watch said Wednesday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:09:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Members of the Islamic State in Iraq and the Levant (ISIL) have destroyed two historic mausoleums in the ancient city of Palmyra, Syria's top antiquities official said Wednesday, raising fears that the armed group could next target the town's famed Roman ruins. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Members of the Islamic State in Iraq and the Levant (ISIL) have destroyed two historic mausoleums in the ancient city of Palmyra, Syria's top antiquities official said Wednesday, raising fears that the armed group could next target the town's famed Roman ruins. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Senate sent President Barack Obama legislation granting fast-track trade-negotiation authority, a hard-fought victory intended to aid completion of an agreement with Pacific nations that is a top second-term priority. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:08:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Senate sent President Barack Obama legislation granting fast-track trade-negotiation authority, a hard-fought victory intended to aid completion of an agreement with Pacific nations that is a top second-term priority. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:07:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 19:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He doesn't even know what he's talking about. The deal hasn't been revealed yet. People really have no idea how trade negotiations work or how to conduct them. You want a fair deal for your country? You want trade to help you (because you *do* need trade and it *can* be helpful)? You're going to need to get with the program and stop shooting yourself in the foot by exposing the negotiations to criticism in the womb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Islamic State car bombs kill or injure 50 in Yemeni capital </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 09:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For those wishing to lose weight and keep it off, heres a simple strategy that works: step on a scale each day and track the results. A two-year study found that frequent self-weighing and tracking results on a chart were effective for both losing weight and keeping it off, especially for men. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 09:34:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 06:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean I would also argue that Jackson was a genocidal maniac toward Native Americans and Alexander Hamilton was, well, not as much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Without public notice or debate, the Obama administration has expanded the National Security Agencys warrantless surveillance of Americans international Internet traffic to search for evidence of malicious computer hacking, according to classified N.S.A. documents. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 00:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Without public notice or debate, the Obama administration has expanded the National Security Agencys warrantless surveillance of Americans international Internet traffic to search for evidence of malicious computer hacking, according to classified N.S.A. documents. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 00:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Without public notice or debate, the Obama administration has expanded the National Security Agencys warrantless surveillance of Americans international Internet traffic to search for evidence of malicious computer hacking, according to classified N.S.A. documents. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 00:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ominous Warning Signs Resurface in Zimbabwe: Ethnic hatreds, murky disappearances, and the purging of enemies are all on the rise in Robert Mugabe's dictatorship. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 00:23:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ISIL wins support from Iraq's Sunni tribes: Influential sheikhs and tribal heads in Anbar province pledge allegiance to group and condemn Iraqi government. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:51:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:16:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your sources are half reputable and half laughable. RT (State-run Russian propaganda), breitbart (koo-koo crazy ultra-conservative webmagazine), random imgur links, random reddit comments?

If you're going to ring alarm bells about something, you need to do it with better sources. Be ironclad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> FIFAs Corruption Stains World Soccer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My DJ Crush: Flume </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 08:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's cloudy a lot. Seriously. Seasonal Affective Disorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 10:16:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God, fuckin' soccer players, every goddamn time. So hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Minorities and poor college students are shouldering the most student debt </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Minorities and poor college students are shouldering the most student debt </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:09:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bernie Sanderss plan to have Wall Street pay for your college tuition, explained </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Media coverage of gang violence sure looks different when the perpetrators are white </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:07:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Media coverage of gang violence sure looks different when the perpetrators are white </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:06:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Germany needs to calm down: The country's political left is hyperventilating over a string of spying revelations. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:05:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Greece says deal near, again: But same old barriers to an agreement with creditors remain. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:04:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kayaktavists Take Over Seattle's Port to Protest Shell Oil's Arctic Drilling Rig </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:57:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kayaktavists Take Over Seattle's Port to Protest Shell Oil's Arctic Drilling Rig </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:57:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kayaktavists Take Over Seattle's Port to Protest Shell Oil's Arctic Drilling Rig </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kayaktavists Take Over Seattle's Port to Protest Shell Oil's Arctic Drilling Rig </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fossil fuels subsidised by $10m a minute, says IMF: Shocking revelation finds $5.3tn subsidy estimate for 2015 is greater than the total health spending of all the worlds governments </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Supreme Court ruled Monday that San Francisco police cannot be sued by a mentally disturbed woman who was shot repeatedly during a 2008 confrontation, but the justices declined to rule on whether the officers involved were required to use less forceful methods. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:31:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Supreme Court ruled Monday that San Francisco police cannot be sued by a mentally disturbed woman who was shot repeatedly during a 2008 confrontation, but the justices declined to rule on whether the officers involved were required to use less forceful methods. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:31:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> US residents' exposure to extreme heat could increase four- to six-fold by mid-century, due to both a warming climate and a population that's growing especially fast in the hottest regions of the country, according to new research. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:29:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> U.S. loses meat labeling case; trade war looms </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:25:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bernie Sanders Wants to Tax Stock Trades to Pay for Free College </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:22:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> EU approves military force against smugglers: The focus now shifts to winning UN approval to take the fight into Libyan territory. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Worker-rights groups are calling labor conditions in Qatar "horrific" and urging FIFA sponsors to take responsibility ahead of the 2022 soccer World Cup. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:17:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> US officials are increasingly anxious about the potential for mass violence in Burundi, a small African country whose troops have received significant American support and play a major role in the fight against Islamist militants. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:14:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why the era of college grads working at restaurants and cafes is coming to an end </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mission Unstoppable: From drone strikes to prison torture, the CIA has been pulling the strings of U.S. foreign policy since 9/11. And if history is a guide, the agency will be calling the shots in the Middle East for years to come. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:10:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mission Unstoppable: From drone strikes to prison torture, the CIA has been pulling the strings of U.S. foreign policy since 9/11. And if history is a guide, the agency will be calling the shots in the Middle East for years to come. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:10:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Captured Russian Special Forces Soldier Describes His Unit Fighting in Eastern Ukraine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Balancing China and the Realist Road to War: The argument for balancing against China rests on some questionable assumptions. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:03:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What Serial Didn't Tell You About Adnan Syed: The addictive public-radio series focused on his background. A broader problem is at play that hurts thousands of kids. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:00:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 01:28:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The bus terminated its route at 8:30pm, and it was the last bus? Is this a true story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jeb Bush didn't say Apple Watches should replace Obamacare. He said something weirder. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:40:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Review Board Notes Rise in New York Officers False Statements </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:38:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tajik Special Police Commander Disappears </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Libya to Europe: Please Dont Come to Our Rescue </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jeb Bush Just Nailed a Flip-Flop-Flip-Flop on the Iraq War </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:23:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Five soldiers killed in fierce fighting in Burundi's capital </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Indias Military Cannot Fight Wars Lasting Longer than 20 Days: A recent report by the Indian government points to an ammunition crisis in the India Army. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 23:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 04:45:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plenty of redditors don't like this quote in particular because the arms industry manufactures the firearms that they love. That's part of it.

The other part is that reddit doesn't like religion very much. The pope is a religious figure.

Another part is that the Catholic Church has caused plenty of deaths in its time, and is hardly a pillar of moral superiority.

Another is that it's just sort of obvious to most people.

That's why the comments are so hostile. Luckily, it seems that many more thousands of people think it's a fine quote, by the vote count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The White House formally threw its support behind the USA Freedom Act Tuesday, fully endorsing a plan to end the government's bulk collection of personal data and replace it with a more tailored program that would allow phone companies to do the collection instead. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:57:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Police in the central Florida city where George Zimmerman suffered minor injuries in an apparent road rage incident said the suspect in the shooting had two guns in his car at the time  and that Zimmerman also had a gun. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Madison, Wisconsin, cop who shot and killed unarmed teenager Tony Terrell Robinson Jr. won't face charges, the prosecutor said Tuesday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great write up, but just to point something out about the idiomatic phrase in the beginning, it's "makes my blood boil" not "makes me boil my blood." For future reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Moving the Drone Program from the CIA to the Pentagon Wont Improve Transparency: Generals arent better than spooks when it comes to reporting civilian casualties. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 22:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Syrian group opposed to the country's autocratic leader, Bashar al-Assad, says airstrikes by the U.S.-led coalition killed 52 civilians. The Syrian Observatory for Human Rights called the alleged killings a "massacre" committed under the "pretext" of targeting ISIS militants. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:16:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Russian warships force Lithuania to halt Baltic power cable construction </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Russian warships force Lithuania to halt Baltic power cable construction </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What Norway Can Teach the U.S. About Getting More Women Into Boardrooms </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:04:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Iraqi forces plead for help as Islamic State closes in on refinery </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:02:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> On Monday, a group of Israeli veterans released sobering testimony from fellow soldiers that suggests permissive rules of engagement coupled with indiscriminate artillery fire contributed to the mass destruction and high numbers of civilian casualties in the [Gaza Strip] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:01:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Journalists Critical Of FIFA Arrested And Detained In Qatar </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Journalists Critical Of FIFA Arrested And Detained In Qatar </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Texas Governor Deploys State Guard To Stave Off Obama Takeover </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:30:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A shocking number of mentally ill Americans end up in prison instead of treatment </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:24:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Saudi-led coalition carrying out airstrikes in Yemen has probably used cluster bombs, which are banned by over 100 countries, the international monitoring group Human Rights Watch (HRW) said on Sunday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saudi-led campaign drops US-made cluster bombs on Yemen rebels: HRW </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:23:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 23:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Latin American countries are culturally similar to the U.S.? Have you visited either place...?

Also, you've completely forgotten how many asian immigrants we take in on the West Coast.

Stop making uneducated excuses for your ill-informed xenophobia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:04:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you hate me, /u/PrettyIceCube?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Washington State Auditor Troy Kelley pleaded not guilty Thursday to federal charges of filing false tax returns, attempted obstruction and possession of stolen property. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:36:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An international team of researchers led by the University of Alberta used MRI video to determine what happens inside finger joints to cause the distinctive popping sounds heard when cracking knuckles. For the first time, they observed that the cause is a cavity forming rapidly inside the joint. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seattle Is Helping Drug Addicts Instead of Locking Them Up  and So Far Its Working </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seattle Is Helping Drug Addicts Instead of Locking Them Up  and So Far Its Working </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:28:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> At least five people have died in a wave of violence against foreigners in Durban, South Africa, while thousands more were driven out of their homes in the coastal city ... in the commercial hub of Johannesburg, immigrant shopkeepers fearing copycat attacks have closed their businesses. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The first F-35 jets ready for combat wont be able to protect forces in ground combat as well as the nearly 40-year-old A-10s the Pentagon wants to retire, according to the Defense Departments chief weapons tester. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:55:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The first F-35 jets ready for combat wont be able to protect forces in ground combat as well as the nearly 40-year-old A-10s the Pentagon wants to retire, according to the Defense Departments chief weapons tester. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Asking people to explain their reasoning is the best way to soften their strongly-clenched belief and win the argument." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:56:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Undocumented Immigrants Pay Billions in Taxes to Fund Programs Theyre Banned From Using </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm very much surprised there hasn't been a shoutout to /r/forearmporn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 07:57:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, there've also been actual cuts to higher ed. In my state, the portion of tuition that was covered by the state has flipped from 66% to 33% in a few years. Meanwhile, we have more students and therefore a need for more bureaucracy.

We can settle for less and argue all we want about who gets the scraps, but the fact is we *need* to raise state funding generally. Both admin and faculty need to get paid, not one or the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why wasn't Italy a great power at the time of WWI? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 20:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm reading "The First World War and the International Power System" by Paul Kennedy, and he uses several tables and a short paragraph to summarize some of the basic causes of Italy's shitty performance during WWI; its industrial incapability, it's lack of economic power, etc. I'm wondering why Italy was so industrially incompetent and economically weak in the first place, despite having the historical power of the Vatican and having famous traders and explorers, and having such strong allies? Also why it militarily did not perform very well, but that's probably related to the answer to the question above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 01:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't it be UPS? Brown shirt and all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The White House is removing a federal regulation that subjects its Office of Administration to the Freedom of Information Act, making official a policy under Presidents Bush and Obama to reject requests for records to that office. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 23:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is attractiveness objective or subjective? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 20:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How did Portugal go from being a colonial empire to Western Europe's poorest country? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 19:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll just bet it has something to do with those meddling British and their dumb Navy, but I really have to clue! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Edward Snowden, the fugitive whistleblower who has been given refuge in Russia, is willing to return to the United States if he is given a fair trial, his lawyer said Tuesday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:55:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The US militarys top-ranking officer has called for Washington to arm Ukraine in its battle with pro-Russian forces, saying he favours doing so through Nato. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The US militarys top-ranking officer has called for Washington to arm Ukraine in its battle with pro-Russian forces, saying he favours doing so through Nato. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:49:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Justice Department has cleared a Ferguson, Mo., police officer of civil rights violations in the shooting of Michael Brown, a black teenager whose death set off racially charged and sometimes violent protests last year. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:43:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Iraqi Campaign to Drive ISIS From Tikrit Reveals Tensions With U.S. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The European Union will need radical new policies to reach goals for safeguarding the environment by 2050 after limited progress in curbing pollution and climate change, the European Environment Agency (EEA) said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:41:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Greece could need a third bailout deal when its current program expires in June because markets may still not be prepared to lend to its government, even with a euro-area credit line, European Commission Vice President Valdis Dombrovskis said. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:07:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The United Nations says the number of people killed in eastern Ukraine since fighting broke out in April now tops 6,000 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Venezuela on Monday ordered the U.S. embassy in Caracas to reduce staff from 100 to 17 amid the worst diplomatic flare-up between the two ideological foes since socialist President Nicolas Maduro was elected in 2013. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:05:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> S Secretary of State John Kerry on Monday delivered a vigorous defense of Israel before the UN Human Rights Council, urging its members to end what the United States says is its unfair and biased focus on the Jewish State that could undermine its credibility. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:02:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 22:29:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't understand why this reply from an expert is not being upvoted more than Dr. Amateur up there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Washington police shoot and kill man throwing rocks </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 21:28:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A rookie New York City police officer was charged with second-degree manslaughter and five other offenses on Wednesday for the fatal shooting of an unarmed man in a dark stairwell of a housing project last November. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 00:56:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Its Hard To Know Where Gluten Sensitivity Stops And The Placebo Effect Begins </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 00:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Live Nation exploits low-wage workers to stage its rock concerts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 23:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Puerto Ricos controversial proposal would fine the parents of obese children </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 23:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One quote that shows how the media covers mass shootings differently based on race </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:56:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One quote that shows how the media covers mass shootings differently based on race </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:56:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new report from the Federal Reserve Bank of New York sends a more sobering message to millennials: Your first 10 years in the labor market likely shape your lifetime earning potential. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:49:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new report from the Federal Reserve Bank of New York sends a more sobering message to millennials: Your first 10 years in the labor market likely shape your lifetime earning potential. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:49:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kansas governor removes protections for LGBT employees </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 19:14:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In a dramatic show of defiance toward the federal judiciary, Chief Justice Roy S. Moore of the Alabama Supreme Court on Sunday night ordered the states probate judges not to issue marriage licenses to gay couples on Monday, the day same-sex marriages were expected to begin here. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 19:08:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Myth Behind Defensive Gun Ownership: Guns are more likely to do harm than good. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-08 21:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 08:21:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And marvel underwear!! Wonder who's on them ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-29 09:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if I told you...it doesn't matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 23:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Another* Jobs biopic? Ugh...

But yes to Michael. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit is: totally avoiding the point for the sake of feeling important by correcting technicalities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-25 06:30:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The basic premise that you're communicating is something I agree with, but you could maybe not be an asshole about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 07:22:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You just ran a half marathon on a whim?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 21:38:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I mean yeah, but certainly the cunts over at /r/worldnews can be a bit cuntier than most, let's not throw ourselves all in their boat.

Edit: although I did use the word "cunt" twice in that sentence, so...maybe I do kind of suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So did you enjoy it? I haven't read it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 05:40:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HEY EVERYBODY!! THIS GUY'S GIVING OUT FREE KARMA FOR ZOOLANDER REFERENCES!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-06 21:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eh, from time to time Disney does some fucked up shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Uncivil society: A genuine grassroots democratic movement to deny rights to same-sex families (Slovakia) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 19:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I would actually totally cuddle with this one </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-04 03:36:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 21:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh please, go back to writing your angsty poetry, would you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 21:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, yeah, but it's *French* you uncultured swine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 20:30:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm. The connection is tenuous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 10:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is, um...is it...a dick?

I think it might be a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-26 00:01:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's got your mother? Or your approval? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 19:52:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Pakistan has...how many nuclear weapons, now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-15 03:02:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, that and well, I mean...y'know, you're...white. Ahem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-15 01:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't be so rudely pointed. You could afford to suggest improvements more tactfully, if you want them taken seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-13 10:59:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just so you know, OP, you misspelled "probably." Otherwise, everything is spelled correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 02:18:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes hello from the US, hopefully you can have your university students send us a "thank you" card or something for subsidizing your defense and freeing up all those education funds!

Not that I resent it or anything, it's just not so lickety-split as it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 02:07:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This article is suuuuper harsh, wow. Idk enough to decide whether it's justified or not, but man that author seems to  really hate them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-30 10:11:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy Birthday Massacre! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-29 21:09:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't think these people were actually real. Is this a troll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-28 09:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DOOOHOOHOOHOOOOOD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-28 00:20:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIL black people are bad, and white people are victimized! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 06:23:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> p[a]edophile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 00:36:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you are not a brick, I assume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 23:37:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're a party pooper, that's what you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 00:54:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I MUST PET THEM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-19 02:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You shut up! My master could beat up your master! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 19:22:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LOL wrong thread dude XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 03:22:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No Eyes is creeping me iut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:20:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG I have those same PJ's! I also have a dick pic in them...funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 20:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That makes more sense, but I prefer the other explanation better because it validates my opinions.

I'm torn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 19:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly I'm very surprised there isn't more content there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 22:33:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You missed the reference, that's why you got downvoted.

Life is unfair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-14 09:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I instantly read it in her voice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 05:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> C'mon man, in layman's terms please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Be careful when you grab that office bagel. The Internal Revenue Service may be watching. The U.S. tax agency is taking a closer look at a popular tax-exempt perk offered by companies such as Google Inc.: free meals. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 19:01:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-28 06:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree. Unsubbed a while ago. Very glad, much fewer random pictures of (what I think are) uninteresting things showing up on my front page.

Some people enjoy the sort of click-baity stuff that makes up most of the defaults, and that's fine, it can be fun. But I don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:03:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where do you live? You can register in WA state online! Maybe you can in your state, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 22:07:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is much hatred for this comment. It isn't the best comment, certainly. But the hatred seems disproportionate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gaza Cease-Fire Efforts Collapse in Heavy Fighting </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 01:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> St. Louis Cops Shoot and Kill Man Near Ferguson, Crowd Gathers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:48:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Washington thinktank has issued an apology after telling the human rights group Amnesty International to suck it on Twitter. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:46:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Washington thinktank has issued an apology after telling the human rights group Amnesty International to suck it on Twitter. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:45:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Liberia battled on Tuesday to halt the spread of the Ebola disease in its crowded, run-down oceanside capital Monrovia, recording the most new deaths as fatalities from the world's worst outbreak of the deadly virus rose above 1,200. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We know very little about when and why police use their weapons </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:38:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Link to study](http://www.asanet.org/documents/press/pdfs/AM_2014_Christin_Munsch_News_Release_FINAL.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Study: Women less likely than men to have flexible work schedule approved </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:32:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> LA schools to end zero-tolerance polices and criminalization of students </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Police to Al Jazeera journalist near Ferguson: 'I'll bust your head' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 06:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, yeah, sorry about that. All you've got to do is close it out, you get like 8 articles a month for free or something like that.

Edit: Alternatively, $2.99 is a pretty good deal for a subscription, if you're as in to foreign affairs as I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Whats the Matter With Europe? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 05:45:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Unidentified war planes flew over the Libyan capital Tripoli early on Monday and explosions could be heard, residents said. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 05:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You Are Not Nearly Scared Enough About Ebola: Experimental drugs and airport screenings will do nothing to stop this plague. If Ebola hits Lagos, we're in real trouble. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 05:36:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to Beat Down a Bully: There's only one way to stop Putin's ugly new doctrine of irregular intervention -- hit back even harder. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 05:28:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Summer Jobs Are Slowly Disappearing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 05:26:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China Home Prices Fall in Majority of Cities on Weak Demand </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 05:24:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China Home Prices Fall in Majority of Cities on Weak Demand </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 05:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tens of thousands of Chinese gathered in sweltering heat in Hong Kong on Sunday to protest against a pro-democracy campaign that has threatened to shut down the city's financial district, exposing a deepening rift over political reforms in the former British colony. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 05:21:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 01:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I'm gay." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 01:10:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Eh, I got work in the morning. Catch ya later!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-17 00:14:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-15 07:18:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ron Paul suggests using DDT to stop the spread of Ebola (like malaria), and is quite wrong about that being an effective treatment. From the article:

"'As far as I can make out he's wrong about everything,' Fordham University's Dr. Alexander van Tulleken told Foreign Policy. No licensed or approved treatment for Ebola exists. Yes, the experimental ZMapp drug seems to have effectively treated two American aid workers transported from Liberia to Atlanta, and more such untested drugs are in development. But those patients have also benefited from expert care, van Tulleken notes, so the jury's still out. 'The only treatments for Ebola really are supportive care' such as ventilation to support lung failure, dialysis for kidney failure or fluid replacement via IV.

As for Paul's claims about DDT and organic phosphates, neither is an actual treatment nor control mechanism for Ebola. While some in the public health community view DDT as a legitimate solution for slowing malaria, there's no science that says it would cure or control Ebola.
'What Ron Paul has done is confuse Ebola with malaria,' van Tulleken says. **'If you hose DDT around, you get rid of the mosquitoes, and maybe get rid of malaria. But Ebola is transmitted by bodily fluid. He's really fucked it up.'** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ebola Expert on Ron Paul: 'He Really Fucked Up' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-15 07:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-15 06:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/botsrights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drug-fueled, EDM-obsessed millennials are saving the music business </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 21:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Associated Press journalist, translator killed by explosion in Gaza </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 00:24:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Associated Press journalist, translator killed by explosion in Gaza </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 00:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Militarization of the Police: Its dangerous and wrong to treat Ferguson, Missouri, as a war zone. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 22:56:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Militarization of the Police: Its dangerous and wrong to treat Ferguson, Missouri, as a war zone. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 22:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 20:49:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't voting mandatory in Australia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-12 08:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God this is gonna be a question on ELI5 in like 6 months, the way things are going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-10 22:36:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [link to study](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate2335.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The much-debated Keystone XL pipeline could produce four times more global warming pollution than the State Department calculated earlier this year, a new study concludes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-10 22:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The night before his husband's funeral, Kendall Capers was told the service was cancelled. The pastor of New Hope Missionary Baptist Church in Tampa learned the pair was gay and the congregation was livid. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-09 20:08:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The night before his husband's funeral, Kendall Capers was told the service was cancelled. The pastor of New Hope Missionary Baptist Church in Tampa learned the pair was gay and the congregation was livid. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-09 20:08:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-09 10:08:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, indubitably! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An "unprecedented" spill from a mine tailings pond in Canadas pristine British Columbia has prompted a local state of emergency and water ban while environmentalists worry the contamination could have far-reaching environmental impacts as salmon return to spawn. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-08 00:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Europes low inflation is sending it into a lost decade </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-08 00:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Europes low inflation is sending it into a lost decade </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-08 00:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> European Spacecraft Pulls Alongside Comet After 10 Years and Four Billion Miles </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:47:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why the Summer Music Festival Bubble is About to Burst </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:26:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 00:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He really could've just given a straightforward "I was happy to see so many great law enforcement folks there last week, whether they were on duty or not." It was a little too bullshitty of an answer. Gotta really tread that line carefully between "bullshit" and "steaming bullshit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An American Jewish blogger who called the genocide of the Palestinian people a "responsible" and "permissible" goal has continued to defend his position on social media despite widespread criticism. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 20:43:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Managers are nearly twice as likely as service workers to get paid time off </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 20:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An internal investigation by the Central Intelligence Agency has found that its officers improperly penetrated a computer network used by the Senate Intelligence Committee in preparing its report on the C.I.A.'s detention and interrogation program. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 19:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A sharply divided House approved a Republican plan Wednesday to launch a campaign-season lawsuit against President Barack Obama, accusing him of exceeding the bounds of his constitutional authority. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 07:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The middle class is 20 percent poorer than it was in 1984 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 23:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The middle class is 20 percent poorer than it was in 1984 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 23:32:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Renting drives U.S. homeownership to 19-year low </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 22:49:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A federal appeals court panel ruled Tuesday that a Mississippi law that would close the state's only abortion clinic is unconstitutional. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 22:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Insurgents fighting in Syria to oust President Bashar al-Assad detonated bomb-packed tunnels under buildings in the contested northern city of Aleppo on Tuesday, killing at least 13 pro-government troops, opposition activists said. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 22:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A top Canadian government research organisation has been struck by Chinese hackers, the government has said. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 22:25:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In a startling charge delivered at an anti-Initiative 594 meeting last week at Silverdale, the National Rifle Associations chief state lobbyist likened Washingtons campaign to close the gun show loophole to Nazi Germany. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 00:38:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The new land of opportunity for immigrants is Germany </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:53:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The new land of opportunity for immigrants is Germany </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:52:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> States that allow officers to pull over a driver for texting while driving saw fewer deaths than those that use secondary enforcement of texting bans. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Five members of a family, including three children, were found shot dead at their southern Maine home on Sunday, with a gun located near one of the bodies and no outside involvement suspected, a police spokesman said. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ebola kills senior doctor in Liberia: First Liberian physician dies in an outbreak that has killed more than 650 people in West Africa since February </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:29:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A tanker carrying crude oil from Iraqi Kurdistan was anchored near the Port of Galveston, Texas, on Sunday, a delivery that has infuriated Baghdad, which has threatened to sue anyone who buys the black gold. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:22:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 'Only stones remain': Gaza lies in ruins | Palestinians in Gaza have been shocked by the scale of Israeli destruction, as long-term truce efforts continue </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> U.S.: Satellite Images Show Russian Rockets Hitting Ukraine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-27 20:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Many Lawyers Does It Take to Fight a War? | When the dust finally settles in Gaza, the battle will head to the courtroom. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-27 20:03:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to Kneecap the Thug in the Kremlin | It's time to treat Vladimir Putin like the crime boss he is: Go after his money. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-27 20:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hamas rejected Israel's four-hour extension of a humanitarian cease-fire Saturday as the Palestinian death toll in the conflict rose to more than 1,000. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 21:18:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Typical Household, Now Worth a Third Less: The inflation-adjusted net worth for the typical household was $87,992 in 2003. Ten years later, it was only $56,335, or a 36 percent decline, according to a study financed by the Russell Sage Foundation. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:44:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The United States shut down its embassy in Libya on Saturday and evacuated its diplomats to neighboring Tunisia under U.S. military escort amid a significant deterioration in security in Tripoli as fighting intensified between rival militias, the State Department said. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:35:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ukraines army advanced on a last main separatist stronghold as the U.S. said Vladimir Putin is poised to give the rebels heavy weapons and European Union leaders considered their toughest sanctions yet on Russia. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ukraines army advanced on a last main separatist stronghold as the U.S. said Vladimir Putin is poised to give the rebels heavy weapons and European Union leaders considered their toughest sanctions yet on Russia. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Barrel Bomb Attacks Devastate Iraqi Families </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Liberian man who died in quarantine in Lagos was suffering from the deadly virus Ebola, Nigerian officials said Friday, confirming that the worst-ever outbreak of the virus has reached Africa's most populous country. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The most conservative way to fight poverty is to send everyone a government check </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In an intensely awkward congressional hearing Thursday, freshman Rep. Curt Clawson misidentified two senior U.S government officials as representatives of the Indian government. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:52:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In an intensely awkward congressional hearing Thursday, freshman Rep. Curt Clawson misidentified two senior U.S government officials as representatives of the Indian government. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:51:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pentagon: Russia Could Move Heavier Weapons Into Ukraine 'Imminently' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> U.S. Considering Refugee Status for Hondurans </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:34:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 19:39:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually in Washington state at least you can fight another person consensually as long as each party agrees that it's consensual, except when there is reasonable suspicion of it being a domestic dispute.

At least, that's how I've had that RCW explained to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The U.S. says it has "new evidence" that Russian forces have been firing artillery across the border to attack Ukrainian military positions, and that Moscow is planning to ship powerful rocket artillery to the rebels it backs in the country's east. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Europe's top human rights court ruled Thursday that Poland broke the law by allowing the CIA to secretly imprison two terror suspects on Polish soil from 2002-2003 and facilitating the conditions under which they were subject to torture. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Iraqi lawmakers elected a veteran Kurdish politician as the nation's new president Thursday, just hours after an attack on a prison convoy killed dozens of people, brutally underscoring the challenges faced by the country's leaders as they struggle to form a new government. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ukraine's prime minister has announced his resignation in protest of the disbanding of the ruling coalition in parliament following the withdrawal of several pro-European parties. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:22:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ukraine's prime minister has announced his resignation in protest of the disbanding of the ruling coalition in parliament following the withdrawal of several pro-European parties. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:21:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Intelligence security initiatives have chilling effect on federal whistleblowers, critics say </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 23:13:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For Israelis on Edge of Battle, Rockets Put On a Show </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 07:54:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Supreme Court allows Ariz. execution despite concerns over drug secrecy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 07:45:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In handling rape, high schools are worse than colleges </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 02:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sen. Chuck Schumer is calling for partisan primaries to be abolished, saying the current system engenders unhealthy political polarization. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 02:35:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> North Dakotas Oil Bonanza Is Unsustainable </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 00:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is the American dream dead? A groundbreaking new study from Johns Hopkins University shows that for big segments of the population it is </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-22 23:54:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 700 Syrians killed in two days of conflict </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-22 23:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The PowerPoint rant that got a colonel fired </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-20 04:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-19 19:39:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG you're the best.

I'm ashamed I didn't recognize that, though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 09:09:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait wait am I correctly seeing a tattoo combining the yin-yang/rebel alliance/galactic empire symbols?

That's the second-best thing in this photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-12 06:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The worst part is that it's a repost? Or that TIL never *actually* learns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cro - Traum </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-10 06:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cro -- Traum [Rap] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 02:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 00:39:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god bad memories from that movie. The one for Lust was awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 00:38:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let's all calm down, old sport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 00:37:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd believe it. Americans are pretty famous for bandwagoning, y'know. (WWI, anyone?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-07 07:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah no apology, it's confusing regardless of any language barrier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-07 07:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh, no to repealing it or no to keeping it?

Double negatives really suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-07 01:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NO MERCY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-06 04:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "So edgy Dianne Feinstein's trying to ban it."

Ugh, can we just agree to leave gun-nut politics in /r/progun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-30 05:14:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quick! Save yourself and put an /s at the end!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-30 05:06:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm Spartacus! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-29 08:08:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that was unexpected. Maybe he/she's in remission or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-28 08:43:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People aren't stupid, we just need a little tort reform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-26 18:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basketball? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 09:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> top two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 02:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the minds of most Americans, yes, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 02:02:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *sighhh*...thanks Belgium, you guys did good today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 02:01:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea no kidding. Americans dig an absolute crushing victory, not a tie at the last minute. If anything this will decrease interest in the next match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 01:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IT WAS YOUUUUUUU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 01:54:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GOD FUCKING DAMN IT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 01:49:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god Oh my god 4 minutes ok we can do this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 01:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> stop stop stop don't speak too soon damn it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Russia's Quiet War Against European Fracking: Environmentalists trying to block shale gas exploration across Europe are unknowingly helping Putin maintain his energy leverage over the continent. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-22 20:06:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-21 04:38:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Remember they need to get approved by congress. That shit ain't easy, Supreme Court justices are always gonna be moderate unless one party controls the government, which is unlikely given the redistricting. And even if the democrats somehow gain control of both houses miraculously, when do they really ever have their ducks in a row to confirm a real progressive justice? The coalition is too broad for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-21 04:31:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How many times do I have to do that? For gods sake, I've already deleted my account once to start fresh and customize my subs. The small, nice subreddits I find keep getting bigger and already I'm seeing some of them decrease in quality.

I wish I could just *enjoy* it. I don't mind a little work finding new subreddits, but it seems to be an endless cycle. Too much work.

*good example of this:* ELI5, ELIAMA, which both used to be pristine, awesome places. Now they're used as soapboxes for neckbeards and armchair revolutionaries, as well as racists (recall the recent "ELI5 Why gypsies suck" thread). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-20 08:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No.

Zinn's one (slightly crackpot) side to a multifaceted story. The senate was an unelected body meant to provide (in theory, mind you) a bulwark against an overreaching federal government and semi-autonomous regional governments. 

Of course the framers were concerned about tyranny of the majority, as they should be, but the senate was not designed *only* to be a check on majority rule, and I disagree with his idea that "the framers" acted as one body that was exclusively interested in protecting their interests, and that that's the primary role they saw for the government. The framers were not a unanimous bloc, they had a lot of ideas for the roles of government, and they all disagreed about many of them. You can't make such blanket statements, things are more nuanced than that.

I can't stand people running around waving *People's History of the United States* and spouting these things as if they're the only way to look at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-19 07:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/polandball! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-18 08:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh. I get it. That's really bad, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 08:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/ladybonersgonecuddly for not just double, but *triple* the karma


^^and ^^compliments, ^^cutie ^^;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm still rooting for Germany tomorrow, but Portugal's got them beat for "Hottest Team Captain." (Cristiano Ronaldo) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-16 06:13:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-13 20:53:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DAE reddit funnier than 9gag? We're so much FUCKING FUNNIER AND DON'T YOU DARE DISAGREE WITH ME.

[L]edit: thanks for the gold :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pentagon preparing for mass civil breakdown: Social science is being militarised to develop 'operational tools' to target peaceful activists and protest movements </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-13 19:57:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-13 01:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [:(](http://i.imgur.com/tDXwZIY.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 23:31:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think the race is a necessary descriptor here
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 23:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The stadium looks a lot emptier now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 22:49:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really digging Croatia's kit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 22:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAALLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 22:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's what happened, and here's a digital recreation. It looks just like what we showed you, see?? Preeeetty nifty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 22:23:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The country might literally become a failed state </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 03:41:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was homophobia?

Edit: Thanks for the prompt responses, I remember the "boy-lover" quote but I kind of consider that just criticism of pedophilia. It's still completely historically inaccurate for the Spartans to be critical of that, but I wouldn't say it's "homophobic" in itself.  But from what you're all telling me this Miller dude does sound like an asshole, and he probably is a homophobe himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 19:05:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a jazz subreddit for everything!

/r/jazzhands? Oh, no apparently not...hm.../r/jazzflute? Huh. I'm a little disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 19:03:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or requests for war stories from visitors misunderstanding the focus of the sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Surrounded </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 18:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "So few want to be rebels anymore." - Ray Bradbury [1920x1200] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 08:19:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-08 17:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You seem a bit tense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-07 21:33:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best way to win in Civ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-31 01:15:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh very nice. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-30 23:39:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there a line graph for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-29 20:23:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds like something straight out of *Fallout.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-28 22:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Why are we changing maps?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eLqC3FNNOaI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-28 20:50:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you work there? How were you able to describe this in so much detail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-28 19:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OH MY GOD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-28 19:52:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus. I'm sorry but where did this actually come from? Did somebody originally type this as a serious comment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-28 19:48:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol somebody isn't STEM hahaha. DAE love getting a job out of college and being better than everyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-27 15:32:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most of the time, yes. I actually pay attention to the NYT comments because the readers' picks and NYT picks are often insightful! Idk if other newspapers do that, though. Maybe the WSJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-26 21:09:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nationalism is an important factor for WWII. Perhaps not *quite* as much in France and GB but nationalism had a huge role in justification and cause for the Nazi party's actions and policies.

It's not the sole cause of either war, but it's an important factor in both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-25 22:07:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Upvotes just for saying the name. God I love that movie, it's why I wanted to become a paleontologist.

I never did become one :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-25 21:45:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then again, most stylists probably make more money if you buy both their shampoo and their conditioner.

/r/Conspiracy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-25 00:33:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh. I thought it was just a historical reference. TIL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-24 19:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait since when did the TEA become an acronym? Why is it all caps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-24 10:13:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 01:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With regard to the categories, a glossary is provided at the bottom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-17 19:18:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The human head weighs eight pounds! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-17 06:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BTW that test was actually only at half the strength! They had designed it to be up to around 100 MT but scaled it to half that in the interest of safety so the bombers could fly out of range of the blast in time.

Just a cool tidbit on how fucking big that bomb actually was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-13 07:48:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahaa...I'm getting nothing done tonight...sighhhhhh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wave Racer -- Streamers [EDM] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-13 06:13:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wave Racer - Streamers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-13 05:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-12 03:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can have all the girls you want if you STOP HOSTING YOUR GIFS ON MINUS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-10 19:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disagree: there are many delicious Mexican restaraunts. They are the only redeeming quality of that town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Taking a photo against a white background? Amazon owns the patent on that </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 21:03:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 01:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right there with you. Too bad I'm stuck here. They have way too much power... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An Open Garage, a Dead Exchange Student and a New Debate on Self-Defense: Montana Homeowner Shoots German Teenager </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 01:07:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Montana Homeowner Shoots German Teenager </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 00:55:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> British View of Europe Faces a Test </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 00:19:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-07 18:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For a quick, extremely well-written read on war in Europe, I recommend *War In European History* by Michael Howard.

It covers a lot of what you talked about, and more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-28 00:15:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> POLAN STRONK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-18 22:05:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would disagree and say a 7.5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-18 01:29:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can always count on /r/science to have one of the top comments be bitching about the article title rather than discussing the article itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-14 06:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GO DAWGS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-11 06:44:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For additional reading I would suggest Horkheimer and Adorno's *Diaclectic of Enlightenment*, for political theorist's explanation for fascism in the context of the Enlightenment, written during the Second World War. You could even just read the first chapter and be a bit more, well, enlightened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-04 20:09:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> interesting choice of thumbnail... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-31 00:59:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Panamanorama" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-30 03:00:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or worsen it...worth it...? Tough question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-29 08:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> didn't he just shoot someone the other day? Or was that just a rumor? I just saw a headline somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>