<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1541</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Went to an antique show over the weekend </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:03:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome! My dad picked up 2 cameras for me last time he went to Hong Kong so I can use them racing. I have a track day on Wednesday so I'll be sure to post some videos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:02:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm almost positive it didn't, but I don't play 5 anymore so I can't say for sure. The straight cuts were one of the best things ever in that game, it truly made it sound like you were driving a race car. Especially the BMWs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:11:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree, I remember back in Forza 4 and 3 when you upgraded the transmission it would actually change the sound like it had straight cut gears  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:58:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll pm you later. I'm going to look at one from an s2 tonight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just blew my ring and pinion. It costs more to replace that than a used transaxle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:01:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just going to swap it out, I already pulled it out today. But now comes the fun part of trying to find one that is in my area for sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:15:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It definitely has crossed my mind. But it's really not worth it with my car. You're better off starting with either a turbo or S2 for upgraded suspension, brakes, trans, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:14:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, it's name was clutch. Probably shouldn't have dumped it so soon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I checked Larts. I have a track day coming up on the 22, so the problem I have is I live in the north east so I'm afraid it is going to come in at the last minute. I did find one from an S2 locally that I may be picking up tonight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in a Porsche parade, and I was cresting a hill and it just went. The ring and pinion went and it sent shrapnel through the whole thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Had a great time in my 944 yesterday... Until I blew the transmission </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:06:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Had a great time in my 944 yesterday... Until I blew the transmission </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:01:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it may have been a 280 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:24:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is my affordable dream. I'd do anything to have a 4AGE with ITBs screaming right behind my head  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see you driving around all the time! I live in wilbraham </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:02:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this the one I see around Ludlow all the time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 21:23:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It completely caught me off guard. I was at a driver's meet, and the way you get to the paddock to the track is over the bridge. I looked over to the bridge and I saw the front end and I nearly shat myself and everybody else at the meeting. It was truly amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw a R32 today at Thompson Speedway, seeing it in person is just incredible </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:08:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:39:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a set of primewells on my 944 when I bought it. It was pretty fun autocrossing with them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 11/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 15:46:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never thought of that, I'm definitely going to have to try it. I have a few autocross mods for Race 07 and they just don't feel right. They seemed herky jerky and the cones make you jump I'd you hit them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really should get back out to Devens. Going to the LAZ lot in Hartford is just so much more convenient for me but it's no where near as fun  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 20:38:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does Amy's Baking Shop count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 04:50:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure how many people use copart for buying cars, but they do have a section for cars that have been declared a biohazard. This most likely fits the bill  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks awesome! Can't wait to try it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I NEED that Turbo Cup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 01:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not exactly sure, mines an 86 and it came with late offset wheels for some reason, but there was already rear spacers so it looked like an actual late offset car. I would definitely do spacers though, fills up the wheel arches much more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:23:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks awesome! By any chance do you know what year those wheels came off of? They look like they came off a late offset car and that's why they're sucked in so much. But really good job, it's hard to believe it came this far! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 15:26:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Howdy neighbor! This was taken in East Longmeadow right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 17:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome looking car, but the front licence plate mounting is questionable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I can't get over how much I love this car </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:04:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I start college this year, I'm trying to get all the track time in I can before I go  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, my dad is an Oldsmobile guy, so he wasn't too keen on letting a Porsche stay in his brand new garage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My 1986 944 track car </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 19:18:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Without a doubt he's going fast, but that GoPros FOV makes it look like he is going at warp speed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:55:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure they are. The only difference is that some of the Porsche ones don't have that little plastic trim on the inside, and they have Porsche written on them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:54:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have actually thought about doing coilovers, I've been kind of going back and forth. I definitely like the idea of being able to adjust coil overs instead of having to change out torsions bars. I got the cage because I bought it used at super cheap price, so it was a mine as well for once I actually start doing road course stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright, rebuilt calipers, Hawk HP Race pads, stoptech slotted rottors, turbo S sway bars with adjustable drop links, fiberglass header panel, I took off the US crash bumpers just because they looked hideous, ac and heat delete, autocross alignment that has maxed out front caster, 1/32 toe front, 1/16 toe rear, -2.5 camber front, -2.0 camber rear, Bilstein HD rear shocks (I have Weltmiester 250 LB front springs coming in as well as a larger torsion bar) I stripped back all interior wires that didn't have to do with necessary equipment, Hankook Ventus RS3s V2, circular throttle cam, Momo steering wheel, full stripped interior, Autopower bolt in roll cage, Momo Daytona FIA containment seat, Schroth Profi 6 point FIA camlock harness, custom billet one piece shifter, radio delete, and lowered rear end. I know I may be missing a few things here and there but that's what I have off the top of my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you like a full build list?
Edit: No, D90s with 205/55 fronts and 225/50 rears  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:32:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's on jackstands right now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:28:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did some 400 first, then moved onto 1000 for the really fine look. I still haven't decided if I'm going to go for a matte or gloss clear yet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:20:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh please. I've already work on suspension and brakes. I did it because I liked the idea and I think it's a great tribute to 356s and Magnus Walkers cars. I didn't do it to save weight, but because it looks pleasing. I'm not trying to be an expert, but I highly doubt that creates any drag at all. If it helps you sleep at night, I can stuff some tin foil in there and Bondo right over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:52:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know full well what they're worth, like I said earlier. It's my car I'm going to do what ever I want to it. And I think it is far from rice if it's actually a purpose built track car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:55:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually just bought some Hankooks, my wallet hurts after buying those. Let alone Hoosiers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To each his own, but this is my car so I'm going to do what I want to it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 03:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm thinking about getting plexiglass quarter Windows and added louvers to them like his 78 SC. I do have a matte black fiberglass header panel that's going on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 00:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I was thinking about something like that for the other side, only my drivers side has a script handle so it would look weird if I just pulled that piece of plastic trim off the other side  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I went for an "Outlaw" look on my 944s door handle </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 23:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:03:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome, thank you so much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 14:07:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm currently in the process of building my 944 into a track car, and by any chance do you remember what you did to make the front splitter/ valence under the front bumper? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 00:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Steel front rotors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More pics of the 911 pleaseeeeeeeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Valid point, I just feel since they're so similar and by the same manufacturer it wouldn't be as extreme as comparing "Prime" vs BBS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:47:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know they're D90s, I think that clubsport just sounds better than D90.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 16:21:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn that sucks... Glad you're okay though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spent my day cleaning and painting my Clubsports for my 944 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 16:21:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 00:46:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I scuffed them with some 400 grit sand paper, used aluminum wheel cleaner, wiped them up with wax and grease remover, then I painted with Rust-Oleum copper metallic spray. They came out very nice for coming out of a can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spent the day cleaning and painting my Clubsports for my 944 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 23:19:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah Massachusetts represent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 19:36:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can confirm, 944 NA box is absolutely garbage, can't even handle it's own power  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 19:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome, definitely going to do the tonight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 22:27:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah to each his own. I think the vents themselves are fine it's just the horizontal black strips in them. I know it's supposed to be like a 935, but it just doesn't look right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I plan on doing a few this year. Would you say that having autocrossed before, it helped a little but with finding out the limits of your car? And did they have in car instructors? I'm pretty excited to actually get out on the track this summer. It's something I've been waiting to do for a very long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:01:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the front end of the slant nose, I just think that they would look better without the rear quarter vents  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 20:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hakosuka would be way better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 03:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gorgeous color  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:46:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What I should have said is that I don't think you'll be able to find one that has the fit and finish of a factory slant nose  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 22:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree, the slant nose is pretty cool but I'd hate to see another 930 molested. Most of the aftermarket slant nose kits just don't look right either  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:52:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is my number one dream car, unbelievably jealous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 22:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome, I love the speedhunters tires  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:53:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Off the top of my head for the things that aren't pictured are, stainless steel braided brake lines, most of the emissions equipment is gone, heater and ac was removed, turbo S sway bars, and poly bushings. I'm pretty sure there's more stuff that I'm forgetting, but as for other mods, gutted interior, Autopower roll cage, Momo Daytona seat, Momo steering wheel, rebuilt calipers, stoptech rotors, Hawk HP Plus race pads, fiberglass header panel, and a custom billet shifter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Was told to post here, my 944 Autocross/Track build </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As an Oldsmobile guy,I'm super jealous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:27:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Favorite evo by far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry rum ham  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 22:37:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oops I dropped my magnum condom for my monster dong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome, thanks for the info. A full M030 setup came up on rennlist a while ago, definitely wish I got it now. The rear end just feels so soggy on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:25:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah yeah yeah Burt versus Myers videos never get old. I still understand how people can race there. My dad crews on an SK team at Stafford and even there is pretty hectic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:41:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No coilovers, all the other suspension is stock right now. I haven't really thought about a light weight flywheel yet. Right now, I'm just trying to get the car buttoned up so if can be ready for the first PCA autocross this Sunday  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 13:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No hablo germano </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 19:03:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Upgarage is the best, I got a brand new Watanabe for only $40. Also, super jelly of all the cars. Especially the Rauh Welts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 14:50:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> M'Vette </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 23:30:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be terrified to do Lemons with the base Autopower... I'm cringing just thinking about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 23:09:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is in an Autopower. There's no way in hell I would actually race with that cage. Not to mention the fact that the windshield bar is way too close to your face. I'm not exactly sure how those cages can be SCCA, or PCA legal. My dad is on an asphalt modified team, so we're going to work with their chassis builder and have them build something for us. Also, the door bars are pretty useless because they don't come above the seat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:10:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Already subbed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:10:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, there are plates underneath it. Once I start doing spec 944, I'm going to ditch the bolt in and go for a full weld in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:09:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am planning on getting one for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 13:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I really appreciate it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 13:03:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very, especially with my helmet on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uploaded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Album is uploaded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:11:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the album: http://imgur.com/a/Ex39G
I know the album is pretty short, but I was rushing to get it posted before my laptop battery died. 
Little bit of a back story and some things that are not shown. I bought the car back in 2013 from a family friend. It's a 1986 944 NA that is going to be my track/autocross car. Not all of the work is shown in the album, but this is what else has been done to it
-Turbo S sway bars
-Poly bushings
-Welded diagonal and harness bar on the cage
-Momo steel seat brackets
-No AC or heat
My goal is to start doing 944 Spec next year so it's been quite a slow process. I really don't have much else planned for it besides bringing it to spec. It's been a great car so far, and hopefully this will be the first of many Porsches I will own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, you guys win. But only because you asked nicely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:40:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll work on an album tonight. It probably won't be posted until tomorrow though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Finally got my seat and harness mounted in my 944 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 23:19:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 14:07:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I'm not going to lie, I miss the super tacky ricers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's actually an awesome idea. I'd love to drive his eclipse, not matter how ricey it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There actually was a 356 in the movie, but only for a brief moment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 11:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started last year when I turned 17. You need to get 2 waivers signed by a parent or legal guardian, and have it motorized. You also need to have a parent with you at the event. And I'm pretty positive that the waiver lasts for the entire season. That being said, good luck out there.
Edit: Notarized not motorized   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 19:50:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At first, I thought it was the banana that was the problem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 13:33:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Labor Day weekend at Lime Rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rauh Welt Tiffany from Hong Kong [1024x768] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 02:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 240Z with race cams and exhaust with all handling upgrades. You won't be disappointed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 01:48:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Funny enough the first and only time I saw one was at the Oldsmobile nationals 3 or 4 years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 12:02:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been looking into importing a Cappuccino, but it's so hard to find websites that are super sketchy. I guess I'll just have to wait until I can afford to fly to Japan and buy one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 12:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did, I was feeling pretty lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Have you guys seen the 1990 Suzuki Lancer? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 21:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-09 15:54:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am almost positive that is an LM spoiler, and not aftermarket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that the Gas Monkey F40? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-06 19:58:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will you marry old gregg I like you I want to marry you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-06 13:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a huge fan of RWB, but their 964s just don't really speak to me as much as their 930s and 993s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Question on skinning for Assetto Corsa </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-06 00:56:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there any way to change rim models on a car? I'm currently working on a Rauh Welt skin for the Yellowbird, and it just does not look right with the base rims. If I made a model for a new rim, is there any way that I can swap it out? More specifically, it really needs 3 piece rims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 17:30:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm having that same exact problem as well, no matter what gear or rpm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 14:40:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, and I don't think that was a factory color either, but the owner could have changed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 13:21:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It doesn't look like it. The fenders don't look flared enough, but still a great looking car either way.
Edit: just noticed there's a rear window wiper, I'm almost positive no GT2s had them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 12:21:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should be in your inbox now, enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 15:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that just ruined my day, German shepards are my favorite breed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fanatec Club sport V2 Invite Code </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 15:05:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey everyone, I just got an email from Fanatec with the invite code. I'm not going to use it, so if any of you want it just let me know. It's US only.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 03:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yaaaaaaaaaaas, I absolutely love these videos. I've been waiting for the 2014 one for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 13:03:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3.1 was probably already wreaking havoc on itself with head gaskets  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 14:51:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really digging the color  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 16:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 16:32:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's really weird, I used to have that problem too but all I had to do was reinstall drivers and firmware and it worked fine. Best of luck though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-21 21:09:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 993 GT2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 20:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just bought it and it's working fine. I don't know why there would be a problem in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Forza 4 DLC </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 18:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recently started playing Forza 4 again, and I was going to buy the Porsche DLC, but I was told by a friend that the DLC doesn't work anymore. I'm not exactly sure what he means, but I was curious to if any of guys have bought DLC lately and have had any problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 15:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'Straya ya bogan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw this rather sad looking 911 today </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-14 18:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would love to see some chase footage, but I have no idea I'd any club would allow it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 00:10:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the winch on the front  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-10 21:01:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aren't you guys in eastern MA sitting at like 50" total right now? And I thought we got it hard here in western MA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 18:58:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My god  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-14 15:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of crack are you smoking? I replaced the timing belt, balance belt, all the pulleys, and water pump in mine for around $400.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-13 12:57:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But 600HP is still pretty impressive considering that its a 3.5 V6. I'm assuming that it will be mostly carbon fiber, so I can imagine that it will be pretty light which will help with power to weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I can't be the only one who doesn't like the new Ford GT </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-13 04:00:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It honestly doesn't make me excited at all. There's so many angles I see in it that look all too familiar to other cars. More specifically, I see a mix of the P1 and La Ferrari in the rear, the quarters are from a Hyuaraurauara, the front end is from a Marcos, and the roof and windshield is from a Agera and the list just goes on. I'm not a Ford guy but I mean come on, it's just ridiculous. It just looks like another generic rendering to me of a supercar.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 21:44:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, god forbid you go against the r/cars circle jerk. The OP asked a question, and I answered it with my opinion, yet it's still wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 19:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's basically it, the 360 and 430 are just... Wrong. They don't look proportional to me. I think the 355 is the last of the beautiful Ferraris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 17:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't say I have  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 17:21:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be honest, I really don't know why I don't like it. I think it looks cool and everything, but there's just something about modern Ferraris that makes me feel bored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 17:12:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ferrari 458 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 17:10:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what happened with my CSR pedals. All the pots got dirty, so the pedals wouldn't be recognized at all. From what I read, there's an auto-calibrate in the wheel, and if the pots are dirty the wheel won't see the pedals at all. The only way I could get it to work before I realized I had to clean them, was the repeatedly unplug and plug in the pedals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 22:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's true, I may just settle for CSRE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 03:30:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dayum, TE37s? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 16:12:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to Japan this summer vacation. Is there anything around the Tokyo area where I can catch some drifting? I've always been fascinated by their drift scene and I really want to check it out. Also, if for say there was a gathering one night, how friendly are they towards spectators? I really don't want to be that guy that shows up uninvited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 15:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish haha, that still may not be enough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 14:43:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm torn, I can either buy brake pads for my 944, or buy Clubsport pedals... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 23:22:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks awesome, I've always loved A-Bodies. I've always had the Oldsmobile bug ever since I can remember. My dad has had his 1971 Cutlass since high school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 17:44:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pics of the Oldsmobile? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 02:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi all. I really don't know much about rocketry except for they go fast and go boom. But being that you are all college undergrads and it seems like you've made some awesome progress. That being said, how close are your ties with other big companies such as NASA and SpaceX?
Edit: Hi Joe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-06 23:20:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His shocks are heavy, his wheels weak hood rotted. There's oil in his coolant already, blown gasket.
Snap back to crimpers, oh there goes busted solder joints.
Oh there goes my 8 gage wire, he's shorted. 
He's so fiery, he explodes.
He's so smokey but he won't burn out that easy.
Edit: Happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-06 19:26:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Knees weak wires spaghetti </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-06 14:56:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi neighbor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-06 03:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty new to autocross and racing in general, but if I'm off the line, is it bad to leave it in first for ~5 seconds if it's held at about 3,500 rpm? I feel like I'm putting strain on the motor, but I also feel if I shift into second it's just going to bog down. It's a 1986 944 if that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 12:58:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say Anywhere But Here, I really like the part where it says "So I dropped out of a mile race, a race with no finish line, no first or last place." But that's just my 2 cents  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 05:30:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Politics and tipping intensifies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 01:45:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought about changing it, but nah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-01 15:50:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cage my 944 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-01 06:19:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's plenty of places that will do ~100 stickers for around $30. If this becomes a thing I will gladly buy some  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 23:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dream car: Dauer 962
Attainable Dream car: Porsche 930 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 23:28:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is like the best news Everest, DRM is possibly my favorite mod ever for any game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 16:58:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try looking inside the force feedback settings of GT5, I normally keep it on 7 or 8 for my GT3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 01:35:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's really a shame because they are really nice looking cars  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 00:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's possibly the cleanest 924 ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 00:04:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this the same Puch that makes mopeds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 04:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn it OP, it's gorgeous. The AW11 is on the top of my list for affordable dream cars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 04:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 94 civic hatch with 13000 in mods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 03:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me, it's just freedom. It's those late nights coming home from hanging out with your friends and being the only one on the road. Windows down, music softly playing with the low rumble of the exhaust, it's just the most surreal experience ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 21:37:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The reason I went with it is because my 944 isn't my daily driver. It's just my autocross car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 19:32:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely, I think the reason why Hagerty is so much lower than normal carriers is because of the restrictions that put on. Meaning it needs to be stored in a garage, can't be driven more than 5,000 miles a year, and you need to have at least 25 to drive alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 18:46:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really depends on which insurance carrier you have. There was a thread a couple weeks ago here about insurance for junior operators. I pay $100 a year on mine and I'm 18, but that's because its on Hagerty. The downfall with Hagerty is that if you're under 25, you're not allowed to drive alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 17:44:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.forzamotorsport.net/Handlers/GetPhoto.ashx?game=fh2 id=1765060 full=true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 17:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do it's in my computer, I'll upload it tonight when I get home from work  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-26 21:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Close enough haha, they are probably my favorite style rim  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-26 01:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the Watanabes, works great with the color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-25 20:35:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I CAN BREAK THESE CUFFS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-23 13:38:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Volvo wagons, and Subaru  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 12:59:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's what I said, until I walked back into school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 21:39:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really sorry for you loss, I can tell you that your father was a great man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 03:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I absolutely love the Maxima, it looks soooooo clean  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-15 00:09:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awwww yes, us Northeastern guys don't get much attention at all in any racing games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-14 16:47:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fujimi, Tskuba, and for new tracks I really want Lime Rock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-14 06:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> M'Jeep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-14 04:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention, that's an eBay no name brand steering wheel. That alone would put me off knowing that the owner was willing to sacrifice safety for the "JDM" factor. Even if it's a small thing like a steering wheel, what else did the owner skimp out on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 20:42:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only somewhat interesting car at my schools parking lot is a Honda Fit that's completely riced out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 02:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooohhhhh my god yes, the shifters in it are amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 02:42:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't forget about the McLaren F1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 23:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not shitty 
Edit: just noticed the gold tooth, that's pretty shitty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 02:30:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this the same Galpin that was on pimp my ride? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 21:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like you got an awesome project on your hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 20:43:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice! What other mods do you have planned if there are any others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 20:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like it. A lot. It reminds of the VIP cars, but yet it's still subtle that it looks completely natural.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 17:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup, Upgarage! It turns out, you can actually have them ship overseas too. What I did was sent all of the parts I wanted to their headquarters, and that's where my dad is going. I just figured since my dad was going there for the week I'd save hundreds on shipping :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 17:20:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sourcing a set of Watanabes, and I'm getting a Momo steering wheel, parts in Japan are soooooo cheap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 17:13:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's in the box.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 16:42:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1996 Porsche 993tt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 16:24:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is what my dad's currently doing for me right now while he's in Japan. I think it you put it in a cardboard box, you can label it as luggage and bring it home on the plane.
Edit: I forgot, I think the total price has to be under $400. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 15:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The race never started because it never worked! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 14:12:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Going by your name I assume you have a 951 track car. Got any pics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 03:40:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Join the 944 master race, 3 years or 20,000 miles
Edit: forgot to mention balance shaft belt, rollers, and water pumps as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 18:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had no idea this existed... Your friend is very lucky  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 17:06:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was this at Stafford? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 15:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 15:43:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First gen Honda NSX, Porsche 964 Turbo 3.8 or 993 GT2, and a Dauer 962 which is the street legal homolgation Porsche 962 Le Mans car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 15:35:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm level 32, the only car I got was a beetle, and I've never gotten a payout above 18,000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember reading somewhere, the 25 year rule had to do with Mercedes. If I'm not mistaken, it had to do with buying car cheaper overseas and importing them, rather than buying directly from show rooms. And yeah, emissions and safety are a massive thing too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:21:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably not, the AE111 had a high revving naturally aspirated 4 banger with ITBs and a 6 speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:19:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every single time I see a petition for it, I back it up and it always gets shot down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-06 20:39:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look! Another car we can't get in the USA but we all want! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-05 02:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mines a 1986, and what I like about it most over the other ones, is that it has the newer interior. But if I'm not mistaken, 87 was the first year when air bags and anti lock brakes were introduced, so if your going for a more mechanical feel, I'd say go 86 or older. As for cost, I can't say for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-04 20:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to go out on a limb and say the 2.0 VTEC. I have it swapped into my AE86, with a maxed out naturally aspirated build and it just revs and makes the coolest induction noise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-04 17:52:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You'll enjoy it, I'm really glad for you it worked out in the end. Post some pics when you get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-04 00:23:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.etsy.com/listing/186489964/my-bad-autocross-road-cone-decal-choose?utm_source=google utm_medium=product_listing_promoted utm_campaign=geekery-humor-low-other ione_adtype=pla ione_creative=56602783835 ione_product_id=186489964 ione_product_partition_id=91551949235 ione_store_code= ione_device=m ione_product_channel=online ione_merchant_id=14469981 ione_product_country=US ione_product_language=en gclid=Cj0KEQiAhvujBRDUpomG5cq_mI0BEiQA7TYq-vHw4KZigZzKNJEPRbbnbpRGgmRkKM0IETKX4q0WVqUaAtVA8P8HAQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 02:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 02:29:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just turned 18, and I can say that trying to find decent rates has been pretty hard just because of age. My dad has Hagerty insurance on his cars, so I threw my 944 on there and I only pay $100 a year. The o my problem is, I'm not allowed to drive it without my dad in the car until I turn 21. What really puzzles me is Hagerty actually has something on their website about younger drivers and getting them involved in the car scene, yet they don't want to insure us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-30 21:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 964 is easily one of my favorite generations, congrats on the purchase!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-30 01:45:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really want a 4AG in my 944 with ITBs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-30 01:41:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's with all the not silver 918s on here lately? Not in a bad way though, the Orange one that was posted here a couple days ago was fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I was sick of looking for wallpapers, so I made my own in Forza </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-30 01:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 18:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it is the CTR, CTR 2 is the 993 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 13:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You'd be correct, black headlight buckets and HRE 935s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm in love with the CTR2 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 02:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-26 21:36:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude your girlfriend has an FRS and 993! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-26 03:43:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who'd you normally do the track days through? NASA does HPDE for around $50 each if you have a membership. You also get instructor time as well.
Edit: I read it wrong. It's $45 membership and the actual varies from track to track. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 23:13:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's doing well. Its my autocross car, and starting next year dedicated track car. I'm in the process of stripping it down to bare minimum now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 21:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dig the blue accents, it suits the car very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-22 18:13:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn't the lotus esprit use them as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-22 15:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's nice to see a 918 that's not silver for once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 14:46:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do it, I bought mine last year right after I turned 17. Out of all the very few cars I've driven, the 944 is the best. I was told it would be a money pit, and since I ordered pretty much all the parts from Rock Auto I saved a bunch of money. The best part is you get the satisfaction of telling people that you fixed a Porsche yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 02:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to guess, timing belt snapped, or you need to replace it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 16:10:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been searching for months for meets in the western Massachusetts area. The only one that's around me is my local elks club and it's really all old dudes in corvettes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 00:03:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He can't even  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 20:48:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mines been sitting in our backyard for about 4 or 5 years now. My dad and I plan on making it into a straight axle drag car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 19:51:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit another redditor with an F85! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 22:22:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good God that thing is gorgeous, you should cross post it back into r/Porsche  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 15:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dads friend has a 1985 Countach. I don't think I have ever ridden in a car that was so amazing and so shitty at the same time. It looked and felt like it was built in a shed. But it was just such a surreal experience being able to ride in one of my hero's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 23:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or as Regular Cars would say FIX IT AGAIN TYRONE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 03:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I spy with my little eye a turbo Buick :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 19:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't remember what they're called, but the rims that are on the 993 GT2, they're a 3 piece rim that's based on the cup rims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 00:46:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How can we see if our eyes aren't real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 16:52:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or did a line, because you know, 80s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 12:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dads best friend has a Countach that had a throw out bearing that went bad, and he asked us to fix it. We have to pull the engine out to get to it. Literally no idea how this is going to go 
Edit: Once the time comes, I'll post a whole album of us doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 23:05:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It just looks so goofy that it works  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 12:00:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As much as I hate low riders, I would definitely drive this one. It's not every day you see a Tercel like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 22:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is Falken stupid, these Falken puns need to stop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-25 21:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The submarine factory called, they want their porthole back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-25 16:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wilwood big brake kits will do wonders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-25 16:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a story as well! Last year, my cousin and I went to a swap meet and I brought literally no money. My dad was in Hong Kong at the time, so he told me to use some of his money if I found some Oldsmobile parts. Well, we head to the car corral, and there's this god awful 1980 Cutlass that's brougham 2 tone baby blue. The seller was asking $3,000 for it, so I told me dad. He said to go get some money and my cousin and I can go halfsies on it so we can flip it. Well, that's what we did. We ended up getting the car for only $1,300. I tell my dad we had bought it and he was pretty proud because we managed to get the price that low. We brought it back to my house and my mom was PISSED. We already have 8 cars at my house and when she saw this Cutlass roll through I thought she was going to kill me. My dad on the other hand, proud as fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 21:13:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ballaban is way worse IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 13:12:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good God... What the hell is going on the with the front bumper cover  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 00:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok I'll have to try that, but no of my other games are crashing like GTR2 though, even the other simbin games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 20:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried configuring it through steam and through the directory for the video settings, but I took a break so I'll try audio next time I get the chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 19:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tried all of that, and nothing. I asking tried running it in compatibility mode, uninstalling and reinstalling and still nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 23:41:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://s1374.photobucket.com/user/train_subject1541/library/Mobile%20Uploads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 12:29:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can see why, there is no such thing as a cheap Porsche. The price of parts isn't too terrible, the thing that gets you is how often you need to do maintenance and all the special tools that you need. It's my autocross car so it only sees wear and tear for about 5 minutes each month. The Cutlass isn't bad at all, just because it has the 3.1 and not the 3.4. I bought mine for a grand and pretty much did a mini restoration. I bought 2 parts cars, got what I needed, and sold what I didn't need. I'm currently into the car for only about 1,200. 
Edit: Words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My 1994 Cutlass Supreme, and my 1986 944 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 02:04:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 03:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn that sucks, I absolutely love it though. I can't tell you the last time I've ever seen one driving on the road. I basically restored it my freshman and sophomore year. When I first purchased it, it was red, broken into, rotted, smelt bad, and had the most disgusting interior ever. Bought 2 parts cars, swapped out all parts I needed, then sold the unwanted parts. It basically looks brand new now inside and out, and I'm only into it for a grand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 21:06:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Picked up a girl after school one day. It was pouring out, and I mean pouring out. I love my Cutlass to death, but since it's a convertible, the thing leaks more than Chernobyl leaks radiation. We're driving home, and water is literally going everywhere and it's not stopping anytime soon. Of course my side doesn't leak that much, and it's the passenger side that's terrible. Needless to say, she wasn't a fan of my Cutlass, and I took that shit right in the feels.
Edit: Completely forgot to mention I spun a bearing in it while in the school parking lot. Made the most horrifying sound ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 23:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll trade you the 550 for my 917/30 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 23:31:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did someone say new wheel bearings every year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 01:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta go fast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 02:08:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a really soft spot for the Javelin, ever since I saw the old Trans Am road race cars, I've been obsessed with them since. 
http://2.bp.blogspot.com/_FoXyvaPSnVk/S_rkktXroxI/AAAAAAAC4ss/8MaD1Te2Jb0/s800/1971-AMC-Javelin-Penske-Transam-001.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 00:28:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So does the supercharger double the money that's supposed to come out then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where's my money? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 00:51:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Each time I money shift in my car, no money comes out but instead my car turns off and there's a lot of smoke. Am I doing something wrong? My mechanic says I've "blown the engine" but no money comes blowing out like it should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 13:03:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While my problems are much less significant, I had to put a splash shield on a Sentra, which should take .2 hours, and it took me a solid 2 hours because aftermarket splash shields just don't fit no matter what you do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 22:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always wanted to be an endurance racer, maaaaaaasive upgrade  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Should I take my clutch out for a nice dinner before I dump it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 23:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We've been through a lot together and it's the least I could do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 03:39:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm hungry like the wolf for specs right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 00:55:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see what you did there 
Edit: Words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 22:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For some reason, this one really hit me in the feels. You know what they say, a dog is a man's best friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 01:00:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 240z long noses are absolutely stunning, almost like a mini E-Type </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-28 22:38:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I couldn't agree more, I gotta find some time to actually get a decent picture of my 944 to post on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-28 02:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, every now and then Hoobastank plays on my local Alt/Rock station, but either way, absolutely gorgeous RX7. I love the idea of a sleeper RX7, even though the RX7 is already fast as it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One of my Favorite Porsches of all Time, The 924 Clubsport </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-28 02:38:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 18:11:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't wave, I flip the lights in my 944 and I don't get anything back sadly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-25 20:05:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well yeah know that, but I'm talking about with paper work or stuff like that, I don't know the slightest thing about importing cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-25 18:58:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you buy yours new? I'm just wondering how you can legally get a Noble into the USA. I see them on eBay all of the time, and if I wasn't a broke high school student I'd love to buy one hahaha. I really want to import an R32 Skyline GTS once I'm older, but I'm scared that I may screw something up and have it get impounded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-25 17:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats, I can see why you won the award. The M12 and M400 are such sexy cars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-25 04:43:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow... I really can't believe I didn't think of that, then again, that's what this subreddit is for, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 17:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, thank you very much. Looks like I'll have to run out to the store for next time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 86 944 Trouble Getting Wheels Off </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 17:19:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not exactly sure if this is the correct place to post this, but it's nearly impossible to take the rims off without chipping the clear coat and paint off of them. It has the early offset phone dials, so the lugs are set pretty far back. I use a 19mm deep impact, and no matter how careful I am, the lugs spin really loose and bounce around everywhere taking clear and paint off. Is there anything else I can do to prevent it? It's a track car, so I regularly take the wheels off, so the rims are starting to look pretty gaudy now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 00:55:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How could you hate it? I think it's amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-15 04:39:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bought a manual for my 944 on eBay for $10 (I think) and it's on a CD. You can rip it as many times as you want to all of your electronic devices which is handy. Especially I'd you have a smart phone that can read PDF files so you can always have your manual on the go in your pocket. I couldn't find an online manual for the 944, but I have no clue if there is an online one for the 924. Anyways, congrats on the purchase, hope you enjoy it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-12 23:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta agree, Lime Rock Parks has some pretty damn good food on the infield. My friends step dad races at the vintage festival, and we always go down, grab some food then watch the races on top of their trailer. And since the restaurant is on the infield, you get to see all of the cars drive by in between races. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-12 02:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Massachusetts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 18:25:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, that was the Burma special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 15:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I learned my lesson. I have an 1986 944 and it's absolutely fantastic, and the way it feels is just unexplainable. But that being said, like everyone else is saying, maintenance is a chore due to high prices of parts. And not to mention, timing belts... I did plan on buying a mk3 supra before I stumbled across the 944. They're cheap where I live, and parts are abundant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 15:33:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know I'm late to the party, but I don't like miatas. They're completely overrated. I'm not saying that they're a bad car by any means, but they're just over hyped.
I'll show myself out now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 05:36:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww hell yeah, I've been growing up with Oldsmobiles all my life. My dad still has his first car from high school, which is a 71 Cutlass. My goal is to keep my 1994 Cutlass for as long as possible. I've always loved that body style, with the narrow quad bucket headlights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 04:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most of it is done. Exterior is basically done, it was in really rough shape when we bought it. The kid we bought it off of had high hopes of restoring it but just couldn't find money for it, so we pulled it out of his yard after it had been sitting for 10 years. All of the exterior was a home base bodge job so it was really rough. And since it was a New England car, every square inch on the quarters, doors, and fenders were completely rotted out. The interior isn't too bad yet we haven't started on it yet. It's all there but a lot of the plastics are faded so they need to be painted. But we really lucked out with the purchase because honestly the car could have been on its way out. Considering how rare they were, we just couldn't pass it up. Luckily since my dad only buys Oldsmobiles we had most of the parts already just from hoarding them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 03:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta ask, is it a legit 442? My dad and I are restoring an 83 Hurst/Olds right now, G Bodies are getting harder and harder to come by now, glad to see at least someone else appreciates them on this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-06 02:54:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have an 86 944 that WAS guards red but then Maaco got a hold of it and did a rather poor paint job on it so all the clear peeled and then turned to guards pink, I would definitely like to repaint it myself as a project this winter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-05 18:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks awesome! How does your posture feel while racing? The problem I had when I built my rig is that I just kinda threw it together, so it's not the most comfortable thing in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 23:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm guessing that they're probably revisiting a challenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 18:56:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention, their customer support is unbelievable. I didn't really know about my 944 when I bought it, and I called them to do my timing belt order and their staff picked out everything I need. They're an extremely helpful group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 15:40:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I think that's the one exception, but no doubt about it it's a dream machine. I go to bed every night thinking about it wishing that it was mine. The hard lines on it are gorgeous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 14:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guards red </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 13:55:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who would have thought of such a concept? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 03:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're also forgetting about the drive train, if I recall correctly, the wheels on the sports train were bigger than the factory wheels on the Jag, and the drive train wouldn't be able to handle it, you're essentially up gearing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 23:48:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah for sure, I think what they do is tell the builders basically what they want, then they stand around with their hands in their pockets monitoring the progress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 22:47:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think many people realize that a lot of the things on the show were not actually made by Jeremy, James, and Richard. I mean look at the cheap train travel episode, do you really think that they were all capable of making a car into train? It's not as simple as just throwing 4 metal discs onto a car. But then again, I still like to believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 16:22:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha I know that pain, I took my family out for a ride in mine for the first time a couple weeks ago, and my dad made my mom sit it the front seat while he laid across the back seats it was pretty funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 14:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But isn't camber beneficial if you're tracking it? As long as if it's not stupid hellacamber like every 18 year olds wet dream Honda, it should be helpful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 14:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So he sold the MR2 because he couldn't put a two year old in it. Quite frankly I don't see how long the 944 will last then, seeing as it really doesn't have rear seats. But anyways, congratulations on the purchase! Where I'm from its very hard to find a MR2 in great condition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-02 19:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god yeah they do... I just had my 1994 Cutlass fixed for rotted trailing arm mounts. I bought new trailing arms and undercoated them, I probably should have done it a while ago living in New England. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 23:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd have a +4 car garage, but have no house. Have the garage be well built, clean, finished, and I would park a Chevy Astro in it with a mattress inside of it and use that as a "house". Of course there would be running water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-27 02:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup, can confirm. I work at an auto body and this happens on almost more than half the cars we get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 16:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never thought of it that way, that does make a a lot of sense then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 00:10:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know much about track days, but would this be considered driver fault? Or track fault. It seems to me that maybe the track should cover damages, but I don't know why. Just my 2 cents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 00:03:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The inertia from its blazing speed will keep it on even if the second one falls off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 18:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 lug wheels are the best  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 23:23:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you very much! Now I'll have some new tracks to fool around with tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 19:01:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Links would be very much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 03:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much, Live for Speed never even crossed my mind. I do have the trial version of it, but it definitely looks like I'll be buying the full version now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any autocross mods? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 02:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure if this gets posted a lot, but I have been looking everywhere for any type of autocross mod for any game. Each time I go to Google all it brings up is rallycross, because as far as I know rallycross is called autocross everywhere but the state's. I do have an autocross track for race 07, and it's okay. I know absolutely nothing about modding and modeling either, so me making a track is absolutely out of the question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Helmets on Sale </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-13 00:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am not sure if this is allowed on this subreddit, but here it goes. I'm not trying to promote this business in any way, nor am I affiliated with them, but they do have coupons on Simpson helmets if anyone is interested. Most of the helmets are $50 off of original MSRP, except for the carbon fiber helmets which are $100 off of MSRP. http://www.biondoracing.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-11 05:11:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit, I think I know who you're talking about. Is his nickname by any chance either Doctor Dave, or Doctor Dan? I've been to his garage before and he collects Hursts like hot cakes, and they are all stupid fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-13 13:04:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kazoo rims go woo woo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-31 02:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always thought that the 944 looked kind of meh in pictures, but I actually recently bought one as a track car project; and holy shit. Pop up headlights and 80s box flares? Does it get any better than that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-22 01:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live about an hour and a half from Lime Rock, I'm seriously regretting not doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 02:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say keep it simple. Start from the ground up with wheel, tires brakes, suspension, etc. You'd be surprised how far that alone would get you. If you feel ambitious, why not do your own paint job. I really don't know what's out there for parts, but then again that's what the internet is for. Lastly, before you do anything I suggest pricing out what you want to do and how far you actually want to go with it. Congratulations on the project, and good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-19 12:59:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm no where near California, but I'll be sure as hell to keep an eye out. Anything to help out a fellow car lover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-16 23:47:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never done either of them, but I feel like plastidip may actually be more expensive. With a wrap as far as I know you can peel off and put the wrap back on, where as plastidip the conditions have to be just perfect and you have to worry about airborne annoyances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-16 23:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had my fanatec for around a year and a half now, somehow I have had no problems with mine which is extremely strange, except for the fact the alacantra is wearing off and it's kind of ratty looking. I'm running a TH8 with it for a shifter and I would highly recommend it. The feel to it is unbelievable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-16 17:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really wish that more sims would have 80s and 90s IMSA cars. I remember reading that someone was going to make a GTO mod for rFactor but it was never actually finished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-11 14:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OK, thank you very much. They are real Irwin vice grips but I will try again when I get the chance. I really don't want to leave gouge marks but I guess if that's what it comes down to I will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>