<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5349</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 5 packaging trends that one ought to know before beginning biz </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:24:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's behind the falling prices of oil, gold and copper </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 13:26:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google Drive Plugin for Microsoft Office Launched for Easier Syncing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 13:14:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Astronomers make a real five-star find - CNET </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 11:22:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> US: Albertsons Owner Launch IPO Plans </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 11:19:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Architectural renderings has been so popular till now </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 11:14:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 11:29:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had same problem my problem solve http://www.rendercraft3d.com/3d-architectural-renderings.php
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 10:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://goo.gl/b2Vooa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Take steps to protect people against tobacco: WHO </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 10:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 09:30:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try http://goo.gl/b2Vooa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Divergent: World's first 3D printed supercar can go from 0-60 in two seconds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:58:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 5 Awesome Tips about Cpanel Server Support from Unlikely Sources </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> West coast wildfires: What's being done to control them </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New Species: Hairy-Chested Yeti Crab Found in Antarctica </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Police Release Photos of Charleston South Carolina Church Shooting Suspect </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 13:48:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Universe's Oldest Stars Discovered In An Ancient, Bright Galaxy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 13:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I want to become a 3D render Designer and establish a company please guide </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 09:01:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Darpa: these robots will save your life (once they learn to walk)  video </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 14:52:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First time ever: Scientists use Wi-Fi signals to power camera without battery </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 14:28:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Large Hadron Collider is cranking up again: prepare to have your mind blown </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 08:56:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Make Realistic Buildings utilizing 3D Architectural Renderings programs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 08:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3d architectural renderings Design- Render craft 3d [1600X800] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 14:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 10 Tips How to Protect Your PC from Virus and Malware </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 14:19:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 10 tips How to protect your PC from Virus and Malware </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 13:58:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why search engine optimization not work </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 14:55:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Guide for Responsive Web design </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 09:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 7 Apps to Boost Your Business online </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 15:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Installation guide for Parallels Plesk Control Panel on Windows </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 12:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why your business needs goodwill in the market? : business </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 11:31:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why your business needs goodwill in the market? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 11:35:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Goodwill is the identity of the business in the market. It is intangible business that showcases value of identifiable business assets. Its fame and name and how it is viewed by the target customers in the world of competitive environment. A company which has perfect goodwill in the market succeeds in roping in mammoth target audience and gets elevated sales and profit figures. Goodwill is in fact the report card of the business that epitomizes its success.

*There are many points why a business needs goodwill in the market and few of them are as follows:*

* **Recognition:** Goodwill acts as identity of the company in the cut throat world of competition. It is with the help of goodwill the customers recognize and accept the products of the company. If the company has goodwill in the market, the customers readily accept its product.

* **Trust and confidence:** Chairman   Managing Director of [Cosmo Films Ltd](http://www.cosmofilms.com/) [Mr. Ashok Jaipuria](http://www.bloomberg.com/research/stocks/people/person.asp?personId=12736847 ticker=11712910) tells, Goodwill inculcates trust and confidence in the minds of the customers. Customers develop trust in the products and services of the company that has goodwill in the market and readily buy the products.

* **Withstand competition:** Firm that has goodwill in the market can withstand competition and is able to sail through the competitive atmosphere very easily. Customers get enticed with the product of the company and readily opt it amidst other competitive products.

* **Selling business:** Company with good will has high sale able value and gets easily absorbed or merged with other reputed company. 

* **Customer retention:** Goodwill aids in retaining existing customers on one hand and on the other it aids in alluring the new target audience. Customers prefer to stick to their brand for umpteen numbers of years if it has goodwill in the market. Say for e.g. women prefer to use the cosmetics brand that has goodwill and that is widely accepted.

* **Confidence:** The Company that has goodwill is able to inculcate confidence not only in the minds of the buyer but also in the minds of the employees who are working in the organization. Employees get motivated to put in their best to maintain the goodwill of the company which will in turn enhance the productivity level of the organization and result in elevated sales and profit figures.

* **Business growth:** Goodwill aids in growth of the business. With customers gluing to the product, new customers accepting the product, the sales and profit figures are catapulted to the new level which results in growth of the business. 

Goodwill is the Armour in the companys ambiance with the help of which it allures the mammoth audience and captures the majority of market. With the help of goodwill company is able to reach new levels of growth, plan for expansion and diversification.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 14:42:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to Make Attractive and Informative Packing of Product: </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 14:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 10:47:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ancient Rome...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are you Producer? You should be careful about labelling your product </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 10:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mobile friendly websites  Now a MUST for Google </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 14:38:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 13:37:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should do so, if you want. not only Reddit it.....
best of luck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 13:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is IT world guys .... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> any can help me?? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 13:23:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 11:07:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only for ladies..??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is social media and how help in business </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 10:59:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 10:55:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think that guy knows what chocolate is . i agree with this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> No kittehs were harmed in the making of this GIF </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 12:01:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> No matter how hard you try you will never be this happy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 12:47:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why couldnt you just have kids </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 12:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 10:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After reading title every one must watch this.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Study links vegetarian diet to reduced risk of colorectal cancer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 10:19:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mars rover Curiosity to resume work after NASA fixed electrical problem in robotic arm </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 10:18:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 10:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  critique
I am new in this field. I want to know, what is demand of people. And it is not advertise
Thank you for your great opening  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-09 07:49:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not an idea.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Residential Interior Portfolio, What do u think </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-09 07:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-09 07:31:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i am back... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 10 exciting developments in mobile </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-09 07:29:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WhatsApp Has Rolled Out Voice Calling Feature </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 13:14:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WhatApp has rolled out voice calling feature in India </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 13:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How school made you a better person </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 08:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Minecraft survival #65 - DIT GAAT VERKEERD! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-24 06:36:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-24 06:33:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yaa  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 5 Tools Everyone in The Website Designing Company Should use </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-23 12:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-23 12:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wandering with friends.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-23 12:18:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you are not there,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists use laser the size of rice grain for quantum computing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-17 11:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Packaging Film Help in Business Marketing? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-17 11:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-12 10:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Find some thing new for thinking, discussing and learning for new week  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-12 09:11:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every one like sick every day after office work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Architectural Rendering </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-12 09:07:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I hope that in this year to come, you make mistakes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 11:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 10:59:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And 2015 bring some spacial for us... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to Increase Website Speed Time and Decrease the Loading Time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 10:54:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 10:49:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It time to enjoy, Not for Playing Video game. We should try to start way for better career and life.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Balance of power in BOPP film markets shifting from India and Middle East to China </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 12:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 12 questions with Pankaj Poddar of Cosmo Films </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 12:40:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spanish BOPP film producer to begin cast PP film production in Portugal / EUR 7m investment in Reifenhuser line </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 12:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jindal Photo, Jindal Poly fall 4-9% post deferral of merger </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 12:38:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 2014s top stories in spaceflight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 12:18:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hacker claims you can steal fingerprints with only a camera </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 12:15:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple issues automated Mac update to fix critical bugs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-24 07:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-24 06:51:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 10 Effective ways to motivate children toward school </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 07:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> * **1. Be open for discussion with your child**
The beginning phase of school is very challenging for every child. Therefore, being a parent, it is your prime responsibility to be open for every discussion with your kids. Always try to counsel them and try to understand their point of view, which helps them to form a positive attitude towards schooling. 

* **2. Share interesting things with your kids about schools**
Often kids go through a phase of dilemma when they start schooling for the first time. They are apprehensive and kind of resistant towards the idea of going to school daily. It is a battle for them to stay away from their home and parents for a long period of time. Hence, you need to make sure that your kids are informed about all the interesting things and fun activities they can explore during their school life to transform their belief towards positivity. 

* **3. Try to make their school homework interesting with your help**
Most of the kids feel negative about school because they need to deal with the burden of school homework every day. It has been proven by studies that parents, who spend time with their kids in daily homework activities, contribute towards development of childrens interest in getting regular with school.

* **4. Celebrate even smallest of the achievements of your kids**
These days, schools organize several types of activities, events and competition in order to offer platform to the students, where they can learn effectively. During these competitions, you should always stand as motivating pillar by your childs side and help them to achieve remarkably. Also, when you celebrate their smallest of achievements, it helps them to build faith in their abilities. 

* **5. Meet frequently with teachers of your child**
Your meeting with the teachers of your child helps you to keep a track of growth and improvement in your son or daughters performance. It also creates a positive impression your kids and encourages them to perform better in routine activities during the school. 

* **6. Motivate your child to read more books**
Motivation is the key for humankind to achieve wonderful results in their endeavors. You should be focused to provide a strong motivation support to your kids since childhood. If they are successful in building the habit of staying self-motivated since school days, then nothing can stop them to achieve big in their lives. 

* **7. Dont put performance pressure on your child**
Mostly, parents make this mistake of putting performance pressure on their children. It is quite obvious for every mother or father to expect excellent performance from their son or daughter but patience is the key to witness ground breaking results. Therefore, child psychologists suggest the parents to stay patient and calm to improve performance level of their kids. 

* **8. Encourage your child to be balanced students**
Balance is virtue for every student. Therefore, parents should not only be inclined towards one particular aspect of schooling. You should encourage your kids to take part in extracurricular activities, sports and co-curricular activities apart from academic performance. This will build up their entire performance in advanced manner. 

* **9. Understand child psychology**
The most common mistake made by elder people is that they consider children psychology same as theirs. But, this is not the truth because children are tend to think in different ways that grown-ups. They are more creative and their brains are fertile. Therefore, they should be treated smartly to ensure a systematic growth. 

* **10. Be patient**
The Chairman Mr. Radhesh Chander Pal of [Rishi Public School](http://www.rishischool.com) tells- Being a responsible parent, your key task is to interact with your children on daily basis and put your efforts to build positive image for schooling in their mind. You should focus on achieving the situation, where your kids start loving school and understand its importance. But, it is important that you stay patient throughout the process.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg on dislike button: Were thinking about it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 09:07:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Study: 270,000 Tons of Plastic Floating in Oceans </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 13:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple and IBM Introduce First Offerings in Line of Mobile Apps for Business </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 13:44:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Laughing gas can treat severe depression </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 14:08:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Curiosity findings provide new evidence Mars could have hosted life </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 08:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 08:33:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NO, now mean after !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Serious] Imagine world without Google ??? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 08:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Imagine A World without Google </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 08:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists Solve Wind-Blown Sand-Dune Mystery on Titan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 13:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obama Riffs on His Presidency with Stephen Colbert </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 13:22:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Attackers knock PlayStation Network offline for hours </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 13:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Compact particle accelerator sets new energy record: 4.25 giga-electron volts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 12:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Deutsche Bank Sued by U.S. Over Alleged Tax Scheme </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 07:44:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rishi public school </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-02 08:50:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cosmo Films Ltd journey from 1901 to 2013 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-02 08:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Visualization is a Good Idea for Architectural presentation? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 07:06:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Office Apps on iOS Are Now Free, Sort of </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 12:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Architectural Visualisation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 08:00:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sysco reports delay for merger with US Foods </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 10:44:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google Releases New Calendar App For Android </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 09:25:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers observe photons interacting like a pendulum </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 09:07:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google kickstarts Indian Language Internet Alliance, initial focus on Hindi </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 13:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My new born baby twins Please suggest me name for twins .. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 11:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gmail 5.0 for Android With Exchange Support Leaked Ahead of Launch </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 11:07:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gmail 5.0 for Android With Exchange Support Leaked Ahead of Launch </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 10:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WhatsApp user-base crosses 70 mn in India </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 10:11:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google Penalty Recovery Case Study  How We Lifted An Unnatural Link Penalty For E-commerce Client in 5 steps! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 08:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>