<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1642</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm gonna be honest and say that I don't really believe in ghosts, but  it'd be pretty awesome if something changed my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep that's the site I've been looking at lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Me and my friends were considering exploring some haunted spots in the Columbus OH area... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:18:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would anyone be interested in YouTube videos, stories, photos, or anything like that? There's quite a few of them around here, and I'm thinking of making something of a series about it. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did email them, they've just ignored it so far lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone know how many hammer of God box mods were made? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:35:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've got number 114, I was just curious about how many were actually produced lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 15:38:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like you're referring to his head... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> No job, no juice! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 11:55:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, I've been without a job for a bit now, and I can't justify spending money on things I don't need. I've got money for bills and such, but my home is definitely more important than vaping lol. Calling on the kindness of a stranger to help me out of a tight spot. Anything you might be giving I'm taking! Thanks for reading (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: Are tattoos at home really that bad? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:30:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like to start off by saying I'll only get tattoos professionally, but are scratchers really that bad? I don't mean your tape player engine with a guitar string, I mean a legitimate artist with a legitimate gun, but between jobs or something like that. It just seems like most people take a stance where it isn't okay no matter what. What kind of problems do people typically run into in these situations?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:05:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't downvote him guys, he just ran out of bombies. We've all been there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol do you even vape? Those cloudz are weeaakk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:33:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can try God Damnit!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I picked it up for 65 in Lancaster Ohio at upright vapor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 14:05:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dual parallel royal wire 20g 7 wrap lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Upgraded from my Buddha to a centurion. Love it! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 10:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 09:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of a certain game I just lost... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Panera bread! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 13:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello, I was homeless for a long time, and I know how hard it can be. I've been meaning to pass this knowledge on to people who can use it, so here it is. Panera bread! Most panera bread's donate to local food shelters, but significantly more often than you might think the shelters don't show up to take it. They wrap everything in two or three layers of plastic before they throw it out. They throw everything out at about 10 to 11pm from the previous day, so it's still fairly fresh. Panera pretty much kept me alive for a long time, so I'm hoping it can help someone else. Thanks for reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:55:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, I've kinda got a general idea of a nerf herder in my mind. Please forgive me for being so prejudice :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:28:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Leave it to a scruffy nerf herder to judge your hygiene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> PSbattle: this chick laughing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:46:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 18:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should've expected Jorge to be involved... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 10:22:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So long, thanks for all the- fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 12:22:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/nottheonion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 12:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These remind me of these "pocket pets" a co worker of mine made. link to the fb page for those who are interested: https://www.facebook.com/pages/Pocket-Pets/616869738409460?fref=ts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 11:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Speed camera vans **hate** this one easy trick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 11:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The streets are getting ***ruff*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 08:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every Zelda game ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 11:04:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 50 hours in
"This park is really neat and tidy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 06:28:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Local fence takin' out the trash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 21:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i Mean, would the horse sized duck still have hollow bones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 08:28:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That form requires four stamps! I'm demoting you to rank 658! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:37:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that was a load off my mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But surely you must have some other pitchforks we could take a look at! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Paging /u/pitchforkemporium </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 08:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With a hammer mod I don't see why a clone would be a problem, but my girl only buys clone tube mods. She's bought two so far, and both have fallen apart on her. So I'd be a little careful at least. Rdas are pretty basic, so I don't see any problems with buying a clone of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 08:14:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have an authentic myself, but I've seen some pretty great clones too. I won't buy any clones personally, it just seems like the quality is often times worth the price.

Plus bragging rights! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 07:47:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It hits like a freight train! I have an el diablo tube mod that I really like the look of, but I just can't put that hog down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 07:18:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've done a little of it myself but I really like machining fantasy weapons. When I was younger I went to a festival with her and there was this guy who had a truck he blew glass out of. The whole side of the truck folded out into a stage and he'd do shows. It was pretty awesome haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 07:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The hog is my favorite mod by far. Just wish I could carry it a bit easier! That dewberry cream actually belongs to my woman, I can't stand it honestly. When I bought it for her I thought I'd just use the dripper from a 30 to get it out but I eventually just had to use a funnel. Definitely not my favorite bottle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 07:12:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They use a small plunger like device, its very crude and will kill all the children ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:45:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom's a glass blowing hippie, my dad's a machinist by day and a drum and bass dj by night. Not sure if that's carnie material, but its a nice thought lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:43:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey! You leave my Styrofoam out of this!!

I have a few, but I'm having trouble tracking 4 battery cases down. I'm gonna fab my own out of some wood when I get around to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 05:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, for those who are interested, the black faces on the back wall are flat glass my mom gave me, she blows and sells glass at local carnivals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I finally went ahead and bought a bookshelf for all my gear! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 05:49:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Was helping a few elderly neighbors move in, and their dog Molly wanted to say hello! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 05:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 18:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The TV isn't actually there. Watch the way it shakes when if hits the ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is Bastet! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:21:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 22:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "What's going on here? Is that blood on the grooaaaaaAAAAAAAAAHHHH" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 17:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very rarely I'll find a wonderball, is that the same thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:24:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> About time to unsubscribe I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 14:17:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've got three vapers in my house, I just went out and bought a book shelf Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 05:04:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://youtu.be/AV_H22UlIic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 02:44:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pooposition 2 you mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 23:19:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glitter is a great way to close a wound I hear... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:40:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm lied about the green </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:58:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well actually I'm in Ohio, I just put in a vape request at /r/vaperequests and /u/EastBayVaper sent me all this for free. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First vape mail! Thanks to EastBayVaper for vaping it forward! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:31:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 11:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks appropriate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:07:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would also put just a little bit of juice in the coil and hit it without firing it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:56:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh ffs no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 12:40:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely is for the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 11:37:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmmm... Still says disabled for me... Maybe because I'm using the reddit app </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:13:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My favorite thing about this is he won't allow comments on his videos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:55:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm guessing punching a cow in the face so hard it flies apart isn't the kosher way then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 12:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely cheating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 11:00:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's going to tell! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 10:24:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As an Ohioan, this project seems like a reasonable and cost effective way to prevent flooding in your basement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 08:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 marijuannas and 7 cracks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 08:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spawny spawny he's our man! If he can't do it no one can! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:17:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never felt like a cat needed eyebrows before now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I started an emo salsa band </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:15:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We aren't terribly popular </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 05:50:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure if racist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 05:44:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The mephisto could do it too I'm sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 06:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just looked up what bullet time fighting was. I see what you mean, I'm not sure they even make a computer that could run that yet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:31:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now here's the thing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always felt like he was rhyming walks with talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:50:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A bird in the hand is worth two in a window </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:10:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been saying that for years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 11:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they mean they literally hit better than sonys. Sony's are made to vent slowly, these things are gonna "hit" like a mother fucker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 08:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I need to kill one anyway so there's no real point in buying it lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AC4: Black Flag. Any tips on white whales? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 07:02:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm trying to go back and complete this game 100%, are there any tips on finding white whales? No one plays this on my friends list anymore so there's not much hope on having it shared to me. Xbox 360 for those who are wondering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:53:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty positive a German soldier didn't burry him. German man maybe but I feel like a soldier probably had bigger stuff going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See that's what I've been looking for!! Thank you. Is that a tough fix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright, so is that going to require taking anything major out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in a spot where I needed to force cold air into the engine, that's what I had to do. I didn't come here for support with my decisions, I came here for help. It's applicable to the problem so I included it. From what I've read it should cool down when I rev the engine or go around 60 if its the fan clutch right? I shouldn't have to hit 100mph to get results. I feel like it cooled down there because there was so much air going into the engine. Is there a definite way to tell if it's one or the other without tearing it apart? I live in an apartment complex that doesn't care for me disassembling my car in the parking lot lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 12:58:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I noticed they were using the "Roman candle" for their spells. It's good, but I think it's a bit reckless considering you cannot turn them off. The "flare gun" item has a lower rate of fire, but the damage is much higher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 12:53:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well the strength skill will be phenomenal also, but I'm not sure which career skill he'd have time for. I have heard that it's possible for a player to incorporate those skills into a career tree but it isn't easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 12:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you aren't picky go for the machining skill tree. I've always been in it, you learn skills that can branch out into other skills like metallurgy, electrical, maintenance, and other kinds of things. Good say to grind currency too, in the US server I've averaged 16.00 an hour! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 12:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a similar experience, I was just drinking some vodka for the happiness buff and my frame rate dropped insanely low. Like we're talking black screen except for a minute every couple hours. Next thing I know I've spawned at this stone query (fortunately I didn't lose any gear) and my pre 2000 update vehicle I just grinded currency for was missing its bumper. The devs really need to work on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 12:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I heard something about the vampire boss thing, but I'm pretty sure they changed it to a hand-spear type weapon in an update following this sword. Apparently the boss was really op so they put in a stronger weapon to counter it. I'm pretty sure they removed the vampire boss completely around the time of the firearm update (at the very latest). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 11:38:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Know if they'll be restocking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where can you preorder the fallout 4 pipboy edition? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 10:56:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I gotta have that thing Lol. Does anyone know if its going to be sold separately? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 10:26:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, the car won't cool down until I hit over 100 so I think the fan clutch is probably okay. Is there a way to check the radiator? That is comparably easy to get out of the car if I can check that out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is there any way to troubleshoot a water pump? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 07:31:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a 94 bmw 325i that's overheating, it seems to be leaking a small bit of oil but not too much. I think it's the water pump but that thing is an absolute nightmare to get to. Is there a way to troubleshoot it to see if that is actually the problem?

May be worth noting that the thermostat was not working but I replaced it... Still overheating though. I think maybe the overheating from the thermostat may have melted the plastic impeller on the water pump. Is there anything else I should look into in addition to that? NTB did a pressure check and said it was holding pressure, if that helps at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think 16 gb of ram will do it? I'm in the midst of building my pc so that's all I have ATM. I plan on adding another 16 gb and a much better graphics card eventually but that's neither here nore there lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pc game suggestions?? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:37:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really into mmorpg's but can't find any free ones I like. Can anyone suggest anything? Please not runescape, that has taken more money and time from my youth that any other game combined.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:23:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did they add another area to mobile? I've got the pc and mobile version but the last I played the phone version they only had the first area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Geez calm down no need to yell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:09:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BE PATIENT?!?! I'LL BE PATIENT WHEN I WANNA BE PATIENT! HOW DARE YOU EXPECT ME TO WAIT FOR A THING! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 03:37:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you play any instruments this would make a decent dampener to reduce echo when recording. That would be my excuse anyway.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 12:56:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I named my son chair, is it the same thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 16:21:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can confirm, need pics of lack of penis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Truth be told I haven't seen the herakles yet. I'm more of an arctic kinda guy myself Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://m.reddit.com/r/electronic_cigarette/comments/2zwr5e/can_some_one_tell_me_why_it_is_dangerous_to_use/ 


pretty good starting point... Search function guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 01:20:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's never a good idea to put a tank on a hybrid mod. Doesn't matter how long the pin is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 06:41:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /u/TrollaBot train_subject1642 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dubbed seasons question (no spoilers please!) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 11:36:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've watched most of the series up to shippuden season 12 dubbed in english, but I can't find season 13 or beyond dubbed. Is there anywhere to watch/download them anywhere? I've got everything later on my pc subbed but that's all I can find. Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Out of juice, now dripping 50/50 pg/vg 6mg nic from the ecig days... Hard to believe this used to be good </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 10:24:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [US] in need of juice! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 06:25:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Out of juice for a few weeks, won't have the money for more until the first. Can anyone help me out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 08:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would replace it if you don't mind driving an older car. I wish I would have done that with my Sebring instead of getting my mazda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 08:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've only found a hammer of God at one store, but the Buddha zephyr is pretty popular. There's also the fat Buddha which is geared more for flavor builds and there's the mangala which is a short version of the Buddha. All the parts for those 3 RDA's are interchangeable too which is nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 07:46:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I'll hit it for a good 4 or 5 usually, the awesome thing about royal wire is it heats up super fast but it takes forever to get too hot. I've used a ton of different wires and royal is my favorite by far. If you build you should try it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 07:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better than I expected honestly. I mean a higher resistance would be better but I'm completely satisfied. It's a bit warm but its not bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 06:50:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My favorite build is the hammer of God box mod with the Buddha zephyr. The Buddha has a MASSIVE chuff cap and handles heat realllyyyyy well, and the deck has deep juice wells. Also, tons of building space. I run 4 vtc5 batteries in the mod but vtc4s are pretty fantastic too. I get a bit less flavor but the clouds are just massive. I'm going to get a lot of hate for this but I've got a .03 ohm build on it and it's never been even remotely a problem. All together it cost me about 300 dollars.

My build is a 6 wrap dual parallel 20g royal wire, so lots of surface area with a super low resistance wire. Flawless on every front. I've been in 4 cloud comps with it and never lost one. It outperforms my 26650 el diablo mod with the mephisto rda which costed me 350 dollars not counting batteries, wire, and cotton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 12:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I'd be too tempted to fire it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It just seems to be the common consensus from the people I've asked. Do you know the other things that will be required after engine replacement.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've heard the head gasket goes out faster after you fix it, so for the same money I can swap the engine and solve the problem for a lot longer... Right? Is it true that the head gasket wears out faster after repairing it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Will changing an engine solve my problems? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:38:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/outside </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 09:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't invoke the holy.... Spirit.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 09:10:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gay + Gay if you will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol sorry if it was too vague. Just caught my attention and I got a kick out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:32:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She looks like she's crying..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:07:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That escalated quickly... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 02:06:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like what are the implications of that though? What can that do? This Atty is made of spare parts from destroyed zephyrs my friends have given me so I'm not too worried about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:45:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guys calm down. The houses are just reeeaaaallllyyyy nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:52:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did that. Did not work. What happens if they touch? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure the insulator melted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Positive post shifting? Anything I can do? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:42:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 11:11:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grandma is died </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 08:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Time to unsubscribe from this sub lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 08:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "And that was when I quit my job" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 07:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gonna be honest here, I run .04 on a 4 battery box mod in my buddha for competitions. Have been for about 3 months now. Never had a bit of trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 94 BMW 325i worth saving? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:19:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 16:48:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Know anywhere I can buy a drop bear helmet?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 10:56:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'That's a bold strategy cotton"
"I don't know, I've seen boulder" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 10:38:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's doing neither actually. Just acting completely normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 07:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I can tomorrow. It doesn't even look too bad the eye lid is just a bit red. Not even puffy really. Might it be possible she poked her eye with some hay? She does tend to toss it around and role in it... A lot... Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 07:11:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will be worth noting that we opened a window and had a bunch of company the day prior. Maybe allergies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 07:08:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My vape store will trade vented batteries for 50 off a new one, see if your will! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bunny is sick, help please! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 07:06:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, my rabbit is sick. One of her eyes is red and she's got a stuffy nose! She's still bouncing around and happy, eating (and tossing her bowl when she's done) with no sign of pain whatsoever. I'm thinking it may be a cold but I'm unsure. The vet literally won't do anything with her. Like that shouldn't even be a thing but he just keeps saying she's okay. The closest one is 3 miles away and I can walk that but the next one is 12 miles away. If it could be something serious I'll do it but she seems fine. Sometimes she'll close the eye but that's it. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 04:01:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it the 18650 size or the 26650? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 02:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd have to say no on that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 02:14:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which mephisto? I've got an authentic mephisto RDA with a 26650 el diablo that work okay. Are the clones any good? I spent 100 on my RDA and for the price I'm disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 02:11:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When my girlfriend wants me to leave the vape store </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 02:10:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With a 9 wrap parallel you'll get the same surface area as an 18 wrap with lower  though is the point I'm making I guess. But definitely if you can push more power through the coils you'll get comparable results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 01:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ohh okay I'm assuming you mean the box is series right? I only have unregulated mechanical boxes that are parallel so I don't actually have experience with controlling power levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 21:56:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are the benefits of doing this instead of a 9 wrap parallel? Are you aiming for a longer ramp time? Not being sarcastic or anything I'm genuinely curious Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe so, I followed a tutorial online. This is the first real repair I've ever done to a car besides like breaks and stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 07:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So what would you make of the smoke? If the pump is out I know it would leak but not at the back of the engine right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 07:04:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really hoping it was a miscommunication. I've had people tell me it wouldn't hold pressure with a blown head gasket, is that correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 06:59:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So that means replacing the water pump may do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 05:43:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fill the back seat with bags of ice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> BMW 328i overheating </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 05:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Edit: it is a 94 BMW 325i not a 328, not sure why the 8 is there.


Hello, I've been having some trouble with my BMW overheating. I bought this car because I wanted something nice to drive and also a car I could learn to work on. So today removed the radiator and the fan blades (?) To change the thermostat which went well but after reassembly when I turned it on and ran it for about 20 minutes it began over heating again! There is white smoke coming from under the left side of the engine which leads me to believe there could be a leaky head gasket but I noticed something rather peculiar. The hose to the right of the water pump was hot to the touch, but to the hose to left of it was much cooler (still hot, but not nearly as much). I took it to national tire and battery for a pressure check and they said it held 75lbs of pressure just fine. Any thought guys?



TLDR: 94 BMW 325i overheating, pressure check went well, small amount of white smoke coming from under engine on passenger side, changed thermostat and it didn't help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 23:31:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's one k away from racism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why don't my incense burn into ash? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 21:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 21:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've come to terms with it. How are they making the money to do this??? I've never seen something this overly advertised in my entire life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hand check: hammer of God with mephisto RDA. Treasure island is my current favorite. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 18:15:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 18:03:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What shop is this and where? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> These game of war adds are push notifications now... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 00:10:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 13:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The whomping willow in its early years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 22:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kinda depends if it's a double cheeseburger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are more batteries better for super sub-ohming? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 22:03:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, so I was wondering if you have a hammer of god (which has 4 batteries) would super sub-ohming be safer? I'm not big into low builds, but in my mind the load would be evenly distributed among all 4 batteries. Is that accurate? Why or why not? Are there any articles I could read on the subject? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 12:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can we get a glow shot?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 12:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah that should be fine. Right guys? Guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 11:57:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had that. I cheated against my girlfriend because I wanted to beat her just once. She had been cheating too so it became a game of luck. She still won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 10:44:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also came here to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 07:47:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Off topic, but is 3/4th proper? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 07:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best part is he takes the rock too. You can tell he's on a budget! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you bring your TURBO rda??! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 00:08:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 20:50:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think we both know that no one thinks a dog has lived 7 years when we have lived 1. Their bodies are aged roughly 7 times faster than a humans though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 15:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Couldn't you just close the door? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 12:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did... Did you just say dogs don't age faster than we do? No one is saying that time passes faster for dogs, but they certainly do age much much faster. I'd like to see one external source that says otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 10:32:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He shouldn't have been standing in front of it in the first place though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 07:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if you'd have to drink the dick because you've been hitting it for so long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 04:24:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kinda the same thing as a gentlemen's club I guess. Men come in to look at women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Batman is in there twice too lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hand check: hammer of god box mod and Buddha zephyr rda </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:18:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:46:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or is it incest?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 18:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see that hammer pipe mod over on the left! I hated that thing... It looks nice but it's pretty finicky. If you're into spending any more money I'd look into the hammer of the gods box mod. It's my personal favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 07:43:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you like the freak show look for the mad hatter. Same manufacturer and they're both fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 12:19:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I said a year not two, that's just ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 09:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn't that take a year to heat up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 14:40:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bet that's got a good throat hit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 11:57:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first one doesn't say "for the better". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 12:52:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's two halves to every lemon professor scam! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 12:52:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From what I can remember in that country people could pay to get that blue light to bypass busy traffic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 12:17:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Work at vegetarian store, can confirm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 09:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Um I guess that depends. I think there are some RDAs that have a kind of tank attachment but a true RDA is a "deck" you build your coils on. Instead of a glass tank you wick them with cotton and put your ejuice on the cotton, so when the coil(s) heat up it/they burn the juice off the cotton, giving you vapor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 07:35:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A vape store owner I know runs .02 on a mephisto with an el diabolo 26650 mod. I've seen the build but am way too nervous to be around when he uses it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 04:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What size wire and how many wraps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:39:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No worries. Its rebuildable dripping atomizer. Look into them, you'll need one of them to get awesome clouds. The only tank I've ever seen that would give you a decent cloud is the arctic with the .2 coil, but that still could never compare to an RDA lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 12:12:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My two favorite mods are my el diabolo 26650 and my hammer of god that takes 4 18650s. I feel like a mod is only going to get you so far though, the RDA is (in my opinion) much more important. The best I've used were the Buddha zephyr, the 26650 mephisto, and the mutation. What RDA are you using now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 04:20:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's awesome! I've just heard stories about it melting so I've not really been interested lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 04:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've not used nickel yet, but with kanthal that would take a year to heat up! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 10:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to say this lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 22:38:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wake up sheeple jet fuel isn't even flammable!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:58:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for those who are interested: https://www.etsy.com/listing/175112598/cat-battle-armor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:57:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> isn't this the stock photo from etsy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:51:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Illuminati! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 21:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> AND MY HAMMER </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 21:37:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10/10 would eat TV dinner on.

I your hardware though! Have you been at it long? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 07:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also come from the wonderful world of hookahs. A few burn holes in my carpet/couch/deck/everything motivated me to switch. Hope you enjoy it as much as we do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 05:21:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah me too. I've drawn up a lot of plans for a box similar to this, I'm a machinist so I could really go crazy with it. I'm a bit nervous though so I'm reading up a lot on the wiring and stuff. 4 batteries that close to my face, really wouldn't want to do that wrong! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hammer of God box mod </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 09:46:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like not many people know about this guy (at least not many people around me), so I thought I'd share:

http://vaperzcloud.com/products/hammer-of-god-box

It was my first mod and it's still my favorite. 10/10 woud buy again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 09:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm assuming its a compressed air cannon, which could toss somebody. I'd be more worried about his ears than anything. Saw this a year or so ago on YouTube and I feel like he got up afterwards.

Edit: here's a link

scientist air cannon prank: https://youtu.be/Bo8Q88bAXyQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 09:52:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sup dog, heard you like vehicles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 12:08:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 09:29:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "This isn't very awes..... OK" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 09:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better than any sweater I own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 08:52:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This pic is from r/psbattles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 04:25:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 11 months in:

"This park is really clean and tidy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 03:50:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone's finding a way to make this work out still... The fish speak English. All the fish speak English. This is verified by "kiss the girl" and when Sebastian tells Eric her name is Ariel. Why the fuck didn't Sebastian just tell him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 03:44:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm no expert, but isn't it leucistic as opposed to albino?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 11:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> omelette du fromage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 10:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Touche'! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 19:30:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They remind me of the rip stick or whatever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 10:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least we can see that your camera didn't go staticy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 08:18:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMFG WHY DIDN'T YOU PUT A TRIGGER WARNING ON THIS NOW I'M TRIGGERED THANKS DICK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: Why do people try to time pictures instead of taking a video and capturing the parts they want? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 15:12:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why do people try to time pictures instead of taking a video and capturing the parts they want? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:09:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 21:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would make a good cake topper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 21:30:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I could find a chick crazy enough to do that, I could use a new car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 08:15:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I knew that was the beerfest gif before I even clicked on it
Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 06:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made one myself, nothing happened. I played with friends, alone, graveyards, and houses... But nothing ever happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 11:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate it when I get on reddit and op costs me 1500 dollars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 08:56:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only one way to find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 06:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The real nightmare is how often this gets reposted and still gets upvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 06:41:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just make sure you kill the skeleton lord that summons the pinwheels last, those things are a pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 06:36:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the mt Vernon infirmary that's for sale right? 40000 something square feet of that type of stuff... Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 11:12:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This makes me feel the teeth on my brain.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 11:08:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just google slenderman pics.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 06:34:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone knows this is from the film the lord of tears right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 10:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't really tell when it stopped being intentional </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 10:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Go ahead, tell them this isn't a repost, see if they believe you!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 22:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use neko wool jap cotton. Most people don't realize you need to peel away the front and back layer of the sheet before wicking so it often gets bad reviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 22:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just look up search by image on Google play or the app store. I'm not sure how exactly it works, but I know it searches for all sizes of the current image and returns visually similar images. All you have to do is select the image from your gallery and search. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 21:27:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never said I was into it, but it's really not that bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 16:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where is the bear cub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 16:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never seen a point made this well before... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 09:02:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Living in a remodeled uhaul truck until I'm done with a road trip, so I'd be a bit more concerned with the appearance of a hallway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 11:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to assume you've never heard of reverse image search?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 10:57:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure he's trying to get insurance money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 10:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She doesn't look super concerned... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 04:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should call him back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-08 09:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hooray for reposts!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-08 09:34:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg! 2spooky4 me! This sub sucks nowadays... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-08 09:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All about that flick bout that flick no tapping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-08 05:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That could be worst </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 21:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I was just there with the Realtor, that place is beyond massive. To all the people who think it's not for sale, it definitely is. It's destroyed though, I'd say 150000 dollars just to keep it standing for 10 more years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 09:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is this creepy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 09:38:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welp just left my contact info. My so is either going to kill me or love it, then the asylum will probably kill me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 12:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "It's been in the box for about 5 weeks so probably dead but I can't be too sure" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 09:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or wet perhaps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 09:39:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love that it's under gigs.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 15:58:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're playing a dangerous game... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 07:34:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With half the following </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 09:57:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The reason they look similar is because they are the exact same picture, op just said that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 07:41:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> None of that is true... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 07:39:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So being barely able to move you felt it a good idea to leave your newborn son in a room with a bobcat?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 07:33:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Poorly written, but good story!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 19:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Arachnophobia and coulrophobia wrapped up in a right little bundle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 18:18:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "There's more than one way to skin a cat" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 04:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This belongs in DIY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ouija Board and doll I made. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-08 12:07:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you shoot me the email or number they have up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 04:39:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're a bad man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-02 04:04:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that the new Razer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> #justantelopethings </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 09:52:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>