<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6084</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:17:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are correct. I wish I could, but titles can't be edited. You are free to edit "emobsymbiotically" to "embosymbiotically" though, if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slightly OT: How do you land the stunt jump from that ramp? I gave up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:17:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Full study in Nature:

[Eye-like ocelloids are built from different endosymbiotically acquired components.](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v523/n7559/full/nature14593.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A rare single-celled sea organism has components that resemble an eye, including a "lens", "cornea" and "retina". A new study indicates that each of the components were acquired embosymbiotically from different sources. The creature could answer some long-standing questions on the evolution of eyes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:15:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 07:24:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I realize this isn't /r/science but I'm gonna put the peer-reviewed study here:

[Imitation Improves Language Comprehension](http://pss.sagepub.com/content/21/12/1903) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that to unintentionally mimic the accent of someone they are talking to, if they have a different accent, is a normal human trait. Psychologists believe it comes from an inbuilt urge to empathise and affiliate with the person you are talking to. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 05:57:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in the mid-1970s pranksters recorded a series of prank calls to a bar in Jersey City, asking for an "Al Coholic" or "Mike Hunt" etc. The recordings and the barman's responses became an underground hit, and may have inspired a running gag on The Simpsons. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:12:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that on Canusa Avenue in Beebe Plain, Vermont and Stanstead, Quebec, houses on one side of the street are in the USA and on the other in Canada. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:43:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 04:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From the source:
 Serge Abrahamovitch Voronoff (Russian:   ; c. July 10, 1866  September 3, 1951) was a French surgeon of Russian extraction who gained fame for his technique of grafting monkey testicle tissue on to the testicles of men for purportedly therapeutic purposes while working in France in the 1920s and 1930s. 

(edit) and:

 By the early 1930s, over 500 men had been treated in France by his rejuvenation technique, and thousands more around the world, such as in a special clinic set up in Algiers.[15] Noteworthy people who had the surgery included Harold McCormick, chairman of the board of International Harvester Company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in the 1920's a French surgeon became famous for his practise of grafting monkey testicles on to male testicles. Hundreds, including the rich and famous, underwent the procedure for its supposed rejuvenating effects. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 04:30:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:38:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I choose to believe that about half way through, mother duck realized that those guys were helping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Facial features: What women perceive as attractive and what men consider attractive. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:02:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's a handy map for that.](http://popvssoda.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL there is a mountain in Tibet that has never been climbed, despite several plans to do so. Locals say of Mt Kailash that a climber would have to "turn himself into a bird and fly to the summit." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:39:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:18:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Post a study with its real title in a peer-reviewed journal and it will get *buried* on /r/science, it's just the way the world works.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 03:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look, I don't see anything in common between the official [Rules of submission](https://www.reddit.com/r/science/wiki/rules#wiki_submission_rules) and what /u/nallen has written at the top of this post.

As an avid reader and frequent submitter to this sub I want to know what the rules are.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:30:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OK so make the rules unambiguous then. It *still* says, in the post:

 linking to a page that contains a video is not allowed.

I'm not being pedantic on purpose, but rules are rules, let us know what they are, and we will follow them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry but this is simply false. Here is the text of the new rules:

 (since we don't allow videos, linking to a page that contains a video is not allowed.)

either you need to edit it or explain why we can't post links that contain videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that mushrooms can create a slight breeze even when the air is calm. They release water vapour, cooling the air and creating a convective current that gets the air moving, carrying spores away from the parent. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:20:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It has always been like this. Or at least since I have been on /r/science. The top comments are always variations of these themes:

- "There is nothing new about this. This has been known for some time."

- "Correlation does not imply causation"

- "Sensationalized clickbait title"

Most of the meaningful discussion happens when you scroll down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:39:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree but sometimes a truly interesting study that belongs here is the meat behind a garbage title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:06:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quite a few headlines in science stories from the mainstream press would violate these rules. So if someone wants to post to /r/science they should adjust them accordingly, rather than use the same headline verbatim? (I agree with the notion, for the record.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 20:46:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the full study in Lancet Psychiatry:

[Does tobacco use cause psychosis? Systematic review and meta-analysis](http://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpsy/article/PIIS2215-0366%2815%2900152-2/abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Brazilian waxes originated in New York, not Brazil. Seven Brazilian sisters started to offer the service in 1987 from their salon in Manhattan. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 20:07:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Smoking may cause schizophrenia. It is well known that schizophrenics smoke at a greater rate than the general population, but a new study indicates that smoking may play a direct role in the development of the condition. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that it was once customary for Indian women to be burned alive on their husband's funeral pyre. A British general outlawed it, saying: This ... is your custom... But my nation has also a custom. When men burn women alive we hang them" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 08:06:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in addition to being fluent in English, Greek, Latin, French, Italian and Spanish, Thomas Jefferson also studied Arabic, Gaelic and Welsh, and remains the most multilingual President of the United States. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:22:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some people like to quote this story as evidence that everything is determined by your DNA. It's a great story but whenever this comes up I'm reminded of the [Texas sharpshooter fallacy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Texas_sharpshooter_fallacy).  Our genomes can predict what happens to us a lot, sure, but a lot of the other coincidences about names etc. came by chance. Indeed, the new field of epigenetics shows that DNA is *not* necessarily your destiny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:37:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is his name Dale Cooper? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 08:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scottish:

 Was a ginger. And a cunt. I didn't like him.

Australian:

"He was a ranga and my best mate."

Just to clear that up. (edit: formatting)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Nelson Rockefeller, once vice President of the United States, died at age 79. of a heart attack rumoured to be caused during sex with his assistant. The New York Magazine quipped: "Nelson thought he was coming, but he was going" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 05:35:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:28:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Hungry yet?](https://www.google.ca/search?q=deep+fried+haggis client=ubuntu hs=SaI channel=fs tbm=isch tbo=u source=univ sa=X ei=zYadVf7ADMvDggTVpL6QCg ved=0CB0QsAQ biw=1630 bih=905) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Irn-Bru, on the other hand, [was once prohibited by the FDA.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Irn-Bru#United_States) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If he switched to soccer at least his diving skills would have come in handy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:21:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> St Louis is getting hammered! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  http://map.norsecorp.com/

That site is mesmerizing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The paper is [here.](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002195)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Genomics will soon produce exabytes of data a year, surpassing the data storage needs of astronomy, Twitter and YouTube, and posing challenges for computing infrastructure. A exabyte is a billion gigabytes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:59:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:42:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not at all. I'm quite sure all of these things were taken into account, that's what a study like this does. It would not be accepted in such a journal as PNAS without doing so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 07:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 90's were best 's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 06:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shh, don't say that, the mods are strict here and this is a great post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that a 2008 poll of 250 children for a report on hospital design found that clowns were universally "frightening and unknowable". It was recommended that clown images were not used in waiting rooms, etc. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 06:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad someone else noticed this, I can't think of any other explanation. If anyone is interested I posted about it elsewhere ITT but it was downvoted. It is [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/3ccozd/women_have_not_always_lived_longer_than_men_the/csuh6e1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:07:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a lot of nonsense in this thread about maternal mortality and war, but if you read [the authors' own abstract](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2015/07/01/1421942112), it's very interesting that they seem to attribute the "mortality gap" to a reduction in infectious disease death rates. We all know that antibiotics have had a profound affect on health:

 The remaining excess male mortality may be explained by underlying traits of vulnerability to cardiovascular disease that emerged with the reduction of infections and changes in diet and other lifestyle factors. 

In other words, infectious diseases killed men and women equally prior to the 20th century, but since then, people lived long enough for the lifestyle factors of men relative to women to make a difference in mortality rates in middle age and beyond. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:16:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks like there may well be some indication of what you are talking about in this study's data. The first figure in OP's article (not the one with the US soccer team) shows a strange outlier of more men than women people dying in their early 40s, say 40 to 45, who were born from 1860 to 1879, compared to the other age cohorts. It's the dark blue part of the graph, and stands out quite a bit.

People who were born from 1860 to 1879 were 40 to 45 from 1900 to 1924. i.e. a large proportion of them were those ages during World War I. Given that we know WWI was catastrophically deadly, and that men were presumably fighting at or over age 40, *and* that this study used data from people in developed countries, I would not be surprised if that dark blue outlier in the chart is an artifact of World War I.

It may be addressed in actual paper, but I don't have access to it right now (paywalled). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 02:08:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Sigh*

Look at the figure in this write-up of the paper - access to the paper itself isn't needed, it is paywalled. The values on the y axis are the male-to-female mortality rate ratios amongst various cohorts for deaths from age 60 to 90 **at those ages**.

Let's take the age 60 for example, as the text does. It clearly shows that a greater ratio of men to women die **at age 60** for those born from 1900-1935 (red and pale blue) than those born from 1800-1839 (grey and black).

This data has nothing to do with life expectancies **at birth**, which I agree, would be skewed by maternal mortality rates.

Edit: Because a demonstrably false post reply is still number one here. Go to the comments of /u/Snoozeybutton or /u/grewapair for more informative comments, guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's coming back in the next Mass Effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Seinfeld re-runs are sped up relative to their original versions in order to accommodate more time for commercials. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the Spice Girls' "Wannabe" is the catchiest pop song in the UK since the 1940s, according to a study. People recognised that song the quickest. Second in the study was "Mambo No 5" by Lou Bega. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 11:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:56:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also notable from that table:

- 3 shots fired by police in England and Wales in 2012-2013
- 2212 people killed by police in Brazil in 2013

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in ancient Rome, one of the most common cooking ingredients was called "laser", from the silphium plant. It does not exist today: it was so delicious that it was harvested to extinction from its natural habitat in what is now Libya. We think that it probably tasted something like garlic. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 08:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that butchers in Australia have a secret language called "Rechtub klat", in which words are spoken backwards. (i.e. "Rechtub klat" = "Butcher talk") It is mostly used so that they can comment on customers without them knowing about it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:26:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in 19th century England, a man by the name of Jack Black was an expert rat catcher. When he caught rats of unusual colour, he would breed them and sell the well bred rats to nobility. Even the Queen kept a pet rat or two. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:08:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:28:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Sneak 90] Bypass rule 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:56:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is currently the most read story on all of the BBC News website. Says so on the right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:06:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RIP scientist's family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists discover the deepest cave-dwelling centipede. The Hades centipede, named after the Greek god of the underworld, lives as far as 1,100 meters below the surface. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it can happen with Twin Peaks it can certainly happen with Star Trek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google searches for the term "housing bubble" in the US and Australia over time, compared. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 21:35:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that a cat named Simon served on a Royal Navy ship in 1949, and received a medal for raising morale, killing off a rat infestation and surviving cannon shells during his service. Hundreds attended his funeral when he died from infected wounds. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:11:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Monsanto once tried to genetically engineer blue cotton, to produce denim without the use of dyes, reducing the pollution involved in the dyeing process. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 01:50:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 21:35:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's up with [this out of place frame in the gif](http://i.imgur.com/yfwWkpL.png)? Subliminal message in the post-it note? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Superfast lasers create a hologram you can touch, feeling "like sandpaper". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 03:35:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Farmers don't need to drive to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that during WWII, the Gestapo's most wanted person was New Zealand born Allied agent Nancy Wake. Among her numerous exploits, she killed an SS soldier with her bare hands, to prevent him from raising the alarm during an undercover raid. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:17:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Racehorses are continuing to get faster, a new study indicates, in a surprise to those in the racing industry who believe that racehorse speed has reached its limit. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:25:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the child's game "Simon Says" is played throughout the world, often with the original "Simon" but also "The King commands" in, for example Norwegian or Portuguese, or "Ship Captain's orders" in Japanese. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 04:45:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 18:53:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cricketers are taught this technique from a very early age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that there was an exhibit of paintings done by a chimpanzee in Paris in 1964. However, people were told they were by a real human artist called "Pierre Brassau". The exhibit was critically acclaimed. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 07:29:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 04:16:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what I thought too. And if you're in another galaxy, why not some Johnny Cash to make you feel at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Manhattan's Central Park contains almost 170,000 different kinds of microbes - a diversity similar to that of wild environments around the world. Also, apparently 2000 of them are unique to Central Park. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:56:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 22:30:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  long **after** the events of the original trilogy

This is actually slightly surprising, in a good way. I thought it would be a sidequel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OK but what about the Trivago Guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The full genome of a bacterium has been sequenced with a USB-powered sequencer that can fit in the palm of your hand. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:30:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:38:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here is the paper they are talking about](http://www.sciencemag.org/content/early/2015/06/10/science.aaa2657.abstract), there was no link in the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Newbie question: To get into the lore, should people play the earlier games, or can they jump right into Witcher 3? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 08:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Title says it all really, I've never played any of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the distress calls of baby mammals share elements across species: a study in the Canadian prairies showed that mother deers rushed towards recorded cries not only of infant deers, but also those of fur seals, dogs, cats and humans. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 05:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 04:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  researchers tested the testosterone levels of the indigenous Tsimane people in central Bolivia before and after they cut down trees. Their results showed a 46.8 percent increase in testosterone levels following the wood cutting, a full 17 percent higher than the testosterone bump caused by playing soccer.

This is a fascinating study for sure, and no offence to the Tsimane people, but it would be really interesting if the results also apply to people in the developed world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:01:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Found this on twitter:

https://twitter.com/sluggahjells/status/609489420769738753?lang=en </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:47:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A pickup truck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Computer scientists are training robots by making them play Minecraft. Robots trained with Minecraft then perform better at a real world task: helping people make brownies. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:12:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Malaysian mountain stripping: 2 Canadians, 2 others get prison time served, to be deported. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:03:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 22:55:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And that's why they're called Secret Service agents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:39:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Women copied her hair and clothing styles (especially when she lowered the neckline on her inaugural gown by 2.5 inches)

Scandalous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the myth that the Great Wall of China is visible from space originated before anyone had ever been into space, and dates back even as far back as the 18th century. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 05:48:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 21:14:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bird red blood cells do, and these guys found what look like nuclei, so they found something that once contained dinosaur DNA. They were just a few million years too late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A google search for "bird erythrocytes" shows that they do have a nucleus, and that it's only in mammals that they are missing. TIL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new test that requires less than a single drop of blood can tell a person every virus they have had over their lifetime. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 06:10:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that hops are not only used for their flavor in beer: they have an antibacterial effect, which promotes the activity of yeast over less desirable microbes during fermentation, which would otherwise ruin the brewing process. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 10:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Steven Spielberg wanted to direct an episode of Twin Peaks, but David Lynch put the kibosh on it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 08:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 07:52:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's the paper.](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0124256)

It's better than the write-up: I didn't know the jellyfish "twitch" their tentacles alluringly as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An Australian species of jellyfish actively hunts its prey. The Irukandji jellyfish uses structures in its tentacles to attract small fish, which it then stings and consumes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 07:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL of "The Green Man", a man severely disfigured as a child who would take long walks only at night in western Pennsylvania. Urban legends at the time said he glowed green, whereas in fact he was real person who was liked by his family and neighbors. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:49:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:52:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All these wacky bribes uncovered so far have been in relation to the World Cups in South Africa and Germany. Imagine what went on for QATAR to be awarded the World Cup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The ability to learn a foreign language during adulthood is strongly associated with a variation in a particular gene: the FOXP2 gene, which has been previously been implicated in disordered speech and language. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:24:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:44:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [MRW seeing this.](http://i.imgur.com/0hTvUkx.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do we feel about the Fallout 4 announcement? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 10:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure you've all seen it. Something like that might soon come for us Mass Effect fans. Discuss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 08:04:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here is the Materials and Methods section of their paper.](http://stm.sciencemag.org/content/7/290/290ra89.full#title9) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The antidepressant Zoloft and heart drug Vascor are shown to be effective treatments for Ebola in mice, after testing thousands of existing medicinal compounds, showing the effectiveness of large-scale testing of drugs for unrelated conditions. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:31:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The most comprehensive map yet of the human epigenome has been published. Among the findings: methylation patterns differ so much among organs that it can be matched with organ type. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 19:23:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 15:16:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a fantastic piece of work! Well done indeed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The evolutionary advantage of homosexuality in fruit flies has been discovered: females with the genetic changes associated with the trait display higher reproductive rates. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 14:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rick Santorum: Climate scientists are like flat-Earth believers. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:14:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Isis in Palmyra: Civilians rounded up and forced to watch execution of 20 men at amphitheatre </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 05:23:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Snowstorm masks in Montreal, 1939. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 13:23:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that there is a plant that grows and even flowers completely underground, in Western Australia. The "underground orchid" was only discovered because of the smell it was giving from the ground alerted a farmer. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 10:49:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 09:22:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is an EXTREMELY HARD platinum. Hawking would be proud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 09:05:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Russell Crowe, you're drunk. That's an Aussie Burger and we all know it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The gut bacteria of pandas are not very well suited to bamboo, their main food source. In fact, they seem to be more suited to a meat based diet. The imbalance may in fact be responsible for these endangered animals' apparent reluctance to have sex. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 05:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that George Lucas offered David Lynch the opportunity to direct The Return of the Jedi. Lynch refused, saying the movie should reflect Lucas' vision of the script. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 08:16:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have figured out how to brew morphine using the same kit used to make beer at home. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 07:31:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:30:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If nothing else that is one well-written and entertaining wiki page. Good job OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:49:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's life trying to, uh, find a way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:08:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surprisingly, there are several other bands from Saudi Arabia on that site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A couple of random examples:

[Danish](http://da.wikipedia.org/wiki/Smoking)

[Portuguese](http://pt.wikipedia.org/wiki/Smoking) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that a tuxedo jacket is called a "smoking" in French, Italian, Portuguese, German, Polish, Russian and other European languages, because of its similarity to Victorian smoking jackets. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:23:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 18:47:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can't, the photos we have of the landing sites were [taken from a satellite currently in orbit around the moon.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Third-party_evidence_for_Apollo_Moon_landings#Photographs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  The way the police knee him in the back is something they should not do. 

No shit, and yet it seems to be the go-to move whenever we see videos of rough arrests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:22:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, I for one did *not* see that coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 22:17:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess this is ironic, in the Alanis Morissette sense of the word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He has an appeal left and will probably be executed on his own later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 20:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the record, the correct breakdown is:

8 executed (1 Indonesian, 2 Australians, 3 Nigerians, 1 Brazilian, 1 Ghanaian)

(source: OP's link - it may well have been updated since it was first posted)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dandelions produce rubber. Scientists have identified the key components involved in the production of rubber in the plants, bringing closer the biotechnological synthesis of rubber. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 19:50:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:05:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Link to the study in Nature Neuroscience.](http://www.nature.com/neuro/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nn.4011.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The neurons responsible for the sensation of hunger have been identified. Mice with this brain circuit activated reduce feeding, "resulting in the same outcome as dieting but without the chronic feeling of hunger" according to a co-author. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 22:59:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the largest opinion gap between the US public and scientists is in whether genetically modified foods are safe to eat, with 88% of scientists in agreement compared to 37% of the public. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 21:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This kid is about 77 now. Probably still cuts a rug, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A retrovirus in the human genome is expressed in 3 day old embryos, which are bundles of 8 cells, and appears to protect embryos against foreign viruses at this stage of life. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:44:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists can now tell where a dust sample comes from in the continental U.S. based on the DNA of the fungi in it. The research has applications in forensic science. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:53:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that a crease in the earlobe may be indicative of heart disease and/or diabetes. This is called "Frank's sign" and notable individuals with it include Steven Spielberg. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 17:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 20:00:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a different cop, folks. The one you're thinking of is unarmed and locked in Charleston County Jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that married women drink more than their unmarried counterparts, whereas the opposite is true for men, according to a 2012 study. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that giant tortoises from the Galapagos can survive without food or water for up to a year. In the past, buccaneers, whalers and fur sealers would store them live in their ships' holds as a fresh meat source that doesn't require feeding. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 11:50:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 04:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, the world returned to a more basic state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 04:36:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have [dealt successfully with another revolting ideology](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Laws_against_Holocaust_denial). It *should* be easy to enact similar laws against radical islamist hate speech, but don't hold your breath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 04:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mark Stein was very [prescient](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/America_Alone). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that aluminum was once so rare that Napoleon III would serve his state dinners on aluminum plates. The rank-and-file guests had had to settle for dinner served on gold or silver plates. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-01 11:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that sometimes a group of ants will get separated from their main foraging party and begin to follow each other in a continuously rotating circle. Eventually they all die of exhaustion. This phenomenon is called an "ant mill". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 10:54:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When the internet and a robot are a better alternative to trying getting a date, your country's gonna have a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Police officer explains why he hit homeless man with his car </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-20 23:05:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-20 18:24:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here is the paper being discussed](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0003347214004643), in case that link is problematic, as it was for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chimpanzees in the wild 'talk' to each other about their favorite fruits and the trees where they can be found. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:50:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-18 19:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, "cuddling". [Just ask these penguins.](http://www.nbcnews.com/id/24585481/ns/technology_and_science-science/t/seal-caught-tape-molesting-penguin/#.VLv6Ro_PF2M) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-12 06:13:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heartbreaking. We have police dash cams, why not body cams? This is a great example of why they're needed, we get to see the humanity of the vast majority of police and the work they do, and make sure that those who abuse their power are held accountable. It's a win-win for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 19:14:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure the racist cartoon analogy is appropriate. A religion is not a race. It is a set of ideas, and satirising ideas is fair game, no matter how "offensive" that may be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 18:56:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems to be an english language thing in general. Unless I'm mistaken none of the papers in the UK, Australia etc. are reproducing the cartoons. In Canada, ALL of the french media in Quebec are showing the cartoons, but the english media in the rest of Canada (and in Montreal) are not. What that all means I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 07:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure either but I think M. Night Shyamalan has optioned it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-23 17:35:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This comes to mind.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VRIUbFLjtX0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-23 17:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The guy promoted his snuff film before it was even made. Surprised it took them 8 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Dominant Life Form in the Cosmos Is Probably Superintelligent Robots </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 01:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 00:54:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely fascinating, all of this, but this part doesn't seem to have any backup based on the links provided, and seems anecdotal (thus the highlighting), can someone help?

December 3rd

The second data leak. This one garnered less press but contained was considerably more dangerous... **I've heard** that much of this information was available because an IT director was comprised apparently he had no background in IT and was actually a marketing exec who reached the position (and thus higher salary) through corporate politics. You can see for example is was good at naming files.

(this is not to detract from the link at all, I'm just curious)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Two scientists have set the world record for time spent living underwater: 10 weeks. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 14:48:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Morning work start times should be delayed to ensure adults get an adequate amount of sleep, according to a new study. For every hour that work started later in the morning, sleep time increased by approximately 20 minutes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 21:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-05 15:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Top ten jobs that attract psychopaths:](http://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyclay/2013/01/05/the-top-10-jobs-that-attract-psychopaths/)

1. CEO
2. Lawyer
3. Media (Television/Radio)
4. Salesperson
5. Surgeon
6. Journalist
7. **Police officer**
8. Clergy person
9. Chef
10. Civil servant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The ancient origins of drinking alcohol: A paleogenomic study reveals it begain around 10 million years ago when primates began eating rotten and fermented fruit. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-05 15:09:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 18:38:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's the "Gangstas in Space" DLC (?). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 18:10:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a pretty interesting infographic about this [in this article by none other than Bill Gates.](http://www.gatesnotes.com/Health/Most-Lethal-Animal-Mosquito-Week?WT.mc_id=MosquitoWeek2014_SharkWeek_tw WT.tsrc=Twitter) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-21 16:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For example, [here](http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0004741). This doesn't detract from OP's link, however. For a start it uses a completely different technique (EEG vs. fMRI).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Canada's Sudbury Basin, the world's second largest impact crater, was formed when a comet struck 1.8 billion years ago, according to an analysis of the geochemistry of the crater. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 18:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Army researchers develop pocket-sized aerial surveillance device. It can, for example, give Soldiers the ability to see around the corner or into the next room during combat missions. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 21:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 19:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The used Burger Shot bag ties it all together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 23:48:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Love is a Holy War!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in the 1980s the Naval Investigative Service undertook a massive and futile search for a woman named "Dorothy" in the Chicago area, after hearing gay men refer to themselves as "friends of Dorothy". They believed she was at the center of a ring of gay military personnel. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 21:42:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 20:24:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to see the movie about this one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dark matter could be detected by looking for time glitches in the existing network of GPS satellites. One researcher is already mining 15 years' worth of GPS timing data for its signature. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 20:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 19:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Destruction magic's fine, just don't go burning down any buildings." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 19:21:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Better still, hire a submarine.](http://d1jqu7g1y74ds1.cloudfront.net/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/halley-newspaper-clip-475x580.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 18:08:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I look forward to an "obesity mod" where you see a beer gut instead and can't run more than a few seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 22:48:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *South Korea. Best Korea has a 100% voter turnout every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 22:07:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Paper: [Mapping the unconscious maintenance of a lost first language.](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2014/11/12/1409411111) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The first language that a baby hears leaves a pattern in the unconscious brain that remains even if the child completely stops using the language, such as in cases of international adoption, a brain imaging study shows. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 22:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 13:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there anything said or shown in the video that gives an indication of when it was filmed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wikipedia page views can predict disease outbreaks nearly a month before official health advice, a team of US scientists says. Their technique allowed them to predict emerging flu, dengue fever and TB outbreaks. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 19:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 21:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Canusa Street.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canusa_Street)

CAN USA. Cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists Make Hilarious Proofreading Error. "Should we cite the crappy Gabor paper here?" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 20:20:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mosquitos evolved to specialize on human prey. They show a stronger affinity for human scents than their "forest" ancestors, due to changes in 14 genes and one olfactory receptor in particular. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 19:28:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 19:03:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, getting home from the night shift and coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:54:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the curious, this makes it the film with the most fucks ever. [There's a wiki page about this.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_films_that_most_frequently_use_the_word_%22fuck%22)

 A documentary called "Fuck" from 2005 about the word itself contains it 857 times, but I don't think that really counts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:21:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We've got [Programming Languange Inventor or Serial Killler?](http://www.malevole.com/mv/misc/killerquiz/), someone needs to make a "Hipster or Jihadi?" website stat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Health and Retirement study indicates people wildly underestimate how long they will live. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:09:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Secret to a long life is still a mystery: a search for genes associated with longevity in people over 110 years of age has drawn a blank. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 21:59:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 22:38:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same thing with Australia if you replace the US border with the ocean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 18:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everybody wins when this happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bald Uakari </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 17:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 23:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Newspaper article from the time:](http://news.google.com/newspapers?nid=2206 dat=19831124 id=ybslAAAAIBAJ sjid=IfMFAAAAIBAJ pg=2235,2463975)

 A nude, screaming dancer found trapped under a man's crushed body on a trick piano pinned against a nightclub ceiling was too drunk to remember how she got there, police said.

...

 The dead man's body provided 2 or 3 inches of cushion that kept the woman from being crushed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's right, it was a happy place. They had flowery meadows and rainbow skies, and rivers made of chocolate, where the children danced and laughed and played with gumdrop smiles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:48:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They thought about it once but nothing came of it: [Project Orion.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Project_Orion_%28nuclear_propulsion%29) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:22:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heh. This *had* to be from Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the plastic chair is known as a "monobloc", and was invented in 1967. Since they cost only about $3 to produce they are ubiquitous around the world. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 21:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seven Italian scientists who were found guilty of manslaughter after failing to warn of an earthquake have had their convictions overturned on appeal. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 19:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why scientists think completely unclassifiable and undiscovered life forms exist. There may be a fourth domain of life on Earth undetectable by current techniques. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 16:55:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> HIV: Genetic mutation leads to two men being 'spontaneously cured' of virus. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 18:47:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 22:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something I noticed: there's a little dig at the then Soviets:

 We don't hide our space program. We don't keep secrets and cover things up. We do it all up front and in public. That's the way freedom is, and we wouldn't change it for a minute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 20:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No matter what you think of Reagan, [the whole speech](http://www.historyplace.com/speeches/reagan-challenger.htm) is really something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that there is a massive "undergound river", or aquifer that runs about 4 kilometers below the Amazon river for 6000 kilometers, following roughly the Amazon river's flow. It eventually empties in the Atlantic Ocean deep below the surface. It was only discovered in 2011. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 05:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 18:59:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Metagenomics is going to increasingly turn up surprises such as this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scratching makes itches worse. It initally relieves itching by creating a minor pain, but the brain responds by releasing serotonin, which influences nerve cells and increases itchiness. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 18:30:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 16:32:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Thanks for this, though, Buzz!](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TZ0axpAwRso) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Projet Montreal is seeking your input on bus 105 overcrowding. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 20:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists grow miniature stomachs from stem cells, which could patch up ulcers one day. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 19:52:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hagel orders quarantine for troops returning from West Africa. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 18:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DNA molecules can carry electric current, a team of researchers has demonstrated. This could lead to the development of DNA-based electronic circuits. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 17:39:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why you should always make important decisions on an empty stomach: Hungry people perform better on a psychological test based on gambling that is supposed to simulate real-life decision making </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 01:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 18:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The folks at /r/conspiracy discuss this [here.](http://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/1y3frt/til_neos_passport_expired_on_091101_the_matrix/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 17:22:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [You could at least change some of the words.](http://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/1s4lbr/til_that_there_is_a_biker_gang_from_arizona_who/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A virus once thought to only infect algea has been found in the human throat cavity. It also appears to affect the cognitive abilities of individuals carrying its DNA. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 17:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that a self-filling water bottle is being developed that draws moisture from the air - up to three liters every hour. It works by mimicking the way a beetle survives in the African desert. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 16:54:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 05:39:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He also had [a romantic relationship with a pigeon](http://claudiears.wordpress.com/2011/10/01/nikola-tesla-and-the-pigeon-love-story/), so, there's that. I assume the pigeon was fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 03:50:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally agree but [this comes a close second.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rMMX8dkbXEU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that a study of film-goers heart rates shows that the "Here's Johnny!" scene from The Shining is the scariest moment in film. Over entire movies, "The Exorcist" is the scariest, sending pulses up by 25.9% on average. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 20:11:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 19:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [No it isn't.](http://www.reddit.com/r/reddit.com/comments/eozhj/til_slang_is_short_for_shortened_language/c19sfbp)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 255 Terabits/s: Researchers demonstrate record data transmission over new type of fiber. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 16:09:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-26 23:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of Brazilians are going to be **really** pissed off about this. Search the words "luto" or "vergonha" on twitter. I'm sure there will be another catchphrase of the night.

Edit: yes, there is a new hashtag, that was quick: #RIPBrasil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-26 21:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I want to apologize for inconveniencing you while trying to protect the lives of millions.

Very true. What this quarantine is doing is protecting the political lives of Governors Christie and Cuomo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-26 20:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This would be right if this quarantine *was* "protecting people from a seriously lethal threat". It isn't. Ebola isn't transmissable until an infected person is gravely ill. We knew that before, and we know that now. The *only* two cases transmitted in the US were nurses who treated patient zero Duncan near death spewing infected fluid everywhere, while wearing ineffective PPE.

It was the pathetic initial response by the CDC in providing the Dallas hospital with adequate protection that was a "seriously lethal threat" to these nurses. Thankfully they have recovered. What's happening now is a fearful over-reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Touching receipts after using hand sanitizers can increase the absorption of BPA into the body by a factor of 100 or more. BPA has been linked to a number of health concerns. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 22:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 19:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The study being referenced is [here.](http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00442-014-2995-6/fulltext.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Plants can tell when theyre being eaten: Arabidopsis plants sense the vibrations of caterpillars as they eat their leaves, and in response secrete mustard oils to deter the predator. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 19:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 17:42:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And it remains the single greatest movie about snakes on a plane in film history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dr. Oz-endorsed diet pill study was bogus, researchers admit. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 17:07:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-18 18:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perhaps the Dallas Cowboys should switch to black for Ebola Awareness Month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Maine teacher who had recently visited Dallas to attend a conference has been placed on paid leave due to Ebola concerns raised by parents. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-17 21:01:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 18:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is comparable to the Dallas Cowboys' value of about $3.2 billion, and the Yankees' value of about $2.5 billion. Basketball and hockey teams are nowhere near as rich.

[The business of football](http://www.forbes.com/nfl-valuations/)

[The business of baseball](http://www.forbes.com/mlb-valuations/) etc...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Early career scientists trapped in 'perpetual adolescence'. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 18:32:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 20:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It gets worse: [Second ebola nurse traveled on plane with low-grade fever.](http://www.wfaa.com/story/news/health/2014/10/15/second-dallas-hospital-worker-diagnosed-ebola/17290677/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 19:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is what they should have done with Duncan when he was diagnosed. The Dallas hospital was *not* prepared for ebola - two infected nurses demonstrate that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google Glass user treated for internet addiction. The patient appeared to suffer withdrawal symptoms when prevented from using Google Glass and dreamed he was wearing it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 18:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 23:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This article](http://jezebel.com/5899815/how-does-ovulation-affect-a-strippers-income-it-doesnt) explains how the study behind this "fact" may be flawed. The sample size was way too small:

 Two researchers at UNM in Albuquerque studied dancers for two months. They studied 18 dancers. In one club, in one city. For two cycles.

Evidently, a **lot** more field research needs to be done on this phenomenon, before it can be confirmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Astronomers have mapped the weather on a planet outside of the Solar System. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 23:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:48:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "TIFU by joining ISIS and getting knocked up by a Jihadi." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd take this story with a grain of salt. Here is the questionable source:

[Central European News](http://www.cen.at/)

Having said that, these stupid girls really *are* missing, and probably in ISIS land.

[Interpol link 1](http://www.interpol.int/notice/search/missing/2014-22367)

[Interpol link 2](http://www.interpol.int/notice/search/missing/2014-22373)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ebola Patient Needs $500,000 to Cover Medical Bills </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 19:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Captive orcas who live with dolphins can imitate dolphin sounds. Orcas therefore join the list of species capable of vocal learning, which includes humans, birds, elephants, bats, seals and dolphins. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 18:44:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 18:31:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not an expert by any means, but I'm pretty sure that's not a shark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 21:59:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here are links to the [two](http://www.sciencemag.org/content/346/6206/251.full) [papers](http://www.sciencemag.org/content/346/6206/256.full) published in Science today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists find lung cancer can lie hidden for 20 years. During this time, tumors will have developed down multiple evolutionary pathways, making it extremely hard for any one targeted medicine to have an effect. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 21:55:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 20:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> UPDATE: probably a false alarm if [this comment](http://www.reddit.com/r/ebola/comments/2irvwf/british_man_dies_of_disease_in_macedonia/cl4wwgz) is correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ebola crisis: 'British man dies of disease in Macedonia' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 19:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new measurement of dark matter in the Milky Way has revealed there is half as much of the mysterious substance as previously thought. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 18:31:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 17:10:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's another thing and is worthy of debate. The survery in OP's link was *explicitly* asking about banning things that don't exist.

Survey Monkey should have asked "Are you in favor of banning entry to people originating from an Ebola stricken country?".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 16:54:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's worth pointing out that the question as it was posed is moot.  **There are no flights** directly to the US from Liberia or Sierra Leone.

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roberts_International_Airport#Airlines_and_destinations

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lungi_International_Airport#Airlines_and_destinations
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 22:06:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Link](http://www.nbcdfw.com/news/local/Frisco-Investigating-Possible-Ebola-Case-278555081.html?_osource=SocialFlowTwt_DFWBrand)

 The person being transported to the hospital is an employee with the Dallas County Sheriff's Office who was in Duncan's apartment, NBC 5 has confirmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 21:54:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's more on the Spanish nurse.](http://www.nytimes.com/2014/10/09/world/europe/spain-nurse-ebola.html?_r=0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 21:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also from that link:

 CBS 11 has confirmed that the patient checked yes to one of the screening questions regarding travel to West Africa.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 21:16:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  The patient claims to have had contact with the Dallas 'patient zero'

So many questions on this. If they did have contact, were they on the CDC watchlist, if not, why not? Is this "claim" just bogus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Ranking of All 118 Sweaters Seen on Twin Peaks </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 20:05:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 17:55:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Frudakis' company, DNAPrint, has yet to turn a profit and may not survive much longer. 

[Looks about right...](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNAPrint_Genomics)

 The company ceased operations in February 2009. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 22:08:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  The list is incomplete.

It sure is. There have been 12 fatal shootings by police since 2000 in Montreal *alone*. [Check out the red markers in this map.](http://www.montrealgazette.com/news/policeshootings/index.html)

There are way more in the US though, this is true.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 21:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This study](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3298261/) examined dogs in a 2001-2002 outbreak in Gabon and seems to be the main source of information on this, and yes, dogs can be asymptomatically infected.

There is a very interesting thing in this paper:

 dogs appear to be the first animal species shown to be naturally and asymptomatically infected by Ebola virus. 

Needless to say, it would be *very* useful to know the biological mechanisms involved in that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chickens have gotten ridiculously large since the 1950s. A modern chicken is about 3 times as efficient at turning feed into breast meat as one from the 1950s. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 20:37:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 22:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know media outlets update their stories, right? When this was posted the story was *very* short and didn't contain this sentence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 21:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This comment](http://www.reddit.com/r/ebola/comments/2igp2w/nurse_infected_with_ebola_in_spain/cl23a5d) from another thread is worth reading. I cannot vouch for the translation. Relevant and eye-opening quotes: 
(edit: emphasis added)

 The infection event is still under investigation; **she went twice into the patient's room**: once to assist him and then after the former patient died. No accidental contact was reported.

 The infected nurse went on vacations the day after the former patient pased away. Her husband is being questioned to elaborate a list of people with who she was in contact.

 First symptoms (temperature under 38.6C) were reported on September 30th. She has been controlled twice a day since then. She mostly stayed at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 20:00:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the first actual *infection* to take place outside Africa right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 22:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the one Al-Nusra urged ISIS to release. He was just a charity worker. Fuck these guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 06:28:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much turmeric would you have to eat to get their dose of curcumin (500mg twice daily)? Is it feasible?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 05:59:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But, but... Hollywood movies tell me that there are crack teams in hazmat suits expertly drilled to deal with situations like this! Everything I've seen so far leads me to believe that they are hopelessly prepared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that a significant percentage of the genetic material found on Earth cannot be attributed to any of the existing categories of living organisms on Earth. This "biological dark matter" may represent a fourth domain of life, yet to be discovered, </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 05:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A particle which is both matter and antimatter - the Majorana fermion - has been detected. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 22:27:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 21:23:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like a story out of Liberia but no, this is Dallas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 18:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If that's the case it would be Darwin Award level stupidity on his part, if the story of him carrying around an ebola patient is true. I guess we don't know enough yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Manhattan's Central Park contains almost 170,000 different kinds of microbes - a diversity similar to that of wild environments around the world. Also, apparently 2000 of them are unique to Central Park. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 18:30:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 17:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very relevant, from [this story](http://www.reuters.com/article/2014/10/01/us-health-ebola-usa-idUSKCN0HP2F720141001):

Duncan, in his mid-40s, helped transport a pregnant woman suffering from Ebola to a hospital in Liberia, where she was turned away for lack of space. Duncan helped bring the woman back to her family's home and carried her into the house, where she later died

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 19:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed, but it is probably worth noting that it was the researchers' University *itself* that chose that title for their press release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 18:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nasal Predator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 17:30:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here is the paper](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/ele.12373/full), there is no link in the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Virus DNA liquefies from a solid-like state in preparation for infection of host cells. Two new studies determine its mechanism and the factors triggering the transition. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 16:32:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 19:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least this model came pre-bent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China warns foreign diplomats in Hong Kong to stay away from Occupy Central. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 17:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Global carbon dioxide emissions in one convenient map. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 19:50:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Water discovered in a small, warm planets atmosphere for the first time. The Neptune-sized planet is about 120 light years from Earth in the constellation of Cygnus. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 19:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 09:48:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for that. That's real information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 06:47:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These critters' shit may be literally [responsible for rosacea, too.](http://www.newscientist.com/article/dn22227-rosacea-may-be-caused-by-mite-faeces-in-your-pores.html#.VCD7Bdf0FNA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 03:53:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This problem is most definitely real, and I wish I had read this thread before buying Undead Nightmare over the weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that one of the most famous actresses of the silent film era in the US was Alla Nazimova, originally from Russia. She had romantic affairs with a number of other actresses and coined the use of the phrase "sewing circle" to refer to closeted lesbian or bisexual actresses of her day. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 03:36:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists seen as competent but not trusted by Americans. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 22:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 18:08:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You hear that? That's the sound of the college textbook bubble bursting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 17:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was curious, so [here's a picture of one of these microbeads embedded in the gum](http://cdn.beverlyhillsladentist.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/MicrobeadToothpaste.jpg). (Warning: very large tooth picture). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 04:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fact that those two mutations can produce such a remarkable change in phenotype is the whole point of the paper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 00:28:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Link to paper.](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2014/09/11/1414542111) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists make mice learn tasks faster by splicing a human gene linked to speech and language into their DNA. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 22:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 17:56:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Paper here](http://www.psjournals.org/doi/abs/10.1666/13-122).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Paleontologists have discovered an ancient swamp pig. "Jaggermeryx naida" has been named after Mick Jagger because of its big, flappy lips that it used to snuffle all over the riverbank. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Largest Liberian Newspaper: US Government Manufactured Ebola, AIDS Virus. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 22:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 20:37:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here is the link to the paper](http://journals.aps.org/prx/abstract/10.1103/PhysRevX.4.031043) they are discussing, the link in OP's article doesn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the ancient Romans and Greeks played a sport that was probably quite similar to rugby. It was rough - a specatator once had his leg broken when he got caught in the middle of play. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 19:46:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The genome of the gibbon has been sequenced - the last ape to have it revealed. Gibbon DNA is 96% identical to human, compared to 98% for the chimpanzee. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 18:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When young people are affected by grief, their immune system becomes more resilient, but older people become more susceptible to infection, according to a new study. It could explain why some elderly couples pass away only a short time apart. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-10 01:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 19:42:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is interesting that the curves differ by country. Liberia is showing a scary  exponential growth in cases. Sierra Leone and Guinea, not as much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 19:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This graph](http://i.imgur.com/wAZTLKG.png)  really is looking exponential. ([Original source](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ebola_virus_epidemic_in_West_Africa#mediaviewer/File:Diseased_Ebola_2014.png)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3D films are no more effective at eliciting emotional responses as 2D films. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 18:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A pond-dwelling, single-celled organism has been found to break its own DNA into nearly a quarter-million pieces and rapidly reassemble those pieces when it's time to mate. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 22:02:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bomb Blast Next to Chile Subway Station Injures Eight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 20:55:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 18:10:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just for some perspective, [here is the solar system at an accurate scale.](http://joshworth.com/dev/pixelspace/pixelspace_solarsystem.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 20:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Obligatory GIF here.](http://imgur.com/a/VIeMk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 19:36:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this is a [Payne Stewart](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1999_South_Dakota_Learjet_crash) type of thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oxygen-producing life was present on the Earth 60 million years earlier than previously thought. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 19:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Perrier water and its competitor San Pellegrino are both owned by the Nestle corporation. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 18:28:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 18:14:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bill Gates will be remembered more fondly by history than Steve Jobs. Try telling that to someone 10+ years ago! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 17:37:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Paper [here](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/add.12730/abstract). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> E-cigarettes could save over 50,000 lives in the UK, experts say, in a paper published in the journal Addiction critical of recent WHO recommendations. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 17:35:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Deep sea mushroom-shaped creatures found off Australia, which are neither fungi nor fish, may represent an early branch on the tree of life. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 20:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 18:35:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This gif should be renamed "Bowel Movements". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 21:35:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the [Altruist Cult](http://gta.wikia.com/Altruist_Cult). I guess they're not a part of any main story mission, so yeah I guess some people could miss them altogether. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists Cannot Explain This Crazy Ant Behavior, but They Love It: Watch as this colony forms a daisy chain to pull a millipedea behavior researchers have never seen before. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 20:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Experimental ebola drug cured 100% of monkeys tested, in a study published Friday by Canadian researchers. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 20:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 19:55:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Urban Dictionary: hung like a gorilla](http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=hung%20like%20a%20gorilla). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 19:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're apparently one of the few non-human species to use a variery of sexual positions, so life, uh... finds a way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 19:19:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  ["It is very exciting," Jorgen Ouren of Statistics Norway tells The Local news website.](http://i.imgur.com/5iQGPFw.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Brazil's economy falls into recession, just a month before the general election, latest figures show. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 18:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-27 20:23:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The study is published [here](http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0105948). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mystery solved: "sailing stones" of Death Valley seen in action for the first time. Thin sheets of ice push rocks across the desert when conditions are just right. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-27 20:17:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-27 18:40:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They don't harm humans, but you really don't want to be small enough to be a pseudoscorpion's next meal:

 the venom is used to capture and immobilize the pseudoscorpion's prey. During digestion, pseudoscorpions pour a mildly corrosive fluid over the prey, then ingest the liquefied remains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Handheld Reusable DNA Sequencer is Here. New Zealand scientists invent a brick-sized prototype that can sequence a DNA sample in less than an hour. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 19:33:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ebola outbreak: Congo becomes fifth country with confirmed cases. This strain is not linked to the epidemic that has spread through west Africa. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-25 20:53:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There is a fungus that controls the minds of ants found in the U.S., and its life-cycle and mechanism of action are a little different than its well-known South American counterparts. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 21:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the earwax in blue whales can form plugs as long as 10 inches (25 cm). Scientists can study the layers in them to get an idea of when certain pollutants were more common, much like tree rings can be counted to go back in time. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 19:12:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 06:24:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In all seriousness [this](http://informahealthcare.com/doi/abs/10.1080/15563650500514590?journalCode=ctx) is the only source for the Romans-eating-it stuff but it's behind a hefty paywall for me. If anyone has free access to it it would be fascinating what if any sources they had for ancient Romans doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How about this one? If identical twin men have sex with a woman at the same time and get her pregnant with non-identical twins, there's no way of knowing if they are full siblings, half siblings, or even who their father is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 22:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This one?](http://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/2co5kb/til_of_the_dream_fish_a_fish_that_causes_you_to/). The link doesn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 21:56:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Another story](http://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-28811232) on this beetle appears to have the answer, which is a little unexpected:

 Cyphochilus beetles are native to South-East Asia, where they live among white fungi.

 This new study proves that they have been optimised by natural selection to be camouflaged among their surroundings, while keeping the scales as light as possible - which is crucial for flying insects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that some plants can warn each other of incoming insect attacks by sending signals through an underground network of fungi. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 19:53:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A species of beetle is exceptionally bright white, because of its scales that reflect light so well. No human technology can match their brilliance using such thin material. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 17:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 17:28:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here is a recent piece by that guy telling the story.](http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2014/08/what-i-did-after-police-killed-my-son-110038.html#.U_NpBFHfu5k).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Real Reason We Yawn. Yawns are contagious, but they keep the brain working in peak form. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 17:15:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL there is a species of fish that can be hallucinogenic when eaten. The Ancient Romans reportedly consumed it as a recreational drug. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 17:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nature publishes a survey of scientists' use of social media. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 17:41:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crayfish can turn blood cells into neurons, regenerating parts of their brain. Understanding the mechanism could lead to new ways of reprogramming human cells. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-12 18:13:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-12 06:24:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of the least insane posts I have seen in the last few months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-11 19:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some people think that's the way natural right-handers *should* play golf, because the leading arm in a golf swing should be the dominant/stronger arm. The leading arm in a "left-handed" swing is the right arm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists Detect a Possible Signal from Dark Matter </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-11 19:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-10 21:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a real Collector's item! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-08 17:31:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The paper is [here](http://www.cs.cmu.edu/~aldrich/papers/ecoop14-tsls.pdf) (PDF). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The World Health Organization is to reconsider its stance against the use of experimental, untested drugs or vaccines, in the light of the current ebola outbreak. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-08 16:11:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New programming language accommodates multiple languages in the same program. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-08 16:05:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in 2002 a study was published in the prestigious journal Science showing that MDMA or "ecstasy" was neurotoxic. However it was retracted the following year, after it was found that methamphetamine had been used in the study rather than MDMA. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 21:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Self-assembling origami robot is world's first Transformer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:30:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Brief, acute psychological stress promotes skin healing in mice. The healing is brought about by glucocorticoids - steroid hormones - which are produced by the adrenal glands in response to stress. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 16:21:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-06 21:48:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's a video of them](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OaPYwlXOTzQ), probably from the 90s when the Indian authorities made some efforts to contact them (which they do not do any more). Amazing stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-05 18:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How many times has a random stranger asked you to say "One does not simply ... (insert line here)"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-05 16:50:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is more accurate to say that 96% of the matter/energy in the universe is undetectable, but is predicted to be there by our current model of physics.

Either it is there and our current model of physics works for it, or it is not there and our current model of physics is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-05 16:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not many. Don't shoot the messenger! I just pointed out that they have a rule and that it's strictly enforced. I'm neither endorsing nor disfavoring the rule.

^(The story in this post I find personally very interesting, however.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-05 15:44:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From the [rules for submissions](http://www.reddit.com/r/science/wiki/rules#wiki_submission_rules):

 Every submission must be a direct link to or a summary of peer-reviewed research with appropriate citations.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-05 14:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It has become clear that there is an important eukaryotic component to the gut microbiome of ruminant mammals, mainly in the form of anaerobic fungi and protozoa. However, when we talk about the human intestinal microbiome we always hear about bacteria. My two questions are: Are there eukaryotes in the human gut microbiome? If so, do they play an important role, with potential clinical implications? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A golden bat has been discovered in Bolivia. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 17:34:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 17:14:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  The process by which the medication was made available to Brantly and Writebol is highly unusual. It may have fallen under the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's "compassionate use" regulation, which allows access to investigational drugs outside clinical trials. Getting approval for compassionate use is often long and laborious. 

A sad fact is we're looking at years if not decades before this treatment is approved for widespread use after the requisite clinical trials, and even then it may be prohibitively expensive for use in Africa. I may be proven wrong, but I don't see it being distributed to the hundreds of sick in the current outbreak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists discover why some people can thrive on less sleep than others. A particular gene variant is responsible, and those with it can also handle extended periods of sleeplessness better. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 17:38:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Many bees are lazy. About 20% of the bees in a beehive account for 50% of the foraging activity. However, the slacker bees step up if the hard working ones are removed. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-01 15:51:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 18:08:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems to be so. Comments in the article and /u/arrc clear that up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 17:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bad, I just trusted the article, including its headline. That's a pretty awful error on their part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 16:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, if that's the case, a remastered release of the trilogy on next-gen while we wait, *please*! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 16:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All are good summaries but to clarify, the stop being negative one is in particular about other people. Quote:

 Needing to talk badly about others indicates low self-esteem. That means, 'I feel so low that instead of picking myself up I have to cut others down,' 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 16:15:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Steer clear of the comments below OP's article, fellow redditor - it must have been linked by the Drudge Report or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Danish team achieves data transmission rate record: 43 terabits per second. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 15:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 21:37:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well he's got an appropriate name if that's the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 20:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is what you have to do when there's no bale of hay down there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 19:56:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dirty Rotten Scoundrels: An inside look at the lead up to the 2008 financial crisis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Moose saliva contains a fungal toxin which enables them to be able to eat grass known to contain harmful fungi without any ill effects. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 17:20:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Kardashian index: a measure of discrepant social media profile for scientists. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 17:10:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 20:03:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this is after one of Liberia's top doctors dies yesterday. This is sad and scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 19:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aussie and Kiwi kids have been doing this [at their schools.](http://www.news.com.au/technology/online/google-maps-still-shows-giant-graffiti-penis-graffiti-at-schools-many-years-after-they-were-drawn/story-fnjwnhzf-1226902303410). Heck, one kid drew a penis on the Google Street View *camera* itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 18:17:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [We need something like this for her.](http://i.imgur.com/Q0SqvwL.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 17:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This seems fitting, since marijuana legalization will do a great deal to reduce the incarceration rate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 17:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That last quote is actually paraphrased from this Hadith: 

http://www.usc.edu/org/cmje/religious-texts/hadith/bukhari/056-sbt.php#004.056.791 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 20:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Classic. [Here's what Justin has to say about that.](http://i.imgur.com/Gty6OM4.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 17:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [He died in 2012](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maurice_Sendak) by the way, so it's not an is but a was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL there is a plant in Australia that grows completely underground. It even flowers underground. The "underground orchid" never sees the sun, instead it feeds on a fungus which grows on the roots of an outback shrub. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 16:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Want a healthier life? Stop shaking hands and start fist-bumping. A new study shows that handshakes can transfer ten times the amount of bacteria as a fist-bump does. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 15:45:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:56:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The British were awful to the Australian Aborigines, no doubt about that, *but*, from OP's first paragraph:

 A number of historians point to **introduced disease** as the major cause of the destruction of the full-blooded Aboriginal population.

A similar thing happened to native populations in Central and South America upon arrival of the Spanish.

(edit: formatting) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 19:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh boy, that video is painful. The guy doesn't know he's in a hole and keeps on digging and digging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 18:40:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Also](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dick_Pound):

[CAN] Dick Pound </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 20:10:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's](http://online.liebertpub.com/doi/full/10.1089/ast.2014.1162) the paper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 19:10:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's something mildly interesting: Israel's [worst ever defeat](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Israel_national_football_team) in soccer was 7-1 against Germany. The exact same scoreline and opponent as Brazil's recent humiliation in the world cup, to which the Israeli gentleman was referring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 17:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, his imitation isn't bad. Needs more tongue out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Neymar's brain activity while playing is less than 10% of the level of amateur players, suggesting he plays as if on auto-pilot, according to a study by Japanese neurologists. It is thought this applies to all elite players. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 17:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Neymar's brain activity while playing is less than 10% of the level of amateur players, suggesting he plays as if on auto-pilot, according to a study by Japanese neurologists. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 16:57:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The bacterium E. coli can build complex 3D formations out of the salt from dried salt water. They hibernate in these. When they are rehydrated, the bacteria are revived. There are implications for the search for extraterrestrial life. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 16:38:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 20:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd bet the farm that the NHL is the least provincial by this metric. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 16:45:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  10 crew members were onboard. 9 were killed in the crash except the Navigator, 2nd Lt Wallace F. Kaufman. He was captured by the Japanese and executed. 

Sobering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 16:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This needs to be higher. FGM is only widespread in Africa and has little to do with radical Islam. I hate ISIS with a passion, to put it mildly, but this story doesn't make much sense. I'll believe it when they themselves publicize it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MH17 victims' mobile phones 'answered by others'. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 16:33:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Chile has a civilian town in Antarctica, complete with a school, hospital, hostel, post office, internet, TV and mobile phone coverage. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-22 21:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-22 16:18:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And that's what you're made of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 23:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Commander Glum

You can't make this stuff up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 22:40:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To paraphrase Hitchens: give that guy an enema and you can bury him in a matchbox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 16:39:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The pilot who shot down the plane [gave an interview late last year](http://www.globalpost.com/dispatch/news/kyodo-news-international/131224/ex-pilot-says-he-performed-duty-shooting-down-s-korea-). He says he was following orders and has frequent nightmares about the incident, but these parts stand out, there are many coping mechanisms for the unthinkable or inexplicable:

  But some Russians still believe no passengers were on board on the Korean Air Lines' jumbo, including Osipovich's wife Lyudmila.

 Lyudmila, 67, told Kyodo News that her husband did nothing wrong, claiming the United States has woven a false story and that no passengers were on board.

 But Osipovich said he saw only the South Korean plane and no U.S. military planes, and that he is sure there were passengers on the plane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 00:27:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I imagine the flight data recorder could in theory be used to determine the *direction* of the missile's impact, based on tiny differences in the times certain components failed. If this is the case, it could be very incriminating when combined with known locations of any surface to air missile sites in the area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-17 19:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here is an [AN-26](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antonov_An-26). Can they be that stupid to confuse this with a 777? Apparently so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-17 18:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can find it at /r/undelete </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-17 18:08:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glenn Greenwald lives in Rio, you can add him if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-17 18:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are Brazilians of every skin color you can think of. This comment is absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 21:32:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was some kind of promising [news](http://www.sciencealert.com.au/news/20141706-25695.html) on this recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 21:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's equally terrifying is the dental bill afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have genetically engineered a worm that cannot get drunk after ingesting alcohol. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 17:23:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Journals weigh up double-blind peer review </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 16:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-15 18:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It wouldn't have been a problem if the reporter was from a real state like New England. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-15 18:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, it's Russia. [This](http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-iv55gja6ulI/U8O0eaeYJmI/AAAAAAAAEls/X8OgFJyYKsE/s1600/hail.gif) can happen at any time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-11 18:38:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  What year is this, 1975?

I said almost exactly the same thing when watching it. It was back to the days before we knew the dangers associated with this kind of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-11 16:32:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's a little more background on this fella.](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2662232/Football-fan-Carl-Wenz-caught-apparently-exchanging-phone-numbers-pretty-Brazilian.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The ability of geckos to grip to surfaces may be due to electrical forces, according to a new study. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-10 16:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that there is a humorous running observation in Russia that their leaders alternate between bald-headed and hairy-headed. This pattern can be traced back to 1825. Their current leader is in the bald position. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 07:21:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-08 22:44:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be nice to brazilans, fellow redditors. This is beyond heartreaking for them. Source: married to one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-08 19:13:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anecdotally, it seems a lot of Southeast Asians in general are fans of Germany in the WC. It's an odd thing but hey, whatever floats your boat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Doobie Brothers -- What a Fool Believes [Soft Rock] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-08 07:26:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-08 03:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its Muphry's law. FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL of Muphry's Law: When a person criticises another's editing or proofreading, there will be a mistake of a similar kind in that criticism. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-07 20:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-26 16:28:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best bit:

 the player Luis Surez is prohibited from entering the confines of any stadium during the period of the ban

[link](http://www.fifa.com/worldcup/news/y=2014/m=6/news=luis-suarez-suspended-for-nine-matches-and-banned-for-four-months-from-2386354.html)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fouad Ajami, Commentator and Expert in Arab History, Dies at 68 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 19:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-20 18:34:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even better, you can **watch** Lethal Weapon on said smartphone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-18 22:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least the Spain-Australia game can be a contest now that Tim Cahill's suspended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-18 01:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This information is a week old and is not news to anyone who has been following the story of the WC in the slightest. Since then things have gone suprisingly well, and I'm one who suspected it *could* have been a complete disaster. It's important to have some perspective on this. There's plenty of that well down among the comments at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 19:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Redditor at the World Cup: let's head to the beach, have a caipirinha, and wait for all of this to blow over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 17:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [For those that missed the reference.](http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/26h0hl/youre_sent_to_brazil_with_5000000_cash_30_clowns/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-13 17:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deus Ex Human Revolution also needs a shout out ITT. The ambient music in Detroit and Hengsha is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists are starting to worry about 'conscious' machines. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 16:41:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-06 20:33:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *"I should buy a boat."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chimpanzees beat humans in simple contests based on game theory. Researchers believe it is because of their excellent short-term memories and talents for pattern recognition and rapid visual assessment. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-06 20:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-06 19:07:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why wasn't it called a strike? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The element bromine is found to be essential for animal life. This brings the number of elements essential for life to 28. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-05 20:25:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-03 20:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A sequel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-02 22:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alexander the Great said that this size was "the amount of wine needed by one man in one sitting to hear the voices of the gods." [Source](http://www.supplewine.com/wine101/wine-bottle-sizes/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Coral reefs are better at coping with rising sea temperatures than we thought. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-30 17:46:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-26 20:30:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Link to study.](http://rspb.royalsocietypublishing.org/content/281/1781/20133039.full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where baby sea turtles go after hatching on the east coast has been a mystery for decades. Now it is solved. They go to the centre of the Atlantic gyre, where they use seaweed for foraging and shelter. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-26 20:26:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-23 22:08:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PK Subban says hi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rare fungi from Australia. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-23 21:18:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have discovered the mechanism through which antidepressants create new brain cells. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-23 20:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-22 20:19:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Right here.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6R1n7pf_riE) South Koreans apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in 1964 two students attempted to kidnap the British Prime Minister. The plot was foiled when he offered them beer. They accepted and abandoned their plot. This breach of security was only revealed in 2009. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-22 19:49:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in 1964 a group of students attempted to kidnap the British Prime Minister. The plot was foiled when he offered them beer, which they accepted, and stalled them for 10 minutes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-22 19:31:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> E-cigarettes boost quitting success among smokers, study finds. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 17:14:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that pineapples don't grow on trees. They grow on the ground. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-11 04:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The convergent evolution of eyes in humans and squids occured via modification of the same ancestral gene. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-06 16:35:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that 27 U.S. states are at least partially north of the southernmost part of Canada. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-05 19:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-04 07:26:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No critique necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in South Asia widowed women were once routinely burned alive on their husbands' funeral pyres. A British general outlawed it, saying "This burning of widows is your custom; prepare the funeral pile... But my nation has also a custom. When men burn women alive we hang them." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-04 04:12:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Twitter blows up with racist reactions after black hockey player scores game winning goal. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-02 17:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-01 06:30:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What I found most surprising was the hippopotamus, they kill 500 each year, more than the shark, wolf and lion combined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-01 04:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Perfect time to bring out this instant classic.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RUY6lDja-DE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-29 19:40:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This guy](http://www.jimmo.org/hippopotamus-milk-is-not-pink/) says hippo milk is NOT pink. Field research is required. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that there are ancient naturally occuring nuclear fission reactors in Africa. They were discovered in mines in Gabon in 1972. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-29 17:48:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Kim Jong Il would order his staff to inspect every grain of rice that was to be cooked for him. Chipped and defective grains were discarded and only those with perfect form were kept. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-24 02:18:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-22 22:09:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Paper here.](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/v7/n3/full/ngeo2098.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-22 19:58:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If the first thing you do after arming a grenade is put it in your mouth, you're gonna have a bad time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the term "hipster" originated in the 1940s, and was used to describe jazz afficionados, characterized by their "dress, slang, use of cannabis and other drugs, relaxed attitude, sarcastic humor, self-imposed poverty and relaxed sexual codes." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-22 18:32:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Volcanos act as air-conditioning for a warming world: eruptions between 2000 and 2012 have helped slow the pace of global warming, according to work published in Nature Geoscience. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-22 16:48:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 19:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It also has grappling hooks. [This article](http://www.nature.com/news/female-insect-uses-spiky-penis-to-take-charge-1.15064) from Nature includes this gruesome tidbit:

 When researchers tried to pull apart two mating insects, the female was gripping so tightly that the male was accidentally ripped in half, leaving his genitalia still attached to the female.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 00:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It also depends on the amount wanted. 25 grams of the L-glucose is $1565, way less than 25 times the price of 1 gram. For these amounts the "50% more expensive" stat will be more accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-15 22:28:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems about right. You can buy a gram of L-glucose [here](http://www.sigmaaldrich.com/catalog/product/sigma/g5500?lang=en region=US) for $84.90. Gold is currently $42 a gram, so yeah at least 50% more than gold by weight.

Google tells me that there are 39 grams of sugar in a can of coke, so a can of left handed coke would cost over $3300.


^(edit: to all those pointing out that 84 is 100% more than 42: this post is intended as a back-of-the-envelope sanity check on the information in the post title. Hence "at least". Many factors can influence the relative costs, including the amount and source of L-glucose, as has been pointed out in comments.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-15 20:58:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm noticing a distinct lack of empty Doritos packets and beer cans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that some species of ants cultivate fungi, much like humans farm crops as a food source. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-15 20:51:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-14 22:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pakistan and India are still in the Commonwealth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-14 21:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was really surprised at this but [it is true](http://www.aboutmyvote.co.uk/who_can_register_to_vote.aspx):

 You can register to vote if you are: 16 years old or over and a British citizen or an Irish, qualifying Commonwealth or European Union citizen who is resident in the UK

They have to be a **resident** of the UK though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-11 21:58:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, they *are* the champions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-11 20:12:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They've got more chance of summoning a Daedra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-11 19:51:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  During the trip, Koepcke could not sleep at night due to numerous insect bites, which became infected. After nine days, several spent floating downstream, she found a boat moored near a shelter, where she found the boat's motor and fuel tank. Relying again on her father's advice, Koepcke poured gasoline on her wounds, which succeeded in removing thirty-five maggots from one arm

Thanks Dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-10 15:51:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Smart family that one. The other daughter [Eve](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/%C3%88ve_Curie) is the only one not to get a Nobel Prize, but she did write the best known biography of her mother and won the National Book Award, and her husband happened to pick up the Nobel Peace Prize.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-10 02:30:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably the result of an Occupy Greenland movement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-09 22:07:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a day-night cycle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-09 20:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are some great photos of abandoned buildings on this island [here](http://kingstonlounge.blogspot.ca/2008/08/hart-island.html). Also, google the nearby North Brother Island for a creepy abandoned hospital, if you like that kind of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-09 20:29:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Australia they even call some seafood "bugs". [Moreton Bay Bugs, Balmain Bugs etc.](http://www.sydneyfishmarket.com.au/FISHline/SpeciesInfo/Bugs/tabid/210/Default.aspx) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-07 19:19:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A corn cob *hanging on a string for re-use*, no less. Makes you appreciate the little things we take for granted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-05 22:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Note to amateur chemists: you don't need to put the silly putty in alcohol for it to become flammable, in case OP's post title confused you as it did me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-05 18:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I imagine similar reactions will occur in North Korea one day, when someone denounces the Kim dynasty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-05 15:37:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The story has since been denied by Chinese spokesman Rong Ping.

^(edit: thanks so much!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-04 22:34:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Link to study [here](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/embj.201488411/abstract). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new world of "micropeptides" glimpsed: genes once thought to be non-coding actually give rise to small proteins. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-04 22:29:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Liberia reports suspected Ebola outbreak unconnected to Guinea </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-03 20:48:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-03 20:35:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Further discussion in [this thread.](http://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/224d3g/til_that_its_common_during_tv_showings_of/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that during World War II, members of the Waffen-SS would have their blood type letters tattooed on their arm. Following the war, these tattoos helped identify former members, leading to their prosecution and in some cases their execution. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-03 19:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-31 21:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I saw that too. Some things can not be unread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-31 19:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Welcome to Winnipeg!](http://cdn2.sbnation.com/imported_assets/1020281/52332465_41206d89e4.jpg)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 23:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ITT: antiverts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 21:33:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit: satisfying the needs of ambiverts since 2005! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 19:57:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All voices were impersonated... poorly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 19:35:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm curious about the "Harvey Hotel" and "Lakeview Hotel" near Lachine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 18:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Portuguese to english translation (via google with some formatting) for the lazy...

**Cetaceans, sex and sea serpents**

In 1741 the missionary Hans Egede published the report of a "terrible monster" seen at sea near the coast of Greenland. Accompanied by an illustration of himself which you can see below, would become a particularly famous story in the collection of stories about "sea snakes".

Over the centuries, various explanations have been suggested to the event, like the sailors might have seen a giant squid (Architeuthis) with a raised tentacles confused with a tail.
But Charles Paxton, University of Saint Andrews in England recently suggested a more interesting hypothesis. Paxton has received the Ig Nobel biology prize in 2002 for his study on the procession of excited to British farmers ostriches, so it's not so surprising that one of the ideas outlined by scientist to explain the story of Egede is that sailors have seen a whale penis.

Yes, a male whale of a species unknown to mariners, excited for some reason and taking his erect member - which can reach almost two meters long - confused by the tail of a sea serpent .One image, however, may be worth more than the past thirty-five words:

The suggestion is serious, and is contained in a paper published in the journal Archives of Natural History, "Cetaceans, fri   sea serpents: an analysis of the Egede accounts of a Most Dreadful Monster seen off the coast of Greenland in 1734".
At work, Paxton together with Erik Knatterud and Sharon Hedley, discusses thoughtfully:

*We do not have "absolute confidence" in our interpretation of the creature Egede. Nor are we suggesting that whale cocks are a universal source of marine sightings of snakes, although we believe that another sighting, the merchant ship Pauline in 1875 when a sea serpent as a White pillar? of views between various sperm? frantic with excitement? (Heuvelmans 1968; Oudemans, 1892), could be a mistake of this nature (penis sperm whales can be white (Harrison, 1938)) .In the case of Egedes, we assume that the use of facsimile snake and drawings were not completely accurate. If they were accurate, then the strongest objection to the interpretation of whale sighting Egede is evident the presence of teeth in the drawing.*

*Our explanation also assumes that the witnesses would not have recognized the penis of a whale and that some species exhibit their penises in the summer of Greenland. Hans Egede (1741 ,1745) described the great Manhood a whale but Egedes may not have realized that he could be seen at sea.*

*Despite these objections, even if the monster was an unknown species, characteristics suggest a cetacean diagnosed. In the end, we will never know for sure. Whatever Poul Egede had seen that day, be a loving whale, a whale without a tail or an unknown species, was a very unusual sight both then and today.*

Which brings us to another fascinating image comparing frightening medieval illustrations with casual pictures whales wildly excited. The first image of a whale penis in this note comes from this site, and second, this. You can also watch the video of a terrifying encounter with sea serpents fighting with whales, whales mating confused with this link . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 18:31:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shot through the heart

And you're to blame

[You give love a bad name](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LiB6Y8LM71k) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 18:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of the Truman Show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Guinea's ebola outbreak has spread to its capital, Conakry. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-27 21:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-26 20:31:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG this gets reposted like, weekly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-24 17:52:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From the [Seattle Post Intelligencer](http://www.seattlepi.com/news/us/article/No-signs-of-life-after-huge-Washington-landslide-5343142.php#photo-6062864):

Of the 49 structures in the neighborhood hit by the slide, authorities believe at least 25 were occupied full-time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-21 20:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It may include rural areas/towns outside of Paris and such places as the Palace of Versailles, though. I'd be surprised if it didn't actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-21 03:35:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/science ... the sub which deletes any kind of joke but allows sensationalist tabloid style titles that would make Rupert Murdoch blush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-20 23:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's Montreal night on reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-20 22:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If only they did a similar one on the other side of the street, replacing that buffalo ad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-20 22:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [The guys who did it](http://www.ashop.ca/) all have a "street art" background, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-20 15:57:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. The fact that more planes and ships are being sent there suggests that there is quite a lot of confidence in the satellite images, and that they are probably at a much higher resolution than those that we are seeing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-20 15:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, [numerous instances](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Convergent_evolution). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A fish that lives at depths of 800 to 1000 meters has a previously unknown type of eye. It is cylindrical and can look up to detect objects against the dim light, and also below to detect bioluminescent flashes from deep-sea creatures. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-20 13:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 19:25:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I'm Gladiator Shepardus and this is my favorite store in the Forum." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 18:09:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure there would be a *lot* of books and TV shows about it if that were the case. It would be one of the biggest unsolved mysteries ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in 1978 a lone pilot flying in Australia reported to air traffic control that he was being accompanied by an aircraft above him. Asked to identify the aircraft, he radioed "It isn't an aircraft". His plane disappeared and has never been found. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 17:53:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 17:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As someone pointed out in a thread about this last week it's probably a case of [Hanlon's razor](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hanlon%27s_razor):

"Never attribute to malice that which is adequately explained by stupidity."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-18 17:28:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Flogging for revealing eyebrows? Something tells me they **really** wouldn't approve of that American Apparel ad on the side of the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-18 16:56:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The emblem of the program is a Dungeons and Dragons style drawing of a wizard in purple robes holding a staff that appears to hold an older model cell-phone. [Really, take a look](http://apps.washingtonpost.com/g/page/world/nsa-symbolizes-data-collection-program-with-wizard/880/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-15 01:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Air Crash Investigations or Unsolved Mysteries, one of the two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 23:41:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Seven days after the jets disappearance, Malaysian authorities have shared few details with American investigators, frustrating senior officials in Washington. Theyre keeping us at a distance, one of the officials said.

What the heck are they hiding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 22:15:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a New Zealand study. I wonder if they ordered a Filet-O-Fush to go along with those chups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 18:42:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, this has been denied by the Malaysian authorities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 17:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slightly off-topic but interesting: one of these islands is [North Sentinel Island](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/North_Sentinel_Island), home to a group of people who have had virutally no contact with the outside world and are hostile to any attempt at contact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 17:12:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the kind of inflation that raises interest rates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 21:36:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OK, well best get the characters to wear green for St. Patrick's day on game day three then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 17:19:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If not jail time. The thing is, this prank was so popular that it was later featured in an ad campaign by Alaska Airlines. I don't see this kind of thing happening today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 16:49:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is much more information on this [here](http://www.museumofhoaxes.com/hoax/af_database/permalink/the_eruption_of_mount_edgecumbe/), including a pic of Mr. Bikar's trollface. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-12 18:21:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I *still* did that knowing full well that it's a gif! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-12 17:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Marrying a nine year old girl?! Never heard of such a thing! Oh wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-11 20:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I take it from the article and the fact that you have "spoken at length with Mr. Taylor in the past" that he was frequently in the jail. Is this correct? Was he well known to the staff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Self-controlled crows pass the 'marshmallow test': they resist the temptation to eat a food if they know a tastier treat is coming later. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-11 16:40:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-08 04:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately, (tragically), this looks like the first time a 777 has crashed, 20 years after their introduction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-06 22:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Joel: Hugh Jackman

Tess: Carrie-Anne Moss

Rob Ford can play the bloaters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-05 22:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grossly misleading headline. [Here](http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/achenblog/wp/2014/03/05/is-nasa-really-going-to-send-a-probe-to-europa/) is more discussion on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-05 21:37:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Although the bleeding by the doctors can't have helped in this case, before antibiotics people did die from "sore throats", if they were caused by an abscess on the tonsil, or quinsy as it used to be called. They can grow so big that they choke the victim to death. Even now it can require emergency treatment in the ER. (source: personal experience) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-05 19:13:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or ACIV OCD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A device that delivers an orgasm at the push of a button has been patented in the US. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-04 23:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When a mathematician views a pleasing formula, a part of the brain associated with emotional responses to visual and musical beauty is activated, according to fMRI studies. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-04 21:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-03 22:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sir, you deserve to reap Karma for your appropriate Capitalisation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-03 22:36:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but SHE'S ALL ALOOONE SAAH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-03 21:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The story has a happy ending though: a visa-free travel agreement is in place, which must be a relief for both of the regular travelers between the two countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-03 19:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did they know it was a Roman girl? The article says the skeleton was found "among other Roman remains", but couldn't it have been the remains of a slave? Maybe some jewelry identified it as Roman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-27 16:32:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If this doesn't get rid of the average Joe's apathy on these matters then I truly don't know what will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Water has been detected on an exoplanet, opening a new chapter in the search for alien life. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-26 18:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-19 20:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, Kleptoposty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-19 19:23:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cantonese hip hop FTW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-19 19:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually, it's a [pretty hot field of research](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Algae_fuel) right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-14 00:25:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They do remove them. [Here](http://psych.cornell.edu/sites/default/files/Medvec.Madey_.Gilo_.pdf) is a non-paywalled copy of the original study (PDF). See the right side of page 605. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-13 21:47:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It turns out that they were aware that this kind of format could skew the results in the [original study](http://psycnet.apa.org/journals/psp/69/4/603.html), so they removed those type of sports where there are gold medal/bronze medal matches from the analysis and still got similar results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-13 19:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I guess the third place finisher can be full of "what if"s too, but in the opposite direction. i.e. "What if I hadn't done that turn so well, and missed out on the bronze!". Hence, feeling better in the situation than the silver medalist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-13 17:48:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may have to eat your words. This has a fighting chance of making the front page! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-13 16:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, [panspermia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Panspermia). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that by analyzing the faces of Olympic medalists after their events, a peer-reviewed study found that silver medalists feel worse, on average, than bronze medalists. Silver medalists feel unlucky, while bronze medalists feel lucky. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-13 16:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-11 20:28:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good guy Garrus. 

Calibrates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-11 19:30:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Context](http://www.businessinsider.com/cross-country-skier-given-ski-2014-2).

TL;DR: The Russian's ski broke. The Canadian coach ran out and gave him a replacement. High fives all round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Clint Eastwood saves PGA tournament director from choking with the Heimlich maneuver. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-07 20:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kazakh leader may drop the "stan" from Kazakhstan. Alternative name for the country is Kazakh Eli. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-07 20:11:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-07 03:09:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Palindromes are a subset of emordnilaps. (edit: spelling) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that when a whale dies and its carcass falls into the Bathyal or Abyssal zone of the ocean floor, it can sustain a complex localized ecosystem of deep-sea organisms for decades. This is called a "whale fall". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-06 19:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is the Chiliad mural a guide for completing the main story missions in a specific order? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 18:04:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are 69 story missions in GTA5. Here is a useful guide to them all:

http://gta.wikia.com/Missions_in_GTA_V

As we know, the order of most of these is optional. You can choose Michael, Trevor or Franklin (or sometimes a combination of the three) before each is begun. Of course, some can only be completed in order, such as the prologue and the ones involving Franklin at the beginning of the story. 

Let's make a very conservative estimate that only 30 of these missions are of the type that can be started in an optional order, and that there is a choice of only 2 before each. Then, there are

2 to the power 30 = 1073741824  **1 billion** ways to complete GTA5, depending on the order of missions.

What if the big easter eggs we would all like to see required someone to complete the story with one specific order of missions? Wouldn't that be the kind of elaborate puzzle that rewarded true fans, which Rockstar is likely to set up?

The chance of someone already finishing the game in the correct order yet is miniscule, and Rockstar needs to leave an elaborate clue about the order required. What in the game looks like it could provide those clues? **The Chiliad Mural**.

This post is an extension of the ideas started in this thread started by /u/Notaredditr from a few days ago:

http://www.reddit.com/r/chiliadmystery/comments/1wny24/my_mural_theorya_hunter_never_really_stops/

Basically, the lines and glyphs in the mural are a represntation of the GTA5 main story. the ufo is Michael, the egg is Franklin and the jetpack is Trevor. Thankfully the mural is to the right of this post, so you can follow along. Now, here are the key pieces of evidence that this whacky theory may be true and why I believe it should be investigated further:

* the line joining the ufo and the jetpack is the Prologue, because it is at the bottom of the mural and only Michale and Trevor are involved in it. As the story progresses, we go up the mural.

* After the Prologue, we start with Franklin (the egg). He goes up the first middle line, turns left, and eventually meets Michael (the ufo). Then they both come to the first heist, the Jewel Store Job, the first red X. Only those two are involved with that.

* The other red Xs are other heists. I come to the final heist in a bit.

* There are 4 lines which seem to leave the main set of lines, two of which even leave the "mountain" on the mural. These could represent the trip to North Yankton and Did Someone say Yoga, where Michael literally leaves the story, for a while.

* There are 6 heists in GTA5 but only 5 red Xs. The final heist is the eye at the top of the mural, representing the end of the story. What about the 5 lines on top of the eye and the two below? Well, after the final heist you can either kill Michael or Trevor. Those are the two lines below. In the Third Way, the five lines represent the first fight plus the 4 people you have to assassinate in that mission.

How does this relate to completing the missions in a specific order? I believe a good place to start thinking about this is to "travel" along the lines in the mural *which cover the shortest possible distance*. Beyond that, I believe someone with more familiarity with the "mission tree" of GTA5 might be able to identify more parts of the mural's lines, in order to confirm or debunk this theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-03 20:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Update: the man who was shot has died.

http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/montreal/man-dies-after-police-shooting-outside-montreal-bus-station-1.2521309 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: If oil only accounts for less than 5% of Dubai / United Arab Emirates economy, where else does their wealth come from? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-01 15:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-31 23:52:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah you do indeed. My bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-31 23:34:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I should point out that under this theory, the line underneath connecting M/ufo and T/jetpack would certainly represent the prologue, since these two are involved in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-31 21:22:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right, is it possible to complete the main storyline by "traversing" the lines in the mural with this idea of M/UFO, F/Egg and T/jetpack in a way that makes any sense? Perhaps by covering the shortest possible distance? This doesn't preclude some big payoff at the end. After all, it's "not how you won or lost, but how you played the game". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-31 20:40:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OK I'll bite. Could the Xs represent the heists? The first heist, Jewel Store Job, involves only Michael (UFO) and Franklin (Egg), it would be the X on the lower left, most connected to the UFO and Egg. The second last heist (Bureau Raid) also only involves these two, it would be the X on the upper left. The other three heists (Merryweather, Blitz Play and Paleto Score) involve all three characters, and could be the three Xs on the right. The final heist (Big Score) could be represented by the eye at the top, which represents the end of the story. "Come back when your story is complete". The lines in between these could represent the paths of the characters in between the heists, i.e. the intervening missions. Therefore the mural could be a graphical representation of the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-31 18:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most trusted **and** least trusted, according to that poll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-30 21:46:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of questions in that article, but what I'd really like to know is: how much of this ends up in the Toronto mayor's office? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-30 20:52:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, his death penalty was applied proactively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-30 20:41:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looking it up because I was curious, [there have been 37 Federal executions](http://www.deathpenaltyinfo.org/federal-executions-1927-2003), and only three since 1963, one of those being for Timothy McVeigh.

Edit: OP's article gives more info on this as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-30 20:25:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either that or the person who retrieved the samples for testing was a smoker with a cocaine habit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thyroid cancer cells become less aggresive in outer space. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-30 16:36:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-28 22:56:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Belgium: Come on vacation, leave upon cremation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-28 22:45:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More on that law:

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cidade_Limpa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-28 20:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think... THINK.. he might have been taking the piss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in 2006, all outdoor advertisements were banned in Sao Paulo, Brazil. Within a year, 15000 billboards were taken down in South America's largest city. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-28 18:52:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-28 18:35:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's why they call the Olympic Stadium there "The Big Owe". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A species of leech can survive storage in liquid nitrogen for 24 hours, as well as long-term storage at temperatures as low as 90C for up to 32 months. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-27 19:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-23 04:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I blame Bieber. He tweeted her a couple hours ago. The whole ridiculous circus must be a distraction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-17 20:28:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're talking about Pope **Benedict** here, in case there is any confusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The genome of the Locust (Locusta migratoria) is the largest animal genome sequenced to date, at 6.5 gigabytes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-17 18:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-16 18:40:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Possibly relevant](http://www.nbcnews.com/science/alcohol-space-da-6C10403671). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Identifyable images of bystanders can be extracted from the reflections in the eye. This could be applied by analyzing photographs of crime victims, whose eyes may be reflecting their perpetrators. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-16 16:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL there is a bubble gum pink colored lake in Western Australia. The cause of its color has not been proven, but may be due to microorganisms living in the water. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-13 18:54:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> More than 180 different species of glowing fish have been discovered, in the first comprehensive survey of marine biofluorescence. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-10 21:32:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that some people greatly dislike the herb coriander (cilantro), saying that it it smells like soap and tastes like crushed bugs. This reaction has been linked to a set of genes in the human genome. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-10 18:59:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-10 18:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The study referenced in the article is [here](http://brit.org/webfm_send/455). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 100 million-year-old flowers found trapped in amber in Burma represent the earliest evidence of sexual reproduction in flowering plants. They are also from a new genus of plants. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-10 18:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-07 21:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a discriminatory practice. Male sailors should also be extended this opportunity where the need exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-07 20:30:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Checked for /r/cloudporn. Yep, it exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL the first hard disk drive, released in 1956, could store 3.75 megabytes of data. It weighed over a ton, had to be moved around with forklifts, and was delivered via large cargo airplanes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-06 20:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that there is a species of fungus from the Amazon that feeds on plastic. It can live on plastic alone, and can do so without oxygen, potentially leading to new techniques for bioremediation. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-20 02:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The life expectancy of HIV-positive adults in America today is nearing that of the general population. According to a new study, a 20-year-old adult in the U.S. or Canada who is receiving antiretroviral therapy can be expected to live into his or her early 70s. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-19 19:03:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-19 18:49:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He really is the gift that keeps on giving. People can't wait to hear what he will say next. Kinda like Pope Francis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An entirely new data compression method has been created by UCLA researchers. It outperforms existing algorithms, such as JPEG for images. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-19 16:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: Why do dimples on golf balls allow them to travel further? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-19 01:03:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would seem that they would increase wind resistance rather than decrease it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why do the dimples on golf balls allow it to fly further? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-19 00:53:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would seem that it would increase resistance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New species of tapir discovered in south-west Amazon. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-17 18:39:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-16 19:46:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing gets deleted from the internet. Just ask Beyonce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists "incredibly concerned" about the fate of bananas as plagues and fungal infections spread across the world's supplies. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-16 19:29:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-16 19:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once Winston Churchill was accused of being drunk in Parliament by a woman MP. His response: 

"I may be drunk, Miss, but in the morning I will be sober and you will still be ugly." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This sub when the mystery is solved. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-16 17:45:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in Spanish-speaking countries, Tuesday the 13th is considered unlucky, not Friday. And in Italy, Friday the 17th is considered unlucky, not the 13th. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-13 18:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-13 18:29:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kids used to drink [small beer](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Small_beer) all the time, before public sanitation. It's probably no worse than Ritalin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in 1662 a horse-drawn public bus service was launched in Paris by philosopher/mathematician Blaise Pascal. It was initially a success, but fare increases meant it was restricted to the very rich, and it folded. No similar services were known until the 1820s. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-13 17:22:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-13 00:23:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a good point, perhaps the phrase "transcription factor *recognition* site" should have been used, as is done in the abstract of the article, instead of "binding site". However I am not familiar with the distinction between the two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-13 00:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That abstract is from an accompanying perspective article. The abstract of the actual paper in question is here:

 Exonic Transcription Factor Binding Directs Codon Choice and Affects Protein Evolution

 Genomes contain both a genetic code specifying amino acids and a regulatory code specifying transcription factor (TF) recognition sequences. We used genomic deoxyribonuclease I footprinting to map nucleotide resolution TF occupancy across the human exome in 81 diverse cell types. We found that ~15% of human codons are dual-use codons (duons) that simultaneously specify both amino acids and TF recognition sites. Duons are highly conserved and have shaped protein evolution, and TF-imposed constraint appears to be a major driver of codon usage bias. Conversely, the regulatory code has been selectively depleted of TFs that recognize stop codons. More than 17% of single-nucleotide variants within duons directly alter TF binding. Pervasive dual encoding of amino acid and regulatory information appears to be a fundamental feature of genome evolution.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-12 21:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It does. The research article is [here](https://www.sciencemag.org/content/342/6164/1367.full) and says that [codons](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Genetic_code), the three-letter codes in our DNA that stand for an amino acid in protein synthesis, can **simultaneously** code for an amino acid **and** a transcription factor binding site. [Transcription factors](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transcription_factor) control the expression of genes, i.e. turning them on or off. These dual-use codons, or "duons" as they have called them, represent the "second code" that OP's article is talking about. Even though I only just read it, it looks like a big deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-12 21:10:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, and it seems that codon bias - the observed preference of some redundant codons over others - may be explained by these "duons", which would be one of the major findings of this paper from a molecular evolution angle. From the abstract:

 Duons are highly conserved and have shaped protein evolution, and TF-imposed constraint appears to be a major driver of codon usage bias.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-12 20:48:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The research article is [here](https://www.sciencemag.org/content/342/6164/1367.full). As mentioned in OP's link, it seems that some codons (of which there are 64 in the standard [genetic code](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Genetic_code)), can simultaneously encode an amino acid and a transcription factor binding site. [Transcription factors](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transcription_factor), put very crudely, control how genes are turned on or off. The discovery of these codons with dual use, hence the term "duons", is very interesting.
(edit: spelling) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A European consortium is developing a device which will enable police to halt cars by pulsing radio waves in their direction. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-12 16:16:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-10 23:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For those looking to emigrate to Liechtenstein, bad news, you actually have to live there for **30 years** before you can apply for citizenship. If you want to apply before the 30 years is up, a vote can be taken by the community of residence, however: 

 Final acceptance also requires consent from the Liechtenstein parliament and granting of citizenship by the Prince

which sounds cool. It's all in this [official guide](http://www.llv.li/pdf-llv-scg-broschuere.englisch.pdf) (PDF, page 25.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that every county in the world is either entirely or partially north of Uruguay. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-10 17:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Putin dissolves state news agency, tightens grip on Russian media. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-09 17:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that there are some plants in Australia that live their entire lives underground. They even flower underground, never seeing the sun. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-08 02:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-08 01:14:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If this is the games industry and its media's attempt at revolutionizing awards shows, the revolution will not be televised, or streamed, or happen next year hopefully. How pathetic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-06 22:03:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of time would be spent in the bathroom, that's for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-06 20:40:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why block the hospital? I guess there could be radioactive material still on the people's clothes, pockets, so it's probably a precautionary measure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-05 06:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was skeptical, but here is an archived report from 1979 about these twins:

http://www.people.com/people/archive/article/0,,20073583,00.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL the US Navy maintains a research vessel that is designed to be capsized vertically. As a result, most rooms on it have two doors: one to use when the ship is horizontal, another when vertical. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 22:03:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 20:05:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. Good to have confirmation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There won't be an ice village at Parc Jean-Drapeau this winter. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 19:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 19:32:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP tells a good story, but nowhere in the link does it go exactly as described. Maybe there's a video somewhere where it does, would be fun to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 17:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Help me, why is OP's link to the editing section of the wiki page?

Edit: it's a common repost: http://www.reddit.com/submit?url=http%3A%2F%2Fen.wikipedia.org%2Fwiki%2FAladdin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weird but awesome! Survival mode is the most fun. Story mode can be challenging, especially the final boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:02:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A google image search for "Roman sling bullets" reveals [this](http://homepages.gac.edu/~panciera/roman_sling_bullets2.jpg). I can't translate the Latin, but the one on the lower right is understandable in anyone's language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-03 18:49:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The same thing happened with the Food Network. It used to be about recipes and cooking, now it's mostly game shows. (edit: and Guy Fieri). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-02 22:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a split second where you can tell he's thinking "Why dont I just eat it?". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mushrooms can create a slight breeze to spread their spores even if the air is calm. They release water vapour, cooling the air and creating a convective current that gets the air moving, carrying spores away from the parent. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-29 17:47:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-29 17:26:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently they have been taking guns to space for decades (e.g. [this one](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/TP-82)). The idea was for self protection in the wilderness after re-entry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that there are usually one or two handguns on board the International Space Station. They belong to the Russians but are kept in an unlocked survival kit. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-29 17:20:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that most of the walk buttons at NYC intersections serve no purpose. They are "placebo buttons" and do not make a walk signal occur faster. Any benefit from them is only imagined. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 21:22:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-27 19:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The movie must have made an impression. From Reagan's 1986 State of the Union address:

"Never has there been a more exciting time to be alive, a time of rousing wonder and heroic achievement. As they said in the film Back to the Future, 'Where we're going, we don't need roads'."

([source](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Back_to_the_Future#Legacy)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-26 19:17:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are some pretty impressive pictures of them [in this thread](http://www.28dayslater.co.uk/forums/european-international-sites/5921-diy-guide-your-own-supervillain-hideout-aka-tailrace-tunnel-niagara.html).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Long-term unemployment is associated with shorter telomeres - a biomarker of premature aging - in 31 year old men. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-22 20:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 17:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes DNA is still fragmented and assembled with PacBio's own proprietary assembly software HGAP. The advantage of SMRT is much longer read lengths (thousands of bases) compared to Illumina for example (50-150 bases). Despite the lower base calling accuracy of SMRT (although I hear the accuracy is getting better all the time) the longer read length helps with assembly greatly, and I can say from personal experience that this gives some *very* promising preliminary results for genome sequencing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 02:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For clarity, it should be also noted that these technologies are just different ways of sequencing sequence fragments. No matter how long they are, especially for SMRT, they still need to be computationally assembled to recover an entire chromosome, for instance. Until someone can rapidly sequence an entire chromosome linearly from start to end, it is still "shotgun sequencing". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 01:37:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OK, perhaps in the future, but there's no way these technologies are routinely used for genome sequencing now, especially novel genomes, which was my initial point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 00:58:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh? All next generation sequencing technologies sequence short random fragments of a larger DNA (or RNA, now) molecule, which are then assembled in silico to recover the larger sequence they came from. This is the essence of shotgun sequencing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 23:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP's link is explicitly about the project resulting in the first draft human genome, which finished in 2000. The X prize didn't start until 2006. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 22:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is partly due to competition from Celera Genomics, Craig Venter's private company, whose improved method, shotgun sequencing, is now routinely used for genome sequencing. This article doesn't seem to mention this at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in Georgia there is an airtight room, sealed in 1940, called the Crypt of Civilization. It contains numerous artifacts documenting what life was like at the time of sealing, and is scheduled to be opened in the year AD 8113. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 20:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 'Comet of the century' brightens as it nears the Sun. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 17:40:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 17:11:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> St Patrick's Day on a Sunday every year? Sold! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I have a confession to make. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 04:25:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 21:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [How I imagine OP](http://imgur.com/vMIv2gj) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Comet ISON is now visible to the naked eye. It could become so bright that it can be seen in the daytime. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 19:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Astronomers surprised by large space rock less dense than water. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 19:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Thomas Jefferson was the most multilingual President of the US. In addition to English, he was fluent in Greek, Latin, French, Italian and Spanish. There is also evidence he studied Arabic, Gaelic and Welsh. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 03:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 01:31:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  In a 1986 paper, Brindley injected 17 different drugs into his own penis and measured the effects. The most successful dose resulted in an erection lasting 44 hours, well beyond the 4 hour limit after which Pfizer recommends you seek immediate medical assistance. 

Now there's dedication to science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 23:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shhh.... they don't follow the trend and have separate words for the fruit and the color, afaik, please correct me if wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 23:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of the most radical and abrupt shifts in healthcare policy ever enacted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 21:52:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  An ISIS spokesman, Omar al-Qahtani, confirmed that Mr Fares had been injured and, thinking he had been captured by members of a Shia militia against which he was fighting, asked them to kill him in terms misunderstood by the ISIS members in fact taking him to hospital. 

Am I the only one having trouble understanding what this paragraph is saying? The guy thought he had been captured by enemies, and so asked them to kill him?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 20:48:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fun facts: oranges (the fruits) are called literally "Apples from China" in Eastern European languages and "Portugals" in Greek and Middle Eastern languages ([source](http://mapsontheweb.zoom-maps.com/image/66276524834)) and I'm pretty sure that most of them call the color orange the same, and for the same reason.

edit: very surprising amount of downvotes - I'm sorry, just wanted to start a discussion on the world's different words for orange, both the fruit and the color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 19:23:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> AMA request: Andy Kaufman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-13 21:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they might be off a bit. According to wikipedia, all the gold in the world [is 9261 cubic meters](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gold). A tennis court is [10.97 m wide and 2 times 11.89 m long](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tennis_court), so has an area of 261 square meters. To get to 9261 cubic meters the tennis court would need to be filled to a depth of 9251 / 261 = 35.48 **meters**. Ahah! the old metric vs. imperial mistake strikes again. (edit: formatting and tldr)

**TL;DR** it's actually 116 feet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-13 18:18:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that would be a good explanation for Rob Ford's weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-13 17:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes it is! If you were on a boat you would never need to turn your rudder. (Assuming zero wind and ocean currents.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-13 02:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And if we just use the same units as we do here on earth, humans arrived 8 hours and 45 minutes ago, using the data from OP's link, was curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 20:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  there's no federal law that requires dates on any food except for infant formula

TIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 17:21:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This page](http://theinquisition.eu/wordpress/2011/history/jameson-cannibalism/) has a little more on the affair, including a defence from Jameson delivered posthumously, which suggests the truth of what actually happened is a little murky. James Jameson died very shortly after the incident, by the way.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The most precise measurement yet of the electron's shape shows that it is spherical, smashing hopes for new physics theories. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 20:51:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-10 21:16:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Shakespeare caused return to be made that William the Conqueror was before Richard the Third

Apparently the use of the verb "to come" as a description of orgasm is recent. [This page](http://english.stackexchange.com/questions/7949/origin-of-the-word-cum) has some info. But anyways, kudos OP it's funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Edward James Olmos was offered, but turned down, the role of Captain Picard on Star Trek, The Next Generation. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-10 07:08:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-09 06:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP would like more discussion on this please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-09 06:27:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ninja turtles were unavailable for comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-09 06:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amazing on face value but it's a recent source. OP, please post this in /r/news or /r/science or something. I'm skeptical to say the least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-09 02:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually if it was Montreal there wouldn't be any NPCs there at all. And there'd be a lot more potholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-09 00:35:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Google tells me this is an example of the [Droste effect](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Droste_effect). So, TIL again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-08 22:11:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And went on to save the galaxy from the Reaper invasion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the web page for "web page" in Wikipedia contains a screenshot of itself as an image, resulting in an infinitely recursive image. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-08 21:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-08 19:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Similar behaviour is observed in a majority of redditors seeking karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that during the American Civil War, a Confederate warship docked in Australia for repairs, and 42 Australians joined its crew. "Officers of the CSS Shenandoah later reflected that the best time of their lives were given to them by the women of Melbourne." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-08 18:52:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-08 18:16:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Today's weather will be cloudy with a chance of hamburger buns". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 18:59:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> End of an era. Relevant [video](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=26eQ3QpNB6Q). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Doobie Brothers - What a fool Believes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 07:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 04:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was the Justin Bieber of his time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that during World War II in Australia, there was a dog whose hearing was so acute that it could warn airforce personnel of incoming Japanese planes 20 minutes before they arrived, and before they showed up on radar. "Gunner" could also differentiate the sounds of allied and enemy aircraft. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 18:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-02 01:36:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not entirely clear from OP's link, but this farm is indeed the oldest business in the US, according to this rather interesting page:

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_oldest_companies_in_the_United_States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-01 20:55:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... according to an anonymous comment in the linked article. Does anyone know the true origin of this quote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in the 1960s Nintendo manufactured a toy called Ultra Hand. made of criss-crossed plastic elements that enabled its user to pick up objects. It was very successful and helped save Nintendo from serious financial difficulties. Its inventor went on to create the Game Boy. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-01 17:06:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-31 15:23:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Although this sounds cool I'm pretty skeptical about this. According to Wikipedia this was an [advertising stunt for Samsung](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Project_Space_Planes). Not one of the found planes were verified, even the ones in Germany, let alone the ones on the other side of the world. The website and their [twitter feed](https://twitter.com/spaceplanes/) haven't been updated since 2011, shortly after the launch. If planes were really found a long way away, Samsung would be publicizing the bejeezus out of this!

(Edit: grammar) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-29 16:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watch out, google tells me that this [has](http://siouxcityjournal.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/south-sioux-dog-found-tagged-with-graffiti/article_1a7e5f89-6bad-5e87-b06f-308c97143d53.html) [happened](http://www.bakersfieldcalifornian.com/local/x457515084/Owner-says-his-dog-was-tagged-with-graffiti). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists have discovered a "lost world" of unknown creatures in a rainforest perched on boulders in a remote part of Queensland, Australia. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-28 16:42:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in the mid 1990s an Australian brewery produced a "Duff beer". Because of the similarity to the beer from the Simpsons, 20th Century Fox sued the company and the beer was pulled from shelves. It since became a collectors item, and a case of the beer was sold for $13,000. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-27 22:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL there is a theory that life didn't start on Earth. Rather, life has existed throughout space since its origin. The theory is called Panspermia, and its adherents have included the great Fred Hoyle. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-26 06:00:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Atlantic hurricane season predictions fall flat. "We haven't had such such poor pre-season forecasts since the early 1990s". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-24 17:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-22 20:58:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Combine this with the [giant clouds of alcohol found floating in space](http://mentalfloss.com/article/51271/there-are-giant-clouds-alcohol-floating-space) and we've got ourselves a cocktail! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-22 19:49:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BE SURE TO CHECK OUT THE [OFFICIAL SITE](http://capslockday.com/) WHICH IS BILLY MAYS APPROVED AND WEB1.0LICIOUS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-21 20:14:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here is a link to the [original study](http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0015591). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL a Harvard study in 2010 showed that the placebo effect works even when patients know that the medicine they are taking is fake. Patients who were told before hand that they would be taking "sugar pills" responded better than than those who received no treatment at all. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-21 20:03:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL there are still 24 dial-up BBS systems in use in North America. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-17 20:42:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Too good to be true: Rhesus monkeys react negatively to better-than-expected offers. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-11 22:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that "Bizarre Foods" host Andrew Zimmern was once a homeless alcoholic and drug addict, who lived on the streets of NYC for a year. It got so bad that he sprinked a bottle of Comet Cleanser around the place so that he could sleep without the rats and roached bothering him. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-11 03:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the first recorded instance of streaking by a college student in the US was in 1804 at Lexington, Virginia. George William Crump was suspended for the remainder of the academic session, but later went on to become a US congressman. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-10 20:25:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-10 16:45:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here](http://pmj.bmj.com/content/49/569/203.short) is the original case report describing this. Again, no pics in the PDF of it. I don't think there are any pictures of this, folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that a fictional country, Val Verde, has appeared in several Hollywood movies and TV programs. It is supposedly somewhere in Latin America, and is used to avoid diplomatic disputes with real countries. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-05 05:28:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-05 04:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed. Interestingly, these plants still possess a chloroplast genome, which has been sequenced. Since chloroplasts are responsible for photosynthesis, you would think that in this species, which has literally never seen the light of day, the chloroplast genome would have been lost over time. However, Rhizanthalla still retains a tiny number (37) of genes in its plastid genome, suggesting that chloroplasts have functions beyond that of photosynthesis. Much more [here](http://www.cosmosmagazine.com/news/rare-underground-orchid-genome-unlocked/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Silk Road mastermind denies running website. "We deny all charges. That's the end of the discussion," says federal public defender in court. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-04 21:45:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-04 20:47:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> or meining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-04 20:08:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This may be an urban legend [according to Snopes](http://message.snopes.com/showthread.php?t=21023), but interesting nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in Australia, there is an orchid which grows entirely underground. It was discovered in 1928 by a farmer after he noticed a sweet smell coming from the ground. The discovery generated such excitement that a wax model was toured around the British Isles. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-04 19:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Leonardo da Vinci painting lost for centuries found in Swiss bank vault </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-04 18:06:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 21:58:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And TIL that he prefers to be addressed as "His Excellency Sheikh Professor Doctor President". [source](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/africaandindianocean/gambia/10353582/Gambia-to-leave-the-Commonwealth-after-president-accuses-West-of-lecturing-him-on-human-rights.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 21:37:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gambia's [ruler](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yahya_Jammeh), by the way, is the guy who thinks he can cure AIDS and says he will cut off the heads of any homosexuals found in his country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Wheel of Fortune hosts Pat Sajak and Vanna White work on the show only 35 days a year. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 20:07:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Silk Road owner charged in second assassination plot. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 16:38:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-02 19:19:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And it goes on...

 Approximately 24 hours later, redandwhite updated DPR, saying "Your problem has been taken care of... Rest easy though, because he won't be blackmailing anyone again. Ever.

 at DPR's request, redandwhite send DPR a picture of the victim after the job was done, with random numbers written on a piece of paper next to the victim that DPR had supplied. On April 5, 2013, DPR wrote redandwhite "I've received the picture and deleted it. Thank you again for your swift action." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-02 18:56:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's in the [criminal complaint](http://www.scribd.com/doc/172768269/Ulbricht-Criminal-Complaint). WTF indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 19:03:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So is the website for the [National Science Foundation](http://www.nsf.gov/). The [NCBI](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov), whose website is used daily by life scientists around the world, has a red banner up saying that information on it may not be up to date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Montreal is home to the oldest inn in North America, the Auberge Saint-Gabriel (1754). It is also the first establishment to be issued an alcohol license. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-26 21:17:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oompa Loompas sentenced over attack on British man </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-25 22:11:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-25 20:20:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Out of interest, here is Willem de Kooning's ["A tree in Naples"](http://www.moma.org/collection/object.php?object_id=80116) which is mentioned in the article. I wish there was a picture of the 4 year old's painting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kenya info blackout? Extraordinary lack of detail about Westgate siege. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-25 18:36:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-25 17:04:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also good is their "Is this written in Oracle bone script?". Have to start using that one at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-25 04:35:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now this is a TIL! Thankyou OP. If only they had these "docking structures" more useful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-24 19:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The paper they are referring to was published in 2010 and has been cited [only one time](http://scholar.google.ca/scholar?cites=3836192125356317566 as_sdt=2005 sciodt=0,5 hl=en). Not saying it isn't interesting, but this hasn't looked to have gained much traction since then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-24 18:47:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Statement](http://www.news.com.au/national-news/mother-describes-8216immeasurable8217-loss-of-son-ross-langdon-his-partner-and-their-unborn-baby/story-fncynjr2-1226725525297) from the husband's mother: "The loss is immeasurable, absurd and excruciating.". I literally can not imagine how she feels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In 1987, someone hijacked broadcast TV in Chicago and appeared wearing a Max Headroom mask. The hijacker has never been identified. Here is the video. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-24 17:27:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-24 14:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly! All the people upvoting this thread either i) didn't bother to click on the link OP provided, or ii) fail at basic reading comprehension.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-23 21:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually, the center of the galaxy is approx. 27000 light years away, so, during the last ice age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The galaxy's core is about to explode. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-23 20:06:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in 2006, teenage fans of a popular Portuguese soap opera began experiencing the physical symptoms of a fictional disease that was introduced to the characters on the show. The "outbreak" spread to over 300 people. It is considered an example of mass hysteria. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-18 18:41:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-16 22:10:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, be careful. Remember when reddit successfully identified 10 of the 2 Boston bombers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that during the Cold War, the US Air Force developed a top secret plan to detonate a nuclear bomb on the Moon, as a show of force. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-16 20:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-15 20:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not lovin' it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in 2004, a 19m tall sculpture of Jesus, named "King of Kings", was erected in Ohio. It was the 7th tallest statue in the United States at the time. In 2010, it was struck by lightning and was destroyed by the subsequent fire. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-15 09:19:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-13 20:36:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see a Dos Equis commercial here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-13 20:21:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will pop right in with this submission to show how hard that is. 50,000 words ~~would be~~ is so tough to do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-13 19:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's right. OP should from now on proof his words prior to posting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-13 18:53:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a 50,000 *word* book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the common or button mushroom is simply the juvenile form of a Portobello mushroom. They are the same species. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-13 17:51:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-12 20:54:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where's the red line for this kind of stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-12 19:28:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually, a good number of those Athenians were of the other persuasion, I hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-12 18:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From the article, TIL also that "toad" was a common nickname given to prostitutes and courtesans at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The human finger can discriminate between surfaces patterned with ridges as small as 13 nanometres in height. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-12 16:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Greece unemployment rate at a record 27.9 percent. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-12 16:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If a hurricane doesn't form in the next 10 days, 2013 will have the slowest start to a hurricane season in recorded history. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-06 15:41:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the concept of an atomic bomb was introduced in a novel by HG Wells in 1914. Eighteen years after its publication, the physicist Le Szilrd read the book, was inspired, and two years later filed a patent on the idea of a neutron chain reaction, leading eventually to atomic bomb technology. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-06 07:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do movers expect a tip? If so, how much? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-06 03:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is in North America, btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 23:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Relevant.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Higher_education_bubble) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 2013 in running for the latest first Atlantic hurricane on record. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 19:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Some 2-Year degrees pay off better than BAs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 19:34:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that during the 1983 US Open, an errant serve from Stefan Edberg struck a linesman directly on the groin. The linesman fell backward, striking his head, and fell unconscious. He died in hospital five days later. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 21:29:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that it is estimated that the number of rats in New York City may be as high as 32 million. That's four rats per person. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 19:15:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-30 06:47:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently the model for Chloe wasn't so happy in Paris."She, after throwing a party for friends, boiled a soup of poisonous matches, drank the concoction and died." The reason for her suicide is thought to be unrequited love. 

RIP Chloe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-30 06:11:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disgraceful yes, but I can report that the painting is doing just fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that one of the most famous pubs in Australia is the Young and Jackson Hotel. It is famous for its portrait "Chloe" of a very nude 19 years old girl, which hangs over one of the bars. It was considered scandalous at the time, but still hangs there. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-30 05:34:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the actor known as Moriarty in Star Trek TNG and the butler in The Nanny is actually from Arkansas, he doesn't have an english accent at all but is one of the best ever at doing one. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-30 05:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in some places in the world, it is illegal to die. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-30 04:25:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Puccini's 1910 opera, "La fanciulla del West", is set in the American old west, featuring a bandit, a sherriff and a "bartender at the Polka saloon". Some consider it the first "Spaghetti Western". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-28 17:28:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ring functions like a smart card for public transit </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-27 21:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that when the Space Shuttle Challenger exploded in 1986, this joke spread quickly around the world: "Q: What does NASA stand for? A: Need Another Seven Astronauts." This was before widespread use of the internet. The joke spread literally by word of mouth. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-26 22:07:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 06:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not me for sure, I may have assumed that people knew that the internet existed prior the the world wide web, and had its own stuff like chat, usenet, and muds/mushs. Sorry, a bad assumption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that before the world wibe web, internet users had multiplayer role-playing online games called MUSHs. This stands for Multi User Shared Hallucination. These games were played via the unix command line, i.e via text, no graphics, but were enourmosly popular amongst college students at the time. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 05:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-21 07:06:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure if serious... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in 2010, a couple from Italy thought they had booked air tickets to Sydney, Australia, but ended up in the small town of Sydney, NS, Canada. My first reaction was fear" said one of the Italian tourists, when learning that he was in Canada, not Australia. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-21 06:37:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-20 05:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry! Time heals all wounds. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-20 05:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit... has anyone ever beaten the game, all of it? Just curious.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that one of the most difficult video games ever is Ghosts 'n Goblins, in arcades in the 80s. Even if you managed to beat it, it was revealed that the boss had laid you a trap and that you had to beat the whole game again at a higher level of diffuclty. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-20 04:58:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that crack pipes are sold as fake flowers in a glass tube at convenience stores. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-18 09:01:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-18 02:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish this wasn't buried. Well said, pacman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-18 01:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recommend [this article](http://www.theaustralian.com.au/news/features/fearless-matriarch-of-resistance/story-e6frg6z6-1226111207166). VERY late in life (age 88 by my reckoning) she said she wanted to die in London and moved to an expensive hotel in Piccadilly. She ran out of money, though, but the hotel didn't want to kick her out. Prince Charles started footing the bill. She had her own stool at the hotel bar, where during her nineties she would have at least 6 gin and tonics a day. Good for her, I say. She died in 2011 at age 98. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-17 22:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I don't wanna talk to a scientist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that during WWII, the Gestapo's most wanted person was New Zealand born Allied agent Nancy Wake. Among her numerous exploits, she killed an SS soldier with her bare hands, to prevent him from raising the alarm during an undercover raid. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-17 21:00:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mass Effect clothing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-16 07:04:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-15 16:54:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know someone who tried to eat a blackberry once. It had to be surgically removed and its battery had gone dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that one of the most misspelled words in the English language is "misspell". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-15 16:45:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China zoo under fire for disguising dog as lion. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-15 14:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-14 21:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ghosts 'n Goblins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Syrian refugee camp </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-12 18:34:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 12:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not this by any chance?

http://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/1j2cqb/til_that_in_ancient_rome_one_of_the_most_common/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 12:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, that was quick! Glad to share your link. I'm very interested in what they cooked up in antiquity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 11:38:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's something very very strange in these woods, Cooper.

Oh, ewoks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that if you ever want to eat a flamingo, there is a recipe for it from the ancient Roman celebrity chef Apicius. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 11:14:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Accident map of Montreal! This map illustrates the relative danger of intersections in Montreal, based on data from police reports. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 02:24:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 00:25:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Relevant: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Higher_education_bubble </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Man finds a pair of trousers inside a tree. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-27 13:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-27 06:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh Perth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the gravestone of ACDC's first frontman, Bon Scott, has been stolen. It's not the only time. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-27 06:25:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-26 18:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They should call it the Colosseam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that in ancient Rome, one of the most common cooking ingredients was called "laser", from the silphium plant. It does not exist today: it was so delicious that it was harvested to extinction from its natural habitat in what is now Libya. We think that it probably tasted something like garlic. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-26 02:24:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-25 02:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm very curious as to why cycling isn't included as a most common mode of transport category. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New interactive map of Montreal filled with census data. It's a major timewaster! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 22:10:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Bashar al-Assad, Queen Elizabeth II and Che Guevara have something in common: They all recieved the "Order of the Southern Cross". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 05:00:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Brazilians' enthusiasm for the internet led to the decline of fotolog.net and google's now sort of defunct orkut.net. There were so many Brazilians on these sites that they stifled anyone else's contributions. It's called the "Brazilian internet phenomenon". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-20 07:41:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-19 07:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've got a gut feeling that this field is just in its infancy, especially with the decreasing cost and increasing usefulness of metagenomic studies of the microbial flora within animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-18 20:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently he wants to build the first one between San Francisco and LA. The trip would take 30 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-17 21:08:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here is the original press release from the Edmonton Police:

http://www.edmontonpolice.ca/News/MediaReleases/markmarekcharges.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-16 20:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of the most underrated games of the last couple of years, was Sleeping Dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 07:52:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The original link contains this sentence:

"In a joint sale for US$40 million, Abbott sold their rights to Desoxyn and Tranxene to Ovation Pharma."

"Ovation Pharma" links to a page to their website and from there directly to the link I just posted, which shows undeniably that methamphetamine is sold by that company. Unless you think we need to be held hands around the internet, don't insult our intelligence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 06:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.lundbeck.com/us/products/cns-products/desoxyn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that methamphetamine is manufactured legally in the United States by Ovation pharmaceuticals and is sold under the brand name Desoxyn. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 06:09:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-13 05:47:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a real tragedy. I hope we can find some way of preserving magnetic tapes. There must be so much out there to preserve but the high throughput means of doing so escapes me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL the first 1 million dollar budget movie in America (1916) also featured the first full female nudity in a mainstram film. It was a commercial success, but no copies of it exist. It is a lost movie. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-13 05:24:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-12 17:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's the working language or languages there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-12 05:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And here's an amazing video of a very brief encounter with these people...

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OaPYwlXOTzQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL the Sentinalese people have lived on an isolated island in the Indian Ocean for an estimated 60,000 years. They reject all contact with outsiders and are the last group of people who have had virtually no contact with the modern world. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-12 04:17:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>