<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4034</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:17:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was published ten years ago. Is there any updated info? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I just finished City on Fire. Anyone else? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't want to give any spoilers away, but I thought the writing here was pretty remarkable. There were a dozen points where I stopped to comprehend the sentence or passage that I had just read. I thought the plot was above average, but maybe not 2 million dollars above average. The end, especially, left a lot to be desired. 

Anyway, I guess I'm asking what everyone else thought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unless I'm mistaken, /r/writingprompts is mainly fiction. I'll have a look though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I could use some writing prompts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:31:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey All - I was a college writing major and now I work in publishing. I help authors come up with ideas for op-eds all the time, but when it comes to my own writing I'm kind of at a loss. In the last few years I've written about gaming dynamics, the changing language of the technology age, fan fiction, and, ironically, Reddit. All of these pieces were for major publications and some were even paid. I also have some random fiction in the works. 

My question is what would you all like to read about? Specifically at the intersection of writing, publishing and technology. It's been the better part of a year since I've written anything worth reading and I could really use some of that famous Reddit juice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 18:28:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "RemindMe! 2 days Donation for /r/millionairemakers" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is John Jay a forgotten founder? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:17:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:54:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe that men who don't wear belts are psychopaths.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 21:00:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Episode 8 of Band of Brothers is the most realistic Holocaust scene I've ever come across, and you already love all the soldiers by this point. Breaks me every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 20:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tom, do you have any plans for the next book in the series? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I help run the Product Hunt Book Club at www.producthuntbookclub.com and we cover 4 or 5 nonfiction titles a month. If anyone is looking to expand their nonfiction reading that's as good a place to start as any. DM me for details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who read Born to Run? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dare you to tell me it didn't inspire you to put the book down and run around outside. Very odd result, and an author I can't help but think would be proud to hear you'd rather be running around then reading his book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 21:06:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just finished Born to Run. What do you think of the idea that human's were designed not to need footwear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 04:29:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Publishing and media </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> link me up fam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:59:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah he's awesome. That post came out the day I finished the book, so as much as I hate to admit it I couldn't read much more about Musk, especially since the post is loosely based on the book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I just finished Ashlee Vance's Elon Musk biography. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 20:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't typically read biographies, and this one won't be published until May 16th, but I got my hands on a copy and holy hell was it awesome. There were some pieces that left you wanting (very little on Solar City) and a few more typos than I would have liked in a finished book, but man it was great. If you're a fan of Elon Musk you need this book. Beyond that, I found that it was incredibly inspiring, on the level I haven't seen very often. I guess this is a bit of a rambling explanation, but I'm wondering if anyone else has been wanting to read this or if I'm the odd man out? Sales seems to be pretty steady on Amazon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 20:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I loved all four of them, but nothing will ever compare to the first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 03:47:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's funny because it's true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I want to get this tattoo on my tricep, but I need someone to draw it better. Any takers? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 19:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 01:04:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Joe Dirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:23:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was writing the book a lot different than filming the show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "In an odd inversion of the usual page-to-screen adaptation process, Ms. McKenzie is extending her brand into print by turning her YouTube show into a series of young adult novels." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 14:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 14:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because something is popular doesn't mean it's not good. You're judging without reading, which reminds me of an old saying... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 00:21:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you know that having not read it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 20:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has anyone read Loving Learning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Girl creates a paranormal YouTube series that becomes so popular Harvey Weinstein gave her a three book deal and optioned the film rights. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 19:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 19:00:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Listen- this is great that you finally read a book and I hope you keep reading and take down a million more. That being said, I'm shocked to see so many people who go so long without reading. Books are the easiest way for us to share our ideas and thoughts and it's a shame that so many people don't take advantage of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm speaking about new innovations in book publishing at SXSW this Monday. Description in comments. Let me know what you'd like me to talk about. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 16:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-06 20:37:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Netscape friendly layouts. I think you just won my heart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-06 20:10:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you think of the UX design on Reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lincolns assassination was part of a larger plan to kill Secretary of State William Seward (who was injured in a concurrent attack at his home) and Vice President Andrew Johnson (whose assigned attacker bailed and got drunk instead). </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 16:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Did you know that Lincolns assassination was part of a larger plan to kill Secretary of State William Seward (who was injured in a concurrent attack at his home) and Vice President Andrew Johnson (whose assigned attacker bailed and got drunk instead)? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 16:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Professor interviews 1500 couple who have been married for 50+ years and collects their relationship tips in a video. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:58:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 17:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "You're not perfect, sport, and let me save you the suspense: this girl you've met, she's not perfect either. But the question is whether or not you're perfect for each other." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 15:22:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't this be so much more effective if the man/woman named themselves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 02:38:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People now wearing belts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 00:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Send me a PM, I'm a book publicist and have worked with him before. Did you want any signed book, or a special inscription? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 23:20:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that bullshit, man, or is it reliable?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Enduring Love by Ian McEwen </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:45:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a professor back in college who swore by this book. I couldn't hear the end of how amazing it was and how McEwan demonstrated his masterful writing skills here. I started reading it yesterday, and am currently about halfway. Holy hell was he right. Every chapter is amazing concise and demonstrates everything that makes writing transformative. voice, POV, narrative distance, blah blah blah. Anyway, read it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 19:49:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's so awesome that I wish I never read any of them so I could read them again for the first time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 19:33:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hyperion by Dan Simmons and it's not even close.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 19:30:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She came by way of Archer, Bridgeport, Nanuet, worked off 95 in jeans and a denim jacket, carrying a plastic bag and shower shoes, a phone number, waiting beneath an underpass, the potato chips long gone, lightheaded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-29 21:48:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So many. 

David Mitchell
JK Rowling
Junot Diaz
Phillip Meyer
Ben Fountain
Lev Grossman
JOshua Ferriss
Jennifer Eagan
Michael Chabon

So many more. The issue is that this trait can reasonably be argued in most any book considered decent. Even short stories show character development. I don't really agree with the the fact that Cormac McCarthy doesn't develop his characters, he just does it differently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 21:45:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Requiem for a Dream. Nightmare fuel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 16:59:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How long did the technical aspects of the book take you to write? I know your background is in the sciences, but there seemed to be a lot of complicated formulas involved in this book. 

Also, did you intentionally write this book to read like a movie script?

Lastly, did you laugh when you realized that Matt Damon was going to play ANOTHER character trapped on a foreign planet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:36:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love to insult people through compliments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 22:56:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How was it listening to the audio book? I read it and loved it, but it was so clearly written for a movie that I bet the audio book was even better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What do people outside of the United States, especially in developing countries, think of Google   Facebook's attempts to bring them Internet access? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 17:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-17 01:03:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't understand how this helps?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-16 17:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a picture! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm on jury duty right now. Would love to hear the best stories you all have of getting out of this. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-15 16:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just found these in my parent's basement </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 22:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A visualization of the more than 2800 beliefs submitted to the atheism ten commandment contest, along with the winning submissions. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 20:38:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 16:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mediocre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I present to you the perfect gift for a child to his/her parents. You're welcome. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 21:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I have an extra tickets for Conor Oberst's Holiday Cheer concert in NYC tomorrow night. PM me if you're interested. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 23:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I have two extra tickets for Conor Oberst's Holiday Cheer concert in NYC tomorrow night. PM me if you're interested. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 18:41:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-21 21:21:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Copyrighting so hard right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does South Park have to pay a fine every time they swear on the show? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 18:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I listened to every episode of Serial this week, and then someone sent me this. I probably shouldn't laugh but it is BRILLIANT. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 23:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 19:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actual chills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Mashable created a TL;DW (too long didn't watch) YouTube channel that profiles movie trilogies including Iron Man, The Matrix   Star Wars in two minutes or less. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> $10,000 ReThink Prize Announced to Crowdsource Secular Alternatives to the Ten Commandments </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 20:26:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 23:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fella with the beard is at work and asked me to respond. As a bit of back story, we all initially began our training with beards- it was kind of a gimmick for charity. He was admirably the only one who kept his throughout, and we actually shaved it off together about an hour after this picture was taken. But here's his response:  

"it definitely kept me warm on a relatively cold day. Disclaimer- Not advisable for use with summer training regimen in NYC and is generally incompatible with most models of girlfriend."

Anyway, thanks for the kudos!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 23:26:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha! Who is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 22:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I think I'm still smiling now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 15:52:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The entire thing was memorable. Even the people who were miserable were smiling because of the crowds. The three of us ran the entire race together so we had a lot of support throughout, and we did about as well as we thought we would. If I had to pick one moment, it was coming off the Queensboro Bridge into Manhattan. The crowds, which were already massive in Brooklyn and Queens, were ENORMOUS in Manhattan. It was such a cool experience. Thanks for asking!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My friends and I just ran our first marathon. Here's our before and after pics. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 15:15:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm at an event at The New America Foundation called 'Will Amazon Lead to the Golden Age of Books?' What do you think? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 00:21:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 20:31:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TL;DR, My twin brother added "I want to come on your hard tits" to my final paper in an AP history class. Teacher was a feminist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 20:26:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some of my favorites:

Ill Bambino,
Sanfords,
Queen's Comfort,
Junkos,
Bartelino's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is Obama's inner circle as loyal to Obama as Putin's is to Putin? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 20:24:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Been in Astoria for 2 years, looking for any restaurants I haven't tried yet. Blow my mind. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 17:13:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is there a new Cold War brewing over the energy market? Interesting video explains why. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 22:58:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 16:20:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two time reader here. The first reading wasn't so much difficult as it was disgusting. I've read some dark stuff, but this one got to me. It wasn't until the second read that I realized how amazingly intricate and beautiful the prose was. I actually sympathized with HH and thought of the book as some great story of love and loss. Every time I mention this I get weird looks, but it has become a favorite of mine. Keep at it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Isis being funded by methamphetamine sales? No... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 16:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What happens when you put a werewolf on the moon? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 19:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There's a new publisher, launched yesterday, dedicated to putting out books about the Jewish American Experience </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 19:33:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There's a new publisher focused on launching books about the Jewish American Experience. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 19:32:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who's 'that guy' in your office and what does he/she do? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 14:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-07 02:12:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is the yellowcake output of your mine? Where is it used/sold? I take it that this is still a growing industry as there are about two dozen nuclear plants slated for construction in the next decade worldwide. Any thoughts on nuclear energy as opposed to oil   gas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 22:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nabokov's wife pulled Lolita out of the trash after he tried to burn his first draft. Guess we know who won the wife contest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What, those aren't books? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Here's a list of books I recently read. Which one is your favorite? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:28:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A random selection of books I recently read. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A random selection of books I've recently read. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-10 22:02:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fillory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 02:22:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Snape killed Dumbledore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-01 18:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This happened to me once after an brutal car wars game. $125 seat cleaning bill delivered in all dimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As someone who doesn't read a lot of comics, what is the significance of Marvel's push for diversification? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-22 14:58:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Female Thor, Mrs. Marvel, black Captain America, Miles Morales as Spider Man. Just curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that this year The Library of America published their 250th volume. Here's a list of all of them. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-22 01:16:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that 2014 is the year the Library of America published its 250th volume. Here's a list of all of them. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 22:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 16:10:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would start with Drown, his first collection of short stories. His second book is a novel called The Brief Wondrous Life of Oscar Wao. This won a Pulitzer for fiction, but is usually the least liked of his books. I loved it, but I would read Drown first. Finally, This is How You Lose Her is his second collection of short stories and was released last year. He's apparently working on a Dominican Apocalypse story now, which will be amazing. If you Google him you can probably find a number of his stories online. He publishes in The New Yorker every couple of years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 15:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Junot Diaz will cure that for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 04:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go home, you're drunk. That's how we say it in the biz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 04:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what got me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 04:25:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not fucker, but he definitely had his moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 04:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 04:22:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll probably be picking that up soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> To ease baseball fans through the long All-Star Break, I present an excerpt from Bernard Malamud's "The Natural" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-15 21:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-15 21:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is an epic western about the Texas frontier. It's a very dark cowboy and Indian story that spans about 100 years, similar to Marquez.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm reading The Son by Philipp Meyer. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-15 21:52:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work in the book biz, so I saw dozens of reviews for this book when it came out. If I can help it I won't read a review before I read the book, so I basically ignored The Son until a few weeks ago, when I met Philipp Meyer and had a beer with him. I started reading the book the next day and, though I'm only a dozen chapters in, I know this will be one of my all time favorites. The writing is as close to perfect as I've seen in recent memory. Have you all read the book and what do you think? I'm afraid I'm just a fan of the man instead of the writing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What will be the greatest turnaround story in American history? This author says Detroit. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-08 15:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-04 01:23:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a publicist, this is an awesome list that will add hours to my workload next week. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-04 01:22:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a book called Christian Nation that is all about if McCain won the election and died weeks later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-03 04:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a book publicist in NYC. My firm is a freelance consulting outfit so I have worked with virtually all publishers and about a dozen bestsellers every year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kim Stolz is doing an AMA right now. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-27 21:17:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kim Stolz discusses some topics from her new book, Unfriending My Ex. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-16 19:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-14 07:33:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ready player one by Ernest cline  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-11 14:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're running the NYC marathon under the banner of the joe Torre safe at home fund. All the money we make goes to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 21:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The money we raise is headed here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gM-meqdHUw4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 21:36:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought the book was inspiring. The whole time I was reading it I was thinking that I should really get out there and do something big. The specifics didn't matter so much to me as that feeling I got while reading it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My friends and I are bearding it for charity. Daily selfies to track growth have commenced on Instagram. Feel free to follow. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 19:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 14:32:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's the fun in that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My 2 friends and I are growing beards to raise $$ for charity, and will be taking daily selfies for the next 5 months. Here's the first week. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-09 22:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-09 01:30:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We had a middle school gym teacher fired and jailed for being intimate with a student. I believe this occurred on several occasions, and they were discovered by the gym teacher's wife, also a gym teacher at the school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-07 16:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-04 15:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You won't even know what chafing looks like until you see us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A crow challenged a hawk to battle for eating his friend today, and it all happened through my back window. I live in Queens. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-22 18:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 03:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're missing an 'e' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 03:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read your autobiography in middle school. Did you write it or was there a ghost? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-19 23:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you please add the Seabrook Star? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ben Mezrich will release the first chapter of his new thriller, Seven Wonders, if enough people add the book to their Goodreads page. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-13 18:38:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-30 19:52:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was the best part of filming Joe Dirt working with Kid Rock, or inspiring millions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why do I have nightmares when I take caffeine pills? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-28 16:52:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-22 18:55:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How has the success of Gone Girl affected your writing habits? Has anything changed now that you don't have to be concerned with your finances? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-22 04:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Romanski how proud are you being from NH? Probably my greatest achievement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 01:46:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ernest Cline's Ready Player One.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-10 16:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Junot Diaz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What does the expiration date of Tylenol and Advil really mean? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-17 20:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My bagel shop today... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-17 15:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Probably shouldn't have done this... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 22:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-06 18:16:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always attended the interactive sessions, so I can't speak to the music. That being said there seems to be a give and take with the popularity of these festivals. They are becoming larger and more intricate, which takes away from the grass roots feel of the whole thing, but also moves them towards bigger acts and more legitimacy. 

Plus even at interactive the music is still killer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm currently on a flight to Austin for SXSW, in my opinion usually the most interesting part of the whole trip, sitting amongst tech luminaries and comm execs. AMA. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-06 18:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> $1 Million in "New Digital Age Grants" Awarded by Google Executive Chairman Eric Schmidt to Organizations Fighting Global Challenges </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-24 13:58:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-18 17:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clay, I'll be attending your talk with Emily Parker this evening at the New America Foundation. How do you know Mrs. Parker and what are your thoughts on the possible balkanization of the Internet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I just wrote this article on fan fiction, and who really owns the worlds we love, for a major media outlet. Let me know your thoughts. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-08 22:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Second Monitor issues </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-24 19:25:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a Lenova laptop, plugged into a Lenova docking station, which is hooked up to a Dell monitor (VGA to VGA). I recently picked up a Lenova monitor. I would like to use the docking station to have dual monitors, but the only other port is a DVI-D and the monitor has a VGA port. 

I ordered an adapter (VGA to DVI-D) and it didn't work. I did some trouble-shooting, and both monitors, chords, and ports work. This leads me to believe that it's the adapter's fault, but before I order a new one I'm curious if there's something I'm missing. My IT team tells me that the video card, comp, and docking station support dual-monitors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-20 21:35:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on experience and writing. Do you have any writing samples? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> CALLING ALL WRITERS </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-20 20:32:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in the process of rolling out a new tech-oriented website with a focus on futurism. I would like to hold an open discussion about how technology is effecting out culture; think "the future of optometry in a world of Google Glass" or "Snapchat is mocking your privacy; here's why you don't care." I'm open to most topics, but I"m looking specifically for beat writers to cover drones, wearables, and 3d printing. 

Message me if this is of interest to you and I can share more details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does brain size effect the potency of your hangover? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-18 23:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do you genuinely think there's a future for closed software systems? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-15 23:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't help but feel that open systems are dominating the market right now, and that any desirable closed system is being cannibalized by open source software anyway. More curious than anything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I changed the light bulb in my kitchen and found a dozen of these. WTF are they? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-18 20:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-12 15:48:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations. As someone who works in publishing, this is no small feat. However I have to warn you, the hard part is just beginning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-29 22:21:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cocker spaniel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It's my cake day, so I decided to buy myself a gift. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-29 17:51:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 22:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm at the national book awards right now. AMA. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 03:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 20:08:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How'd you get your verification? I want one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 20:02:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Pres was drunk during this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3D comics? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 19:21:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-18 16:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> page views is not misleading when it comes to financing the websites. More pageviews = more money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is There an Expiration Date on Evil? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-18 16:44:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For KFC: Will there ever be a Barstool BK? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 22:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 22:25:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> manhunted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 22:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lazy fat blogger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 22:20:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So basically just put all of them in the bcc line to increase your chances of getting on the stool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Do I Know Which Philippine Aid Organizations to Donate to? An aid worker explains? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 18:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 16:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> According to the press kit on the site, which hasn't been updated in months, the page views are as follows:

Boston - 700k unique users/month
New York - 500k unique users/month
Chicago - 500k unique users/month
BarstoolU - 500k unique users/month
Philly - 350k unique users/month

So, there you have it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Comments show this is not necessarily the best way to improve medical treatment. What is? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 20:59:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reading this was the most inspiring part of my day. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 15:48:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-31 21:36:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't used chewing tobacco in 58 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-25 18:10:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 52 second mark... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-24 16:51:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't help but feel you're a bad person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 16:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you could choose your friend's Halloween costume, what would you choose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If you could choose your friend's Halloween costume, what would you choose? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 15:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The most popular dog in my neighborhood </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-02 17:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The greatest speech. We could use more of these about now. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-27 17:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Today, Secretary Lew sent this debt limit letter to Congress. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-25 22:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Turns out Hollywood collaborated with Hitler prior to WWII. Great. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-12 19:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-11 17:06:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I'm sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-10 16:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I once wrote a 15,000 page story 3 separate times, in first, second, and third person respectively. Finally I realized that I liked it best in third person, but that I needed to rewrite it AGAIN. I think in the end, I kept about 100 words of the roughly 50,000 I initially wrote. 

The silver lining is that the story thrived from the endless editing, and is now a published piece of fiction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is officially the greatest commercial on television. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-04 22:37:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-29 19:50:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention some of these folks aren't even alive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Here's a list of the 50 wealthiest authors in the world. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-29 19:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-20 19:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been waiting to read this book for months. So it's worth it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-30 14:40:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahhhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-29 23:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> John Keats is a poet from 200 years back. He's an interesting guy, and Hyperion gets its namesake from one of his poems. This book takes a VERY interesting twist on him. 

Also, the book is chronological.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-29 23:44:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ayn Rand is a wizard with a plot, but her writing is grueling. 

Ender's Shadow is brilliant, as well as the entire Hegemon series. I have a sneaking suspicion you'll be hearing a lot more about this book after November hits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-29 23:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first book is about a pilgrimage to an abandoned planet, and each of 7 chapters is told by a different pilgrim. Each subsequent book takes a different narrative approach, but all of the characters remain the same. On a side note, if you're at all a John Keats fan, this is a can't miss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-29 22:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bright Lights, Big City.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-29 22:20:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hyperion by Dan Simmons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-29 22:19:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out Hyperion by Dan Simmons. It's a 4 book series that runs through about 7 narrators, but each of them have a compelling story and they all come together flawlessly. One of the best (and most underrated) series around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Buzzfeed launched a vertical for books. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 20:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-18 15:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't this why fan fiction exists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-18 15:34:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love this guy's swagger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-18 21:48:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never been but would love to share a meal with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-18 21:21:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Long live Chauncey. Mitch, have you ever eaten at his restaurant in Colorado? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-18 21:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-18 20:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm still rooting for the Celtics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-12 23:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bright Lights, Big City </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There's going to be an AMA on June 18th at 2pm with Mitch Albom, Scott Turow, Roger McGuinn, Sam Barry, Ridley Pearson,   James McBride. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-12 22:36:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-06 14:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When men don't wear belts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-05 21:04:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When will there be a Gattaca sequel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-03 20:34:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out the Hyperion series by Dan Simmons. Keats included.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I need a new high capacity printer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-22 20:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that doesn't charge hundreds of dollars for new ink cartridges. I have a Konica Minolta Magicolor 4750DN and to replace everything (toner, ink, imaging units) costs more than a thousand dollars every 6 months. This is for less than 5,000 pages printed. Any thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-24 00:37:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But his ideologies ARE kind of reflected... Ender was never supposed to exist. The Wiggins had him so that they could procreate as their religion said they were supposed to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it the best man's responsibility to finance the bachelor party, or does he typically split the cost with the whole crew? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 15:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm the best man at a wedding this fall and have the whole bachelor party planned, but it's expensive and as I've never done this before I don't know what the protocol is. Anyone have any experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Bre Pettis is a genius. And he sold his first Makerbot prototypes by printing shot glasses at bars.  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-08 21:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-19 18:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> eggs and lots of toilet paper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kansas Jayhawks bring a whole new meaning to the big dance </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-10 21:46:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do you think he knew the world was going to end? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-20 16:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-18 22:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Favorite is relative to you. There is no wrong answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-18 22:22:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahhh what an evil bloke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-18 22:21:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have my vote- but Atticus. Scout got all her good grace from him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who's your favorite character in all of literature? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-18 16:30:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found a list of the top 100 fictional characters of the last 100 years and I just don't know how they came up with them. Love to know your opinions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Big Business Takes On Gamification </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-05 23:55:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Big Business Takes On Gamification </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-05 20:37:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Herman Melville's Moby-Dick was released on this day (11/14) in 1851 to belittlement and slander. Here's why.  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-14 19:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-14 05:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm reading we are anonymous by parmy Olson. Really well researched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-14 05:29:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dan Simmon's Hyperion. I dare you to read it and not enjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-14 05:29:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out Dan Simmon's Hyperion or Orson Scott Card's Enders Game. Both have subsequent books and will hook you from the starts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There's nothing I can do... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-12 05:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-11 19:59:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Rumpus is great as well-  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-11 19:57:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome! Definitely one of the best book blogs out there- I trust you guys more than many of the legacy newspaper reviews out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-11 19:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why don't you create it and we'll see what comes of it. I would love to contribute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-11 19:50:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I still remember reading #5 where you find out Marco's history. Genius books, awful television show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I told you, no more pictures </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-11 19:34:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-11 19:30:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-11 19:30:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Much appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-11 19:30:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chemically, what makes us want to play games? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-11 04:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is it in the human brain that tells us to compete with others with no material gain?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Has anyone been able to actually play Peter Molynieux's Curiosity? I've had server issues for three days. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-09 15:46:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who's read the Hyperion series by Dan Simmons? Commence discussion.  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-09 04:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-08 22:59:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whelp, consider me informed. I'm ridiculously impressed that you knew that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Books I Lost in the Process of Losing Her" a list by Junot Diaz </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-08 05:00:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-07 18:38:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't even care if Enders Game is awful- I've been waiting most of my life for that movie so ill be there on opening day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-07 18:37:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may want to begin with history books. Anything by Michael Beschless is amazing. Nowadays the best politics books are about individual issues. Authors go hand in hand, like Joseph Stiglitz and the economy. What are you interested in learning about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-07 14:54:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even receipts are plastered with exclamation points.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jack Kerouac, a flat tire, a jug of wine, and the original mass market 1957 cover of On The Road.  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-07 04:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-07 04:06:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This American Life made me nostalgic about the NH I know. The current NH political scene is still vibrant, but much of it is completely fukt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-04 01:02:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> website problems are not my issue buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Internet is mutating the English language.  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-04 00:07:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gabby turns one, the stuffed animals suffer.  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-03 18:59:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-30 22:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the best Twitter analytics system that I've used yet, and I've used a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crowdbooster: Social Media Marketing Analytics and Optimization </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-30 22:03:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>