<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9585</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People need to seriously chill out with this nonsense. It was wrong for the biker to steal and damage someone's property. People keep stealing and attacking people who have different opinions expecting the other person to not defend themselves and their property.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been pulled over for that myself and I'm white. I had to pay the fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Samuel Dubose, a 43-year-old father of 13 children, according to CNN affiliate WKRC-TV. A CNN records search showed that Dubose had more than 60 arrests.

 nbsp;

Wow, what a quality fellow with 60 arrests. My next question is how the hell does he afford to have 13 children with an arrest record like that?! No one would hire him. Who was paying for these children? I hope he wasn't forcing other people to pay for his inability to control his dick or wear a condom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Army chief Odierno, in exit interview, says US could have prevented ISIS rise </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:10:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obama greeted in Oklahoma by pro-Confederate protest led by black man </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obama greeted in Oklahoma by pro-Confederate protest led by black man </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gay Pride Event Bans Drag Because It Offends Transgendered </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:13:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SJWs in a nutshell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A key part of President Obamas legacy will be the feds unprecedented collection of sensitive data on Americans by race. The government is prying into our most personal information at the most local levels, all for the purpose of racial and economic justice. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Man robs 2 sisters at lemonade stand after they gave him free drink </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:47:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Actress in viral catcall video sues man who made her famous </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:11:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Teen made rape victim swear on Bible she wouldnt call cops </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL: After 1993 the Army imposed regulations forbidding military personnel from carrying their personal firearms and making it almost impossible for commanders to issue firearms to soldiers in the U.S. for personal protection. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:34:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People are loosing their minds over this issue. Whatever you beliefs are you have the right to express them regardless if I agree with you or not. For example, recently there was a group of individuals who beat up a man carrying the Army of Tennessee flag. Here is a link to the video. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=REM54O04KXE

 nbsp;

It is a shame the people that cheer on this kind violence and destruction of property that isn't theirs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:29:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you make a poster that I disagree with and consider rude, because what is rude is subjective, do I have the right to assault you and destroy your property. Funny how left-wing extremists such as yourself only support free speech when it is something that you agree with but not for others with whom you disagree with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Patricks Westport Grill apologizes for receipt: FOX 2 received a photo from viewers angry about a receipt from Patricks Westport Grill where the customers are referred to as Black Couple. Management goes on to explain that the employee has been terminated. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:45:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL: Despite making up roughly 1 in 12 Americans, blacks accounted for half of all homicides. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:35:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:47:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Another backwards left-wing idiot reactionary afraid of change, efficiency, and competition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:10:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gawker and their whole network are garbage, especially Jezebel. Only Jalopnik, which is part of the Gawker network, is the exception to that rule. I automatically assume that anyone from my facebook friends list that likes Gawker's or Jezebel's facebook page or links to an article of theirs is an automatic left-wing idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:04:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good to see you understand how every publication can be biased. Do you also apply such logic to Gawker, Jezebel, The Guardian and MSNBC or do you let them slide because their biases are also your biases.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This very true. What is interesting about this study is that nearly every SJW would fit this type of pattern of behavior as many of them are losers in life and often lash out as a result because someone that they don't like or are prejudiced against is getting ahead of them in life. Many women I have observed that exhibit this type of aggressive behavior also turned out to be losers in life. This study won't just apply to men. I think the more likely explanation is the crabs in a bucket explanation. Losers tend to want to pull other people down especially if the person happens to be different than them or if they are prejudiced against that group.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:13:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very true. Many people are happy to throw away the first amendment when someone disagrees with them but don't want the same to be done to them. This is very common especially as of lately with the political left. They term everything that they disagree with as hate speech that should be banned, sometimes even arguing for jail time for it. They are the arbiters of what is "hate speech", which is very convenient for them because it could be used as a tool to silence anyone that disagrees with their political agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 20:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The author discusses the overreach of the administration's powers to force a certain outcome by abusing the "disparate impact" concept.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A key part of President Obamas legacy will be the feds unprecedented collection of sensitive data on Americans by race. The government is prying into our most personal information at the most local levels, all for the purpose of racial and economic justice. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 20:19:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> East Baltimore anti-violence group work suspended after guns, drugs found in raid </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 19:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL: That fewer than 385,000 individuals owned slaves in the US. That even if all slaveholders had been white, that would amount to only 1.4% of whites in the country. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:21:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Man robs 2 sisters at lemonade stand after they gave him free drink </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ruling in Twitter harassment trial could have enormous fallout for free speech </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL: Histrionic personality disorder is a personality disorder characterized by a pattern of excessive attention-seeking emotions. Histrionic people are lively, dramatic, vivacious, enthusiastic, and flirtatious. HPD affects four times as many women as men. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:47:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:42:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So the creator of Minions is a sexist bigot. Sigh, I was looking forward to taking my nephews to see the movie. -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, that government efficiency at work. What a terrible return on investment that was. Don't worry, there are plenty of suckers who will try to downplay this wasted money and beg for you to take even more from them like good little sadists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 08:54:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glenn Beck's segment hasn't been on Fox News since 2011. 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Glenn_Beck#Television

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 07:18:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is no such thing as free, someone else is paying for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 07:14:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let's not forget Gawker, Jezebel, MSNBC, and Salon, quite possibly the most biased news sites on the internet. http://i.imgur.com/S0j2kCD.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 07:03:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I keep getting told by the left that all these terrorist Muslims are being oppressed and come from poor uneducated backgrounds, that this is reason why they commit acts of terror. Also I keep getting told that the Quran is the most progressive religious text out there despite numerous violent, sexists, and homophobic verses. So much for that theory, I guess reality doesn't quite have the liberal bias that idiotic SJWs keep shouting about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 06:43:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not surprised at all, a lot of feminists and SJWs tend to be very scummy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 06:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The very same people that are eager to overlook Planned Parenthood's dark history are often the same people that are eager to point out the history of the battle flag of Virginia which they keep confusing for the confederate flag. It is as if things change but the left is very selective about applying the same standards to everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 00:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The author takes a look at a recent court trial's ruling and how it will affect the current rape hysteria trend and kangaroo courts that are popping up at various schools due to the pressures of Title IX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Court Ruling Highlights Flaws In College Sexual Assault Proceedings: Male student at UC San Diego who was accused of sexual assault and suspended after a campus investigation filed a countersuit  and won. Heres a look at if and how this could affect college rape trials across the country. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 00:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:20:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nor should he resign. People called Bush a monkey all the time and yet I heard few calling for them to resign. Calling people ugly or insulting them is nothing new, get over it and get a thicker skin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Casablanca mosque stampede blamed on mouse: A mouse is responsible for triggering a stampede in a mosque in the Moroccan city of Casablanca which left more than 80 people injured, officials say. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 20:43:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rachel Dolezal meets Bill Cosby </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 20:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Three Christians in Egypt Arrested for Allegedly Showing Contempt for Islam </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:38:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disagreeing with someone on the interpretation of something doesn't give you the right to assault them. Imagine if you and I disagreed on something, does that give me the right to attack you with physical violence? Of course it doesn't. It is a shame that the left supports violence when it suits their causes and denounce it when it doesn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rapper "Young Thug" involved in conspiracy to kill Lil Wayne: Rapper Young Thug was arrested Wednesday morning by U.S. Marshals executing an outstanding warrant issued by Dunwoody police. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:23:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:08:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The quality of Guardian's articles have been going down a lot lately. They were once a respectable organization, now they are slowly turning into a biased left-wing rag.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rapper "Young Thug" involved in conspiracy to kill Lil Wayne: Rapper Young Thug was arrested Wednesday morning by U.S. Marshals executing an outstanding warrant issued by Dunwoody police. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 09:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing wrong with such friends. Me and my girlfriends make these kinds of jokes all the time. Jokes are subjective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 09:13:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:35:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jezebel is a horrible place. When people say these straw feminists don't exist I always point them to Jezebel to prove them wrong. If there would be a 10th circle of hell in Dante's Inferno it would be Jezebel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:03:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If a man and a woman both have sex while drunk who is the rapist? Unfortunately, many of these college kangaroo courts side with the woman rather than saying neither was a rapist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:00:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You seem like a vindictive person if you are doing this partially out of spite. I am a little bit disappointed in you that you decided to play on that angle in your submission.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MARTA Police said a man they were looking for in connection with a rape at the Indian Creek MARTA station on June 14 surrendered Tuesday evening. Marquis Lamonte Butts, 21, turned himself at the DeKalb Police Department Tuesday evening. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:23:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:18:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can fathers also get this or does this only apply to mothers? It would only be fair for fathers to get the same treatment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bill Cosby's Favorite Pokemon </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:08:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL: A Princeton University study concluded that Asian Americans get penalized 50 points from their SAT scores while African Americans gain a 230 point score bonus in college admissions. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 11:08:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would be even slower, what you have is the purgatory model. 56k modems are for heck, 28k modems are for hell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 11:06:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Served along with a bag of generic Doritos that is 99% air and 1% potato chip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 11:03:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the line of "The enemy of my enemy is my friend." This is what is going on in Ukraine right now with Chechnyan fighters helping Ukrainian forces put down the Russian rebels. The same with Syria in which many Free Syrian Army fighters having defected to groups such as ISIS because they hate Bashar al-Assad more than they hate ISIS. It makes war very messy, especially once the conflict is over the temporarily united factions under a common enemy might then fight it out after their common enemy falls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 11:00:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Then my brother's alcoholic girlfriend drank it one night. Doesn't even remember it, just wanted more stuff to get her drunk. I will never forgive her.

 nbsp;

When someone is stealing other people's booze to get drunk that means that there is a very serious problem. Is she and your brother still together or did he move on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:20:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ray Romano kept reminding me of Kermit the Frog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:14:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If anyone is curious about the reference, this is referring to Emma Sulkowicz a.k.a. Mattress girl. She carried around her mattress as a publicity stunt even though it was shown that she lied about being raped. She made a crazy website where she films herself simulating rape and tells anyone that watches the video that they have committed stare rape if they don't agree with her. She is a nut case that harms not only the people she falsely accused, but real rape victims. When websites like Gawker and Jezebel picked her up as some sort of feminist hero, that is when I stopped reading those sites and I finally realized how terrible they have become.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:08:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is sad but true, taxpayer like you and I who are responsible will be stuck footing the bill for her irresponsibility. -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>