<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4364</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 13 Award winning pancake recipes that will blow rainbows in your mouth. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 23:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/upvotedbecausevictoria </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:18:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably doesn't need saying but...

THERE CAN BE ONLYYYY ONE!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:02:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 08:20:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great article! I always wonder when I should put more weight on value or mana cost in arena, and it really sums it up quite well. 

Never thought about drafting a more flat and value-based curve early in order to fit more curved-out yet quality cards. Thanks for the read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:55:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Executing face is my favorite lethal as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 03:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm... I did see him play 2 imp gang bosses and assorted 2-drops which led me to believe he was drafting a more zooish-aggro style deck, but I just consider the likelihood of both drafting and drawing voidcaller coupled with a considerable demon drop to be too low to play around. Just too much effort goes into letting the warlock keep a 3/4 to trade up or get value out of, but you do make a good point in reading your opponent, will consider it next time I approach a voidcaller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 03:37:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I feel with the entire randomness with arena what first drafting voidcaller and a big drop demon and having drawn both of them make these kinds of situations unlikely, but they do happen :/

Thanks for the input, probably will try to commit to board with no fear next time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In arena, should you ever proc a Voidcaller deathrattle? If so, when? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:45:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So in context, I was maintaining pretty good board presence (water ele + haunted creeper) as mage until the warlock decides to drop a voidcaller turn 5. My typical midrange-controllish mage mindset tells me to clear it, and when I do, I get punished by the Dread Infernal that pops out.

How can I avoid these kinds of situations besides the obvious silence or poly/hex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that right clicking a card in deck editor will bring you to the page of that card </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 03:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wish they had a tutorial or hint on the wheel for these kinds of things... totally helpful when trying to add another copy of that Kezan Mystic for the 7 consecutive huntards you've faced on ladder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 04:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gonna have to buy the season pass to unlock the other 4 planets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> FOUND THOSE MISSING DECKSLOTS! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:03:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 01:04:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Caught them right in the middle of mitosis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 01:43:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIL base turrets have a slow ;__; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 06:19:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't know which is more surprising, the freeze mage win vs warrior or the fact that warrior doesn't have at least 50 armor by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can't wait for the next update! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:12:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 01:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [oh yaaaah, look at it go!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HmZYgqBp1gI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-07 16:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those coke rewards tho... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-01 02:36:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worked like a charm, thanks and keep up the good work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What if we sometimes dream about trying to sleep so when we wake up, it feels like we never have dreams. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 14:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a person that almost never dreams, it makes more sense than it should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 19:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Urgot to be kidding me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 02:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE GET OUT OF THE FIRE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> No god has ever done that in the history of Smite... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 02:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-16 15:03:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> affect* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 04:23:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> VSBN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The epitome of my entire Smite experience </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-11 04:06:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-31 15:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> satan approves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>