<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5763</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Male bee (drone) being used for artificial insemination at the USDA bee lab in Baton Rouge. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:36:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> IRS: 7.5 Million Americans Paid Penalty For Lack Of Health Coverage </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:24:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Secretary of State John Kerry will travel to Havana on Aug. 14, to raise the American flag over the U.S. embassy in Cuba. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A.C.L.U. Asks Court to Stop Part of N.S.A.s Bulk Phone Data Collection </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bernie Sanders Trolls Hillary Clinton Outside Her Meeting With Senate Democrats </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> International violation? US Army considering hollow point bullets for pistols </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Detroit...Greece...Puerto Rico...Does Anyone See A Pattern? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:54:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Katherine Archuleta, Director of the Office of Personnel Management steps down one day after cyberintrusions at the agency were revealed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:26:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Protesters Burn American Flag In Fort Greene Park; Opponents Rush In </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 16:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Steve Buscemi, he looks like one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 04:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No update?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Escaped New York Inmate Richard Matt Shot and Killed by Police, Officials Say </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 22:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:41:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, out of all the allocations the best one is the L fund? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I was able to go to the webpage and like there I'm in the S fund. So, I guess I'm doing something right. Following these types of models could help in moving the money were it's more profitable, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:31:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The reason I'm asking it's because I've heard that people move the allocations based on the stock market.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried looking at the model but the webpage is not working. So such models would show me where it should be best to move my allocations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:09:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't I lose all my money if I invested in one fund? If I don't manage them, how can I make a decision in which one to use? What should I know or be paying attention to so I can choose one that would be more profitable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:03:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Thrift Savings Plan.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So if the G fund is the only one guaranteed return, how can I invest in the other funds without loosing all my money? If the G fund is managed by experts, how could I manage the other funds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:59:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On Modern Marvels Season 17 Episode 6 Built to Last they showed the black box testing was done, explaining the temperature test clearly showing how they could withstand the temperatures on the 9/11 plane crash but somehow got destroyed that day. Now, for the ones that don't know L-3 is the company that makes the black boxes and also has a contract with the federal government.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:32:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That Anna Kendrick is not the same, she's the actress from the Twilight Saga.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: How TSP works and how can I get the most of it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thrift Savings Plan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:21:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /u/lwarrent I guess somebody recognized her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:19:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in the south and I'm not originally from here either. The only thing I can say is that you can see the difference very clearly. In the south they naturally segregate each other blacks with blacks, whites with whites, hispanics with hispanic, etc.. Now for the hispanics  I can say they tend to stay with each other because of the language barrier but if you meet one that's fully bilingual they would interact with everyone regardless of the race. In the northeaste is completely different you can go to the mall and you see groups of teenagers mingling (whites, blacks, hispanics, mixed, etc.). Trust me there's a big difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:04:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my God! I didn't even know they made postcards about this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:35:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That would be great if an AMA could be done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wonder if any of them are still alive and if they still feel the same way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gay Marriage Is Upheld by Supreme Court </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:07:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 04:04:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You would think something like this would get more attention, same way as the TPP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 04:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Before I posted this I had also posted the article of the Intercept on /r/news and only got 2 up votes. I'm fairly new to Reddit and I've noticed that TPP articles don't come up on the front page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Intercept just published 26 new documents (199 pages) from the Snowden archive. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Controversial GCHQ unit engaged in domestic law enforcement, online propaganda, psychology research manipulating public opinion </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 14:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8 inches?! And flaccid?!? Holy fuck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 04:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If indeed he took your phone and you say you've never been there you shouldn't be worried about going to the police. If you haven't been to that house never in your life then there's no evidence putting you there. Clear your phone's location and call the police. I'm worried about your friend OP, I think your neighbor might have to do with him disappearing. Worry about your friend and call the police! Don't be a shitty friend twice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL The New York Public Library is the proud home of the REAL Winnie-the-Pooh, the actual toy teddy bear that once belonged to Christopher Robin Milne, son of A. A. Milne. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 18:18:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:32:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very interesting OP, keep us updated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Doctors remove woman's reproductive organs accidentally because of her tattoos </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 17:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any update coming soon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 23:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This comment will probably get lost in here but I wanted to tell you that your stories are AMAZING! I'm fairly new to Reddit and happened to stumble upon this thread. I've read others stories here in NoSleep that've been good but none of them compare to yours, none of them have made me feel like yours. I just read them and I'm fascinated as to the way the made me feel. I hope the Penpal movie does come out soon and that you post more stories. You have a new fan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:10:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Waiting for an update! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally! I check everyday for an update.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 20:24:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been voting 3rd party, even when people tell me I'm wasting my vote, I tell them that people need to stop voting for the lesser of two evils. We have to vote smart. Vote for a candidate that talks the talk, study the person. Look up on the issues that he/she has voted for and who backs them up. Please stop voting by parties, race or gender. Make history in a good and correct way!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:14:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Update please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL As Of November 16, 2014, Your Bank Account Has Been Collateralized Against The Derivatives Debt. If The Banks Are Collapsed, Your Money Will Be Used To Pay Down The Derivatives Debt. Therefore, The Regulations Requiring That Your Money Be Insured By The FDIC Are No Longer In Effect! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 02:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 21:08:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you have enough money to get groceries?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 04:26:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That reminds me of the movie Insidious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 22:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please update with the new info.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 17:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Tyrant episode of House explains this. Very interesting how the brain works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that US Representative Robert Pittenger created a booklet on how to be prepared for a terrorist attack and as part of the Emergency Kit contents the bible is one of them. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 17:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll be back in a jiffy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 21:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love conquers all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 19:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read it from the book 50 Things you're not supposed to know from the same author, Russ Kick. Couldn't find a link to that book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL Virginia colonists practiced cannibalism and ate feces. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:10:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>