<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7865</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Websites can now block users based on genetic traits such as sex, ethnicity or susceptibility to disease </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Two Bored 1970s Housewives Helped Create The PC Industry </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Quest to Get Every NES Game in 30 DaysWithout the Web </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:47:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple grows its electric car team but still wont admit the project is real </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Grit in the Google machine: why technology needs the friction of politics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:44:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As US relations thaw, hopes grow in Cuba for a faster, freer internet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:43:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:29:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Given he's the first with this specific condition to receive the treatment, his age may have actually been a factor in why he was chosen - if something goes wrong, he has a much shorter time to live with the consequences that someone younger. It's not like he's the only person who will ever get this treatment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit time machine: See what was on the front page when you joined </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DIY Surgery: The Future Of Medicine? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can see what you mean, but I'm not sure people often get the chance to see others' handwriting often. Apart from the occasional shopping list I'm not sure anyone has seen mine in a long time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 19:26:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Writing in cursive is an important life skill  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Service robots get multiple positive forecasts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> VRs First Big Hit Could Be This Simple Soccer Game </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:30:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 22:41:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you considered contacting [Watchdog](https://ssl.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b006mg74/contact)? Might involve a TV appearance but could do the trick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Despite new information, Pluto will remain a dwarf planet, cosmologist says </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:26:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Deus Ex would be perfect for virtual reality: Mankind Divided executive game director </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:23:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Deus Ex would be perfect for virtual reality: Mankind Divided executive game director </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:23:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Virtual Reality is the Future of Religion </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New Pill Will Let People With Celiac Disease Eat Gluten-Filled Meals Of Their Dreams </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hoverbike could be a reality in three to five years, creators say </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The mysterious way your body changes with the weather </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:14:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers show new Ice Age may begin by 2030 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hitchhiking robot embarking on coast-to-coast tour across US </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ReWalk Robotics's New Exoskeleton Lets Paraplegic Stroll the Streets of NYC </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The paradox of the under-performing professor </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:10:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Lib Dems is now led by a Harry Enfield lookalike </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 22:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There was a double grape in the snack pack I bought for lunch </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:41:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 11:49:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oddly with WSJ articles, if you access them via Google they aren't paywalled.

Here you go:

Technology Will Speed You Through the Airport of the Future

Car-parking robots, tracking beacons and facial recognition systems aim to make travel relaxing

Like a good matre d, the airport of the future will recognize you, greet you by name and know exactly where to put you.

Airports around the world are beginning to move in this direction. At Londons Gatwick Airport, beacons identify you by your smartphone and give GPS-like directions to your gate, pointing out food or shopping along the way. In Germany, robots at Dsseldorfs airport park your car and return it curbside after you land, linking your itinerary to your license plate. Researchers are developing robots that will be able to check your bags and deliver them within minutes of landing.

Facial-recognition systems speed you through passport control in places including Dulles International Airport near Washington, D.C. Some airports use facial-recognition systems to track your movements around terminals. Gates in some airports are automated with doors that flash open like a subway turnstile when you scan your boarding pass or flash your smartwatch.

At the airport of the future, directional signs will be only for backup. Check-in kiosks will be tucked in a corner. Human agents may be even more unnecessary.

The idea is to cut costs, speed up travel and make airports more hospitable. In theory, travelers will be more relaxed, with time to get work done, shop or enjoy entertainment since the airport will track their time and location and tell them where they need to be. Travelers may fret less about sitting down at a nice restaurant when a flight is delayed, rather than camping at the gate.

The airport becomes fun again, says Terry Hartmann, vice president of transportation and industry applications for Unisys Corp., which makes the technology for some of the new airport features. You feel you know whats going on, you interact with the environment and travel is an enjoyable experience.

Of course, planes will still have cramped seats and airlines will still run habitually late. But flyers wont need to arrive 90 minutes early if they know lines and walks are short. Travelers worried about the airport being too invasive can opt out by turning off their Bluetooth connections.

In June, Unisys announced completion of the initial testing phase of a facial-recognition system at Dulles to help U.S. Customs and Border Protection identify imposters attempting to enter the country. New passports have a chip imbedded with data including your photo. The facial recognition systems, also in use in the United Kingdom, Portugal, Australia, New Zealand, Germany and other countries, compare the travelers face with the passport and assign a score. If the match scores high enough, the passport control officer can be more certain of identity than todays system of eyeballing people entering the country.

Manually checking that the person in front of you is the same as a photo five years old is a challenge, Mr. Hartmann says.

At Gatwick Airport, systems estimate queues in real time at security and immigration checkpoints. And some countries have automated border control setups where the facial recognition system automatically clears someone to enter the country without seeing an officer. The U.S. hasnt gone that far partly because not enough travelers have the required chip in their passports.

San Francisco International Airport has 350 beacons installed in Terminal 2 and is testing an app that can give visually impaired passengers audible directions. American Airlines has signed on to a beacon rollout to help customers find their way, starting at Dallas-Fort Worth International Airport.

Virgin Atlantics lounge in London and Cathay Pacifics lounge in San Francisco have beacons that can recognize members when they walk through the door and offer information like food and drink menus. Miami International Airport has been doing limited trials. One potential use: tracking when someone enters the baggage carousel area and when they leave, showing how long they waited for baggage.

By 2018, 44% of airlines world-wide plan to use beacons, compared with 9% that have experimented with the technology currently, according to a survey this year by SITA, an aviation information and communications company. Geneva-based SITA is owned by 430 air transport companies and develops technology for the industry.

In Germany, Dusseldorfs airport is growing in passenger traffic but it doesnt have real estate to expand parking. The answer: a valet parking robot.

From the airports website, travelers make a reservation and enter flight information. Then they drive to a spot in the garage and lock their car. The system reads the license plate and decides where it will park the vehicle. A robot nicknamed Ray, which looks like a giant forklift, picks up the car by the wheels and moves it. At night, robots reshuffle the garage so cars that will be returned the next day are easily accessible. The system tracks if travelers flights are delayed or canceled and has their cars ready when they arrive.

The robots have operated for nearly a year and boosted garage capacity by 32%, says SITA managing director Christian Jahncke, who oversees the robot project. It has had one ding in one of the 40,000 cars handled. One problem: Sometimes the robot sets off the anti-theft alarm. Eventually the screeching stops. High-quality cars are very sensitive to being picked up, Mr. Jahncke says.

Close-in valet robot parking costs 29, or about $32, a day. That compares with 24.5 for premium parking the same distance from the terminal without valet service.

Each robot costs about $250,000, and Dusseldorf uses three so far. In all, Dusseldorf has spent about $1 million, far less than building a new garage, says Mr. Jahncke.

SITA is looking at whether it could make a robot to check bags, says Jim Peters, the firms chief technology officer. Travelers would self-tag, or have a permanent-use bag tag that identifies them. Robots would pick up the bags and maybe even deliver them, speeding up the process and reducing manual labor costs. Managing your baggage and not making it a pain is a part of the airport of the future, Mr. Peters says. The number of airlines offering self-tagging bag drop, but without robots, has increased to 17% from 9% last year. That is expected to rise to 74% of airlines by 2018, according to the SITA technology survey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Technology Will Speed You Through the Airport of the Future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 11:19:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple News is seriously good and might become your only news app </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:51:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:25:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a very cool idea - a lot of potential for epic pranks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair point - I also wonder if the road surface would have any effect on stopping distance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fish feed shortage could provide missing link in the bid to make insects the food of the future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:48:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Verizon to Add Vice Content to Its Coming Mobile Video Service </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:46:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 'Mad genius' no more: the genetic link between creativity and psychosis is pretty weak </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:44:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Solar Cost Less than Half of What EIA Projected </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:43:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Future Dutch roadways made of recycled plastic will snap together like LEGO </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:33:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> More Evidence Life Could Have Come From Space </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does Agave Hold the Secret to Drought-Resistant Farming? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Conservatives Choose More Unwanted Pregnancy and Abortion over Better Birth Control for Teens </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:52:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:02:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that's a very fair response, although it often seems like some people let articles, tv etc form opinions on every aspect of their lives! 

I quite agree about the job issue, I think perhaps more articles about how people can transition to new jobs unaffected by AI (or even create them themselves) would help. Obviously no article would be a perfect solution, but this sort of approach, even if it is very basic, would help people realise it wasn't all doom! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple Pay has launched in the UK </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:41:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Welsh Government Responds to UFO Questions in Klingon </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:40:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Graphic] How worried should you be about artificial intelligence? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:36:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Universal basic income is not the solution to robots taking our jobs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:00:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Two more critical Flash flaws discovered in Hacking Team data breach </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Transhumanist Party presidential candidate to drive Immortality Bus across the U.S. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:56:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sleep On The Side Of A Mountain In These Vertigo-Inducing Pods </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:40:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Digg Cofounder Jay Adelson On The Reddit Mess - And Why It Isn't Digg All Over Again </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:28:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sharks have been discovered living inside an active volcano </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:27:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> M9 crash report man 'feels guilt' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:26:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [podcast] Can technology make meat sustainable? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Virtual reality technology expands to a blitz of uses, including football </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In case anyone is interested, that's equivalent to $8.39 a gallon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:19:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We can always spot the imposters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:15:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would work, but he'd need to be absurdly posh and be saying to a friend as affectionate 'banter'. 
Source: am British. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends what industry you work in, but in general that doesn't sound unreasonable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think we might well develop systems to create life from sequenced DNA to enable robots to terraform planets and that sort of thing, but this would be robots essentially carrying out tasks programmed by humans, so I'm not sure if it would count as robots re-creating life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:50:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I might just be being an idiot, but what exactly do you mean by a 4D object? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How technology could kill the art of lying </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New wireless charging technology can simultaneously power 30 mobile phones or five laptops at distance </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:23:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Inside Amazons Warehouse, Human-Robot Symbiosis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Facebook's new friends icon takes the chip off the womans shoulder </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sensor technology can improve accuracy of prostate cancer diagnosis, research shows </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An unpatched security flaw in Adobe Flash, discovered then kept secret by Italian cyber-surveillance firm Hacking Team, is now being used by malware developers to hack victims computers following the leak of over 400GB of data from the companys servers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:00:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anthropology grad here. Put it like this, you're going to get reeally good at explaining what anthropology is to people in suits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Huge, Alien-Hunting Telescope Could Become Hubble's Successor </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:20:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Desperate man with dying phone jumps on Broadway stage to revive it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:14:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> See the wearable tech of the future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:59:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:34:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some of us are!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why news editors can't ignore online comments </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 13:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Subtle nuances: Language tiff nearly derailed world heritage designations for Japan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 13:38:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robosapiens  merging with machines will improve humanity at an exponential rate </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 13:31:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 18:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> UK officials discussed resettling 5.5m Hong Kong Chinese in Northern Ireland </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A man can dream... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, Steve is a friend of my Mum's - I never expected to see him mentioned on Reddit! 

This is an awesome piece, thanks for sharing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hacking the brain: can DIY neuroscience make you happier </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 14:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists announce major breakthrough in the understanding of memory formation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:16:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new cloud tax law goes into effect in Chicago today, aimed at seeking out more revenue from popular streaming platforms such as Netflix </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:13:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Super-Muscular Pigs Created by Small Genetic Tweak </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:08:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> These headphones let you switch between styles in a snap </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:04:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cuban Babies Are Now HIV-Free </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:03:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Males and females process pain using different cells, a new study with mice suggests </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:39:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Man Who Wants to Turn Our Clothes Into Modular Gadgets </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:29:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Toyota's Mirai will go 312 miles on a tank of hydrogen </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:28:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My dentist saved my tooth, but wiped my memory </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 10:21:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Gene-Editing Technology Has Scientists Excited </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can Technology Ease The Burden Of Caring For People With Dementia? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Conservative research confirms sixth mass extinction has arrived </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:04:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> E3 2015 signals the beginning of overdue change for big budget games </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 18:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> UK's Legalization of CD Ripping is Unlawful, Court Rules </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 18:10:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NASAs Space Launch System  the essential next step in space exploration </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 18:00:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is facial recognition tech really a threat to privacy? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:59:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Space technology: how to clear up space junk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:56:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:04:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. I only have a Wii U and was gutted by the lack of content. 

My SO has theorised that they aren't doing any more games for the Wii U after the announced ones, and are moving Zelda U to NX. I bloody well hope not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bitcoin technology will disrupt derivatives, says banker </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:48:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oculus unveils Half Moon, a VR Rift controller to reach out and touch the virtual world </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:48:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google creates Sidewalk Labs to redesign city living with technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> To make its prototype augmented-reality goggles a product, Magic Leap will have to scale up silicon photonicssomething heavyweights like Intel have struggled to do </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:46:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple iPhones could soon be built in India </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Quantum technology probes ultimate limits of vision </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:44:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Technology to Prevent Drunken Driving Could Soon Come in New Cars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:43:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The World Custard Pie Championships, as seen through a GoPro </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Craziness. Reddit makes the world feel weirdly small! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 00:25:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hang on, is this the Swan in East Peckham? I thought it looked familiar - it's my parents local! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:05:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with this - it looks like a country pub in north Kent or another of the neighbouring counties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:50:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently I've switched genders in a lot of parallel universes! 

Very cool though, thanks for posting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:42:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should try, if only to give the person who decides a good laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:37:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to love that pub - it was all no-nonsense tasty stuff. What a shame its gone all hipster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I particularly cannot cope with the horrendous word 'Brexit' that the Guardian keeps using. If I have to see it repeatedly for the next 2 years I might have to seek out its inventor and bludgeon them with a spoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple To Launch New Flipboard-Like App, While Newsstand Goes Away </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:23:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:30:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm fairly certain its a British passport </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The secret history of Wes Andersons Rushmore </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Revolutionary technology to improve bedside tumor diagnosis in patients </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Solar Impulse makes unplanned landing in Japan, breaking solar flight record </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:44:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Earth organisms survive under low-pressure Martian conditions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Article] Why Dinosaurs Would Have Never Built Spaceships </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:38:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Christians Should Embrace Transhumanism </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:35:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Virtual Reality Gets Huge Boost Thanks to Googles Jump Platform   3D Printing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does Technology Ruin the Expat Experience? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:18:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AI Supercomputer Built by Tapping Data Warehouses for Their Idle Computing Power </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:02:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Muslim Invents First Space Tech Prayer Mat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:01:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google's new finger control technology is straight out of a science fiction movie </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:00:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Genomic sequencing technology advances make food poisoning outbreaks easier to control </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 12:55:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China Unveils World's First ATM that Can Identify Faces </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 12:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 13:03:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Zoltan Istvan of the Transhumanism Party is, but he's not exactly one of the major players </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Theres a fork in the road today": Edward Snowden on the future of surveillance </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Hollywood Is Learning To Tell Stories In Virtual Reality </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> UK Watchdog Says YouTube Viewers Must Know A Video Is Sponsored Before They Click </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drone Giant DJI And Top VC Firm Accel Partners Launch A $10 Million Drone Fund </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DARPAs legacy: Open source simulation for robotics development and testing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:00:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Quantum computer emulated by a classical system </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 16:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> IIWTL: I'd get one of these geodesic walking pods custom built, hook it up with Internet and tour the world </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 16:52:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Twitter Needs to Change, But Only if It Stays the Same </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 13:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robot Journalism: Algorithms are More of a Tool than a Threat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 13:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You could soon be taking a robot pill that delivers drugs with sugar needles </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 11:29:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Man breaks Guinness hoverboard record after standing on a drone </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 10:38:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 13:35:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Must be run by a dude called Fit Nes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 20:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The changes were observed using a European Space Agency satellite, the CryoSat-2, which is designed to sense ice remotely.

According to the article, the GRACE was just used to measure gravitational changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sudden, rapid ice loss detected in previously stable Antarctic region </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 20:03:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In A Little-Seen Early Apple Video, Jobs And Wozniak Talk About The Company's Beginnings </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:54:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Razer will now sell you a mouse pad that glows in 16.8 million colors </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where The Ancients Saw Miracles, Science May Find Climate Answers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 16:08:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tales From an Era When Airlines Knew Good Design </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:43:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If Your Shark Photos Aren't Good, You're Not Close Enough </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In The 18th Century, Wig-Stealing Bandits Roamed England's Countryside </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:12:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Simple website flaw exposed data of charter internet customers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:10:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crows, like humans, store their tools when not in use </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boss switched our offices and now we don't even have a kitchen. I envy your sub-standard mug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:29:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's not even close to a source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:20:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fake refugees and IS fighters

Source please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Inside a Bonkers Plan to Build a 5-Story Skatepark </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The UK's EU referendum is taking us towards a global future of restricted movement and closed borders </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In a future world without oil, we'd end up with thousands of unusable massive oil tankers, some as long as 40-story buildings. Instead of sending them to scrapyards, a team of architects wants to turn them into floating neighborhoods </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Transhuman Future Has Been Humanitys Goal Since Discovering Fire </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Brain-Controlled Bionic Legs Are Finally Here </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Those old AOL CD-ROMs arent junk, theyre history and this guy wants yours </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We Should Consider The Future World As One Of Multi-Species Intelligence </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:31:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could solar-powered floating farms provide enough food for the entire world? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 12:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neuromancer is a scifi book by William Gibson that was released in the mid eighties - it's regarded as a seminal work in the cyberpunk subgenre (it basically transformed cyberpunk from a fringe subgenre to a major form of scifi), and popularised the work cyberspace (the term itself was coined by Gibson in an earlier work. 

The story is set in a dystopian future, where people can log onto a VR digital space called the Matrix, which is kind of a VR web, and people have gone as far as suggesting it actually influenced the way the web was developed.

It's an amazing book and I highly recommend reading it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Neuromancer Movie Lives Again </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 11:30:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Burglars use drone helicopters to target homes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 10:44:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Case of the Rickety Cossack reveals unease about our fossil past </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 10:13:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spotify Is Turning Starbucks Baristas Into Coffee Shop DJs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 10:13:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:10:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't understand why you've been downvoted so much - this is an astute point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As technology enables us to live ever longer, Earth is set to become a crowded place. A look at whether space colonisation is a realistic solution to overpopulation, and how soon we could be settling on Mars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 12:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Used cigarette butts may power future computers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 12:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Tech Bubbles Happen </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 12:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Trident whistleblower 'to hand himself in to police' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 12:06:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Indonesia sends three warships and a plane to turn away migrant boats </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 11:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chasing Ghosts in a Cartel-Controlled Mexican Town </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 11:54:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Car of the future to have a supercomputer of the size of a stereo : Nvidia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 11:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spy games: US quietly calls North Korea's missile bluff </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 11:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> People with disabilities losing jobs to technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 11:36:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why tech companies think they can do news and how traditional news organisations can fight back </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 11:04:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nissan will be ready with autonomous driving by 2020 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 10:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Edward Snowden: Complete web encryption is the best way to counter mass surveillance </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:42:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 'Venom' vulnerability found in virtualization platforms allows complete access to all user data </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In Ikea's Kitchen Of The Future, You Won't Have A Fridge, But You Will Have Drones </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:23:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The US government wants to speed up deployment of vehicle-to-vehicle communication </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:22:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tiny Victorian Biospheres Could Re-green the Worlds Most Polluted Cities </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:15:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Prozac treatment can help anxious dogs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:12:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Going west: China's expansion plans take aim at US supremacy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 12:24:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Next Big Future: DARPA investigating ways to Restore Active Memory </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 11:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Andrew McAfee: The Second Machine Age Will Awaken Us From a Malthusian Nightmare </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 10:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What the UK election results mean for the world </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MRI wire map might predict schizophrenia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 15:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Quantify me: The hidden risks of a wearable future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 11:57:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> India's endangered lion numbers increase </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 11:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Virtual-Reality Tools Will Redefine Remote Work </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 11:20:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> High profile tech start-up Ninja Blocks goes bust </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 11:18:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Iran admits technology makes media control impossible </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 11:02:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Snoopers' charter set to return to UK law as Theresa May suggests Conservative majority could lead to huge increase in surveillance powers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 13:45:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Architecture Review: An Exclusive Look at Facebooks New Headquarters </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Antler trade led up to Viking invasion of England </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 14:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they must all use the same bunch of close-minded focus groups </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new age in automaking is about to arrive as 3D-printed car maker Local Motors develops a plant with the aim of starting commercial production in 2015 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 11:55:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The underground lab testing sleep in space </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 11:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bill Nye is testing a spaceship that rides on sunbeams </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 10:37:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 08:56:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And yet he named Apple's big release at the time [after her](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apple_Lisa#Etymology) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 11:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/futurology would be full of shiny tech with packaging making lots of outrageous promises, but which turn out to be nowhere near as good when you get them home. Their employees would be wildly enthusiastic about their stock and condescending to any shoppers questioning their products' claims </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Beginning of the end for ageing? Scientists identify DNA bundle that plays major role </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 20:07:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 14:06:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was posted [yesterday](http://i.imgur.com/rNqnIAA.jpg?1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We are on the cusp of a third industrial revolution, where a convergence of new technologies in communication, energy and transport will completely change the structure of the economy from linear to circular </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 13:40:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Human gene editing has arrived  here's why it matters </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 13:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Era of Japan's All-Powerful Videogame Designers Is Over </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 13:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sasaki Architecture convert a former disco club into an office space with floating walls and pillars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 12:45:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 10:42:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if you're going to the trouble of learning how to talk absolute bullshit, why not just learn enough to know what you're talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sensor to help robots read human expressions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 09:41:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ATM Cash Withdrawals Based on Vein, Iris Recognition to Become Possible in Korea Next Year </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 09:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rosetta Captures Stunning New Images of Comets Surface and Activity </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Agriculture An Industry Ripe for Disruption States Peter Diamandis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:56:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Article] This animal is so weird that researchers are calling it the platypus of dinosaurs' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:55:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Electric solar wind sail could make bidirectional manned Mars flights economically feasible </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 15:16:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> VR feedback glove to bring sense of touch to virtual reality </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 13:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How much of the Amazon rainforest would it take to print the Internet? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 13:07:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who you call, what you post on Facebook and where you are will soon all be used by banks to gauge how much money you can borrow </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 12:56:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Horticulturalists develop two new berries </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 12:55:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Human ancestors had tentacles </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 12:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robots Step Into New Planting, Harvesting Roles </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 12:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ang Lee film Billy Lynns Long Halftime Walk to force new cinema projection technology development </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 12:25:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Arctic nations meet under threat of new Cold War </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 11:38:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Carphone Warehouse Is Launching Its Own UK Mobile Network next Month </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 11:14:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:48:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Salmon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:15:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The shoes have got their own twitter account https://twitter.com/ronniesshoes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My SO is having a stoma reversal on Monday - any advice/tips? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 13:34:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd love to hear any advice about what he can expect and what I can do to help

Edit: Thanks so much for all the response and advice, it is really appreciated. Sorry for the slow response - it's been a crazy few days. His surgery went great, so now its onto the recovery process!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The future of the Internet may well depend on a trade agencys decision in a patent case about teeth </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 15:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Graphene-based spintronics to enable faster, more efficient computer processing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 13:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First report of a new crop virus in North America </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 13:04:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Next-generation supercomputer will have 180 petaflop/s peak performance </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 12:58:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Meet Walnut, the crane who fell in love with her zookeeper </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 12:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Over Game Delays and Remakes? Welcome to Consoles in 2015 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 12:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MINI augmented vision eyewear enhances safety using head-up display </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 12:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kindergartners who shared iPads in class scored higher on achievement tests </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 11:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:14:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I 100% agree! I think this could be one of the biggest markets for replacement bionics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What if a bionic leg is so good that someone chooses to amputate? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 14:58:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 13:34:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In theory yes, but we're going to have to scrap retirement too. Here in the UK we're already facing serious problems due to our ageing population, and the sad reality is that we'd be better off if less of them were living as long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Premier League set for video technology in five years - Dutch FA </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 19:31:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Two ancient human fossils from Laos reveal early human diversity </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:11:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm quite shocked at how hostile everyone is being - I asked a genuine question after posting an article I found interesting. Clearly I have missed something - so sorry to have blighted your day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robotics researcher discusses robot evolution </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:06:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:01:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got that part, but I'm not clear on why. I'm not a Tumblr user so I'm not familiar with what's commonly posted there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What can Deus Ex: Human Revolution teach us about the ethics of human augmentation? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:40:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry? Can you please explain what you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chicago man sues Facebook over facial recognition use in Tag Suggestions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:30:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:23:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Breathtaking Thorncrown Chapel is one of Americas greatest architectural masterpieces </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:23:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Urban Drivers Are Emitting Way More Carbon Dioxide Than We Thought </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:12:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This massive airship is getting a $2.7 million grant to revolutionize transport </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:09:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Research seeks to make robotic 'human patient simulators' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:04:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Best Wearables Will Be The Ones You Throw Away </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 17:56:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rise of the Machines: The Future has Lots of Robots, Few Jobs for Humans </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 16:50:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple wants people to stop sleeping in front of its stores for new products </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 16:32:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Don't People Understand Nintendo Directs? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 13:59:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sensory augmentation of blind rats suggests we can use tech to expand our senses </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:14:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Greece tells creditors it will run out of cash on April 9 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:41:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New tool could make it easy to build dynamic virtual worlds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Patients, caregivers differ on end-of-life choices </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:19:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It's 3015, and Times Square is crammed inside a giant skyscraper </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:14:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I completely agree - I thought it would be interesting to share this to see if anyone thought it was a good idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> BBC uses BitTorrent Bundle to sell a 10-episode set of Doctor Who </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Periodic Table Of Elements That The World Is Running Out Of </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:06:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nintendo could learn a lot from Netflix </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:04:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scary times for Europe's comet-chaser Rosetta </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 11:14:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Console wars pre-date the web (admittedly not the Internet, but pre-web internet was hardly tailored to arguing about video game consoles) - the first was between the Sega Genesis (89) and the SNES (91). The web was only made publicly available in August 91 and wasn't popularised til 93 when the Mosaic browser was released.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 11:01:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Possibly, but the game pad makes it great as an entertainment box too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:56:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try the [Loving Hut](http://archway.lovinghut.co.uk/) in Archway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a similar experience a while back and made a concious decision not to thank him when he got off. Thanks to habit I ended up thanking him anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Our prime minister either celebrates April Fools a day early or thinks he's related to Kim Kardashian </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:29:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Source: http://www.independent.co.uk/news/people/david-cameron-claims-hes-related-to-kim-kardashian-did-you-know-im-13th-cousins-10146513.html  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 10:06:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go with someone else - BT are a useless nightmare! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 01:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At my work we don't even have the means to make tea. A co-worker got 300 employees to sign a petition requesting a kettle and the HR head just laughed in her face when she delivered it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:10:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 20:36:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please excuse my ignorance, but what would an exoskeleton for riding a motorcycle do? Would it improve safety somehow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> British probation officers face redundancy in plan to replace them with machines </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 20:33:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah my bad, i will delete it - thanks for letting me know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 14:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If there aren't many longitudinal studies, how do people develop informed opinions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 13:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If men are going to start wearing skirts, they will need to learn about the magical world of thermal tights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Walking with exoskeletons: The road to improving human ability </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 12:41:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Secrecy on the Set: Hollywood Embraces Digital Security </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 12:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Flood alerts issued in Kashmir as rivers cross danger mark </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 12:31:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Uber denies security breach despite reports of logins for sale online </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 12:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 11:54:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a 'friend' like that at uni - we came to the conclusion that she probably has [histrionic personality disorder](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Histrionic_personality_disorder) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Simple and cheap DNA editing is hereand even its inventors worry about its awesome power to alter our genetic future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 11:32:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drone herding sheep </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 11:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 11:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's interesting - the author sees it as a really bad thing. I'm not sure I'd want to spend the bulk of my life away from the physical world, but I'd love to be able to make regular holidays! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Sofalarity is Near: a hypothetical point in human history when the majority of human beings spend most of their time engaged in activities that have little or no connection to actual life in the physical world </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 11:15:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 05:00:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those two things don't sound mutually exclusive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 03:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That film caused a spate of mini breaks among my friends. I've seen so many photos and heard so many stories about how wonderful a city it is that I almost don't need to go there myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 02:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hackers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Morphing wings help drones manage collisions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 11:00:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Voice Control Will Force an Overhaul of the Whole Internet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 13:06:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Archivists unearth rare first edition of 'The Map that Changed the World' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 12:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spooky action at a distance demonstrated in single-particle quantum experiment for first time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 12:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Feel-Good Switch: The Radical Future of Emotion </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 12:14:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Utah reinstates death by firing squad </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 12:11:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ice age people hunted horse and camel 13,300 years ago </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 12:10:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Russia to resume space tourism in 2018 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 11:54:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The NFL Will Broadcast a Game Only on the Web </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 10:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Waves of the Future May Bend Around Metamaterials </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 10:37:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> More flavorful, healthful chocolate could be on its way </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 10:35:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could the death star destroy a planet? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 17:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When Steve Jobs Returned To Apple, Jony Ive Thought His Job Was Toast </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 17:41:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Future of pro sports wearables: Accurate betting and more TV data </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 16:34:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MRIs show our brains shutting down when we see security prompts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 16:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In Bristol, you can soon ride on a poop-powered bus four days a week </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 16:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Make the NHS a well-being service not sickness service </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 15:15:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What Doomsday Preppers Would Eat After the Apocalypse </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 15:04:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lack of effective timing signals could hamper 'Internet of things' development </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 15:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers find the gene that makes us 3D </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 15:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> CISA security bill: An F for security but an A+ for spying </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 12:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google Maps now adds 31 Indian heritage sites </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 11:56:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A prototype hybrid quadcopter can fly several times farther than conventional battery-powered ones </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 11:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An 'octopus' robot with eight limbs developed to clear rubble in Fukushima, Japan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 11:07:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Edward Snowden: Without change, future surveillance will be in the hands of countries, companies and criminals </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 20:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Remarkable Story of a Tech Incubator Inside a Prison </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 15:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Doctors claim first successful penis transplant </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 15:15:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A cyber war staged in central London </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 15:12:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> UK bank Halifax trials heartbeat ID technology for online banking </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 09:29:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Exterminate Your Stress With This Dalek Relaxation Tape </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 09:23:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New-age gaming: Nintendo's recovery hinges on new profit model </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 09:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Attack of the drones: new Audi commercial goes cyberpunk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 09:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google to open first UK garage to fix small firms web problems </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 09:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-09 08:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a commercial/concept video [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AtRz6UBLNrk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Samsung and Ikea collaborate on universal wireless charging </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 13:42:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Light photographed as a wave and a particle for the first time ever </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 11:03:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google will test 90% internet service for parts of southern hemisphere via Internet Balloons by the end of 2015 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 10:59:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google+ Split Into Photos and Streams, Gets a New Head </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 10:57:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bjork's next music video will be available for Oculus Rift </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 10:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 01:21:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most people regard ending ageing to be akin to magic - it's never taught as a possibility in schools, and has not entered mainstream consciousness as a viable idea. Because of this it's not widely discussed in mainstream media, and so most people never get the chance to hear about anything related to sens, let alone the organisation itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 01:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totes amazeballs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 01:10:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Links to websites that steal their content. They're usually fairly easy to spot as they tend to have a very generic theme and no authors  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 01:07:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My MIL donated a bag of my clothes to charity - they'd been drying and I put them there as I didn't have time to put them all away. I had a bunch of stuff in there I really liked that was no longer on sale :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 10:09:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Assassins Creed. The storylines are just absurd, the collectibles tedious and 3 has the most infuriating use of loading screens since Sonic 06. Like the sea battles in 4 though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 19:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Fun fact - as long as your doing it frequently enough, you [can't get pregnant while breast feeding](http://www.plannedparenthood.org/health-info/birth-control/breastfeeding) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> No, Human Head Transplants Will Not Be Possible By 2017 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 16:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Brain signals turn into drone commands in Lisbon presentation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 13:32:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Future of Consumer Tech Is About Making You Forget It's There </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 12:38:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers have created a biologically inspired computer model that can autonomously design urban residential layouts without human assistance </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-26 17:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There Aren't Many Women in Magic, But Those Who Are Kick Ass </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-26 15:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-26 15:31:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's been a pretty awesome week for futurology in general! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Facebook Is Adding a New Feature to Help with Suicide Prevention in the US </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-26 12:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cyber thugs taking data hostage: ransomware has been around a while, but has been making a big comeback </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-26 11:08:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Men Who Mine Volcanoes: Photos from two days in a sulfurous crater in Indonesia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-26 10:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thought-controlled prosthetics: Pioneering bionic reconstruction surgery performed for first time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-25 01:02:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Internet of Things will soon be joining us in space </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 23:47:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hydrogen Highways Are Becoming Realities In California </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 19:12:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 19:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The guys over at /r/farming have [weighed in on this](http://www.reddit.com/r/farming/comments/2wzsgo/just_came_across_this_vertical_farming_story_do/covl838) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Luring deer away from livestock feed with fall cover crops </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 19:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> University of Surrey Claims 1Tbps Speed via 5G Mobile Technology Test </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 19:05:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drone Vs. Volcano: How Robotic Flyers are Changing Exploration </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 18:35:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Arup and RFA Fenwick Iribarren Architects reveal their design for the new Qatar Foundation Stadium </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 16:26:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Actual race on moon could decide Lunar XPrize winner </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 16:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Vacant Lot In Wyoming Will Become One Of The World's First Vertical Farms </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 16:16:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Godzilla Hotel Opening in Japan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 16:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 13:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good luck all :) I hope whoever wins is justly rewarded for their efforts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What was the last music CD you ever bought? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 09:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For most of us, the CD is a dead format for music. So what was the CD that will forever be your final purchase?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Farmers Eye Drones For The Future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 17:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> US emerging tech policies are risking the countrys place in the future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 16:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> US Treasury Wakes Up in the 21st Century, Starts Accepting PayPal </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 14:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Apples iCar may never happen </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 14:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Out of Africa: Did humans migrate in a single wave or in phases based on weather? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 14:11:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Boston Is Partnering With Waze to Make Its Roads Less of a Nightmare </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 13:35:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Christ the Redeemer mapped by drone to create first ever accurate model </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 13:01:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> BIG designs looping country villa to showcase high-end cars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 12:55:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Indian IT firms eye robotics; driverless cars for next round of growth </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 12:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Next Big Future: DARPA Developing Squad level Robotics and sensing technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 10:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Antarctica: Mystery continent holds key to mankind's future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 10:23:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Internet for all: The plan to turn one billion vehicles into free WiFi hotspots </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 19:12:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Samsung Design Stinks </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 19:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could Analyzing How Humans Think Make Better Video Games? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 19:05:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In Driverless Cars, Champion Racing Skills Will Come Standard </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 18:32:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cyber attacks on Israel traced to Gaza: researchers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 18:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> These Headphones From 1927 Look So Much Worse Than Earbuds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 18:16:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Proposed small drone rules give hope for drone journalism in the US </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 18:03:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Penguins can't taste the umami flavor of fish </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 18:02:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 15:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those of you that have bought the Link Amiibo - has it got the yellow stalk? Did you find that a problem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Link is the most popular Nintendo Amiibo </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 10:19:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Buildings should make us feel better </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 13:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The oncoming collapse: Is humanity's future the end of civilisation? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 13:52:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The oncoming collapse: Is humanity's future the end of civilisation? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 12:21:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could driverless cars own themselves? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 12:20:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> BBC Radio 1 DJ Zane Lowe is joining Apple </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 12:18:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Amsterdam to host worlds first drone circus </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 12:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Technology Is Unlocking A Lifestyle Without Keys  And Experts Say That Invites Risk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 11:59:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Football should embrace technology to prevent, monitor concussions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 11:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How terrifying food technology has changed our lives </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 11:50:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3D Printing on Mars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 11:46:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What Should Hospitals Look Like In The Future? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-13 14:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-13 12:05:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why was this downvoted? It's an entirely legitimate comment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Future of Crime: Smartphone Tracking, Neurohacking, and AI Assisted Murder </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Stranger than pulp fiction: meet Bob Nygaard, America's psychic-crime fighter | </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 15:57:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Artifact from the Future: Meat Counter </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 15:51:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Angelina Jolie Just Might Direct Captain Marvel </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 15:44:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are analogue quantum computers still wishful thinking? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 15:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ebola Arises Again and Again </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 15:37:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3 Tech Futures A Particle Accelerator On Long Island Could Bring Us </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 15:33:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mars rover nearing marathon achievement </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 14:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In The Office Of The Future, You'll Scale A Climbing Wall To Harvest Your Lunch </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 13:38:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These days both countries have some great beers, but they don't tend to get exported </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-10 17:01:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the biggest problem is that most countries are governed by politicians who change after quite a small period of time, so stuff like this usually isn't worth making a big deal of yet, because the effects will mostly be felt after they are out of office. 
They'll probably tell you it's your fault you haven't opted to become a cyborg.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Academic article on magic: Magic trick choices aren't as random as they seem </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-10 16:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Future of space exploration: Drones, submarines and self-replicating robots </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-10 13:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Definitive Strategy To Eliminate the Gender Pay Gap </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-10 13:57:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could Apple be planning a search engine to outshine Google? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-10 12:37:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Planning Korea envisions futuristic pod habitats in Paris </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-10 12:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Flyability set to empower drones for good deeds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-10 12:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Xbox Marketing Fail... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-10 10:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robots replacing human factory workers at faster pace </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-10 10:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mars is the next step for humanity  we must take it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 16:57:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Argodesign's drone ambulance quickens emergency responses </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 16:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mars One mission: a one-way trip to the red planet in 2024 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 15:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-09 12:58:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for posting - good to know about! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 20:00:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Back when I was studying for a degree in anthropology (and hence studying evolution), I was astounded by the number of intelligent people who would ask me whether humans had stopped evolving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Never mind the ethics: Babies from three sets of DNA is the start of great things for humanity </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 16:02:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Ubuntu phone is real and going on sale next week </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 16:00:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> FAA appears to be attempting to expand its authority to moon activities </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 15:34:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Washington lawmakers want computer science to count as foreign language </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 15:31:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We Can Now Build Autonomous Killing Machines. And That's a Very, Very Bad Idea </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 15:29:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> British web surveillance violated human rights, court rules </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 15:27:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> With HoloLens, the future of reality is augmented </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 15:25:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 13:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out the bar/restaurant [Solar](http://www.solarberlin.com/en/) - its hidden away off the main road (you have to access it through the car park next to a carpet shop)  and doesn't look like much from the outside, but once you go in you go on a glass elevator up the side of the building to the top and its really awesome. Amazing city views, cool interior and great food. A bit expensive but totally worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Twitter Is in Danger of Becoming the Bing of Social Media </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 13:38:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alibabas Teabag Stunt Doesnt Prove That Drone Delivery Works </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 11:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Huge Engineering Project May Be Our Best Chance At Colonizing Space </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 10:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Artifact from the Future: VR Eating </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 10:48:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Facebook signs users up to privacy policy that allows it to track everywhere on the internet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-04 11:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists make large-scale holographic displays an affordable reality </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Our taste for alcohol goes back millions of years </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:14:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Update on Shackleton Energy Moon Mining </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:12:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists use pulsed light to modify the protein that causes milk allergy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:09:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Eero could do for Wi-Fi what Nest did for thermostats </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:03:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google killed 500 million bad ads in 2014 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:01:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Batman   Robin is terrible, and here's why you should watch it immediately </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 16:59:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sony Sells Online Game Business </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 16:57:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> UK aiming for 10 million solar-powered homes by 2020 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 16:54:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Our ancient 'small brain' can adapt to robot arms </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 16:53:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 08:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a very important clarification. They do completely different things to butter when hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How mathematics inspires Doctor Who: Scriptwriter Stephen Thompson explains all </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 12:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Amusingly Blunt Senate Note Dropped by Staffer, Picked Up by Reporter Describes Hearing as BS </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 12:05:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Japan to launch new spy satellite </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 12:00:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Everyday life can make an awesome video game </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 11:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Microsoft to Invest in Android Startup Cyanogen, Says Report </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 11:54:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google admits Glass had major problems, says its time for a pause, strategy reset </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 11:40:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Forgotten 13th Avenue That New York City Built and Then Destroyed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 11:38:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You want cheaper smartphones so Foxconn will use robots to make them </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 10:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Diamond can replace silicon for computer chips for faster, lighter and simpler devices </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 10:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sony is now actually removing features from PlayStation Vita </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 18:22:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seven future uses for Microsoft's HoloLens that will make someone disgustingly rich </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 18:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Open source surge: Companies may ditch patents in favour of open tech research </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 14:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Forget Virtual Reality. Are You Ready for Virtual Sushi? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 14:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Internet of Things just got a watchdog: FTC issues official report </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 17:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drones Will Be Everywhere Watching, Listening, andPlanting Millions of Trees? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 17:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> IED blasts leave distinct scars on the brain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 17:17:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is facial recognition the next privacy battleground? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 14:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China Shows Off Drones Fired From Cannon </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 14:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chemical pollutants are breaking polar bears' penises </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 14:36:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Twitter introduces postcode targeted ads in time for the UK general election </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 14:09:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Star Trek-style transporter comes closer to reality </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 12:25:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why We're Looking for Alien Life on Moons, Not Just Planets </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 12:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Don't Worry: Drones Are Making Sure You'll Never Have To Go Without Wine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-27 12:21:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Now departing: Are virtual reality holidays the future? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 13:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The choking problem of Asias air pollution </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 13:33:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> London's Skyline Is About To Get Very Crowded </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 13:12:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This concept turns old phone parts into a supercomputer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 11:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cobots enhance robotic manufacturing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 11:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are We Passing Through a Bottleneck, or Will the Explosion of Existential Risks Continue? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 11:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dr. Peter H. Diamandis  Intelligent Self-directed Evolution </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 11:35:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It's complicated: why playing a video game is like having a relationship </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 10:18:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Unease for What Microsofts HoloLens Will Mean for Our Screen-Obsessed Lives </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 10:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New algorithm resolves Wi-Fi interference problems </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-23 15:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researcher uncovers surprising cause of the demise of Easter Island indigenous population </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 15:14:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Innovative organ preservation system to boost transplant rates and success </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 11:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google Hopes to Take the Web Directly to Billions Lacking Access </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 11:32:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AGI Innovations secures $4 Million in Funding to develop Artificial General Intelligence - AI that can be taught and not programmed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 11:03:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In next 15 years, Gates Foundation sees big jump for poor </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 11:02:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The world pays too high a price for cheap meat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 10:09:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In theory, the Milky Way could be a 'galactic transport system' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-21 13:23:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The World Is Watching Our Net Neutrality Debate, So Lets Not Screw This Up </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-21 13:22:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Predictions About The Last Decade, From Futurists In 2005 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-21 13:20:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Your call is important to Google: A YouTube horror story </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-21 12:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Its time for Microsoft to open source Internet Explorer: Being the only closed source mainstream browser isn't a good position </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-21 10:59:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Solar Impulse announces path for historic round-the-world flight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-20 09:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Working Lab-Grown Human Muscles to Serve as Clinical Trials in a Dish </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 18:24:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bacteria build 'coat' for medical implants </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 18:22:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is NASA's asteroid mission the agency's political downfall? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 15:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WinSun China builds worlds first 3D printed villa and tallest 3D printed apartment building </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 15:52:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 'Molecular scissors' could prevent genetic diseases before conception </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 15:16:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Vega ready to launch spaceplane </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 14:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists tame Schrodinger's cat for a new type of quantum computer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 14:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A "Robot Chicken" Animator Turned A Nintendo Power Glove Into The Ultimate Stop-Motion Animation Tool </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 13:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Satellite Internet: meet the hip new investment for Richard Branson, Elon Musk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 10:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Britain could become a leader in the billion-pound drone industry </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-16 19:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Norwegian Man Got Fined for Not Keeping His Promise to Murder Someone </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-16 12:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The normal future: Tomorrow is never as futuristic as we want it to be </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-14 17:59:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An un-consenting child, a pointless invasive surgery: is there any moral difference between male and female circumcision? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-13 20:35:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> GM open to working with Google on self-driving car technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-13 12:31:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 4K TVs Are Forked. You Should Wait Before You Buy One </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-13 12:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This black box promises to wirelessly charge a dozen gadgets at once </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 10:04:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Cyberattack Has Caused Confirmed Physical Damage for the Second Time Ever </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 13:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One of Silicon Valley's Top VC Firms Just Invested Millions in Weed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 13:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Vinyl goes viral: McDonald's Japan sorry for foreign objects in food </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 10:33:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Glyph head-mounted display shoots DLP images directly into your eyeballs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 16:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Adventures in Mapmaking: Mapping a Fracking Boom in North Dakota </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 15:22:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Car of the future emerges at Las Vegas electronics show </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 15:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Vipp's plug and play shelter serves as a comfortable retreat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 15:20:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Virtuix Omni gaming treadmill is finally a finished product </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 15:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Robotification of Society is Coming </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 15:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Adding leap second this year expected to cause Internet problems </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-07 15:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Imaginary meal tricks the body into losing weight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-06 11:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Internet of Anything: The 3-D Printer That Can Spit Out Custom Electronics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 13:16:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apocalypse when? Infographic guide to Doomsday threats </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 12:05:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nvidia wants to power the self-driving car of the future (and every display inside that car) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 11:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NVIDIAs Tegra X1 will put a teraflop of computing power in your pocket </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 11:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How 3-D printing could revolutionize war and foreign policy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-05 10:48:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 16:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I misread this as Pot Noodle. I was trying to figure out how that would work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 15:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The article is based on a [press release](http://www.sony.net/SonyInfo/News/Press/201412/14-118E/) Sony released today, so I assume there must be something new about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New Nintendo products may use Sharp's wild 'free-form' displays </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 11:00:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 10:59:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This is the press release](http://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2014-12/bmj-ian121214.php) it was based on. It's one of the most poorly researched releases I have seen in ages - honestly I have no idea how it got funded. 

Plus its waay out of date as moral panic-fuelling research goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Greenpeace Accidentally Destroyed A World Heritage Site </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 10:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sony invents a wearable display to make your glasses smart </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 10:47:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Future of construction: Working towards bricklaying drones that can 3D print in flight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 19:54:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 18:23:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True - here in the UK we have problems with coastal erosion in some areas, and if the cost of preventing it is too high, it's standard practice to let houses fall into the sea. (Obviously is relatively uncommon, but it does happen). 

We have to be practical about when it makes sense to save a settlement, and when it is better to cut our losses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As Carbon Dioxide Grows, Tropical Trees Do Not </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 18:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Neal Stephenson Is Helping To Make Snow Crash's Metaverse A Reality </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 18:17:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Uber Isn't the Only Future for the Business of Other People's Cars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 17:39:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Futuristic Office Doesn't Have Chairs And Desks </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 17:35:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Getting bot responders into shape </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 17:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Diabetic Charts A Year's Worth Of His Health Data </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 17:24:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Climate change will leave Christmas trees in hot water </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 16:48:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> McDonald's is running out of fries in Japan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 13:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Warning: Cybotopia Ahead by 2030 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 13:06:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rolls-Royce oX bridge concept visualizes futuristic autonomous vessels </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-15 12:45:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AI With a Heart: Will 2015 be the year of the personal robot? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-15 11:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google Glass to enter International Space Station </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-15 10:23:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Data From Our Wearables Is Now Courtroom Fodder </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 13:21:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 15:48:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not involved in this personally, but the point is once they have the lantern they can keep accessing new content, not have to get a new lantern (or in your version USB stick) each time they want new data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wearable Tech Is Getting There. Next Challenge: Actually Look Good </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 15:10:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Roomba's New Cousin Is Built for Custom Programming </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 13:00:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 10:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How are you going to get it to people? The value in Outernet is its ability to be used by people in remote areas with little infrastructure - sending them all USB sticks would be incredibly expensive and a logistical nightmare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 10:33:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really like this site - it feels way more unique than most! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 17:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would also like to know if anyone has tried it, but bear in mind this is not the full internet - it's a broadcast selection of articles and bits and pieces, so it won't be a replacement for a dastardly service provider.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 17:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blocks it on Chrome fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sony is planning a crossover movie between Men in Black and Jump Street </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 16:21:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 14:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What did he say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Contact lens merges plastics and active electronics via 3-D printing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 14:10:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A silk casing enables long-lasting, implantable Wi-Fi medical devices </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 16:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why We Need a Federal Agency on Robotics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 16:06:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 13:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, but you can use it to print lots of cars, and these machines are going to drop in cost far faster than a traditional automobile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Malaria deaths halved since 2000 in quest for total eradication </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 12:35:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The rarely-seen robots that package what we eat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 12:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why I shunned the US and started up in London </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 12:27:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In the future youll never stop learning </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 11:21:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tortoise regains mobility with LEGO wheelchair </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 11:11:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Monkey-style 'bromance' helps macaques weather life's hard knocks </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 10:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Berkeley lab builds world record tabletop-size particle accelerator </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 10:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sources: FAA May Require Licenses To Fly Commercial Drones </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 10:22:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Artificial leaf technology can cleanly produce hydrogen fuel </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 10:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Autonomous vehicles: are there downsides? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 16:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Will robot shop assistants spell the end for shop work? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 16:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> World-first 'bionic bra' inches closer to reality </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 13:51:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wireless brain sensor-transmitter could unchain neuroscience from cables </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 11:02:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What Will Life Be Like Inside A Computer? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-08 11:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lung scans predict best meds to treat TB </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-04 11:21:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Horizontal elevators will change how we design and build cities </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-04 11:17:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Report: artificial intelligence will cause structural collapse of law firms by 2030 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-02 10:20:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 5 Open Source Home Automation Projects We Love </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 15:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google-Glass Deal Thrusts Intel Deeper Into Wearable Tech </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 11:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Designed to address the issue of Singapores rapidly aging population, this conceptual project combines residential living for seniors with vertical urban farming </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 11:49:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Firefly Space Systems charges full-speed toward low Earth orbit </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 10:20:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Amazon's new robot army is ready to ship </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 10:02:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why some posthumanisms are better than others </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-28 12:17:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Martian obsession: The story of Black Beauty, a shiny, scaly-skinned, 4.4-billion-year-old rock from Mars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-28 12:03:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ebay's new 'smart stores' feel like the future of shopping </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-28 11:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Internet Dads: On Having "The Talk" In The Digital Age </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-28 11:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-28 11:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to take your class. That sounds like an awesome unit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Off-Earth mining: The challenge of turning asteroids into gas stations in space </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 15:14:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Next Era of Designers Will Use Data as Their Medium </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 13:16:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Science fiction: How not to build a future society </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 12:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Natasha Vita-More, "Informed Radical Life Extension, by Design" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 11:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-26 16:59:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you sure you aren't applying cosmetics to an object if you make-up something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-26 16:16:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine the conspiracies if it were to be adopted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-26 16:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Airships can only be so high because they are lighter than air, I assume the weight of a rocket and all its fuel would make keeping them afloat impossible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ideo Perfectly Predicted The Future Of Google In 2003 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-26 14:37:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NASA is the first to 3D-print objects in space </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-26 10:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Genetics Suggest Autism Isnt Just One DisorderIts Hundreds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 14:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nanodot team aims to charge phones in less than a minute </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 12:23:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Meet Andy, The Robot Headed Into The Moons Lake of Death </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 12:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 11:59:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the kind of awesome, leftfield stuff that makes futurology great. 

It might be a long way from being practical, but it's very cool to imagine this stuff might one day be normal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 11:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a spammer - I post a wide mix of sites! This user has had it in for me since I started reporting their (and their other account's) spammy submissions to futurology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> IDEO Envisions the Future of Self-Driving Cars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 18:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> SpaceX Planning to Land Autonomous Reusable Rockets on Drone Ships </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 17:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientists urge governments to turn old TV frequencies into free super WiFi </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 16:46:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Automakers aim to drive away car computer hackers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 16:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Art and Science Team Up To Steal Your Attention With Magic </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 16:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drones and virtual reality headsets are a delicious combination </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 16:36:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Citizen Explorers, Meet Your New Submersible </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 16:18:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The FAA's upcoming small-drone rules could be brutally restrictive </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 15:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Primates indispensable for regeneration of tropical forests </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 15:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could we encounter the Terminator in real life? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 14:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 40,000-year-old blood brings mammoth cloning closer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 13:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Glorious Old-School Gadgets of Ferris Buellers Day Off </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 13:10:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The monitored office: Dystopian future workplace or efficient business of tomorrow? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 13:07:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The monitored office: Dystopian future workplace or efficient business of tomorrow? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 11:14:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are We Fit for the Future? Making the Case for Moral Bioenhancement </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 11:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tech Trends Shaping The Future Of Medicine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 11:11:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What Barbie Looks Like When She's Battling Aliens, Taking Nude Rides On Dragons, And Getting Zombified </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 10:52:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Advanced cyberspying tool dates from 2008 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 10:47:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Linguistic Mapping Reveals How Word Meanings Sometimes Change Overnight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 10:38:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Facebooks social network for businesses reportedly launching January 2015 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 10:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> After a three-year copyright battle, Aereo gives up the ghost </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-21 16:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I spent a weekend on the high-tech cruise ship of tomorrow </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-21 16:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-21 13:02:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed. I find his nice persona somewhat disturbing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 17:50:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah yes, you are correct - I've just found the [original on Behance](https://www.behance.net/gallery/21263599/iPad-Glass). Looks like the garbled text accompanying this is just some nonsensical waffle to justify posting it as an article.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 17:43:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to get a pair of these so much! 

If they become a commercial product, you just know they'll become a common sight at cosplay events.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 17:41:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct - pretty handy for camping in cold weather </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 17:39:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's an interesting point - I wonder if this will have an impact on the concept of original art being of higher value - I guess the same goes for digital art.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spider man sleeping bag with detached arms and legs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 15:05:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 14:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree, I don't really get why people keep upvoting them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 13:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The text in this reads a lot like it was translated from another language. 

Does anyone have another link to this concept? It would be interesting to read a bit more about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In Pictures: 3D printed art showcases incredible possibilities of additive manufacturing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 13:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In Silicon Valley, Journalists Balance Booster and Critic </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 13:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Georgia Tech professor proposes another alternative to the Turing Test </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 13:30:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gifted men and women define success differently, 40-year study says </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 13:23:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Netflix takes up 9.5% of upstream traffic on the North American Internet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 13:21:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Tricky Ethics of Intergalactic Colonization </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 13:17:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 12:36:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sounds like something a crazy cartoon villain would do. If it weren't so awful and terrifying it would be utterly hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Concept Mercedes Generates Power From Its Paint Job </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 11:54:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What will New York City's skyline look like in 2018? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 11:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Video Game Proves That Telepathy Is Possible </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 10:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 18:26:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds like a potentially brilliant idea for food aid, thanks for sharing it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gecko inspired pads allow researchers to climb glass wall </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 17:41:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 16:52:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, this is a different article - note the way the text is different. 

You and your many accounts need to stop downvoting and negatively commenting on things I post - your attempt at revenge is weird and petty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Marley Natural: First global cannabis brand shows future is bright for marijuana </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 15:49:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jellyfish Barge: A floating architectural greenhouse proposed for sustainable future crop cultivation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 15:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is car technology creating stupid drivers? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 15:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 14:56:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is really disappointing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 14:55:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a repost of a [Daily Mail article](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-2839558/Could-POO-soon-power-smartphones-Bacteria-faeces-improve-bio-batteries.html) - bit of a trend at the moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The internet fixes Barbie's 'I Can Be a Computer Engineer' picture book </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 13:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 13:47:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Erm, isn't the link you've posted just a preview to their magazine?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 13:35:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you include redditors that post articles that have sensationalised headlines? Or just ones that sensationalise them themselves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 13:31:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As with the article yesterday, this is a repost of a [Daily Mail](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-2840627/A-house-seasons-Shape-shifting-home-transforms-year-response-changing-temperatures.html) article </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Transhumanist Manifesto </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 12:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Comet probe 'sniffed' organic molecules, early data show </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 18:01:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Disney Is Building A Gigantic Toy Story Hotel And It Looks Totally Rad </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 17:34:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 16:47:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought they looked familiar when I posted this and I couldn't think why! They certainly do :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Building a globe-spanning quantum internet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 16:06:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 14:02:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is a repost of an article from the [Daily Mail](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-2839124/The-bottle-makes-water-appear-AIR-Gadget-uses-solar-energy-collect-moisture-flask-ride-bike.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could pod seats be the future of air travel? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 13:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google and Stanford unveil new machine vision technology that recognizes complex scenes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 13:52:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Intel unveils "feminine communications accessory" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 13:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for a stock tip? Check the CEO's face </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 13:39:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 10:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you get to demo any of their stuff? How was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 18:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does Alexander Gerst ever stop smiling? He must be the world's cheeriest astronaut! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 17:53:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I wouldn't - responding to an article you haven't read, particularly with such vitriol, just seems foolish. 

The answer you linked to didn't answer my question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 17:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you read it or not? It doesn't seem  like you have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 16:48:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds like a hilarious article - I wish that was what it was about! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 16:37:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only very briefly at the start of the intro and the first section, and the fact that you have focused so heavily on this makes it seem a lot like you haven't read the vast majority of this article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 16:34:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, this is one of those technologies where it feels as if people are only exploring it because its part of a romantic view of the future, not because it's actually a useful, problem solving technology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 16:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everything you've said about the article suggests you think it takes a different angle and chain of discussion to the one it does, which leads me to assume you haven't actually read it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 16:05:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you read the article? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Amazon's UK Drone Tests Branded "Barking Mad" By Locals </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 16:04:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nokia says it's 'up to something' with picture of mysterious black box </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 15:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Magic tricks created using artificial intelligence for the first time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 12:01:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Forget Siri: The virtual assistants of the future will transform the way we work and live </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 11:59:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 03:04:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who buys print media anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I want to build a device to clean shopping carts, because germs. I have some sketches, but instead of showing those here's a really pixelated picture of a shopping cart. $10,000 please </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 13:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Two Dudes Prove How Easy It Is to Hack ATMs for Free Cash </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 12:57:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can your voice get you hired? New software helps people find jobs by analyzing the sound of their speech </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 12:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Forget boots on the ground, half of US-Mexico border watched via drone </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 10:40:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Volvo starts offering virtual test drives using Google Cardboard </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 10:37:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tokyo stocks fall in morning on profit-taking </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 10:34:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Indian government is seriously looking at banning online pornography </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 10:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:08:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to live in a future where those exist! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Amazon is hiring drone testing pilots </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 16:46:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nvidia to launch its Grid game streaming service on November 18, but only for Shield devices </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 16:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Europe's very first 3D printer in space is scheduled for installation aboard the ISS next year </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 16:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Intel Spent a Half A Million Dollars To Support Drone Selfies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 15:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I don't care if you landed a spacecraft on a comet, your shirt is sexist and ostracizing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 15:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Startup Is Turning the Human Body Into a Next Gen Design Platform </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 14:05:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 10:47:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the idea of us actually taking action on something - im sure between us we do have the skills to achieve some v cool things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:26:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a huge number of other reasons for GM crops other than to be resistant to pesticides etc. These include making the stems shorter to reduce growing cycles and adding key vitamins to aid nutrition. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dutchman has bitcoin 'wallets' inserted in hands </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:07:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 17:55:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What don't you like about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Age of the digital nomad: The plan to abandon cities in favour of freelance freedom </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 16:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Googles DoubleClick for Publishers is down, removing ads from sites across the Web </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 16:04:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> California cities, counties have spent $65M on spy tech in past decade </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 16:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New analysis of the cat genome suggest cats stuck with humans because of treats </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 16:02:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 'Baby pics' offer peek at infant solar system </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 15:58:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thomas Heatherwicks Garden Bridge Gets Green Light from Londons Lambeth Council </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 15:57:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hamada Designs Glass + Wood Building in Japan Wraps Around Living Trees </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 15:52:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Restart Game? Text Adventures Make A Comeback </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 15:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Despite decades of sending sounds and pictures into space no aliens have responded. Have we been doing it wrong? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 14:07:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 13:20:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Given our societies and living conditions are constantly changing, I don't think our on-Earth problems will ever be 'solved'. Plus things don't have to be dealt with one at a time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ubisofts Sneaky Scheme to Keep You From Seeing Bad Reviews </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 13:18:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Will Quantum Computing Become an Everyday Reality? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 13:11:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Video: Watch this 3D printed self-learning robot limp across the room </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 13:01:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Office Robot Knows When to Ask for Help </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 12:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> People Are Calling The Police To Get Out of the World's Biggest Corn Maze </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 12:38:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Illinois man builds a drivable upside down pickup truck </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 12:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 12:11:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His appointment on such a board should be illegal. It's like making a massive racist the minister for equality (UK position - please insert local equivalent!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 12:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's been a lot of negativity about this technology, but at the end of the day it has got to be being built, which is a lot more than can be said for a lot of environmentally friendly tech. It will be really interesting to see how it works in reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 11:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe [this is the article](http://www.abc.net.au/news/2014-11-04/scientists-reverse-ageing-process-in-mice/5865714) you were looking for - you're correct about it being the muscles:

"We've discovered genes that control how the body fights against ageing and these genes, if you turn them on just the right way, they can have very powerful effects, even reversing ageing - at least in mice so far," he said. "We fed them a molecule that's called NMN and this reversed ageing completely within just a week of treatment in the muscle, and now we're looking to reverse all aspects of ageing if possible."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 11:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm afraid I'm not the creator - I just thought this was a cool project. You make a solid point though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 11:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Customers pay to have a Cloud Heat fire-proof cabinet installed in their homes or offices (the cost is comparable to installing a standard heating system). Then Cloud Heat pays for the electricity and Internet service the cabinet needs and the owner gets to enjoy free heat and hot water.

Not a bad deal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> German cloud company offers free heat for people willing to house their servers - do people see this catching on? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 10:55:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Flexible organic solar cells with record 10.8% efficiency </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 10:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Amazon Plans Prime Air Delivery Drone Tests In The UK </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 10:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drone sightings up dramatically </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 10:47:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mozilla foundation working on MozVR to bring virtual reality to the web </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 10:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A folding electric bike that weighs less than 5KG and can fit into a backpack </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 10:37:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 19:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A BSc in History actually sounds like an awesome course - I'm imagining modules on 16th century theories that have long been disproved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-11 14:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once 3D metal printing gets good/cheap enough, maybe a metal version will be doable, which i assume would be stronger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:06:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure if its about fat so much as about hand size - people that work with their hands and so have a lot of callouses etc seem to have more trouble. My Dad is a good example - he works with his hands a lot so his fingers are far too big to use a smartphone properly, but he isn't particularly fat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Personalised medicine would cut breast cancer chemotherapy by a third </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 15:27:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New tool makes tracking research impact easier </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 15:21:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alleged Silk Road 2 Mastermind Worked for Ex-Googlers Secret Startup </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 15:20:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spy group stole business secrets over compromised hotel Wi-Fi </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 15:17:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ThickButtons: iPhone Keyboard App for Fat Fingers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 15:04:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> These Jeans Come In 400 Sizes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 15:04:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Glimpse Into the Incredible High-Tech Future of Museums </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 14:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The world beard + moustache championships captured by Jaclyn Campanaro </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 14:53:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Human Errors In Digitized Google Books </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 14:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DARPA is seeking ideas for transforming planes into "aircraft carriers in the sky" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 14:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How 3D imaging could change the way we take photographs forever </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 10:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Communities Fight State Laws That Can Divide Broadband Access </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 10:59:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Microsoft 3D SoundScape headset aims to help the blind travel freely </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 10:41:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 52 Of The World's Most Widespread Myths And Misconceptions, Debunked </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 10:35:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Discrediting Space Tourism Insults the People Who Risk Their Lives for It </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 10:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Who to launch virtual reality app for Oculus Rift </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 10:24:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In the Future, Everyone Will Play Video Games </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 10:09:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Novel process could let consumers 3D-print metal parts for the first time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-10 10:07:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Inflatable Incubator Could Save Premature Babies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 15:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Krome Retouch launches on Android to let humans tweak your photos </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 10:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 10:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This type of approach to tackling insect-borne diseases is pretty exciting - I hope it proves successful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 10:35:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with this - a party would alienate the movement from other potentially sympathetic parties in a way that a lobby would not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Transhumanists Should Support Right-To-Die </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 10:33:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Problem solved: Autocomplete for coding is being developed by DARPA </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 18:34:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could Dark Matter Make Invisible, Parallel Universes? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 18:26:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The future of books is on your phone, not your tablet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 18:25:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Samsung's Gear Circle Bluetooth Headphone Arrives in the US </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 18:24:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How corals can actually benefit from climate change effects </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 18:20:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 12:17:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aren't these technically wave turbines not wind turbines? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 11:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You might be able to adapt [solar tube technology](http://www.solatube.co.uk/) to solve this problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A history of the 20th century in maps </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 11:18:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 09:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine is February 28. I am now utterly curious about what would have happened if last year was a leap year and I'd signed up one day later. Would I have one cake day every 4 years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Should Boston Become A City Of Canals? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 18:04:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robotic Micro-Scallops Can Swim Through Your Eyeballs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Computer scientist sees new possibilities for ocular biometrics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:36:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Fabrics May Soon Yield More Health Data Than Devices </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:22:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 11:55:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't this be exceptionally expensive to implement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 09:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is an excellent point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Passenger-carrying solar planes may be only a decade away </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 08:48:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Steve Jobs' Russian memorial dismantled after Apple CEO comes out as gay </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 08:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What happens when you accidentally become internet famous? | Technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 08:42:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An Unprecedented Look at Stuxnet, the Worlds First Digital Weapon </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 14:42:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New robots will revolutionise the built environment </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 11:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China unveils 'laser to shoot down low-flying drones' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 10:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 16:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's hard to say, because it is the decision of each publisher if they want to port it. If it becomes as popular as Zuckerberg wants it to be, though, I'm sure plenty of publishers will embrace the format </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A trip to Turn 10, the Forza studio merging car culture with games </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 15:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 15:14:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry i think i must be having an idiot day, will delete now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What Futurists Think Of HP's Bold And Weird New PC </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 13:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Self-driving vehicles generate enthusiasm, concerns worldwide </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 13:38:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Zuckerberg sees 50 to 100 million Oculus units sold in next decade </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 17:47:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 17:45:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you watch TV in the UK you have to pay for a TV licence, which funds the BBC. So its like HBO except you have to get it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 17:39:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You had me at "IQ of a toothbrush" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nintendos sleep monitor: Are non-wearables the future? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 17:31:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nintendos sleep monitor: Are non-wearables the future? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 17:03:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Future of Lunar Archeology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 16:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Computerized Harness Might Be The Dog Translator We've Been Waiting For </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 16:37:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 15:28:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or write headlines that make the author sound sane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> World's tallest set of twin towers planned for Dubai skyline </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 13:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Misleading Headlines Can Leave Lasting Impressions, Even If You Read The Article </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 13:41:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Prophet's ancient seal provides insights from antiquity </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 13:32:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 12:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of thing does one need to do to get a ban on Facebook? I've never heard of that happening before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Samsung will 'fundamentally reform' its smartphones after dire earnings report </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 12:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Facebook Could End Up Controlling Everything You Watch and Read Online </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 12:03:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Future air passengers may get unique, windowless view </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 11:35:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Try Windows 93: The Hilarious OS That Never Was </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-30 11:34:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hungarians March Against Proposed Tax on Internet Use </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 17:59:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Elon Musk Calling Artificial Intelligence a 'Demon' Could Actually Hurt Research </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 16:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> HP's new Sprout PC ditches mouse and keyboard for a touch mat future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 16:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ikea's 5-Minute Furniture Really Takes 17 Minutes To Build </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 16:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 15:10:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah I see! Thanks for the explanation. 

I thought the research in this article was interesting because of the potential for average joes - they often get the short straw on this sub! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 15:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cannot upvote this enough. Time and time again people on this sub have declared a technology developed outside the US will never work, often because of a legal or infrastructure issue that is only a problem in the US. It's close-minded madness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 15:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! Once in a blue moon I encounter a company that does this and they are gods in my eyes. 

It's weirdly more common to find them in alphabetical order, including an array of countries that are clearly never going to be needed, such as the Democratic People's Republic of Korea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nestle Japan hiring 1,000 robots to sell espresso machines </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 13:36:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 12:59:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This has gone completely over my head. Would you mind explaining, please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new spin on virtual reality helps engineers read robots' minds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 12:39:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Take a Google Seaview Tour of the World's Most Stunning Coral Reefs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 12:30:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Making any car autonomous: Scientists say affordable driverless cars just a decade away </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 11:36:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Singapore to deploy massive surveillance balloon </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 10:41:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My SO wrote this post about his experiences of getting Crohns and a stoma - I thought you guys would find it interesting </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 10:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The rise of the quantified pupil: Why classroom tracking can boost prospects </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 10:23:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The best 'Mario Kart' ever steers Nintendo to profit </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 10:19:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could music videos be the real killer app for VR? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 10:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Stan Lee Cameo Is A Pun You Can Wear </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 10:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A crazy J-pop music video is the best Oculus Rift demo yet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 10:13:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robot Reality Check: The Truth About Ebola Bots And Iron Man Suits </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 10:06:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lowe's debuts customer service robots in store </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 16:05:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One giant leap for preservation: Protecting Moon landing sites </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 15:55:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 15:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I quite agree, although he was not the first and he won't be the last to put forward that idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 15:15:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can understand your concern, but if he fired you for requesting hot water you could take him to court for unfair dismissal. At least mention it to your colleagues so they are aware too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 15:06:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People who do this fill me with a quiet fury </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Biotech Beating Out GMO When it Comes to Food Production, Says Greenpeace </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 13:46:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Solar city: Hidden-in-plain-sight solar panels to boost renewables revolution </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 13:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Solar city: Hidden-in-plain-sight solar panels to boost renewables revolution </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 13:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Complex City Grids Visualized With Day-Glo Maps </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 12:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> US currency reimagined to celebrate ideas, not the dead </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 10:56:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In the Future Your Therapy and Education Will Be Tailored to Your Brain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 10:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Your future home will be mind-controlled </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 10:28:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> YouTube is considering offering an ad-free subscription package </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 10:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-23 15:25:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of thing should they be trying instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-23 15:02:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This website](https://plentific.com/buying-process/) may also be worth reading - its a very thorough guide to buying a house in the UK that should provide some useful info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A sprawling videogame city filled with buildings made by generative algorithms </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-23 13:21:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jakarta's $40 Billion Plan To Stop Sinking Into The Ocean </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-23 11:17:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A huge number of cities around the world remain unmapped. The missing maps project wants to crowdsource digital maps of the entire globe </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 18:27:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Psychology of Web Design: How colors, typefaces and spacing affect your mood </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 18:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Simpsons World lets cable subscribers stream every episode of the show </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 18:17:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reprogrammed skin cells give hope for Huntingtons treatment </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 18:05:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reprogrammed skin cells give hope for Huntingtons treatment </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 18:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Foldable, bendable actuators could lead to foldable, bendable UAVs that you can stuff into your pocket </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 16:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Australian convicted in child sex sting using virtual girl </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 15:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 15:38:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this aimed at me or the writer? I usually try and stick with the actual headline of the article unless its really vague </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is big data heading for its 'horsemeat moment'? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 14:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NASA is catalyst for hydrogen technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 14:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bowers   Wilkins T7: A Bluetooth Speaker for People Who Hate Bluetooth Speakers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 14:50:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Excerpts from a SkyMall-esque catalog from the future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 12:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple co-founder to mentor at Australian university </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 11:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 11:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a hell of a lot wrong with his study and the conclusions he draws - the fact that they were all instructed to play as violently as possible but the control group was bowling seems pretty suspect to me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Death To Page Views! Long Live "Acts Of Engagement" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 11:29:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Freezing Your Eggs Isn't the Future of Reproduction. Here's What Is. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 11:21:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 11:12:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd love to know what people think of this - to me it just sounds like a blood infection waiting to happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jewelry that harvests energy from your veins </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 11:10:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> IKEA captures shopping horror with halloween tribute to 'The Shining' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 11:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Study finds "playing violent games in 3D leads to higher anger levels" - does anyone actually game in 3D? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 10:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 21:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love that you both explained he was in the wrong place and answered his question! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The future fracturing of the internet: How access will define the web of tomorrow </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 16:51:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> UK politicians among the world's most crazy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 14:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Incredible Oculus Sim Lets Soccer Players Relive Games </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 13:31:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "So Bad Ass You Can't Believe It" Magic Leap Raises $542 Million To Launch The Future Of Computing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 13:16:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What It Could Be Like to Live on Mars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 13:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Revolutionary Delta Printer 3D Prints Structurally Sound Homes from Clay </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 18:06:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 17:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might be worth dropping by /r/aquaponics and seeing what they recommend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 17:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cost-wise, it really depends on where you are - the price of land is they key deciding factor in how much it will cost to grow food in natural sunlight. 
What kind of scale are you thinking about? Philips are leading the way in the tech for this sort of thing, so it might be worth [checking out their site](http://www.lighting.philips.com/main/application_areas/horticultural/cityfarming.wpd) for prices etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 15:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I never understand this desire - if you want them so much get empty frames, don't envy people who need to wear lenses to function! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 15:30:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can confirm. Have a permanent, albeit mild, back injury from school trampoline classes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hey Dubai: A 160 MPH Ambulance May Not Be a Great Idea </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 14:34:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Energy storage of the future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 14:33:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Do Astronomers Find Exoplanets? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 14:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New commercial rocket descent data may help NASA with future Mars landings </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 14:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why there are so many spiders in Britain's homes this year </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 14:24:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New Smart Street Corners That Will Act Like a Fitbit for the City </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 13:38:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drinking pop daily can shorten your life: Study </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 12:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Japan firm showcases Bat-Signal of the future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 12:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You Know Your Company Needs More Women, But Do You Know Why? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 12:26:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers Take an Up-Close and Personal Look at What Pollution Does to the Body </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 12:24:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Video: Inside the pioneering urban farm growing plants under London </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 11:52:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wearable tech lets boss track your work, rest and play </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 11:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> British internet trolls could face two years in prison if new proposal becomes law </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 11:50:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Internet Sleeps at Night. Really. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 10:47:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Advice on the Avengers' Motivational Posters Is a Little Warped </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 10:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Shouts on Bond-Trading Floor Yield to Robot Beeps </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 10:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Japanese man jailed for making guns with 3D printer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 10:24:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-18 00:26:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah I see! My apologies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-17 13:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this aimed at the article's author? Because I didn't write the article  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Archaeology powered by communities: new crowd-funding platform </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-17 10:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 20:37:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok real talk time: some girls will be put off if you are shorter than them. But plenty won't, and there are plenty of girls in the world who are shorter than you. 

You will meet plenty of women in your life who are not remotely bothered about your height. I guarantee it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 19:40:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pick something you enjoy doing and dedicate as much free time as you can to mastering it. Read everything you can find on it and seek out tips to make yourself better. Take on small projects related to it, and share the results with relevant communities/subreddits and ask for feedback, then use that to improve.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 19:36:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get yourself out there - start a blog, post your work to illustration sites and generally build a name for yourself. Find projects looking for illustrators and offer your services - all in all, build yourself a portfolio and make yourself someone people want to illustrate their stuff. 

Art school will help you improve your skills, but if you are already good you may find you can build a career without it. But if you don't put yourself out there and build a portfolio, school on its own won't be the answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 19:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grades don't matter as much once you graduate from college - your grades reflect on your teachers so of course they are going to stress about it. Try not to let it bother you too much and focus on trying new things and working out what you want from life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 19:29:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What you study will not define your future, only help you on the path towards it, so focus on picking something you will enjoy studying now and try out different types of work in your summers to help you figure out what you want to pursue later. 

You do not have to make a complete decision about what you want to do with your future now. There is always time for you to change your mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 17:50:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get tested - at least then you will know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 17:49:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you teach it to yourself using info online? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 17:40:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry to sound like an old woman, but what is swag? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 17:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can always finish your high school degree later. 

Is playing soccer what you want to do with your life? If so, you will probably regret it if you don't give it a shot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 17:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I appreciate this is not technically legal, but can you torrent the software you need? There are no marks given for playing by the rules.

Once you get a good job with your degree your parents will most likely shut up - they probably don't understand enough about IT to understand what a potentially valuable degree you are doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 17:32:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't worry, just try out things that sound like they might suit you and use those experiences to help you think further about it - there is no deadline to deciding and nothing to stop you switching careers later if you decide what you're doing isn't for you. 

This notion that you have to pick now and be stuck with it is outdated at best - people will certainly ask you what you want to do, but there is nothing wrong with not having a simple answer. (If you listen to the folks at /r/futurology you stand a good chance of living to 200, so its not like you're short on time to decide!)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 17:25:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try not to worry and just enjoy it - who knows? Maybe it will last - a friend long-distanced between different continents with a girl he met as a freshman and ended up marrying her. If it does end, you'll deal with it and the experience may even help you forge stronger future relationships. 

For now, though, make the most of it and enjoy the time you do get with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ophelia   Brijs - Don't Start [Rap/Pop] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 15:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 13:55:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go for it! I'm female and travelled solo for 6 months when I was 18/19. Stay sensible and you'll be fine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 12:41:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are your thoughts on 3D printed organs?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-16 10:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The weather this week was bloody awful! The tube was packed thanks to all the line closures! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A 3-D Printed Seat With a Cellular Structure That Molds to Your Butt </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 12:46:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nursing Grandma with a robot </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 12:30:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robots will be your future co-workers, not your replacements </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 12:16:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A magician's thoughts on why practitioners of magic are often a bit strange </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 09:27:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Archaeologists discover bronze remains of Iron Age chariot </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 18:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TrackingPoint releases ShotGlass: Shades that let you shoot around corners </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 18:12:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chemical in broccoli sprouts may treat autism </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 18:10:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Meet Chelsea Manning's official portrait artist </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 18:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pentagon warns the US military of climate change </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 18:06:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Vacuum May Be A Space Exploration Game Changer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 12:19:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Let science decide the voting age </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 10:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There's less Gears, more Bricks in these cool Steampunk Lego Creations </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-14 10:39:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 15:13:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you well enough to travel? If so it might be worth you taking a trip to somewhere that it is legal to buy (eg Amsterdam) in order to see if it helps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is This The World's Best Bike-Share Bike? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 11:40:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Barbies First Dream House Was a Tiny Studio Apartment Made from Cardboard </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 11:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rebranding Cannabis: The legal future of the worlds favourite high </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 11:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rebranding Cannabis: The legal future of the worlds favourite high </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 11:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tesla Brings you the Future of Immersive Technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 11:18:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A look at how your voice is being used to ID you </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 11:17:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Optics experts offering $99 VR ONE headset for December </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 11:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nowhere to hide: the danger of satellite spies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 11:00:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robot Mass Unemployment Delayed as Million IPhone Building Robots at Foxconn delayed a decade or more </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 10:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google testing service to connect patients with doctors over video chat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 10:50:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What The Statue Of Liberty Would Look Like As A $300M Condo </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 13:00:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> UK Is Using White Space Spectrum to Livestream Meerkats </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 12:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Postcards From The Future Show What London Will Look Like After Climate Change </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 12:49:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3-D Printed Shoes Generated Using Conways Game of Life </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 12:47:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 00:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You eat meat because it suffers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 22:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Are there still aboriginals in the wild?" Few years ago now, but I still can't believe a final year anthropology student said this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 20:03:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you been on the London underground? They are part of the heritage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 19:10:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally I'm holding out for ghost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 19:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! Although I will miss those rare comedy comments from the drivers. 

Plus I'm pretty certain King's Cross will never be as deserted as it is in the video.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Londons futuristic new driverless underground trains </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 16:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If You'd Like To Interact With The Future Of Audio Ads, Please Say, "Proceed" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 16:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Start-up Has Invented Veggie Burgers That Bleed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 16:02:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Found: closest link to Eve, our universal ancestor </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 15:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Political animosity exceeds racial hostility according to research </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 13:35:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Wild Evolution of Vampires, From Bram Stoker to Dracula Untold </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 13:06:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 13:05:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is anyone suggesting we excavate new underground areas? I can't find any mention of that in the article </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Toshiba Glass shown at Ceatec in Japan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 11:16:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A robot is starring in an upcoming theatrical production of Kafka's The Metamorphosis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 11:01:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Our future celebrities will be technologists </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 10:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Designing future cities </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 14:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sea farms producing fuel and food will dominate coastlines by 2030 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 13:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Technology Isnt Truly Wearable </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 13:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A UK student who gathered video evidence of himself being harassed on a pair of specially adapted sunglasses has been allowed to carry out a private prosecution of his tormentor. The highly unusual case may point the way to a future of do-it-yourself justice </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 00:41:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 22:59:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Given how much money some people spend on fertility now, I expect fertility will be one of the faster developments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 21:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the way they thought everyone would still be wearing Victorian clothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nintendo to Release First Amiibo Figures in November </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 14:32:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Japanese tech titans turn to wearables and vegetables </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 13:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Dark Ride That Scares You Out Of The Oculus Rift's Uncanny Valley </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 12:33:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pressing the accelerator on quantum robotics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 10:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Here's why you're bouncing off the walls: the genetics of coffee consumption </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 10:26:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 10:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Treat them as equal - don't focus on the fact they are women and don't act like its a boys club. Just encourage them in the same way as you would the boys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Microsoft imagines an incredible transparent smart cover for Surface tablets </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 18:01:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 15:11:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  As education increases, people tend to have less children.

This is particularly key - if we give people a basic income but don't improve education it won't have a big impact. I don't think it is the income as DerpyGrooves says, so much as the fact that people's (particularly women's) time is taken up with other things  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 11:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was lucky enough to see him in person a while back and was delighted to see that his beard wobbles when he talks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Should we upgrade photosynthesis and grow supercrops? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 11:16:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Aubrey de Grey: Longer lives wont mean overpopulation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 11:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Girlification of engineering has failed, says expert </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 11:08:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New Camera Will End 'Unexpected Item In Bagging Area' Rage </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 11:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Barcoding tool for stem cells: New technology that tracks the origin of blood cells challenges scientific dogma </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 10:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pet Technology Market Going 'Ballistic' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 10:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Letting Your Car Find a Spot and Park Itself </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 10:48:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The overlooked history of African technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 10:47:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Watch the developer become god in this precursor to the Metaverse </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 10:28:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sex toys for plants </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 10:27:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3D Printing Skin Grafts to Heal Burns </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 16:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> VR robot and animal test subjects to be used for experiments </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 16:08:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I tried living on one browser tab and almost died </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 16:07:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> World falling short of biodiversity targets, according to report </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 16:01:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One more absolutely amazing timelapse from the International Space Station </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 15:54:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If the World Started Over, Would Life Evolve the Same Way? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 15:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Metal snow on Venus - something about that just sounds very cyberpunk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 15:44:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 9 Perfect Works From the Illustrator Who Ruled the Mad Men Era </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 15:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crumpled graphene could provide an unconventional energy storage </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 15:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 10:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too - its a great article. Thanks for sharing - I couldn't find the link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 10:50:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My SO had a similar experience when he developed Crohn's Disease - took 4 months with many, many visits to the doctor and one hospital admission before they realised what was up, by which time he had developed severe complications and needed an emergency surgery. If you need treatment and think it may be more severe than the docs are saying, demand blood tests! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Beautiful LEGO 2: Dark, a New Book about the Dark Side of LEGO by Mike Doyle </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 17:33:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Multivariate Beer: Creating beer using census data </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 17:31:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How commercial spaceflight makes a profit </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 17:29:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Four scenarios for the all-age-friendly cities of the future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 16:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Inside The Fashion Incubator Thats Hacking Global Manufacturing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 15:16:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google Glass to be used by Dubai police to fight crime </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 15:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jane Goodall On The Importance Of Empathy In Science </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 12:37:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First floating solar farm in UK comes to life in Berkshire </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 12:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 11:03:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think there will certainly be a market for this (assuming it was possible - presumably these meats would be much harder to develop), but I expect it will always be a fraction of the main market - novelty and speciality food that people have at dinner parties or in hipster noodle bars, but not the sort of thing you'd eat at home during the day. 

But who knows, maybe there will be a food craze for synthetic dodo meat? It's a fascinating prospect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Maps Of Modern Cities Drawn In The Style Of J.R.R. Tolkien </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 10:25:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Half of Our Planet's Wildlife Is Gone. Here's Why. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 10:16:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Snake Robot Walks by Turning Its Head and Tail Into Legs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 10:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robot researcher combines nature to nurture 'superhuman' navigation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 10:12:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 16:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmm grain-fed skeletal muscle meat, my favourite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Semen secrets: How a previous sexual partner can influence another male's offspring </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 15:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Swarm of house-building mini robots to get more intelligent, faster and agile </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 16:28:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 16:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I think familiarity is going to be pretty important if people are going to take to this as an acceptable solution. Just look at all the "ew I am never eating bugs" reactions each time an ento as food article gets published </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 16:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spot the foodie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Unless we change direction, the world will warm 3-5 degrees Celsius </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 15:31:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blame coffee farm rust fungus for rising coffee prices </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 15:27:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Space debris expert warns of increasing CubeSat collision risk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 15:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 5G mobile networks will support an internet that's so good you can feel it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 15:18:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Non-Profit That's Using Technology to Put Itself Out of Business </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 15:15:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 14:41:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're not talking about people not trying, we're talking about people who try and struggle anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Meet Nixie, the Worlds First Wearable Drone </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 12:53:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Synthetic Meat  Passes Taste Tests, But Still Five Years Away from Commercial Availability </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 10:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to build a cheaper cloaking device </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 17:59:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Commercial drone regulations: Canada vs. US </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 17:43:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Minority report-style tech to transform trucks and windows into supersized touch screens </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 17:42:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ancient human genome from southern Africa throws light on our origins </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 17:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 16:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe they will have to install new tracks for the maglev service - unless there's something someone who knows more about trains can add? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Minority report-style tech to transform trucks and windows into supersized touch screens </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 12:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hubble finds jets and explosions in NGC 7793 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 12:29:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> UK to build unique intergalactic GPS instrument to map the stars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 12:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Japan Conducts First Public Test of New 311 MPH L-Zero Maglev Train </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 12:04:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Greenland Ice Sheet more vulnerable to climate change than previously thought </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 11:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One creepy looking chair </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 11:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Embedded urban furniture for physical activity in the city </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 10:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> BBsuit 0.2 cleans polluted air using wearable filtration technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 10:30:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Tiny Wireless Earbuds Of The Future Are Made Possible By Software </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 16:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 16:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They posted an [update to their Kickstarter](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/37135808/loading-human/posts/975504) project a couple of weeks ago saying the game is due for late February and announcing the launch of their [new website](http://www.untoldgames.com/) so I wouldn't write them off just yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Five ways the superintelligence revolution might happen </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 16:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blackout-fighting robots could be heroes during a disaster </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 16:11:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hubble team finds male led teams still getting more telescope time than those led by females </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 16:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bungies first Destiny dev notes address rebalancing, chat, exploits </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 16:09:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If trees could talk: Forest research network reveals global change effects </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 16:07:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> French Island is Building Perhaps the Most Beautiful Solar Plant </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 15:23:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Security robot can skim discreetly along a ship's hull to seek hollow compartments concealing contraband </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 15:22:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 13:30:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So what do you do when the quadcopters tranq everyone? Either they will wake up annoyed and get back to it, die from tranq-related injury or need to be detained by soldiers on the ground. It sounds incredibly impractical.

How about instead of marching in and educating these people we focus on understanding their culture, why some people feel this way and how we can help. They aren't animals that need to be herded. 

Technology - at least not the warfare kind - is not the answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 12:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The traditional perception that bonobos are all peace and love has been challenged by recent studies. It's a bit of an overplayed stereotype.

[Source](http://primatologie.revues.org/1090#tocto1n6) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 11:23:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that's an awesome idea! Pah squandering, they can make more for the important stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 4 Oculus Rift Developers Who Are Going To Blow Your Mind </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 10:58:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How To Kill In The Sims 4 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 10:55:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3DS Smash Bros Is an Exhilarating Return to Excellence </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 10:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 16:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It kind of seems like the US is going to fall behind a lot of the rest of the world with this drone stuff if they don't change their approach soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robot lab's snake, copter combo rethinks search and rescue </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 13:57:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Watch the Synthetic Leaf Creator Explain How We Could Colonize Space </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 13:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Worlds first regular drone delivery service takes flight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 13:46:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Worlds first regular drone delivery service takes flight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 13:03:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> EmTech: Nest Technologist on the Problem of Remaking Unloved Devices </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 13:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Three Ways to Visualize Our Melting Northern Ice Cap </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 13:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple Watch Mashups Hint at How the Company Could Go High-Fashion </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 12:59:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Palm-Sized Laser Could Make Self-Driving Cars Way Cheaper </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 12:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Live long and phosphor: Blue LED breakthrough for efficient electronics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 12:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robot cheerleading squad showcases sensor technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 12:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Electric vehicle chargers popping up in China </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 12:39:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A city past the point of no return? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 11:39:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> FAA expected to approve drones for moviemaking </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-25 10:49:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 22:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean in the sense that it's quite an impersonal choice of noun in the context </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 22:28:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Female is also an acceptable, if slightly dehumanising, noun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In Pictures: The industry magazines of the future </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 16:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ealing aparthotel gets OK'd </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 16:04:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Harem-holding male primates fail to rise to the challenge </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 15:51:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What It's Like To Use North Korea's Internet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 15:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Digital Archaeology changes exploration of the past </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 15:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Octopus-Inspired Robot Matches Real Octopus For Speed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 15:40:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> UNC professor says black holes can't exist </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 15:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why is everyone vying for a piece of Mars? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 14:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Japanese Firm Selling Videogames to Women Using Sex </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 13:52:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MIT's Slick New UI Lets Your Phone and Desktop Screens Behave as One </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 13:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wearable robots: The workwear and spacesuits of tomorrow </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 13:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Virtual Nurse Is (Almost) Ready To See You Now </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 12:21:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drones Will Transform Sports PhotographyOnce the FAA Gets Out of the Way </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 12:55:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Getting It Wrong Is the Future of Design </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 12:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Turning winery waste into biofuels </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 12:06:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Preferences for manly men and feminine women linked to urbanization </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 12:06:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chinese wireless-networking gear giant Huawei has acquired British Internet of Things (IoT) company Neul for $25m </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 11:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is Pluto a Planet? The Votes Are In </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 10:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Incredible New Nanothreads Could Help Us Build a Space Elevator </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 10:44:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Test-Rifting The Oculus Crescent Bay VR Headset </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 10:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Insightful article on brand-sponsored online communities </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 16:19:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [How Sephora Discovered That Lurkers Are Also Its "Superfans"](http://www.fastcolabs.com/3035236/how-sephora-discovered-that-lurkers-are-also-its-superfans) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How the digital revolution has changed the music industry - thought you guys might find this interesting </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 16:03:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where is that spacecraft? Statistically measuring uncertainty for space surveillance </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 16:01:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robots Use RFID to Find and Navigate to Household Objects </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 15:53:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kickstarter lays down new rules for when a project fails </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 15:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Radical But Possible Plan to Connect African Nations With Cargo Drones </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 15:48:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This $19K Leica Has No Screen, But the Separate $11K Lens Is Legendary </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 15:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Utopian Cloud-Shaped Skyscraper Wins Top Prize in Shenzhen Bay Super City Competition </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 15:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fracking's environmental impacts scrutinised </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 14:09:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> US hotels don't understand Chinese tourists, study says </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 14:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alex Chinneck on his architectural intervention at London's Covent Garden </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 14:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tactile touchless feedback will let you reach out and feel virtual worlds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 13:29:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Exercise added to chemo shrinks tumors faster </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 12:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 22:43:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The site also has links - they are on the right hand side  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Electric car breaks 200 mph barrier to set new land speed record </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 14:46:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kim Dotcoms fledgling Internet Party has a chance of winning a place in New Zealands Parliament </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 14:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 5 startups that could radically transform the world around us </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 14:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Quick-change materials break the silicon speed limit for computers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 13:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fingertip sensor gives robot unprecedented dexterity </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 13:43:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Radinn electric powered wakeboard commanded by a wireless handcontrol </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 12:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 12:21:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you mind saying how old you are (assuming that is acceptable under Reddit's rules) - the impression I have is that the younger you are, the more ok you are with trading privacy for technology.

I generally agree with you - I really only worry about privacy when its on a local scale, ie people I know/live near knowing private info about me. On a goverment scale this info is used en-masse; its not about individuals, its about having data to optimise cities, maintain good healthcare and similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Welcome to the museum experience of the future: immersive, interactive, high-tech and compelling </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 12:17:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NVIDIA takes on Apollo 11 Moon landing deniers with technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 12:12:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Introducing the Samsung Gear VR Innovator Edition </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 12:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Asian stars enlisted to fight African rhino poaching </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 11:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Neal Stephenson's Kickstarter Game Is Dead </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 11:07:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 17:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is such a classic example of considering a future technology only in today's terms - you seen remarkably certain that the technology for hardware upgrades will remain just as it is now, while everything else changes. I would suggest that such an assumption is the true hogwash here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 17:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it would save on electricity if you only had to juice up your phone once a week  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 13:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess if they build it on a route people actually use this time they might have a better chance of success!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 13:19:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know! I would love them to remake all the assets into an open world game, but that's clearly never going to happen. Such a shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Squid skin: Nanoparticle screens lay foundations for self-camouflaging metamaterials </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 17:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I thought you guys would be interested in this new breed. I give you the Werewolf Cat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 10:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 10:48:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found it really visually one-note - I really wish they had varied it more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 10:47:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup - the art director should be given a medal, but the gameplay is just awful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 10:39:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's sense of what is "right" is programmed in - how it interprets this in real-world scenarios is the interesting bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can a robot learn right from wrong? Attempts to imbue robots, self-driving cars and military machines with a sense of ethics reveal just how hard this is </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 10:28:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 01:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like we've found the guy OP was on a date with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 00:45:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While I agree with you, I think it does mean a lot of people read it who otherwise wouldn't have, and that has got to be a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 23:51:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Used to work in triage for an accident management company. Best one I ever heard was "I was driving down this narrow road and it kept getting narrower until the car was wedged on both sides" Why the guy didn't stop driving before that I will never know.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Minecraft Creator Explains Controversial $2.5 Billion Sale to Microsoft </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 17:37:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wearable computing and privacy invasions you might want to think about now </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 15:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Clearpath Hits Husky With Shrink Ray, Announces Jackal UGV </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 15:19:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Text Message Web Browser Is Less Crazy Than It Sounds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 15:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Digital Literacy Is the Key to the Future, But We Still Don't Know What It Means </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 13:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A closer look at the space shuttle that never got to space </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 12:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple's Tim Cook on TV: 'If we're really honest it's stuck back in the seventies' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 11:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-14 19:29:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree completely. I really wish those people would call themselves something else, because it completely taints feminism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-14 18:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some feminists are sexist against males because they aren't good at empathy and fail to appreciate it from the other side. They also often spend a lot of time chatting to other feminists with similar views, which validates their own attitudes. There are blinkered people in every walk of life, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-14 18:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. The institution of marriage is far older than christianity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-14 18:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could legitimately argue that many major magazines basically are for white people (eg womens magazines v rarely feature non-white people on the cover). 
Plus, if a magazine specifically identified itself as 'for white people', would enough people actually buy it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-14 17:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you please give some examples? I'm struggling to think of what you mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 19:46:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for sharing! That sounds amazing - good luck with it all :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 19:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's awesome, I've always wanted an airstream. Is it as a primary home, or as a holiday home? Do you think you'll kit it out with loads of high-tech bits and pieces, or are you planning to go more off grid? (Sorry for all the questions!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 19:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah not one I normally read, but I stumbled across this and it looked interesting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Escaping the city: The coming rise of mass digital nomadism </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:25:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cars that drive themselves starting to chat with each other </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:24:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Identity Management in the age of wearable technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:22:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The journalists who never sleep: Robot writers that can interpret data and generate stories are starting to appear in certain business and media sectors </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Justice Sotomayor says technology could lead to Orwellian world </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:18:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A super-strong and lightweight new material that could be used to build lighter, stronger airplanes and batteries </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:17:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 11:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope at least $1000 of that is to pay for sewing lessons  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 10:45:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it is pretty itchy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Zeus, the Great Dane who held the title of worlds tallest dog, has died of old age, two months short of his sixth birthday </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 15:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Engineers develop first intelligent, heated clothing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 13:40:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 13:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you by any chance mean the [Kingdom of Lovely](http://micronations.wikia.com/wiki/Kingdom_of_Lovely)?

It was founded by UK author Danny Wallace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The First Space Vessel Designed Entirely for Tourists </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 10:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Here's How Japanese Pop Videos Depicted Cyberspace Back In 1989 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 10:47:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 10:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, that's so they can find out who's visiting their site - virtually all modern sites use analytics, and they aren't all selling the info to advertisers. 
Plus, what exactly do you mean by "your tracking information"? You know individuals can't be identified by analytics programs, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 08:55:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Zarrow.co.uk specialises in this kind of work  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Space garbage men: Tracking the movement and spin of orbiting space junk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 14:04:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Space garbage men: Tracking the movement and spin of orbiting space junk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 13:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chemists create 'assembly-line' for organic molecules </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 12:48:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Incredible Buckminster Fuller-Inspired Bioclimatic Dome Shows Off the Power of Digital Prefabrication </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 12:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chip packets help make safer water in Papua New Guinea </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 12:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Android KitKat on 24.5 percent of devices, but Jelly Bean is still king: Google </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 12:16:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> China to launch second space lab in 2016, official says </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-10 12:37:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The CO2 Increase Rate Has Reached a Three Decade High </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-10 12:36:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sharks lose their appetite in acidic oceans </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-10 12:35:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When Do We Get Catbots? We Have the Technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-10 11:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 22:40:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The funniest example of this was one my boyfriend's mum did (she believes in that crap, despite my bf's repeated explanations of cold reading etc) - it was one done over Skype (who knew that was a thing!) and everything the 'psychic' woman said was way off, so she blamed it on the 'bad vibes' of the McDonalds my bf's mum was in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 22:06:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah apologies, I missed that you weren't in the country. Good luck with it all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New restaurant aims to bring flavour of Caribbean to Ealing Broadway </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 21:42:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 21:41:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the same - it's insanely expensive and I'm really starting to consider moving out, but jobs in my field are thin on the ground outside of the city. I tend to escape to Bristol to see friends whenever it gets too much. 

I'd love for there to be some kind of solution to this, but I'm really struggling to think of anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ealing Half Marathon builds on London Olympic legacy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 21:31:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 21:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you can transform it into a real voice for the area it could be successful - my suggestion would be to get it going with regular posts and maybe try posting flyers around Ealing promoting it? Maybe try and launch discussions about any local issues and add pictures of any new features in the area for people to discuss. I'm close but not in your borough, but I will post anything I find that's relevant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 21:25:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for sharing - I had no idea this had been preserved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 16:20:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that might be a bit of a pandora's box issue - Midlanders would probably decry not being given their own specific government and the old Cornwall independence campaign would refire. The UK has a huge number of regional identities - we could easily end up with as many states as the US if we really tried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 16:17:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very true - eureka-alert is just a science press release portal, so it's only as accurate as each university's pr writers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 14:55:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about the rest of England?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The dawn of tiny tech: Molecular electronics closer to reality </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 13:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fossil   Intel partner on wearable technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 13:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The impossible triple star KIC 2856960 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 13:17:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers look to carbon dioxide as a more environmentally friendly refrigerant gas </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 13:14:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Shape-Shifting Architecture That Responds to Heat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 12:58:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blast from the past: 5 high-impact Apple keynotes that captured our imaginations </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 11:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Winter is coming: British weather set to become more unsettled </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 10:57:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new route to making graphene has been discovered that could make the 21st century's wonder material easier to ramp up to industrial scale </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 10:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 10:21:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really depends on the location and geology of the cliffs in question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What Would Make You Move To A Space Colony? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 10:15:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cliff house by Modscape suspended above the Australian ocean </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 10:13:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 16:56:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you mean to post this in [/r/gaming](http://www.reddit.com/r/gaming)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 16:54:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wonder at what point the pirates will decide to automate too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 14:06:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why don't you think they'll be built on Earth? I myself think it will happen eventually, but this might be partly because I just think they're an awesome idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Space elevators: Sci-Fi dream or future reality? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 13:25:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where to Watch Livestreams of Tomorrows Apple Event </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 13:05:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:56:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very true! I just feel bad for the poor fools who get taken in and hand over their money for stuff like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Buddhist singing bowls inspire new tandem solar cell design </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:55:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Massive BigRep Pro 3D Printer Offers 53 Cubic Foot Build Volume For $79,000 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:54:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apple Hires Renowned Designer Marc Newson </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:52:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Researchers uncover chemistry behind ancient Indigenous art </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:48:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bottle feeding changes infant's immune system </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:38:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This appears to be a campaign for a perpetual motion device </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bringing gesture-control technology from Hollywood to corporate conference rooms </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:12:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tokyo stocks end higher on rise in US shares- Nikkei Asian Review </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 11:20:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Before Android Wear and Apple iWatch: How watches got their smarts over the years </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 11:19:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-07 17:21:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, but those poorer are largely not paying UK prices </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-07 11:49:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't think it happened until I started working in an office in a touristy area of London. Some people seem to think the world is there to serve them. 

Mind you, it only ever happened with British tourists - everyone else has been nothing but polite and appreciative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 09:48:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> South Park are clearly going to do an episode on the fappening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 09:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait... there is a use for gold? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 09:40:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You stubbed your toe and your first reaction was to kick something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 09:21:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I've missed something here - what has being an arts student got to do with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-05 08:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! It seems crazy that the person I've been with for over five years gets the same title as in a teenage 'relationship' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In Pictures: The future of Londons transport is cycling </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 11:44:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It's good to talk: China opens up to psychotherapy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 09:29:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Atlantic slows warming, temperature rises seen resuming from 2030: study </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 09:27:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Garden cities: Where will we live in 2030 in maps </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 09:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Departments use technology to ID troubled officers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 09:25:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 09:14:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> factor-tech.com also does a lot of futurology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bitcoin hosting center will open in Michigan with the aim of lowering costs for professional Bitcoin miners </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 18:17:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> $100,000 in donations help Comcast get merger support from Chicago mayor </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 18:02:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is The Internet Scrambling Our Teenagers Brains? We Dont Know, But Probably Not. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 17:34:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Neuromodulation 2.0: New Developments in Brain Implants, Super Soldiers and the Treatment of Chronic Disease </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 17:30:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Solar Rain Tree Oasis Could Alleviate Drought-Striken California Using Rainwater Collection and Clean Energy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 17:05:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 17:02:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Space-only machinery is a very cool thought - it will be fascinating to see how it differs from Earth-designed stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Samsung reveals virtual reality headset powered by a smartphone </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 16:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First 3D printer in space to mark start of extraterrestrial manufacturing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 16:10:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 15:55:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or screen them for awesomeness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 15:49:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting story, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 15:12:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you mind telling us about it? I haven't heard that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NASA invites public to submit messages for asteroid mission time capsule </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 14:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Weird Facts About 5 of the Worlds Most Famous Logos </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 13:18:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Your Next Chevy May Watch You Watching the Road </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 13:16:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> BioShock Game Developer Mocks His Industry in The Magic Circle </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 13:13:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First 3D printer in space to mark start of extraterrestrial manufacturing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 13:10:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nearly 80,00 Gallons of Crude Oil Spill Into Alberta Waterway </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 12:30:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MasterCard-backed biometric ID system launched in Nigeria </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 12:11:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Doctor Who Sonic Screwdriver Cutlery Set </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 11:59:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3D-printed robotic birds of prey are undergoing trials </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 11:56:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Micron Technology (MU) Stock Is Down Today </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 10:42:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gulf of Maine: 'Poster child' for global warming </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 10:30:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Weaved treehouse with bamboo modules </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 10:28:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Burnt out birds suggest hard work could be bad for your health </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 10:26:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-03 00:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A key part of that profit comes from not paying over and above for staff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 23:34:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a very common practice in large news organisations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 22:34:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love that picture of him looking out of the window - he looks like he's surveying his kingdom! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 21:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There some decent online-only news sites, although any site that thinks 4chan is a person probably isn't in that group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Robots unlikely to take big bites out of employment, expert says </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 16:40:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nanoparticle-detecting microlasers to be used to identify viruses </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 14:42:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Homepages are a product of journalists who came from print and thought in print terms - i100 and Quartz prove homepages are increasingly irrelevant </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 11:50:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Windows 9 accidentally teased by Microsoft </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 11:43:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Behold! The Upcoming Estonian Bitcoin Castle </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 11:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Facebook Gears Up In Africa </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 10:52:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Japan space agency unveils asteroid hunting probe </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 10:51:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Korean Yujin Robot launches meal transport robot </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 10:38:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Has microfinance lost its moral compass? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 10:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> United Nations predicts climate hell in 2050 with imagined weather forecasts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-02 02:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: Given that images of 101 celebrities were leaked, why has all the media focus been on Jennifer Lawrence? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 23:11:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Almost every news article I have come across has focused on Jennifer Lawrence, but 101 people were affected, including a lot of other high-profile celebs. What's the deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3D printed concrete castle and plans to create and sell a concrete printer kit for about $30,000 to $50,000 that can print two story houses </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 17:12:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Archaeologists can now say for certain that Stonehenge was once a complete circle after the dry weather revealed the ghostly outlines of missing stones </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 16:49:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Japan firm showcases 'touchable' 3D technology </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 15:16:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Has Dysons robotic dream become a reality? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 14:56:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Space Pizza and Robotic Gardens: Producing food in orbit </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 13:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seismic engineering for tall buildings in Asia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 11:21:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-26 14:10:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I suspect the publisher is the one setting the prices - a friend is currently writing a textbook for a major publisher and pricing decisions are made by them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 22:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be honest with yourself and think carefully about how you could be better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 22:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cider </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 22:14:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First week-long break in over a year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 21:49:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed - it was surprisingly good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 20:01:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lots of dwarves and nearly being killed by a massive dragon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 20:00:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Utter silence as everyone stood browsing Reddit on their phones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:57:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only studied history up to the age of 14, but it wasn't mentioned in any of our classes. We mainly studied the tudors and the industrial revolution. Quite honestly I suspect it is something that very few British people know much about.

That was more than a decade ago though - does anyone else have a more recent experience?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sam Vimes likes cheap boots - they allow him to identify where he is in the city just by feeling the street through the thin soles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Got it for this reason. Can confirm it's worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:34:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He is pretty awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:33:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmmbop - Hanson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not really from London, are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This music](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OQnNH7I07RY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 17:59:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My tutor told us about a student that got caught plagiarising in her dissertation and in the plagiarism hearing yelled "I paid 300 for that - I should at least get a 2:1". 

She did not get a 2:1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spiraling Skyscraper Farms for a Future Manhattan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 17:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Airbus Unveils Incredible Design for a Transparent Plane </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 17:06:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 11:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to have the music stuck in my head for the rest of the day now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-23 17:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People who declare some cool new tech will never work because of some political or cultural quirk that is unique to the US - there are other places in the world! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-23 15:24:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If something bad happens to me, it is likely to in some way be my fault </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Famed Galapagos tortoise 'Pepe the Missionary' dies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-23 15:17:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-23 15:14:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It always surprises me that this annoys people so much - it just seems like the polite thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This week in iPhone rumors: Its all about the screen </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 19:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why the Robots Might Not Take Our Jobs After All: They Lack Common Sense </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 19:30:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are These Incredible Rice Paddy-Topped Hong Kong Towers the Skyscrapers of the Future? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 19:26:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Tiny House Villages Could Solve Americas Homeless Epidemic </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 19:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Drone Fleets Could Monitor Bridge Safety </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 19:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tech Time Warp of the Week: Watch Apples Awkwardly Wrong Prediction of the Future From 1987 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 19:24:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Space and the law: How decades-old policy is shaping exploration and commercialisation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 14:44:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Space and the law: How decades-old policy is shaping exploration and commercialisation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 14:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Class action against Facebook attracts 60,000 users </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 10:51:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ouya is turning to Asia to capture the growth that has eluded the startup on its own home turf </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 10:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oil thieves cause pipeline leak, pollute Mexico river </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 10:22:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Parents Dont Need Procreation Licenses  Transhumanism Vs. A Conservative Death Ethos </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 10:07:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 01:28:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is, although mainly because you can't forget to take it. I have one and it is really great, although a bit weird to feel in your arm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-21 22:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The article says "will be" - I assume they wrote this from a press release put out ahead of the presentation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hacking Gmail with 92 percent success </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-21 13:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 6 Fantasy Steampunk Contraptions Made Only From Cardboard </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-21 13:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Clearpaths public stance on Killer Robots sets precedence in corporate responsibility </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-21 13:05:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cities Are Making Spiders Grow Bigger and Multiply Faster </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 21:04:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gateway bug: How crickets could hook America on eating insects </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 13:52:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Transparent solar collector to turn skyscrapers into power plants </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 13:27:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Developers explore game experience for the blind </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 12:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> OSO creates a world of LEGO for the famous toy company's Istanbul HQ </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 10:29:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This fungus turns ants into zombies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 16:43:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Laser 'Lightning rods' channel electricity through thin air </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 16:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DIY diagnosis: How an extreme athlete uncovered her genetic flaw </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 16:06:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lockheed Martin conducts first fully autonomous robot mission </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 15:30:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can Starbucks Make 23,000 Coffee Shops Feel Unique? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 15:29:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is what your home on Mars could look like </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 15:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Have You Ever Wondered How Replicants Are Made in Blade Runner? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 10:32:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Study reveals immune system is dazed and confused during spaceflight </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 18:31:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 17:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Link to the NPR interview](http://hereandnow.wbur.org/2014/08/14/nasa-future-bolden) in case anyone is interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 17:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Planetary Resources is [actually hiring](http://www.planetaryresources.com/careers/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Heres a Terrible Idea: Robot Cars With Adjustable Ethics Settings </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 13:44:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Asteroids: The Next Frontier of Mining? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 13:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Asteroids: The Next Frontier of Mining? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 13:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tokyo stocks almost flat in morning amid lack of fresh incentives </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 11:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Emerging solar plants scorch birds in mid-air </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 11:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Coordinated UAV docking </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 11:09:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Men viewed more favorably than women when seeking work-life balance </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 11:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Look, no hands! Test driving a Google car </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 10:03:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 01:45:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please update us after - interested in seeing how this plays out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kim Dotcom: from playboy entrepreneur to political firebrand </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-17 22:01:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alopecia sufferers given new treatment hope with repurposed drug </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-17 21:59:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> RoboThespian: the first commercial robot that behaves like a person </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-17 20:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-16 10:25:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The cynic in me wonders if part of it is that robots don't need tips, which I can see being highly popular with some customers. 
Plus, novelty value - any hotel staffed by robots is going to attract a lot of interest! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Interview with Flavio Manzoni, chief designer at Ferrari </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-15 15:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Re-writing Asimov's laws of robotics for 21st century healthcare robots </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-15 14:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Re-writing Asimov's laws of robotics for 21st century healthcare robots </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-15 14:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 18:29:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Typical! Thanks for the heads up, I will take this down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 17:51:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not anymore - Siri no longer recommends locations, possibly because of this case </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-12 10:17:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't developing food solutions for space will benefit other missions too? What about when we want to take a journey that is a lot longer than 50 years? Or if we want to develop some form of colony or base? 
Surely it would be better to be able to create new food? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-11 17:43:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah I see! Thanks for the explanation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-11 16:54:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apologies if I am misunderstanding, but surely the food wouldn't survive in that growing environment?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 09:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How exactly would that help anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-25 00:13:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What made you decide to make the transition from computer scientist to futurist, and how did you go about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 23:46:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ten years from now, how different do you expect our daily lives to be from today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 13:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably because old people would go on mad spending binges before they died, rendering the whole exercise pointless. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-24 01:27:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You'd probably feel differently if you or your friends or family were the ones infected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 12:15:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish we'd had this class when I was in school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 18:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you addressing this to me? Or in general?  
I shared the article because I thought it was an interesting perspective rather than disliking religion's role.
I suspect that religion will recede due to people's lack of need for it, but I don't have a dislike of it in this context </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 17:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least he hasn't started blaming the Illuminati. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 17:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not so sure - for very large items (for example wind turbines) I can see the benefit, and I do wonder why companies would still be pursuing this if there was no benefit to it at all. 
I hope we see a time when airships are used (plus they'd remind me of the Twains from Terry Pratchett and Stephen Baxter's Long Earth series!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 17:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would argue that living longer lives isn't a true endgoal because it doesn't have a defined target - once we all feel like 50 when we're 100 we'll only be looking to the next horizon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-21 13:27:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure myself - does anyone know about this? Although obviously there are a lot of landlocked areas where shipping won't be much help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-10 16:33:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the title of the article - not my title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-03 01:28:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They have the machines to buy tickets by a lot of the bus stops on the route too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-02 21:32:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting to see that [BT is blocking Reddit](https://www.blocked.org.uk/results?url=http://www.reddit.com) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-27 12:46:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would higher speeds not be possible with a hanging rail design?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-25 20:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a fascinating story, and a pretty good insight into the practices of early archaeologists - amazing this stuff wasn't found earlier! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 11:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No one game - just the fact that every game previewed looked awesome, even the (very few) that wouldn't normally be my thing. I'd been thinking about if for a long time, but that was when I realised I had to go for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-19 15:34:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for doing the AMA.

What do you think the state of privacy and freedom of information will be a decade from now? Do you think Wikileaks will have an impact on future policy in this area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 16:38:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being immune to pathogens and diseases doesn't automatically make you physically attractive - unless there is some element of this that I have missed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 16:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not if they were a complete dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 16:07:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I quite agree - I didn't mean that it was a reason not to do this, just that achieving 'perfect' babies was a different thing to making them healthy. I think its an excellent idea, and I hope it becomes a reality as quickly as the article says.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 15:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there not a difference between 'perfect' and not carrying a disease? I took it to mean aesthetic features such as hair/eye colour etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 15:10:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here in the UK courses like these are starting to popup for various industries, mainly in tech. From what I hear they are doing a far better job of preparing people for employment than traditional degrees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 14:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a general rule, if an article leads with a question the answer will be no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-04 18:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about the cost argument? Meat could get too expensive to eat on a daily basis - would you consider bugs then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-04 13:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These guys seem to have quite a selection: http://www.thailandunique.com/ I haven't used them myself but I've tried the candy they carry before and was quite impressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-03 12:37:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The two aren't mutually exclusive, surely? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-03 12:29:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You just blew my mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-03 12:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really can't decide if this would be a good thing or not - it might make football a bit sterile. What do people think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 22:26:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair point, although I live in London and given house prices here are approaching a million quid for anything larger than a shoebox in a lot of boroughs I might end up being in the position where space-saving furniture was a still better option financially </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 20:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about being able to quickly rearrange the room for exercise or a party and then putting it back just by pressing a button? I live in a small flat and this would be a big plus for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 18:32:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> perhaps we could even have a robot robo chair technician? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 13:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's called a joke. And you might want to calm down before you pop an artery. 
To return to the intellectual side of this, yes I know the sun does it, but I was referring to human-made technology. It's never been achieved by humans, and given that we can't just recreate the sun there is no way yet to be certain it will definitely be achieved, particularly if it gets superseded by another technology that is cheaper to create.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 13:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Others may be able to shed more light on this, but I believe in US business this is known as a Chinese Wall, where information is prevented from moving between parts of the business to prevent conflicts of interest. I gather it is very common among big businesses, although how normal it is outside of the US I don't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 13:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Methinks you may have misunderstood my point. Keep working on that intellectual insight, sweetheart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 13:08:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What exactly is a grey ceiling tile supposed to contribute to this discussion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 13:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're putting a lot of faith in a technology that has never actually generated more energy than it takes to run it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-19 16:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a projection is not the same as a projector. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-19 14:46:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah my bad - missed this when it was first announced </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-14 13:47:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know, they seem to have a lot more information on their website than classic vapourware  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-12 15:49:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the shortlist (from the last paragraph of the article): Colombia, Costa Rica, El Salvador, Ghana, Guatemala, Guyana, Honduras, Hong Kong, Maldives, Montenegro, Mozambique, Nicaragua, Norfolk Islands, Palau, Panama, Senegal, Sierre Leone, Singapore, Suriname and Vanuatu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-12 15:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for doing the AMA guys, very much appreciated. 

My question is, do you see humanity going extinct in the future? If so when and from what cause? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 15:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree - I heard a rumour they were going into wearable tech, and I cannot see that ending well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 15:10:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My additions to that would be:

1. Make sure people know you've released a new console, not just a new controller
2. Release more games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 13:24:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Judging by the stage the tech mentioned in the article is at, we're likely to be looking at 5 years minimum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-06 17:26:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beyond Good and Evil (gamecube, HD version for PS3) uses a camera heavily for gameplay, although you are mainly photographing animals/revolutionary occurrences - it makes for a pretty awesome gameplay mechanic :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-06 13:21:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might be partly to do with the UK bank holiday - I didn't realise this was already out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-30 17:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Report came out today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-25 14:49:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want your brother's job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-23 20:17:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it depends on the size of the community there and what kinds of policies you are talking about - outside organizations and earth-based politicians are only going to affect some issues, so even if they are technically in control, a lot of issues are still going to be decided internally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-23 16:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My pleasure! There's something so cool about old maps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-08 18:17:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting technology - if this got going I think there might be an initial tree loss but I guess we'd see more being planted as the technology became commercialised </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-03 15:07:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mmm tasty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-01 15:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would they not be flying quite a bit lower than commercial jets? I have to admit I'm no expert on airspace, but I assume that if they are able to land on buildings they will be a long way off the airspace jets will be in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-01 15:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What makes you so sure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-21 14:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't regard an obese person to be inherently unhealthy, only if they were sick or their size appeared to be affecting their health (eg their breathing). When my SO has no symptoms I would regard him to be healthier than an obese person, but not so much when he is sick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-21 11:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Medical treatments with stem cells - it will have a radical impact on the way diseases etc are treated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-21 11:11:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're good in smoothies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-21 10:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a video game mirror </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-21 01:08:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Invasive surgery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-21 01:03:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah exactly that - when he has no symptoms he seems as healthy as the next person despite having a chronic condition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-21 00:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure there is a more precise medical definition, but I would consider people with disabilities to be healthy on the basis that they are not suffering from something that is affecting their immune system.
Similarly, my SO has crohn's disease, which is a chronic autoimmune disease, but I consider him healthy when he has no symptoms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-21 00:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree! Some people I know who say its rubbish haven't even used it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-21 00:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might be time to invest in a USB extension cable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-11 22:30:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Salt, pepper and a decent range of herbs and spices - helps improve cheap food no end!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-10 16:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-10 15:17:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine actually sticks out of my bag (although I do have a small bag) when I take it to work. 
I think it could make much larger screens more portable, though, so that would be cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-10 13:07:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That actually sounds pretty interesting too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-10 13:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some very cool stuff here, but wouldn't all of this put farm workers out of business? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-10 12:59:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally I think the optical networks-on-chip for future multicore computer systems one would be the most interesting in terms of potential for cool findings and similar.
I was not clear on what the Vellum project was - could you please elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-03 15:39:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have had the same experience, but I don't think it's on the same scale. So many people stuck with XP that they never got to 7 to then respond that way to it. 
I think a bigger part of it is that XP is what was out when many people finally got on board with the idea of computers - that OS is literally all they've known and all they are prepared to cope with. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-28 13:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd agree with this - my PS3 is a great Netflix machine and doesn't get the audio sync issues that I have with my PC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-28 13:21:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think getting more people online could have a really interesting effect on both the world and the internet. The internet does give you the tools to do an amazing amount - it really does make starting a business easier, so I could see it really benefiting people currently in poverty.

But it will be interesting to see what the impact will be on the internet - will the next mega internet company come from India? Will we see an increase in memes that derived from the pop culture of developing countries? Or will variation in internet speeds lead to region-specific ghettos online? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>