<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2959</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do I get my girlfriend to open up and talk to me about her depression? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:18:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My girlfriend recently has started taking antidepressants (Lexapro). I have known she has been depressed, but she really struggles talking about it. Anytime it ever comes up, she says that she hates talking about it and quickly changes the subject. How can I get my girlfriend to try to talk about her depression with me? 

What are better ways to phrase questions such as
"What do you think the source of your depression is?
Is your depression situational or clinical? What exactly have you been diagnosed with (All I have been told is she has anxiety and depression, nothing like the name of a specific disorder). 

I know that a depressed person has trouble explaining how they feel to a person without depression, but how can I get her to open up to me so I can help her more? Am I actually completely wrong in trying to do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:06:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My girlfriend just started taking antidepressants for her depression. She is really struggling to open up to people about her depression. I want to help so badly, but all I really know is that she's depressed. I don't know what's causing it, if its situational or an actual disorder. How can I get her to open up to me/how can I help her cope with/overcome her condition? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:50:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I need shoe help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 04:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Madeon [Only Way Out](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NXGk_GcQ09g). Probably my favorite song on this amazing album, also definitely not the most popular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 02:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Giraffage at Porter's Worlds tour. Still listen to his stuff, it's amazing. 10/10 would see a show he headlined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:59:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FUCK BRITT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can I wear JCP Stafford Wingtip Boots with a suit? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 04:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bought a pair of [these boots](http://www.jcpenney.com/shoes/extended-sizes/large-sizes-13-over/stafford-deacon-mens-wingtip-leather-boots/prod.jump?ppId=pp5004560043 catId=cat100250175 topDim=Brand topDimvalue=stafford dimCombo=Brand%7C dimComboVal=stafford%7C currentDim=Brand currentDimVal=stafford _dyncharset=UTF-8 colorizedImg=DP0902201417014697M.tif urlState=/shoes/shop-men-s-shoes/dress-shoes/stafford/_/N-1nopj3Z7i/cat.jump) a few months ago after seeing them on this subreddit. My question is could I pair them with a grey suit? Or are they too casual?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-18 02:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like seriously Jade is the only one who realistically would move to Iowa. Whitney would never leave her job, Kaitlyn seems like she isn't ready to get married and have children, and lets be real Becca is so flat and one-dimensional, if she doesn't go home next episode I'm breaking my tv. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-18 01:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I could not agree more about Jade. She was my favorite ever since the cinderella episode. She's smart, funny. and fucking gorgeous. Jade if you somehow are reading this, will you marry me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 04:16:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Playboy got cut for never has played with a boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 04:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tits: 8/10 only because they're fake (in the video you can see scars)
Ass: 10/10
Face: 9/10

Overall 9.5/10 literally I am in love with this girl
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-17 04:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone else really pissed Jade didn't get a rose? I feel like she was the only one who would actually live in Iowa with Chris. I don't see Whitney moving, Kaitlyn isn't ready for marriage, and Becca just doesn't have the chemistry/is too 1-dimensional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 02:55:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think people that commit suicide are completely pathetic. You should be able to help yourself before you get to that point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Armin Van Buuren Echostage 1/24/15 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-24 21:58:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone here on r/aves also going to this show? I've read other threads on how Armin's live sets are amazing, and echostage has gotten good reviews on this sub. Anyone have any tips for tonight (this will be my 5th rave).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 4th graders plotted to kill 'mean' teacher with hand sanitizer, cops say </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-14 03:38:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Aliens have contacted Earth. You must choose one man and one woman to be ambassadors representing the human race. Who do you pick? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 17:03:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-31 17:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live about 30 miles away from a nuclear power plant, so anything associated with that would freak me out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Puma G. Vilas L 2 Sneaker $45.50 (Usually $65) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 19:34:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AIAIAI- TMA 1 for $50 at Best Buy worth the investment? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:51:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here is the link](http://www.bestbuy.com/site/aiaiai-tma-1-beatport-edition-over-the-ear-dj-headphones/4860443.p?id=1218555763360 skuId=4860443#tabbed-customerreviews) to these headphones. They were shown in [DJ Ravine's](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WrnKWBkAk4I) headphone review and are normally priced at $200. I already own pioneer hdj 500 headphones and I am happy with them. Is this deal too good to pass up? Or would it not be worth it, meaning should I just wait to upgrade headphones to something better like the Sennheiser hdj 25-II?

Tl;dr- Do I upgrade or keep my pioneer hdj 500s?

Edit: Ended up buying these before the price increase, burned them in for 12 hours overnight and I'm definitely happy. Not as bass heavy as the hdj 500, but a clear upgrade. More comfortable, better isolation, and better sound overall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> (Request) Black Friday Peacoat deal </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 21:32:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 07:28:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is my swamp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can I wear a knit tie to homecoming? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-21 05:27:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Going to homecoming this weekend (I'm a senior in high school) and I was wondering if it's appropriate to wear a knit tie with a 2 button suit. Aren't knit ties supposed to be more casual? Also, what is the appropriate width of a knit tie? I know they're supposed to be skinnier, but what is the correct width? 2 in or 2.75 in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chrome Resolution/Sizing Problem </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-11 21:12:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recently updated chrome along with a bunch of other windows 8 updates and now my browser sizing is off. The resolution is blurrier and larger than normal. My laptop is 1920x1080 and it feels like I'm back at 1360x768 when using chrome. For example, here is my new tab page, clearly something happened to the resolution as this image used to be full screen: [Here](http://imgur.com/DofT7ca)

How can I fix the resolution of chrome? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 05:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really just want a cheaper version of a brogue boot. Something inexpensive, but still durable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Frugal Version of Allen Edmonds Boots? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love [these boots](http://www.allenedmonds.com/aeonline/producti_SF0181_1_40000000001_-1_) but need a MUCH cheaper option. Like around $100-$150. I definitely want burgundy as my color, but I am definitely open to looking into other styles, materials even (doesn't have to be leather, could be suede, what are options outside of suede burgundy CDBs?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 03:20:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my question really is just how much is your heel supposed to move </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do Clarks Desert Boots size? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 02:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just got a pair of Clarks Desert Boots in the mail, but I am confused on the sizing. I wear an 11 in Vans and dress shoes, so I ordered a 10.5 in CDBs. However, the shoes still feel somewhat big. Should I send them back and size down to a 10? Do CDBs usually fit loosely? (The fit of the shoe isn't bad, it just isn't perfect). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-13 07:01:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in love with [these](http://us.puma.com/en_US/pd/el-seevo-canvas-mens-sneakers/pna887706697532.html?selvar=true), and for $36, how can you not get them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 12:50:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If someone wants to PM me a code that would be fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could I connect a DJ controller to these? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-28 13:00:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dad is getting rid of his Pioneer [SC-AK310 speaker system](http://welectronics.com/stereo/sc-ak310.jpg) for a newer upgrade. Could I connect a controller to these such as the DDJ-SX or DDJ-SR? What cable(s) would I need?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 04:35:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely want to go darker, get to a darker brown like in [this](https://www.3wisemen.co.nz/media/catalog/product/cache/1/image/6efaed196d6ddc33b03f911d25dbe699/b/t/bt1068_1.jpg) picture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How can I darken this leather belt? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-20 03:45:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bought [this](http://i.imgur.com/cg6EaRz.jpg) leather belt today, got tricked by the lighting to make me think it was darker. What is a good way to darken it? Would oil rub off on the clothes I wear with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>