<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1208</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:22:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:09:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh. Ignore me. Nothing to see here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This has been called LONG before /u/Sneffy. Pretty sure people were thinking Waltz was Blofeld as soon as he was announced.

~~Think it's more likely he has the scar already, seeing as the right side of his face was hidden in the shadows in the trailer.~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cancelled my fight pass already. piratebay here I come </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dunno. seems spurious. Chekhov's Gun would suggest she has an important role to play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:12:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty tech illiterate. Is there anything with the same ease of use as Hola? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try refreshing a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:20:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> doing god's work. cheers old horse

edit: tried it again and it worked first time. the fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't find anything in the news about it either. Will keep trolling sources in the meantime, but I'm guessing this is what they were talking about earlier in the year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> VPN users across the world are now blocked from accessing US version of Netflix. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:16:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems this has just happened in the last hour or so. Users from across the world reporting the same thing.

[Thread in /r/netflix](https://www.reddit.com/r/netflix/comments/3e54i4/all_has_netflix_begun_blocking_hola_users/)

Guess it's time to go outside...

EDIT: now it's working again... kinda. Hola users can keep refreshing and it will work. Not sure about others. But clearly Netflix have stepped up their security. If you have a working VPN service that can access the US library, please share. I don't want to go outside. Tis a silly place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hm. Same here. UK version still works for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:04:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was fired from my reporting job for reporting disparaging stories about the company's health insurer. it's a two way street. fuck the UFC for pandering to corporate interests, and fuck Reebok for complaining. UFC wouldn't have done this without Reebok making a fuss. Not a hope in hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [ALL] Has Netflix begun blocking Hola users? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:59:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just happened to me and a friend down here in Bermuda. Wondering if it's country-specific or across the board

EDIT: seems like it was only temporary? It's working again for me using Hola. Did an adorable puppy break into the server room or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> suprised it hasnt been done already. Stich is a fucking staple for me. This pisses me off more than anything that's happened in sports during my lifetime. He's a goddamn legend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:11:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> butter for scale needs to be the new banana for scale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:01:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> to know better than what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:38:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:52:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what I said. Black people aren't bad swimmers because they're black. Rather, black people are usually bad swimmers. Probably for a number of reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:45:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, that's stereotyping. And many stereotypes are there for a reason. The one about black people not being good swimmers is more true than it is false. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:44:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bermuda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:42:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just edited my comment because that's how it came off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:37:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Racism is the one thing in the world that makes me actually rage. This is not racism. I live on an island with a majority black population. While black people love the water just as much as us whiteys do, if not more, they really are terrible swimmers. I've seen black kids jump 40 feet off cliffs, do a perfect backflip jackknife, then pop up and doggy paddle their ass back to the dock asap. That said, it's not a rule, rather a trend. The armchair Freakonomics writer in me wants to say it might just come down to whose parents pay for swim classes, or where you grow up. I'm a super strong swimmer because I grew up on a beach with a vicious rip-tide and a father who'd chuck me into it then tell me to swim back to him, not because I'm white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well if we're going with the neck injury, surely there's more of a chance of that pushing someone and whipping their neck back, rather than just smacking them on the head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:20:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... hwat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Touch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *wry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:06:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://media1.giphy.com/media/iUXJeVZyKneO4/200_s.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:05:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know those charts at the doctor's office showing faces correlated to pain? I feel like that's the total range of her acting ability. The pain chart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:03:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you shut your whore mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:30:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wait really? I thought it was just the shortened version of babe, a grammatical corruption.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:23:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know this opinion is super unpopular on reddit, but I just don't see it. He's a perfectly adequate actor to me, but really nothing special. And in A Young Doctor's Notebook I think he's trash, helped  by very good writing and Jon Hamm. So many actors that could do so, so much more with that role than Radcliff ever could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 22:00:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure there are enough people doing that already. You can't just enslave an entire people then give them their freedom and expect the entire population to swing into step with the rest of society. White people have had an entire system of support that's been improved for thousands of generations.

Imagine sending two kids out into the wild to fend for themselves. Which one is going to do better: the kid that's been raised by a family of avid campers, or the kid that's never ventured beyond the city limits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 18:54:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I've TRIED to explain this in one of my articles, but really, I have no idea. Short story is that it's a combination of factors. The wing-sail exploits the Bernoulli principle, the same thing that makes planes fly. The foils then practically eliminate drag by pushing the boats out of the water. These two combinations mean the boats can get going way faster than anyone, even the designers of the boats themselves, predicted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 18:51:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For safety reasons, no. Luckily the course they'll be racing in Bermuda has a pretty steady breeze, rarely getting above 20-25 knots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 18:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The AC World Series comes down here in October, when flights and hotels rooms will be cheaper. Come check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 18:38:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The point is that they can sail much faster in wind speeds that would have been too low to race in with a J-Class. I get to see the AC45's from my porch. The water is flat calm but they're fucking flying, crew boats behind them going full pelt just to keep up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 18:12:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3x the wind speed fast. Boggles the mind  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 18:10:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not only that, they are capable of reaching three times the wind speed in much shallower waters, allowing stadium seating for spectators. Historically only those with access to private boats were able to watch the races. The wing sail the boats are using is also a huge improvement as it allows them to not be at the mercy of the wind as much as they were in the past. This meant there were huge delays in the action, which is terrible for TV.

For the next finals though they've shrunk the size down to 48 feet. The AC48 while smaller is a lot more affordable to build (SF only had three boats competing because of the price). 

I'm actually the America's Cup correspondent for my paper when it comes to my home of Bermuda in 2017. Can't. Fucking. Wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 18:01:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel safe here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 16:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's ok. Can't miss what you never had, right? ^^^^except ^^^^you ^^^^can ^^^^and ^^^^I ^^^^just ^^^^really ^^^^want ^^^^a ^^^^dad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 16:44:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> did you just mix up Princess Bride and Star Wars? I'm not even mad. I'm impressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 16:16:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok but you have to call me Dragon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 16:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DID WE JUST BECOME BEST FRIENDS!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This all should be a thing. I've never wanted something that never existed this bad

Besides my own father of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Opinions are fun!

e: comment above me originally said "I won't".

e2: commenter above me has now referred to his original comment, making edit #1 superfluous. This edit may also be superfluous. But if I could just bring everyone's attention back to me for a second, that'd be great. Not for any particular reason. I'm just a slut like that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 09:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not quite. Just live in a country where conserving water is drilled into you from birth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 09:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do you want a drought? because that's how you get droughts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 04:03:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HEAD NIGGA IN CHARGE, for anyone who doesn't know

source: had a Trini boss who called himself that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 03:46:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I just sucked blood out of a boob... [Body Issue] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me and my FWB were fucking around with each other on the couch roughhousing, and I pinned her down and started sucking on her boob (not the nipple) really hard to give her a huge hickey, and when I pulled away I tasted iron in my mouth. Turns out it was blood. Not a lot, but when I wiped the spot where I was sucking you could clearly see it. And it was on my tongue.

How the fuck did I just suck blood out of her titty!? Can someone please explain this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 19:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, that's why I've stuck with journalism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:07:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lucid or vivid? Because if I can take something for lucid dreams I doubt I'll ever bother leaving my bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 17:01:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shine on each other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Strange memories on this nervous night in Las Vegas. Five years later? Six? It seems like a lifetime, or at least a Main Erathe kind of peak that never comes again. San Francisco in the middle sixties was a very special time and place to be a part of. Maybe it meant something. Maybe not, in the long run . . . but no explanation, no mix of words or music or memories can touch that sense of knowing that you were there and alive in that corner of time and the world. Whatever it meant. . . .

History is hard to know, because of all the hired bullshit, but even without being sure of history it seems entirely reasonable to think that every now and then the energy of a whole generation comes to a head in a long fine flash, for reasons that nobody really understands at the timeand which never explain, in retrospect, what actually happened.

My central memory of that time seems to hang on one or five or maybe forty nightsor very early morningswhen I left the Fillmore half-crazy and, instead of going home, aimed the big 650 Lightning across the Bay Bridge at a hundred miles an hour wearing L. L. Bean shorts and a Butte sheepherder's jacket . . . booming through the Treasure Island tunnel at the lights of Oakland and Berkeley and Richmond, not quite sure which turn-off to take when I got to the other end (always stalling at the toll-gate, too twisted to find neutral while I fumbled for change) . . . but being absolutely certain that no matter which way I went I would come to a place where people were just as high and wild as I was: No doubt at all about that. . . .

There was madness in any direction, at any hour. If not across the Bay, then up the Golden Gate or down 101 to Los Altos or La Honda. . . . You could strike sparks anywhere. There was a fantastic universal sense that whatever we were doing was right, that we were winning. . . .

And that, I think, was the handlethat sense of inevitable victory over the forces of Old and Evil. Not in any mean or military sense; we didnt need that. Our energy would simply prevail. There was no point in fightingon our side or theirs. We had all the momentum; we were riding the crest of a high and beautiful wave. . . .

So now, less than five years later, you can go up on a steep hill in Las Vegas and look West, and with the right kind of eyes you can almost see the high-water markthat place where the wave finally broke and rolled back.

EDIT: I went through an HST phase like everyone else, but I went a bit further. I devoured everything he wrote. Even copied his short stories out by hand. Without a doubt Fear and Loathing is his best work, but I'd really recommend people pick up The Great Shark Hunt, which is a collection of his short stories. That said, out of his entire bibliography, this quote still sticks with me the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 02:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> apparently people don't like South Park references  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 02:23:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not my neighbor. My best friend's neighbor. And I guess they are. The two families are very close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 02:22:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lucy is her name. She's also called Lulu. Or just Lu. Or Lucifer.

e: Lu. Cy. She was Lulu, plain Lulu, in the morning, standing two foot one in one sock. She was Lu in slacks. She was Lucifer at school. She was Lucindra on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lucy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:57:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My best friend's dog does this every morning to his neighbors. She's the sweetest chocolate lab you've ever met, Lucy. She pops over to the neighbors house at the exact time the mom goes for a run. Trots along with her for a little while, turns back, hits the pool, then goes home to be fed and have a nap.

The whole being a human thing is way overrated. I'd trade places with dear old Lulu any day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:54:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Step ~~3~~ 4: bro down.

e: [seriously thought Reddit would get this reference.](http://media.bizj.us/view/img/3873531/cartman-south-park-twitter-ubjjpg-large*1200xx946-532-0-16.png)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:53:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your posts recently have been not bad for someone who can't spell their name ^^^^I'm ^^^^sorry ^^^^I ^^^^can't ^^^^resist ^^^^it's ^^^^a ^^^^problem. ^^^^I ^^^^know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well there goes my Friday night plans ^^^I ^^^need ^^^to ^^^get ^^^a ^^^life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That;s exactly the type of solution I was thinking of. Use your head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is ALWAYS ok to laugh and upload to reddit. SCHAAAAAADENFRUEDE is like when a college kid find out what he put his dick in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my 27 years I've learned dealing with assholes is a part of life. There's a family that's moved onto a sailboat just off my dock (I live on an island) and I initially said they could use it to move their shit back and forth as they made it into a place they were able to live in.

They've since torn the ass out of my favour, use it all the time, and disrupt the guests I have living in the vacation cottage I rent out when they're down on my dock relaxing/kayaking/gawking at the turtles. I posted private property signs, put a chain across the path leading to my dock, but they kept using it. Instead of going out to their boat and smashing it, I called the respective authorities, reported them for illegal mooring and trespassing without filing charges. The police spoke to them and they haven't used it since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then you get the list of registered license plates from the property manager, call the authorities, show them the unregistered license plate parked illegally, and have it towed. Not sure if property managers do that everywhere, but they do where I'm from.

Or you come up with a creative, infruriatingly annoying (but legal) solution yourself. Box them in. Cover the car in bird food. Have a stakeout and wait for the repeat offender to show up and don't let him park there. Cover their car in sticky notes. The reason they are parking there in the first place is because it's clearly more convenient. Make it inconvenient. 

My problem is that the punishment doesn't match the crime. This is an inconvenience. Smashing someone's window as a response is outright destructive, not to mention foolish because in the end it will most likely cause you way more grief than it's worth. I'd rather not risk the ball-ache that would come with being charged with destruction of property. I was a court reporter for three years and I can assure you that risking a legal battle over something like this is just not. worth. your. time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:15:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not what I said at all. Just think you should deal with assholes reasonably and within the bounds of the law. Glad you fuck law for a living. So euphoric.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think I'll just have to use last year's stats and find a total average. I'm not even good at math, just really want to know the answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dunno, because that's what grown ups do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:57:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cheers. I'm bored and curious, so trying to figure out how much energy the racers in the Tour produce over the course of the event and how that compares to the energy consumption of a town or city. Ie: riders produce an average combined total of X watts over the course of the TdF, enough to power x for x amount of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How much wattage is produced by a GC rider over the course of the Tour? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:43:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:52:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah we don't have that where I'm from. Mostly just clamping, which is retarded since the whole idea is to move a car from where it's not supposed to be, not keep it there.

E: the fuck are people downvoting me for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on where you live. Could call and have it clamped, but that won't solve the issue. Could file a report with the police and have the towed.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:47:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly what I thought of. My country is mostly black. I got serious dirty looks during American History class in middle school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm not getting how this is funny. There's perfectly legal recourse for getting people to stop parking where they shouldn't be. Seems to me the residents are the bigger cunts in this scenario, unless it's just some random window smashing bandit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:02:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have two dents in one shin, another dent in the other. First two came from running full sprint in the dark into a shin-height wall. 

The other one I got while sailing. I was in a two man boat with a weighted keel and we hit a rock, sending my crew overboard. As I tried to wheel the boat around to get him, I hit another rock and my leg slipped out from under me and wailed the traveller bar.

Excruciating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 02:58:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Funny that this is a popular idea with a website like Reddit but not with online news. Sorry /r/KotakuInAction, while it would be nice to have ethics, the advertisers funding the content you enjoy have far more of a say than you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 01:48:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> huh... had no idea Pesci was gay. TIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:30:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/CasualJiggles  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:31:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't jump to conclusions just yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:23:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> -- Abraham Lincoln  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you for my new background 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:17:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't say "not to be pedantic." I apologised in advance for being pedantic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This guy's a way better actor. Let's be real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:09:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> different events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:07:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry to be pedantic, but you can't read the IPCC. He'd need to read the IPCC's AR5 (Fifth Annual Report). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly what I was thinking. You can bet your ass if I had an island like that I'd be chucking spears at anyone that came near. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! Have to admit, I really thought this was a clever question. The rule that no thought is original holds true once again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:59:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking hell. Ever since Inception every fucking trailer has that WHOMMMMMMP noise. I can't stand it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:51:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of when everyone thought Serena Williams could beat a male tennis player ranked 110th. She was demolished.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dunno, I think people underestimate the power difference. I'd be willing to bet she'd have a tough time taking him down alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If I have to run 100m in the rain, will I get less wet by running quickly or walking steadily? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:12:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I drive a motorcycle and I get caught in the rain from time to time, so I've always wondered this.

Driving fast means I arrive at my destination faster, reducing my overall exposure, but surely the faster I move forward the more rain I come in contact with. But driving slowly has the exact same problem. I reduce my overall contact with the raindrops, but increase my exposure time.

For the purpose of the question, I've made things simpler, and perhaps more applicable to the everyday person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not seen What If, but Horns and Notebook were exactly what I was thinking. There are a lot of actors that would've killed those roles. Radcliffe merely fills them. He's a well trained actor, don't get me wrong, but he's only where he is today because he looked the part for Harry Potter when he was a boy. A Young Doctor's Notebook is extremely well written, and I think deserved more than Radcliffe alongside Hamm.

I'd just like to add downvoting someone because they don't like an actor you do is why this site is going down the drain soon. I think I'm contributing to the discussion by adding an alternative viewpoint, one that's been informed by experience in film and screenwriting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:39:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Humblebrag much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:39:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Minus the acting ability. Lovely chap. Really. But his latest work has showed him to be pretty one dimensional, despite his efforts to find unique roles. Lucky for him, people will take one dimension Daniel Radcliffe.

EDIT: the downvote button is not for disagreement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:31:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:23:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last I checked Luda was a supporting actor in a multiple oscar-winning film... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP clarified saying the dog could only pee in small, bloody drips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:07:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuckass deleted it. Alas we can only remember </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:49:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly what I was thinking. Reads more like the top post on /r/soccer yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You need to get better at maths, champ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:24:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe when you get a little older you'll realize the world isn't as cut and dry as you'd like to think it is. 

You just said "it's hard not to imagine" and followed that up by declaring yourself "completely right."

Must be weird believing your imagination to be completely right, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pao: "Hey guys, could you get these shit slinging monkeys off my back? Just tell them what's what."

Alexis, eating popcorn: "No, they wouldn't believe us anyways. You're tough, Ellen. Keep it up." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:17:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least it wasn't comic sans.

Serious tip though. Pao was pre-packaged for redditors to dislike considering her history. The fact she has an easily punnable name didn't help either. Also, she isn't a founder of the site. The decisions made while she was in charge gave the distinct appearance that this was a CEO who didn't know what they were doing and was enforcing their own agenda on the company.

At the end of the day I'm blown away nobody stepped up to the plate to let Reddit know what was really going on, that Pao was not to blame. This could have been avoided entirely if someone had the stones to say: "This is what we all think should happen going forward, and that's been the case since before Ms Pao was hired." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:48:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [MRW I'm not actually a cow.](http://gfycat.com/ThosePerfectBeardedcollie) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Went for a beautiful hike through the Pyrenees with the girls today, only to have it ruined by a bunch of stupid boys on their bikes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:47:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Narada Michael Walden - I Shoulda Loved Ya (1979) [Funk] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:32:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BAW GAHD THAT MAN HAD A FAMILY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> PETITION: Reboot Power Rangers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:26:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> AWESOME. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for Stage 10 replay or highlights </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:00:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Citi -- Power Play [Disco] 1979 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:06:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly think this is Mos' magnum opus (no rhyme intended).

The lyricism is out of control. And premonitory, especially for 1999.

 Sixteen ounces to a pound, twenty more to a key,
 
 A five minute sentence hearing and you're no longer free.
 
 40% of Americans own a cell phone
 
 so they can hear everything that you say when you ain't home.
 
 I guess Michael Jackson was right, "You Are Not Alone".
 
 Rock your hardhat black cuz you in the Terrordome,
 
 Full of hard niggaz, large niggaz, dice tumblers
 
 Young teens in prison greens facin life numbers,
 
 Crack mothers, crack babies and AIDS patients,
 
 Young bloods can't spell but they could rock you in PlayStation.
 
 This new math is whippin motherfuckers' ass
 
 You wanna know how to rhyme you better learn how to add

It's mathematics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  whiskey and coke or you are doing fat lines and drinking booze.

porque no los dos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:31:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yesssss. Good. Let the peasantry flow through you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pew pew

honestly though, I feel like this might be the one and only time I as a console gamer can feel just a litttttttle bit superior. I maybe game 4 hours a week normally. This weekend I had a booze fuelled coke fest with my buddies playing Batman and it's INCREDIBLE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:48:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont remember that in Going Clear... at all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:47:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dunno, it's pretty disappointing he won't come out as gay. Everyone in Hollywood knows. It's no secret. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... what?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:11:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  "rage trance" isn't an excuse.

Sure, but a mental health condition might be. Or brain damage. Have you ever seen a video of a person acting like this? There's usually some logic to people's actions, at least fuzzy logic. This type of attack makes no sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That made me think it was more than just road rage. It's like he's coming out of a rage trance. The guy at the end of the video seemed to know him as well, and was treating him gently, like he's seen it before. I don't know if outright rage is symptom of any behavioral or psychological issues, but I wouldn't be surprised if this guy has had these kind of moments before. And that's not normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 00:26:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the best description I've ever read....... Spot. Fucking. On. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the need to point out it's the Muslims that are violent towards UK soldiers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:31:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Coincidentally, the man who led the gunpowder plot, Sir Henry Tucker, is my ancestor. If it wasn't for the Continental Congress going back on our deal to give you all our gunpowder in exchange for the lifting of a trade embargo, we'd be American today, instead of... *shudder*... British. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dear Murica: /r/Bermuda here. Our nations were founded by the same men, but separated by destiny. Today I'd like to extend an olive branch, and remind you that while we may funnel a lot of your would-be tax money through our shores, we too are Patriots. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:24:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Non American chiming in here. Not only are Americans good hosts in America, they're good hosts outside of America as well. The British are awful when it comes to socialising. Americans (and Canadians) will be your best friend for the day just because you ordered their favourite beer. They'll strike up a conversation with you about golf because you wear a Calloway hat. I went to boarding school in the US and the number of friends I've made outside of America based solely on the school I went to is astounding.

You guys were my saving grace when I was living in England. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:05:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Give it a shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't believe I've never seen this. Baw gahd chuckles were had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:54:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh honey... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:29:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> C'mon let's be real here. Wearing kilts? They're asking for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 05:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even better that it's a 14 year old writing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 04:21:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WORLDSTAR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bermuda checking in. We're the pimple on your tectonic ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A while back I upvoted my own comments on an alt to see if my total karma went up. I know. Bad, bad juju. Unidan etc. I was young and naive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn't matter. Still fapped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:40:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> doot doot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shit. There's no context. The thread was asking girls what was the most arbitrary reason they've ever chosen to have sex with a guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A true patriot </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, I dont like it because you presume your link to wikipedia completely nullifies the entire argument of the article. Which it doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:38:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dammit. I was so ready to mount my high horse and pretend I wasn't the least bit worried when they rejected me back in my uni days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No offense, but I feel like Bernie's endorsements is a game of "People That Don't Matter" Bingo.

Up next: Jonathan Lipnicki Endorses Sanders! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:18:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THe annoying part is that GallowBoob is actually a really good looking guy. He posted a pic of himself in his sub, IIRC. And this is coming from a man normally petty enough to denigrate other men sheerly for their better looks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're totally right. A simple link to wikipedia is far better than writing an intensely well researched article in the New Yorker, a known rag for shills and pansy liberals. A tip of the hat to you, good sir. You've bested Ms Lepore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 20:58:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  straddled with massive debt

I'd love to be straddled by anything at this point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 20:45:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like you're captaining the caboose into assumption junction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 20:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...

"Unattended babies can drown in bathtubs"

"That's hardly universal law...." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 20:42:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try not using wikipedia.

http://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/the-lost-amendment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:47:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I dont bother with the comments. I have loads of other sources but I use it to make sure I don't miss anything big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THere's a vast difference between the original and modern interpretation of the 2nd Amendment. It wasn't until a republican did a "history" on the amendment in the 50s/60s IIRC that people began interpreting it as "the right to have a gun". Up until then it was known as the Forgotten Amendment, because it was solely to do with the people's rights to "bear arms" against a tyrannical government.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Power does corrupt though. They've done studies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:11:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> did... did you just say meow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:10:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kinda like Shadow, Chance, and Sassy...

^^^I'm ^^^sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the thing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 16:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure it's awesome sitting on a high horse demanding companies do what you say without paying them. You can't have ethics in journalism when your primary customer is advertisers. As I said in another comment, I run a tiny regional magazine and I've had advertising pulled for writing a bad review, putting me in the red for the quarter. What do you propose I do? Keep writing bad reviews until my company files for bankruptcy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 15:40:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a journalist and I keep tabs open on rising submissions in /r/worldnews and other news subs. So technically Redditing IS working. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/retiredgif  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:47:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finding it hard to breathe up there on your high horse? I don't disagree but fucking hell you have to love yourself to quote yourself. Get a life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More talking about the whole of KiA. I've posted here before trying to explain this, but nobody wants to listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:06:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gaming journalism is probably bottom rung on the ladder of importance for the Guardian or TIME. They're far more concerned with making money so that they can insure their journalists in war zones, buy new equipment, offer competitive salaries for new hires etc. Clickbait pays for that by pageviews, upping the value of advertising on their site.

That could EASILY be done away with if people started paying for news on the internet like they do for newspapers. But people don't want to pay.

I run my own magazine. I've written bad reviews of restaurants and had them pull their advertising, putting me in the red for the quarter. Trust me, nobody likes doing it, but it's the only way to survive right now.

I wish people understood that instead of getting on their high horses and braying about stuff they aren't remotely familiar with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 20:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They aren't selling shit. You're the ones that demand FREE content. If the internet was willing to pay for news, there might be reason to uphold ethics in the name of journalism. Unfortunately, many have to scrape to survive, in which case appeasing advertisers becomes the primary objective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 20:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HA! That's my uncle's name. And his nickname is Mad Dog! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:07:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did you just reply to yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God bless the seam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:35:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I expected a cool answer because it was so highly upvoted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:15:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fantastic film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:15:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is the definition of a handsome woman. Baw gahd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read the title expecting a cool answer. Nope. The air inside a bell pepper is composed of... air. Regular, over the counter air. 

Wh... why would people think it's made of anything else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 14:19:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Without IV's, should be interesting to see if he can even get hydrated before the fight in the first place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BINGO NAME-O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, Reddit DID do it. You can't pretend the shitparade over Pao had nothing to do with her resignation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What it looks like is the whole of reddit was moving toward something Victoria was not comfortable with, if rumors are to be believed. Pao as the face would naturally take the heat, but there's nothing to suggest it was her decision alone to move Reddit in whatever direction it was that Victoria disagreed with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "resignation" could very well mean "dethroned by the board" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 21:35:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shit. I swear I knew that. For some reason I was thinking he and Hulkenberg were the same person... God knows why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 21:32:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait. Is there talk of Magnusson not staying in F1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People get pissed because I admit to speeding on a motorcycle, gettings lots of tickets etc. I may not obey the rules of the road to a tee, but I'm 1000x more aware of what I'm doing than a teenage girl going 10mph below the speed limit listening to James Blunt in the AC and texting her friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My godmother is in charge of putting together the Vanity Fair Oscar parties every year. I've been 3 times. That's her. Nothing fake about it. You're probably just a bit peeved such a beautiful, talented woman actually happens to act like a regular person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bhi Bhiman - Guttersnipe [Folk] 2012 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:54:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am suffering serious cuddle withdrawal after breaking up with my gf. So yes. Yes, cuddles are needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It still takes a shitload of work to develop a compelling story from Campbell's work, but I'm not sure I'm ready to believe it was Lucas alone who developed it. I was a script reader with BBC and I saw plenty of great monomyth structured stories that were trashed for their ambition alone. Core concepts were good, great even, but had such a large scope it wouldn't be financially viable, even with the Lotto money GBR uses to fund British film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:49:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:48:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never heard anyone echo my feelings about HD vanilla so perfectly. Come to my bed. Bring HD vanilla and famous amos cookies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's because Lee has fencing training. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's not a mastermind. He just read Hero of a Thousand Faces. Star Wars follows Campbell's monomyth to a tee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 05:29:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A continuous tab, I mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 05:19:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They still let people have bar tabs? Only place I get a tab is the fucking coffee shop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:47:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> banned

EDIT: OH I'M SORRY I THOUGHT WE DID MEMES HERE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like this needs to be said A LOT MORE OFTEN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:40:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Russia, you dont make the memes. The memes make you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We met at the grocery store. I'd like to say I found her there, after searching for her all my life, but really... she found me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> doot doot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> MRS WEINER IS A GODDAMN SAINT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 00:02:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having drinks with my mom.

Show her this.

I'm no longer having drinks with my mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:14:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit get your ass there RIGHTFUCKINGNOW. PISTACHIO AS WELL. GO. GO. GO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Classic vanilla has always been my soulmate.

Talenti sea salt caramel gelato is my side bitch though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Snuggles with bae </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:04:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I still maintain one day I'll be a reggae superstar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/Music/comments/3cf2fy/lorde_just_posted_this/csuz5i9?context=3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Legit thought I was in /r/skyrim  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:19:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good thing you wrote "RIP my inbox", I might have mistaken this thread for a burrito.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:08:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not when that mature business needs changing. If it does, at least the 23 year old hasn't been pounded into social submission and is optimistic about turning things around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll be checking in every time I see you. Rest assured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's the Jim Norton of rap. Except Norton doesn't get made fun of for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you famous yet or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:32:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is 1000000x worse without the YIPSKIDDLEDOOOO and the terrified kid yelling at his wasted dad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:30:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  We live in (at least in the West) a society where any time a man does something against a woman it is given far too much attention... it helps to show that both genders are equally capable of doing horrible things and that it isn't just men doing it.

Any rational person knows this. MensRights is more than welcome to have that end of the market about male issues. I, and many others, don't need constant reminding that people can be cunts regardless of gender.

 When new people come to the sub, they tend to vent a lot because they're not used to having a place to talk about the things they experience.

For this exact reason, the sub has done more harm than good, as that venting has evolved into a weird conspiracy that feminism is actively trying to suppress male issues and vice versa. The reactionary women-bashing by some has become a trademark, not just on reddit, but in the media as well. One can vent without perpetuating the idea that men concerned with male issues are diametrically opposed to female issues.

 they're talking about the double-standard that an athlete is going through because he was assaulted and had the audacity to hit a woman back after she kicked and punched him

Again, another thing I believe does more harm than good. "Equal rights and equal lefts" is massively popular. I think the manly thing to do when a (presumably weaker) woman assaults you is to restrain her instead of punching her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have! Last I checked I had a top 10 post on there hahaha. I feel, though, there's less focus on issues that affect men, and more focus on man stuff. Which is great, obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:01:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately I feel a distinct separation from that sub these days. When I first got on Reddit it was awesome, but it's become associated with values I actively dislike. The top posts usually have something to do with injustices perpetrated by women against men, and I just don't feel those are the things that deserve much attention.

I love women. I love feminists. Not the kind that go to Tumblr to conduct their slacktivism, but women who break gender stereotypes or devote their careers to causes beyond teaching "Women's Studies". One of my best friends, a volunteer abortion clinic defender, hates that stuff as much as I do. 

I want a place that recognizes the difference between working to better their respective gender, and a place that bitches about the problems affecting their gender. I'm not sure /r/mensrights qualifies at this point. Two years ago it certainly did. Notsomuch these days.

EDIT: literally just checked /r/all and there's a top post from /r/mensrights about how female models make more than male models. EXACTLY what I'm talking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cheers brother! And thanks for being the first to post. Hopefully we can help this sub grow and find like-minded redditors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:46:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hahaha cheers.

"KNIGHTS OF BROHIRRAM, MOUNT UP!" was my battle cry whenever I had nights out with the boys. Seemed only natural. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:43:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately I don't have friends like that. I have plenty of guy friends, just none I feel comfortable discussing my issues with. Not that I mind, but I get called a faggot just by having a glass of wine. We're brutal to each other, which is fun at the right time, but doesn't exactly foster a trusting environment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really like this sub. It's just only for asking questions. You can't post content here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are there any male-oriented subs that haven't devolved into women bashing circlejerks? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:32:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slowly but surely I've seen popular posts on /r/MensRights et al. go from content that affects men, to childish bitchfests about double-standards and anti-feminist circlejerks.

I just want a sub where I can read and discuss issues that affect men without it devolving into abject rage about the opposite gender. Fuck me, right?

I've created /r/Brohan for the interim, if anyone is interested.

Otherwise, I'd love to know where I can go to vent my frustrations as a man in a forum that doesn't throw a hissy fit every time women are mentioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for Mods </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Leave a comment if you'd like to help grow the Kingdom of Brohan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EXACTLY how I feel. Literally just created a subreddit for exactly that, since these seem to be run by whiny teens. Come on over to /r/Brohan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've called it /r/Brohan, after Middle Earth's Rohan, the Kingdom of Men. Thanks for the idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are there any male-oriented subs that haven't devolved into women bashing circlejerks? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slowly but surely I've seen popular posts on /r/MensRights et al. go from content that affects men, to childish bitchfests about double-standards and anti-feminist circlejerks.

I just want a sub where I can read and discuss issues that affect men without it devolving into abject rage about the opposite gender. Fuck me, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fuck kind of title is this? I'm here for posts about self betterment as a man, not horseshit like "Don't sit next to women because you never know which ones are drugged out of their goddamn minds and might attack you with their tiny, ineffectual fists."

God DAMN these male oriented subs have gone to shit. I'd ask the mods to at least instill some kind of measures so this doesn't turn into a hurr durr women suck circlejerk, but I'd probably be wasting my time.

Between this and all the other totally irrelevant posts on here, I'm out. Unsubbed. Call me when the content has to do with forging one's own identity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd love to go paddle boating with greipel in the engine room... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 02:32:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1196az/why_do_men_have_to_hide_their_erections/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> /r/PenmanshipPorn and and /r/ButtSharpies should swap subs, like /r/trees and /r/MarijuanaEnthusiasts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 02:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:54:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *I SEE THE BATMAN SHIIIINING,*

*FROM THE WEST DOWN TO THE EAST.*

*ANY DAY NOW...*

*ANY DAY NOW...*

*I SHAAAAL BEEEEE DECEASED* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a meme world... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 00:32:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obligatory "I haven't seen this, and I fucking loved it."

If a single irrelevant post gets you this irritated, I think you need to cut down on the redditing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 00:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amen. Just thinking of the angry little boners I got from holding hands with my first date makes me immensely happy nobody had cameraphones back in my day.

Angry, angry little boners. Furious. Two inches of fully torqued hellfire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CARIBOUUUU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RemindMe! 1 year. "Has this guy busted his pedo father yet?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:31:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why be informed when you can be outraged? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:24:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RemindMe! 5 years. "When this redditor is famous." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ran a satire blog for a while. The amount of people that would post my stories in abject rage after only reading the headline was incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:08:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus... it's not like you could sub on a defender that would do a better job. He could command the back line on one leg and still be better than any other option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either this is ripping off James Blunt, or James Blunt is ripping off this. Cant be bothered to find the source but someone made fun of him on twitter for only having 200,000 followers. James Blunt responded by saying: "Jesus only needed twelve."

Hate his music, but love the man. His comebacks are the stuff of legend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure when Lorde started getting famous, but this makes me wonder how many celebrities-to-be are redditors right now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:42:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a reporter and redditor, I can pretty confidently say I wouldn't have been able to summarize it as well as this guy did. There's a reason he works for Bloomberg. 

What people don't know is that the reporter will often send the anchor the questions, and in this case the anchor was given exactly the right questions to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:03:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only thing preventing you from having that life is yourself. Smile big. Walk fast. People will follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:01:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8,000+ comment karma for the amount you post is pretty sad. so sad in fact, I'd be willing to bet the people that call you their friend only do so out of some childhood obligation, or just sheer pity. You are a dessicated cunthole; a blind, wobbly-legged calf loved by nobody in this world except the mewling beast that brought you into it, and even she, upon seeing your shitsipping face, can only muster a half-hearted "meh." You are a disappointment to all that know you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:36:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TV reporter here. Can confirm. I can't upload my own reports to a separate youtube channel because they are owned by the company I did them for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:31:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> right click the image. click "show controls." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:57:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Can this to the front page!

At first I thought you meant "Can this make it to the front page", but then I saw the exclamation mark and thought, "Maybe they meant 'Get this to the front page'", at which point I gave up and didn't bother to sign and came here to leave this comment instead.

I have the attention of a concussed goldfish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I lived in Camden for a year as well. Right near Mornington Crescent.

1. Got mobbed by screaming teenage girls coming out of the Tesco right by Koko. Turns out I was walking next to Oly Murs, and they thought I was famous too. I wasn't.

2. Great place to meet random people. I'd go out with some American buddies of mine and we'd inevitably end up back at my flat with a few people to do copious amounts of whatever drugs we had on us. 

3. Once saw a muslim man getting dragged down a dark alley, screaming for his life. Called 999, but the guy let the muslim man go when he saw me on the phone. 

4. Great place for picking up women. Especially Aussie women, for some reason. Maybe they're just easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait... ACTUALLY!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 19:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  dickshonary

22edgy1974me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 19:54:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Denise the downer? Really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 19:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm more sick and tired of people telling me they went to school with Tadasha (T-A) and Ladasha (L-A). NO YOU DIDN'T. NO YOU FUCKING DIDN'T.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:56:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not making any direct comparison per se. More a contrasting example of what a good CEO looks like and how they treat their employees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:43:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Today, the company is doing better than ever.](https://www.bostonglobe.com/business/2015/06/27/year-later-market-basket-thriving-after-near-meltdown/EIePjTzCJYhgLWwRpBuoAI/story.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL of the Market Basket Uprising: a walkout organized last summer by employees of Market Basket grocery stores to protest the firing of their beloved president and CEO, Arthur T. DeMoulas. The walkout worked. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cottages in Bermuda [1200x800] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:31:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> After intense deliberation and uproar from the community, /r/Bermuda has buckled and is no longer private. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:21:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know. I know. This has come as a shock to all of us, but the mod team for /r/Bermuda felt it best that we reopen the community, and will endeavor to stick it to Pao in the days ahead, whatever way we can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Available for hire: [27M] swings ban hammer mightily and judiciously, likes long walks on the beach, and ain't afraid of no Pao. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 23:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Skills include 

* satisfying OP's mom

* markdown

* copywriting (I am a former advertising copywriter and currently a journalist)

* judging   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 23:36:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are usually clauses in such termination contracts that prevent the employee from speaking about the nature of their termination. I was very surprised to see that AMA, so it's no surprise it's been taken down now, probably by him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 21:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> still waiting on someone to post an actual "tribute me" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 18:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> KiA could do with applying this to some of the more popular posts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It rhymes with honey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:51:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you specialise in bird law as well?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:48:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, I've gotten death threats for mixing up Britain and England. God have mercy on your soul if you accidentally repost. The amount of times I've been called a faggot is astounding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:43:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would be great to see a full timeline of his fall from... grace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What does this have to do with this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 15:25:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Bermuda Triangle is closed for repairs. /r/Bermuda now private. Sorry everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Triangle is closed for repairs. /r/Bermuda joins the blackout in solidarity. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 14:50:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All the cool kids are doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 14:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is the windows logo on her badge? Is the title "in discussion" a hint at Microsoft trying to acquire reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 02:32:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Redpill: "I can't get a woman by being myself. How do I become a massive slut-slaying douchebag instead?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:54:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always maintained that he was worth it for the goal he scored against Barca alone (not to mention the Nevillegasm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:21:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:59:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Subbed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:59:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like more credit should go to Chris whenever this is mentioned. Everyone blames Anderson for clowning, but against any other fighter he would've been able to slip his way out of that. Chris NAILS him with 5 straight off balance punches. That's next level accuracy and power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bermudian here. He is a total nutjob, but the fish you're holding has been a part of that dive pretty much since it's inception. Can't remember his name, but he has one, and he's doing just fine. We've been worldwide leaders in conservation since we first protected the green turtle in 1620. Touching a few snapper isn't going to hurt anyone, and in fact the only reason that snapper is still around is because the area you dove in is protected against fishing. If I had a friendly snapper come up to me like that anywhere else, you'd be damn sure he wind up with a spear through his gills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually worked with this dive company for a summer. Lived in Bermuda my whole life. We are miles ahead of the world when it comes to marine protection. We first protected turtles in 1620 and have always had strict catch limits. The fish OP is holding has been a part of that dive since it first started. Nothing's ever happened to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:02:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally JUST posted about this same thing! Horses know their way home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's actually an old story in my country of two brothers and their horse. Every weekend they'd go to one of the hotels with all the American women, get wasted, then climb back into their carriage and fall asleep. Every time, they'd wake up back in their driveway, and give the horse the day off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:42:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... you take the chains off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 15:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately all of that is wayyyyyyy outside our budget :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 05:31:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:46:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HA! Amazing. Sluggo is the shit. Used to be a cop. Very nice man. Makes excellent cricket catches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had, as in, at the time. He's now her wonderful fiance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:42:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only thing lacking is a cat. And seeing as this is going pretty well, might as well get the karma while I can. [Obligatory tax cat cat tax](http://ihavecat.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/PetieTaxGuy1.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:38:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Google Whitney and Alfonso - Carlton Dance and you should get a result. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:19:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Whoore. I was just expressing my love for her in Always Sunny quotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing fancy. Just a little whaler. Takes 10 minutes by sea, 45 by land during rush hour, so it's a no brainer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The curse of being from Bermuda is having this song sung whenever you tell people where you're from. That, or they ask about the goddamn triangle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like a normal friend, but she lets me touch her britney </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd drag my dick a mile through freshly laid asphalt just to hear Whitney fart through a walkie talkie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:29:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus by all accounts she's an actual human being and not a vacuous gold digging whoore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Not your typical aww, but this is the World's Smallest (and most adorable) Drawbridge. I get to drive under it every day on my way to work in Bermuda. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:23:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:12:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome, thanks for your thoughts. Oracle has two boats down here right now. The standard AC42 that'll be used in the World Series this October, and the AC42 "Turbo" which is the boat they use to test out new designs and tech. What those new designs are though is anyone's guess. They won't let anyone near it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sister had long term, awesome boyfriend, and my little nibling is the shit. I on the other hand have more of a fuckbuddy. So... bullet dodged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Computer went into overdrive with all my extensions blocking the ungodly amount of trackers on that site. Lord have mercy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:00:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually happened to my sister last year. That's the only reason I knew they had that effect at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:59:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure Matt Taibbi has a baseball cap he can lend you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thaaaaaat BITCH! I KNEW IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:33:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BYEEEEE BYE MISS AMERICAN PIE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:32:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TV hardly counts. It's entertainment, not news.

Source: did it for a year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It does not have that ability. At all. Da_fuhje is a master bullshitter. Check his mod credentials  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then you have a woeful understanding of what an average journalist does on a day to day basis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:14:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought that's what your father's friends were for. My dad's buddy gave me the whole rundown on what to do.

"Carlos, one day you're going to find your hand on a girl's boob. And it's gonna be great. But you're quickly going to realize you have no idea what to do once you get it there. Sit down, kiddo. We need to talk." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MRW the pregnancy tests come back negative after my ladyfriend accidentally took antibiotics while on the pill. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:12:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like to think [this girl](http://i.imgur.com/2xA8bhS.jpg) popped up into the cabin moments before it began plummeting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:57:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd totally forgotten about that. holy shit. How is there not better footage of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:55:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was the exact scene that made me wonder whether she was hot in real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the fuck is a telephonist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:21:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good guy discount. 60% of the time it works EVERY time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Margaret McPoyle, everyone... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:11:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've heard this from a few of my friends as well, so I think sailor profiles are a definite must. Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The financial costs of competing in the cup are pretty transparent. It's the bidding process that's a little shady.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 15:05:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> open wide and say oink </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 14:26:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are people religiously defending consoles? Honest question. I've never seen it on reddit. at all. 

I've always had a console because I'm a casual gamer, know fuck all about computers, and use my laptop for work. Don't see much wrong with that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 14:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You go right ahead and try and teach a class of children how to fuck without being decapitated by angry fathers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:52:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just because you don't know where to look for quality journalism doesn't mean it doesn't exist. read a newspaper. pick up a magazine. the majority of people in my field take their jobs extremely seriously, and while the talent varies, the desire to do our job properly is first and foremost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:45:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not quite. Never went to college. Worked my whole life as a reporter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 05:27:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The "one man band" you're describing is a new role in news, but that's by no means the typical journalist these days. Grunts get sent out on that stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 05:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Contrary to popular belief, the majority of journalists take their job very seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> IAmA journalist in Bermuda writing about the America's Cup. What kind of coverage would you like to see? (x-post /r/americascup) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:11:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will be starting a new series with a newspaper on the America's Cup, and I was wondering what the fans would like to see in terms of media coverage. 

Because of my connections with the people involved, from the sailors to the administrators, I'm uniquely placed to offer really good coverage on what's going on with the 2017 America's Cup, and everything leading up to it.

So what would be of the biggest interest to you? High quality videos? Interviews? Analysis? History? Gossip? I'd love your two cents! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> IAmA journalist in Bermuda writing about the America's Cup. What kind of coverage would you like to see? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will be starting a new series with a newspaper on the America's Cup, and I was wondering what the fans would like to see in terms of media coverage. Because of my connections with the people involved, from the sailors to the administrators, I'm uniquely placed to offer really good coverage on what's going on with the 2017 America's Cup, and everything leading up to it.

So what would be of the biggest interest to you? High quality videos? Interviews? Analysis? History? Gossip? I'd love your two cents! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:35:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is where a novelty account that turns comments into songs would be useful... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:41:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Does anyone know the season and episode so I can flair this thread?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MRW when Hans Moleman is nowhere to be found in a thread about TV's best running gags. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:39:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> can anyone fill me in on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Video made me cringe too hard. Did he actually say that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:13:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You shut your whore mouth. /u/da_fuhje is an artist.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 20:42:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're pretty talented at photoshop, so was really hoping this was OC. So... slightly disappointing. Do you ever post your own stuff? I have no issue with what you do, but on a personal note there's no better feeling than having your own original content make the front page. Maybe give it a try? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 20:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Got all excited to see what he did for my country of Bermuda.

Nope. Fucker forgot us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Think I may have jinxed today's SpaceX launch. My bad, folks. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:26:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Every time I see one of your comments.](http://i.imgur.com/NQHKSVE.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:13:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "The more I know about people, the better I like my dog." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:10:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  "Please don't kill butts. In the US, the overwhelming majority of species are non-thundering and completely harmless. Even the ones that do thunder usually aren't aggressive..."

Cloud to butt extension changes this massively... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 10:00:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YOU ARE A BLINKING, SENSELESS CALF, LOVED BY NO ONE EXCEPT THE DROOLING BEAST THAT BROUGHT YOU INTO THIS WORLD. COME AT ME, BRO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:45:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the founder of Black Jaguar White Tiger, a big cat rescue foundation. He just fucks around with awesome beasties all day. (I'm sure there's other less glamorous work he does, but that's what I'm telling myself.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:42:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Appears so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:17:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I know about Filipinos is that they fuck up every time one replaces my toilet paper. THE END FACES FORWARD, MARTA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 01:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Source](https://www.reddit.com/r/Portland/comments/3bckcf/at_a_church_on_se_92nd_when_i_inquired_i_was_told/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Portland wedding (x-post /r/Portland) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 01:20:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Things Meatloaf Would Do For Love </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:48:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:37:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This right here is why I fucking love this site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:18:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ellipseseses* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DOOT DOOT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "A man who says a thing can't be done is quite apt to be interrupted by some idiot doing it." - Elbert Hubbard </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Those who say a thing can't be done are quite apt to be interrupted by some idiot doing it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 23:37:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You were dead serious about that corgi puppy eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 22:28:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually posted a while in the Bernie Sanders sub asking why more Americans don't just fund candidates online like kickstarter campaigns. Got downvoted to hell and told a million different ways it wouldn't work.

And now I see that's exactly what's gone and been done.

I like Bernie, but some of his supporters are goddamn morons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Some people have life goals, I just want a god damned puppy.

Well I just found the quote that's going on my tombstone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:32:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry I couldn't provide more detail. I have a book by the photographer who tells that story, just cant be bothered to go find the proper quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:31:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What IS the goal? Or are you one of those "it's not the destination, it's the adventure" guys... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is your goal to get the most karma on reddit or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You forgot to mention that they're all on fire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:05:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Station fire shook me to my core. It's so hard not to imagine yourself being in that position... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WOW that's dumb. I've been using corn starch to "breath fire" since I was 12. How do people not know that it's flammable as fuck???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 18:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From what I can tell this is basically just rugby, soccer, and MMA all rolled into one.

Booking my trip NOW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 18:05:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See the guy between Ali's legs? He was Sports Illustrated's top photographer at the time. The man who took this picture was new on the job, and would have been in the same spot, which was considered the best angle. He was told to go find his own spot on the ring. He did, and he got this picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:38:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, it was totally because of his weight. Sleep apnea I think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure if there's a word for it, but my family does this all the time. My mom has started telling some of my stories like she was actually there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 20:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not in the slightest. There are far more extreme wings of the conservative party. That's not bias, that's a simple observation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:54:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Compare it to the NYT, America's paper of record and a proven government mouthpiece... At least their bias is obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:52:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deadly groove: check.

Soulful white guy: check.

Hand spasms: check.

Joe Cocker 2 confirmed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except their morons are conservative morons, which are just like liberal morons but with an added dash of insanity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:38:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm well aware of what they do and how they do it. I've been a journalist for ten years and have worked with them and CNN affiliates. My point is that their "news" is no different to other tv news channels in America. They're all inherently biased because they are all privately owned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly what I was thinking. What I hate about racing sims is not being able to quickly glance around. Oculus would do that perfectly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did... did you ask him to read you a bedtime story? Because I would've asked for a bedtime story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's precisely what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:30:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which is why I said they're no different to any other TV news station in America. MSNBC and CNN are just as guilty of that as Fox is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:24:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Al Jazeera is one of the most respected news organizations in the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's exactly what I was saying. They give airtime to morons. Their actual reporters are sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:15:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every time this comes up I defend Fox News and get downvoted to oblivion. It's their TALKING HEADS that are fucking retarded. Their news coverage is no different from any other TV news station in America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:11:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TBH he probably stole it from another writer (I want to say Stephen King?) who used it as an example on how to create interesting short stories. The only difference to the short story example and the Purge is that in the short story idea, people were allowed to commit any crime as long as they compensated those who they committed the crime against. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:40:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Real life Cooper reporting in. My mom's friends called me Cooper Cooper, because her maiden name was Cooper, which then became my middle name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:39:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a character with the exact same name in one of my AP English short stories. C'mon Nolan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 08:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it might just come down to driver preference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *oooooooo - eeeeeeeeeeeee  - hehehehehehehehe - oooo^O^^O^^^O^^^^oooooooooooooooooooo* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I literally just slapped my knee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doot doot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:19:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what's this from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 21:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Went to school with his nephew actually. He got HEATED whenever you brought that video up hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 21:17:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work with one other full time employee publishing a magazine I can barely get out four times a year, and running a website. So not exactly six figures, although our office IS air conditioned. We run sponsored stories on that website because our audience demands they have free access to our content and advertisers have gotten wise to the fact that slapping a banner ad on a website isn't good business. And yet we get criticized for "duping" the customer.

I certainly don't like Bungie's model either, but I'm not going to criticize it just because they're making money in different ways to their competitors. If the market is willing to purchase those kinds of games, more power to Bungie. Consumers are morons. But I won't be buying it. Nor will you. Hopefully that sentiment is shared across the market and we can disincentivise game dev's from this brand of business. And if it all goes tits up, you can sit calmly on your high horse and say "I told you so." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  The best product on the lowest possible budget. This is basic business.

You're not including deadlines, which play probably the most critical role. An indie dev team with a small budget and no deadline can spend as long as they want on a game. But if something goes wrong for a team working on a deadline, you have to sink more money into fixing that problem in order to meet the mark, putting you over budget.

 ...the rest of the industry has been able to finance their games without selling missions bundled with soft drinks, Bungie should be no exception.

Sounds pretty communist to me. A company finding an alternate source of revenue untapped by their competitors is unfair????

The bottom line of Bungie is not at hand here, the budget allocated to the game is. You don't know what that budget was, nor whether they were able to deliver the product within that given budget. If shit hit the fan, as I mentioned above, that could force the budget to skyrocket in order for them to meet their deadline. Bungie creates value for itself by creating video games, but they can't do that at a loss.

 This is not advertising.

You're definition of advertising is incredibly narrow. Perhaps the best word is "marketing". This is Red Bull. The way they go about marketing is radically different to everyone else. Other energy drinks would slap a COD logo on the can, certainly, but that is not and has never been Red Bull's strategy. Instead of slapping their logo on an F1 car, they created an F1 team. Instead of slapping Destiny's logo on their cans, they have exclusive content. It's pretty genius IMO.

 That's greedy

Is this communist Russia? This isn't communist Russia, is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:59:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So because other developers have done really cool stuff with a tiny budget, other developers should do that too? That doesn't make much sense, but ok. And how do you know it's not about funding the game? Can you provide a source for that, or are you just guessing because it looks like they're money grubbing whores?

If it wasn't for advertising, my industry would be dead because the money we make selling our product is JUST enough for us to make a new product every four months. That pain is shared by a LOT of others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:57:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah, fuck those guys for finding additional funding for their game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:35:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're a champ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bada-buh-ba-bah.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take your filthy upvote and get out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should try pronouncing Southwark, or Gloucester correctly. The British pronounce things different to Americans, strange as it might seem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure more clever people than I have already figured this out. But it was satisfying as hell when I put two and two together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:15:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Inb4 people get their knickers in a twist. I have nothing against karmawhoring, reposting, x-posting, etc. Just thought I should say... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "I suppose I'm one of those fellows my father always warned me against." - P.G. Wodehouse </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 01:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It just dawned on me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:37:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you sought counseling? My ex was a rape victim and had the opposite reaction to you, she felt disgusting during sex, like she was debasing herself. We went to therapy together and that helped her discuss and synthesize her feelings, which lead to a much more fulfilling sex life. More than anything the therapy just allowed her to talk about what she was feeling, and hear herself saying it, rather than bottling it all up in her head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:17:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for your service  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:01:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The small sail at the front of a sailboat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best one yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is. You can judge age pretty well by the dorsal and this one is very small </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Still got dick

I like the cut of your jib </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Come on down to Bermuda. Our wood is fantastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:20:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've tried this at least a dozen times. Never worked. You're like an anal loving unicorn...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:19:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So... how much damage was there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Recently learned my ex first slept with me because I had the balls to tell her I didn't think child support should be mandatory. The thing is, I don't even really believe that. Neither does she. I think I just said it to be cool and contradictory, and it totally worked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Girls of Reddit, what's the most arbitrary reason you've ever chosen to have sex with someone? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 13:57:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jolly good, old horse.

***blows***

I say! This could knock out a caribou! CARIBOUUUUUU. Lovely woody word, wouldn't you say old beast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, is the headline being intentionally dumb by calling rioters "peaceful protesters"? Literally the first line of the story calls them violent protesters. Aka rioters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:04:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youuuuu lucky ducks you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:22:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Come visit Bermuda. Luscious man-calf abound! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of my best friends is Christian. I can never argue about the negatives of religion with him because he's grown up in a house that embodies every positive aspect. His mother is a goddamn saint. Church every Sunday, constant community outreach, food drives etc. Grew up with him and his mom my entire life and she's never once mentioned God besides when they have grace at dinner. 

Point being, for many, religion is just a vessel in which valuable, noble traits can be delivered and instilled. If living a life like my friend's mom has lived is done in order to get into heaven, why worry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow this sub is such a circle jerk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:33:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Zouma is a captain in waiting. He's been referred to as France's future captain, so I see no reason why he can't eventually be ours. I fucking love the kid.

On another note, I'll be sad to see Mikel go but he could really lock down another team's midfield, and his talents are wasted on the bench. If Schneiderlin leaves Soton, I think he'd make for a great replacement. Obviously not in terms of playmaking, but I've always rated him for his ability to shut down a midfield. He's a beast, and I'd love to see him do well on another team with regular starts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It goes to show you how fickle Hollywood can be though. Here's a girl that has been stunning in every film she's been in since Leon, and yet three shitty but high grossing films nearly derailed her career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:24:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I misremembered the article I read. It was Cold Mountain that gave her career new life. Linked to the article in my original comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL Natalie Portman blames the Star Wars prequels for nearly ruining her career. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:20:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The films nearly ruined Portman's career, lest we forget. She had faded into obscurity until ~~Black Swan~~ Cold Mountain, and the only reason she got that role was through a lot of connections going to bat for her. Everyone in Hollywood had written her off directly because of Star Wars.

EDIT: Cold Mountain, not Black Swan.

Source: http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/natalie-portman-blames-star-wars-prequels-for-almost-ruining-her-career-everyone-thought-i-was-a-horrible-actress-9933636.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Asking the important questions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 50 Shades of Shit did it first

"Aro laughed. 'Hahaha', he giggled." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, that's correct. I was 16 when I first started smoking. *High* school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:52:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being a journalist is basically just having good Google-fu and knowing how proper sentence structure works... and interviews... and the stomach to transcribe hour long interviews. But mostly Google-fu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DING DING ^^^shame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:58:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let's play Spot The Reason OP Is An Idiot!

Fuck my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I've missed a lot of great moments in sports. Here's why. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:13:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You'd have to be a pretty shitty seamstress not to account for movement...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:59:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a journalist, this interviewer is fucking slobbering all over Pao and it's making me sick. Don't hide your bias or anything... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:47:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have to agree to share, first off. I live in Bermuda and have a dock. There's a couple that lives on a houseboat in the bay and they use it without permission all the time. I was actually on it flying my friend's drone around and they just walked past me and loaded up their dinghy like it was nothing. I told them it was a private dock, and that they could use it this one time. They've since teared the ass out of it and are using it all the time, disrupting the guests that pay $600 per night for our vacation rental cottage. I've spoken to them at least a dozen times about it and yet they continue to use it, leaving bags of doritos, beer bottles, etc floating in the mangroves by my slip. I've since called the police, had them charged for mooring without a license and trespassing.

In other words, don't use people's shit without their permission. And if you give a moose a muffin, he'll ask you for some milk. Far better to lay down the law and not let people use your shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:16:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This could pretty much apply to everything I do in life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:05:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro. I'm so fucking altitudinous right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I KNEW THAT! One of the few things I remember from science class. No idea why the name Bernoulli stuck, but it did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I... I dont remember installing the cloud to butt extension... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Dos Equis has its new spokesman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *midly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 18:25:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My thoughts exactly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:53:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just can't help but thinking of Klitschko utterly destroying this girl... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 13:28:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't. I was bullied for my dad dying. Again, don't feel sorry for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:13:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont worry. They're most likely fake. At least I hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 05:57:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't. I've had a lot worse shit negatively affect my life than being in a blockbuster movie, and I'm doing just fine. Rub some dirt on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 05:10:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For people out of the loop. 

http://www.reddit.com/user/concerneddad1965/submitted/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 01:54:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait... are you telling me girls play Twitch with their tits out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 01:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SHAME </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 01:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same situation happened to a friend of mine. She hasn't spoken to her mother in 4 years because of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 01:11:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think those were spandex underneath  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-21 22:19:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> doot doot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-21 22:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're welcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-21 21:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/3104cq/boyfriend_and_i_got_the_same_valentines_day_car/cpxmg0q </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-21 21:05:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man. I really do appreciate it. This may or may not apply to you, but it's a life lesson I learned through a tragic example: never let stubbornness get in the way of your health. My dad was having bad heartburn but skipped his Dr appointment. A week later he died of a heart attack in a Texas hotel room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:15:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was working with the NY Times on the story, which he broke open, reporting for them and for the local daily here in Bermuda. The reporters he was working with got the award. He didn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine died when I was 12. Power-washed his grave today, then sat by his headstone with a 6-pack and bawled like I was 12 again. At 1130 am. 

He was a journalist. Nearly won a pulitzer after exposing the US for storing nuclear depth bombs in my country. I'm a journalist now too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 19:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry.

#(  _ ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 19:17:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  their

#()  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 17:47:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's really ok. Thank you for your apology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 17:41:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's so bad you think it's actually intentional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 17:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you knew anything about the Romani you'd know their living situation is their own choosing. Many don't need to beg and have a fair amount of wealth, but do it because that's "their culture". They are professional thieves and vagrants. I had no problem hitting a Romani woman in the nose when she tried to steal my camera on the Spanish Steps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 16:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Despite your childish comment, I actually did that at a coffee shop this week. GOT is the only thing I ever have to talk about with the super hot barista, and we got a bit over zealous. A poor couple waiting in line plugged their ears and started shouting "LALALALALALA"... but it was too late. Sorry cute hipster couple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 16:07:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First time I saw that show, 100% thought it was a hilarious reality tv spoof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 16:05:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh hey, it's ~~/r/quityourbullshit's~~ /r/TodayIBullshitted's favourite redditor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 15:03:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Carpet or blanket? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 14:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not as bad as Throatzilla </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 05:33:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Humping. Breeding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 05:23:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are a few German military dog breeders that are still in operation after being started by the Nazi's. IIRC they still breed shepherds with grey wolves every 18th generation to create new lines that don't have any of the problems the breed suffers from today.

My uncle has one of the breeder's dogs that were rejected by the military. Not sure how much he bought him for, he won't say, but he gets well over $500 from studding him out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 05:07:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> somebody for the love of god ELI5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 05:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Father was born in Toronto. Spent my summers in Banff growing up. Went to Camp Onandoga. UWO. Moving to Toronto in September.

Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 03:52:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the fuck outta here with that weak ass frou frou bullshit. It's piqued. 

http://grammarist.com/spelling/peak-peek-pique/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 03:14:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 01:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Wrong.](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/science/dinosaurs/11519933/Brontosaurus-raised-from-dead-as-scientists-rule-dinosaur-did-exist.html)

Tryin'a step up with that weak ass, frou frou bullshit. The fuck outta here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 01:42:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry to be that guy... but the word is "piqued" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The newspaper I worked for in Bermuda actually shipped Saddam a pair of Bermuda shorts when the Daily Mail ran this story. I had the idea to do it again years later with a politician I was close to, after the Houston Chronicle ran a story making fun of our lone Winter Olympian during the opening ceremony at Sochi.

You can read the story [here](http://www.royalgazette.com/article/20140211/NEWS/140219953). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL Saddam Hussein banned Bermuda shorts because the exposed flesh of a man's calf might "inflame the passions of women and lead to immoral behaviour." (x-post /r/ObscureKnowledge) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 22:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that's that then. No need to intervene. They did it to themselves, folks. Our hands are clean! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 19:14:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus, Coaster. Calm your tits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:04:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooooh so much butthurt in one comment. Over imaginary internet points... You ok little faggot? Did your daddy take his dick out of your mouth too early today? That must've made you terribly cranky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see this is going to be one of those threads where OP should just shut up and keep the filthy karma </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:26:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was my comment...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:24:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually wasn't trying to make it seem like I saw this IRL, was just posting my opinion on what I think is a dopey ad. You can see I posted pretty much the same comment when I came across it earlier today in /r/adporn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:22:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess she missed that LPT post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [$3.50 please](http://1.media.collegehumor.cvcdn.com/53/64/c256000587089393b73898e581adf237-fat-girl-fails-to-jump-over-bar.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meow? Did I just say meow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:14:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You strike me as the type to make wild assumptions about strangers on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:12:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This fucking girl behind me wouldn't shut up during Jurassic World. Lost her shit when Claire went running from a T-Rex in heels. "HEELS? HAHAHAHAHA"

You're watching a movie with a T Rex in it and you're complaining that the protagonist has heels on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  ,

...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 16:59:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3edgy5moi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 16:57:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck off you cadaverous little cumspitoon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 16:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get that. I was just making a joke. But it stands to reason that a person seeking out a park bench doesn't need to be told to run at that given moment. And that's kinda the point of ambient advertising. To deliver a message to people at a specific moment, where that message might be motivational, or aspirational, or just clever and helpful. The only specific moments I see arising from this are bedraggled workers looking for a bench to have their lunch on, only to find a benchless bench with Nike telling them run.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Instead of sitting down on a park bench, run. What? I just want to eat my sandwich and enjoy some fresh air during my lunch break, not have some holier than thou shoe company tell me to fucking run. RUN! Run where? Back to my cubicle? Fuck you Nike. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 16:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 16:05:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus. Nobody is debating the relative ease of being a presenter vs construction worker in Qatar. I'm just saying it's a shitload harder than it looks, and it takes a lot of skill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:57:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can't commit a crime in retaliation for a crime, Sir Lightbulb. And get your shit together with those contradicting Z's and S's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty retarded if you ask me. What's the message here? Run instead of sitting down on a park bench? Those two activities have nothing to do with each other. I just want to eat my sandwich and enjoy some fresh air during my lunch break, not have some holier than thou shoe company tell me to fucking run. Run where? Back to my cubicle? Fuck you Nike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've seen fellas like you in court A LOT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Time lapse of a chameleon changing colour </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 13:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 13:10:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not as simple as just reading your lines because the camera picks up your eyes moving. You have to look into the teleprompter and read with your peripheral vision. I invite you to give that a go without looking or sounding like a moron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 06:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or just ignore it and add assaulting a police officer to the charges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 01:30:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh Heidi.... You tried, hun. You tried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 01:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Former TV news presenter here. She deserves more than props. Karl throws her a segment ahead of time and she goes straight into it and delivers her lines straight into the camera, with only a brief glance at her script, before realizing the teleprompter is showing the script for different segment.

To break down the skill that involves: she's got her lede lines memorized, the composure to deliver them at any given moment without tipping the audience off, and the awareness to be reading the teleprompter, which would be showing Celeb Buzz's script, while delivering completely different lines.

There's a reason I'm a former TV presenter.... shit's HARD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How did the invention of the Bermuda Rig in the 17th Century change the course of shipping, trade, and naval war? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 19:10:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My home of Bermuda is famous for a few things: shorts, that 2spooky4me eponymous triangle, and tax avoidance. But the biggest mark our tiny archipelago has made in the history books can be found in every marina across the globe: [the Bermuda Rig.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bermuda_rig)

The rigging allowed us, and subsequently the world, to sail upwind with precision around the reefs that claimed so many ships in years gone by. The design was so transformative, within a few decades of its popularisation, King Charles II would soon be sailing one. 

A poem published by John H. Hardie in 1671 described Bermuda's boats such: 

 With tripple corner'd Sayls they always float, 
 About the Islands, in the world there are, 
 None in all points that may with them compare.

I've always been curious to know what the wider implications of the Bermuda Rig were in the world of sailing, beyond piracy and competition. Did the ability to sail upwind alter shipping routes, or naval war strategy?

I'd love to learn more about my island's sailing heritage, especially with the America's Cup World Series coming to our shores this October. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait what? How do you not see that the definition of harassment is what FPH was doing to Imgur staff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FPH put pictures of the entire Imgur staff on their sidebar. That's pretty harassy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:30:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And that, friends, is the secret to good advertising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> HELP: I'm trying to find out who owns the screen rights to my late grandfather's book (x-post /r/television) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:54:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My grandfather, William Stevenson, wrote the non fiction spy novel 'A Man Called Intrepid', which was subsequently turned into a TV miniseries starring David Niven. 

[On IMDB](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0078649/companycredits?ref_=tt_dt_co) it says NBC was the US distributor, along with the list of production companies that made it, but I can't find anything on who has the film rights.

Can anyone point me in the right direction, or could someone with IMDB Pro have a deeper look at the film's details?

I'd very much like to look into reviving his book for the big screen, and I need all the help I can get! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:39:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just curious to know where people are meeting women that display such "common" traits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> HELP: I'm trying to find out who owns the TV rights to my late grandfather's book. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:36:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My grandfather, William Stevenson, wrote the non fiction spy novel 'A Man Called Intrepid', which was subsequently turned into a TV miniseries starring David Niven. 

[On IMDB](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0078649/companycredits?ref_=tt_dt_co) it says NBC was the US distributor, along with the list of production companies that made it, but I can't find anything on who own the rights.

Can anyone point me in the right direction, or could someone with IMDB Pro have a deeper look at the details?

I'd very much like to look into reviving his book for the big screen, and I need all the help I can get! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If I give a tax break to a hotel developer, who uses the money saved in that tax break to build a hotel, creating jobs, bringing in tourism etc, how is that NOT trickle down economics? How does that differ from what the IMF found? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is the greatest screenplay of all time, and why is it Legally Blonde? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let's be honest here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:47:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to rent mopeds to tourists. The number of people who put their feet out to somehow assist in braking is ridiculous. So many crashes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:08:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't say I've ever encountered a girl that likes assaulting people, then specifically gets defensive when she gets assaulted back. You've met so many of these women, you can say confidently they're 1 in 15? Wow. You must come from a pretty shitty place if that's how people act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 06:12:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really annoys me when people bitch about product placement. Those brands funded a record breaking movie. A movie that you probably loved, although you'd never admit it here. Fuck them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:56:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well pew pew to you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:51:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rosebud is his sled. The thing is, there was nobody at his bedside when he died. So how could anyone possibly know "Rosebud" was his last word? I never got that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:47:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You need to hang around better women if you think that kind of behavior is "%100 typical" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> During warfare in the high middle ages, what would more greatly ensure your survival during battle: cowardice or skill? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:58:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always been curious to know whether it was the greatest, most skilled soldiers that survived the longest, or if your survival came down more to luck. If I am hell bent on surviving a battle, do I flee -- as the old idiom says -- or do I become as skilled as possible with my sword and mount? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure this was on TIL recently. Mammal's distress calls are recognizable across species. So it's not so much that the scream is human, it's that human screams are mammalian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  a good background

hahaha yeah, just some casual listening really. nothing too heavy. Check out his Common Sense podcasts as well for his take on modern events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:46:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, the Supreme Court HAS ruled that companies are people, and because money = free speech this now means that companies can support political candidates. I don't know anywhere else where this can be done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:44:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dan Carlin explained the recent Supreme Court decision on this really well. You're spot on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Has all the FPH ban shitstorm died down, or has everyone been banned? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:41:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:39:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't. And the only reason I did it was laziness. ADRIAN'S REVENGE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The High Commission for Human Rights at the UN? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Getting got" is slang for someone getting the better of you.

If lil Billy gets got by lil Bobby in hopscotch, Billy got got by Bobby. Got it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Um... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> all time recorded best. the true joy of the modern era is that we get this shit on record. the epic but insignificant fails of history are lost to the sands of time. I bet some hilarious shit went down. Horrible, horrible shit too. But also, occasionally... y'know, when someone isn't knocking down your gates threatening to rape all your women and erase all traces of you from the earth... I bet in between all... that... some funny shit went down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the thing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 22:44:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having an attachment to your work is never good. You have to be attached to working in that medium, just not the stuff you produce. Learning to kill my babies has benefitted me immeasurably in terms of my creative output.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 22:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, not a whole lot of thought going into this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:32:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love that you think niggardly is an epithet. Well done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:05:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks for actually answering and not downvoting and moving on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 18:42:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 18:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was thinking something along the lines of

#STARS WAR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 18:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Leave ME alone you scummy little shitstain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 18:31:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll do no such thing you slimy, dessicated fetus fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 18:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck you, you cadaverous cumspitoon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 14:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And here I am getting freaked out when the gf tries a little stinky pinky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are your favourite 80's summer hits? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:37:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The hair was big and the hits were bigger.

Whether it's the Swedish stylings Gyllene Tider's '[Sommartider](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=beFPoiNn0Bs)', or Righeria's impossibly contagious '[Vamos a la Playa](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sTsVJ1PsnMs)', my love for cheesy 80's summer hits knows no bounds.

What are some of your all time favourite 80's summer tunes?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:37:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're being downvoted because the only accurate wording possible is saying that one car hit another. The fact you don't understand that and are calling everyone else ignorant is compounding your downvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:27:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The seat covers are also specifically designed to hide all the crap.

[Source](http://www.thekongblog.com/2012/11/inside-knowledge-why-are-bus-seats-so.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:12:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Journalist here. Granted, the article actually has a lot of errors, but that's not one of them. It's called reporting the facts. You don't know the exact circumstances that caused the crash, and speculation about that could get you sued for libel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bless you. I hope you never have to meet one of these kinds of lawyers, but the reason the prosecutor is a dick is because the defense attorney has made an issue out of the definition of a photocopier, and coached his client into feigning ignorance. Bit of a legal trickfuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:24:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/retiredusernames  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:15:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just went with the NYTimes on this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is a photocopier? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:26:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whatever you do, don't listen to reggae.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for that edit. A crucial detail many might have missed /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/GfJNU68.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:05:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll include the further definition then... 

 "an outcome cruelly, humorously, or strangely at odds with assumptions or expectations."

A black fly in white wine? A post-mortem death pardon? That's pretty clear cut to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:46:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What're you talking about? Irony is "a state of affairs or an event that seems deliberately contrary to what was or might be expected." Every last bit of that song is ironic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 07:16:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CUT HIS FUCKING HEAD OFF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 04:02:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used it when I was putting my advertising portfolio together, and it really helps for inspiration. There's a lot of cool shit on there that you won't find on reddit. I didn't encounter any of the stuff you see here when I was using it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 03:56:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Venezuela? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 03:52:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How'd he die? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 23:37:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the thing.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 23:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you dead yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 21:57:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I figured as much re: their value. Not that I planned on selling them anyways. I suppose I should give my grandfather's book a go. I've read Spymistress and Intrepid, and I find his prose a bit jaunty. That, combined with his general habit of being an asshole when he was alive, has discouraged me somewhat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 21:41:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did notice that rule in the sidebar, but I hoped my question at the end on which book to read first would accomplish that. Is the current edit sufficient?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My father's collection of old Robert Louis Stevenson books </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 21:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure if this is allowed, but I don't really know where else to share it. Recently, while digging through the archives of my family's publishing company, I found a pile of old books by Robert Louis Stevenson, my ~great great great great grandfather.

No idea what they are worth, nor if anyone will find this interesting, but thought I would share.

[Enjoy.](http://imgur.com/a/9HjXF)

EDIT: I wish this post was more informative, but unfortunately I'm not really in touch with that side of my family. If anyone knows anything about these books, or about RLS (or my grandfather) in particular, I'd love to hear more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:12:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *suggestive beeping* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:35:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The show and the foundation are separate entities. The foundation funds it. I'm just saying I agree with you and pointing out there might be just a wee bit of bias seeing as it wasn't an independant study  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A study commissioned by the Sesame Foundation.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:28:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, I thoroughly agree with the educational value Sesame Street brings to the table, but all these studies ARE commissioned by the Sesame Foundation.

That aside, here's a fun fact/ shameless plug for /r/bermuda: The CEO of the Sesame Foundation, Mel Ming, is fucking awesome and grew up in a really hard part of my country. I've interviewed him a few times and he's a top notch man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of how the lizards my cat eats must feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Illegal." Wait what? I don't want the whims of the public determining a major foreign policy decision like war... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 10:31:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  people with nothing to offer the world need to feel superior to somebody else.

Not really. I know this may be a shock, but there are plenty of intelligent, successful people on this site from a diverse range of background who get their kicks laughing at fatties as much as silly kittens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 21:53:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because how he was poisoned is debatable. What he was poisoned with is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 19:00:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As someone who didn't know anything about Turing beforehand, I thought the film was great. Reading up on it afterwards though, it was abundantly clear the portrayal of him was well off the mark. That said, I didn't buy Keira Knightly being a maths whiz for one second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 17:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that's not very nice. I'll have you know I have lovers in a vast array of area codes

* 718s
* 202s

I send small cities and states IOU's

* 901 
* matter fact 305

I jump off the D4, we can meet outside. So control your hormones and keep your drawers on til I close the door and I'm jumping your bones

* 312

* 313

* 215

* 803

Read your horoscope and eat some hors-d'oeuvres. Til I pump one of these hoes is self serve.

* 757

* 410 

My cell phone says overload

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 17:48:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well hey there pilonidal cyst brother. High five for having two holes in our butts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 16:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/popping would LOVE you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 16:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was. And I bet that asshole didn't earn the name from getting a handy andy from his girlfriend after she sliced up jalapenos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 16:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I'm white as heck.

Checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The beautiful bond of father and son </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 16:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 16:06:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mrs Blount. 9th grade World History. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 16:03:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  that were made public after the revolution in Russia

via www.bolshevikleaks.org IIRC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 15:59:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That fucking seal had the meal of his life. Dorado are fucking tastyyyyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 15:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Something something sausage and politics." -- Otto von Bismarck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 15:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, people seem to forget that not 50 years earlier France had the most dominant land army in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 15:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, the main reason (IIRC) is because the land was given to the Saudi family after the Ottoman Empire was defeated in WWI, and the Allies were all like "Yo Saudi's, hold my pocket." At that point I'm not sure they were thinking oil would become so valuable in the coming years, or even knew there WAS oil in them thar hills.

This history lesson brought to you by the scraps of memory I retain from my high-school education, so take it with a grain of salt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 15:14:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you make it sound like people are just going around guzzling genitals willy nilly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 15:02:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suppose you either die a content provider, or live long enough to see yourself become a filthy reposter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:56:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I didn't know Alan Turing had asperger's" -- My mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah. Didn't know this was a repost. I've become what I hate the most... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A frozen cyst inside a roast </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 13:43:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 13:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> H... how am I doing that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 13:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now that you've shown up, this is going to reach the front page. That's how it works right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:27:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like this comment just lacks proper grammar and you are encouraging /u/WisconsinHoosierZwei to watch a film titled Faces of Death... but part of me thinks it just as likely you're telling him to go find and watch the faces of dying people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:17:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Corporate on the phone: "What precisely do you mean by 'He dun fucked up'?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By sheer coincidence, I just finished The Imitation Game which gives the date of his suicide at the end of the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alan Turing died of cyanide poisoning 61 years ago today. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:56:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:51:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/YswTSQm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:46:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess it's my fault for reading "no spoilers" not thinking that wouldn't apply for the comments section </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:44:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that comma is really bothering, me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Verizon commercials make this one cry. So... Weird, but not out of the ordinary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:06:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With a misspelled name, nonetheless. Paging /u/jstrydor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:55:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom is screaming her tits off. She has no clue about horse racing....

EDIT: now she's crying. What the hell.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Makes you wonder how many bodies might be buried beneath.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More artillery, not bigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 22:53:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's moby dick. No frou-frou symbolism. Just a good old fashioned tale about a man and a whale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 18:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's not a backhanded compliment.... That's a straight diss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 18:00:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I am not a smart man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 17:59:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Frank N. Stein  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mother of God. 211,743 words.....

EDIT: just realized it's Moby fucking Dick. I am not a smart man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hence why I said "good satire" specifically. And in order for there to be libel, the person would have to prove damages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. After I left my job at my local national paper, I started a satire blog that people immediately began sharing thinking it was real. [This one,](http://thebermudalampoon.com/2015/02/27/michael-fahy-not-about-to-start-giving-a-shit/#more-192) about an appointed official (rather than elected) caused a 1000+ comment chain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:06:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good satire is taken seriously by LOTS of people. The former FIFA vice president, for example. Or even the OG satirist, Jonathan Swift. A Modest Proposal caused an uproar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the most satisfying part of writing satire, when people think it's real. It's really the highest compliment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 00:48:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's kinda the nature of sketch comedy, [as expressed perfectly by the Mitchell and Webb Look](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OE_Glg85-60) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:01:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Journalist here. An indoor, private gym is most certainly not a public space, and therefor you cannot film without consent. The reason it's legal to film in public without consent is because you don't have a reasonable expectation of privacy. While you are a patron inside an establishment, you have a reasonable expectation of privacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saddam Hussein banned Bermuda shorts because the exposed flesh of a man's calf might "inflame the passions of women and lead to immoral behaviour." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Source](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/His_Girl_Friday) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The 1940 screwball comedy His Girl Friday (available in full here) was the first film to use overlapping dialogue. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 21:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This kills the weasel  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bermuda was home to a number of nuclear depth bombs, stored there by the USA in case of all-out nuclear war. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:52:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:43:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember reading it somewhere. Was it on Reddit? If so I'd happily give credit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The BBC iPlayer volume goes up to 11... a subtle nod from the developer to Spinal Tap </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:41:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy mother of moses this is amazing. Thank you so much. On mobile right now so will check this out further when I get home. Cheers dude! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So glad I tagged you when you were called out on /r/quityourbullshit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:18:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually, they should thank Bills QB Ed Rutkowski for losing the final game of the ~~'78~~ '68 season, giving the Bills the #1 pick in the combined AFL/NFL draft over the Eagles. If Rutkowski hadn't fumbled on the 1 yard line, the Bills wouldn't have gotten OJ Simpson, meaning OJ would've gone to Philly, meaning he'd never have met Nicole, meaning he'd never have murdered her (allegedly), meaning he'd never have hired a lawyer named Kardashian, meaning when his daughter has sex with some cousin of Snoop's named Ray J, the only people that would know the Kardashian name would be Pornhub aficionados. If the Bills weren't so awful at football, we wouldn't have to be dealing with the Kardashians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 20:21:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Full comments from [Greg 'Picard' Dyke](http://i.guim.co.uk/static/w-620/h--/q-95/sys-images/Guardian/Pix/pictures/2015/6/2/1433265613069/d2e0376f-bb63-4132-95de-007706124be2-620x372.jpeg), since they'll be hard to find on the auto-feed I linked.

 Hes stood down. Hes gone. Lets celebrate  this is nothing to do with Mr Blatter being honourable, he hasnt been honourable in years.
 
 Something has come out of the events of last week that has caused Mr Blatter to resign  Hes gone. At long last we can sort out Fifa. We can go back to looking at those two World Cups. If I were Qatar right now I wouldnt be feeling very comfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 19:28:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Psh. Crimea river. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 19:19:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well, that and the piles of dead people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 19:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tony Pulis? Great track record of pulling businesses out of the shitter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> FA Chairman: "Hes gone. At long last we can sort out Fifa. We can go back to looking at those two World Cups. If I were Qatar right now I wouldnt be feeling comfortable." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 19:04:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 23:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Ah, the old reddit high-school-aroo](http://www.reddit.com/r/aww/comments/382z5y/today_is_mabels_14th_birthday_heres_the_cutest/crs9vg3?context=5) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 21:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm fine with spiders, cockroaches, junebugs, bats, sharks, you name it. Dolphins though? Fuck that. I'm convinced they're smarter than us, they just live a simpler life. 

I once volunteered at a dolphin experience place for a summer and had to go down with SCUBA gear to fix the fencing separating their enclosures. The 11 foot alpha named Khyber got hyper aggro and started jaw snapping at me. The shockwave shook my ribcage so much it felt like someone let off a grenade underwater.

They are terrifying animals. Nobody ever takes my phobia seriously, but I challenge anyone to get into a tank with a pissed off dolphin and tell me they didn't fear for their life.

(before people get on my back for working at such a cruel place, I was like 14 years old. I know now how awful it is to keep such amazing creatures penned in.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 21:39:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because there's a goalie doesn't mean you can't score </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 00:41:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is Bully Beatdown still going? That might actually be a good fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:48:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  dodged a ~~bullet~~ knife
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Townie was the kind of kid to punch you in the face when rough-housing. Apparently he was also the kind of kid to get high on acid and murder his mother's boyfriend, a retired US Army general.

Source: http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2005/jun/28/20050628-115956-6417r/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Since we're talking about sad endings to our childhood bullies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 15:43:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be careful. That could come back to haunt you. http://www.gifbin.com/bin/082009/1249287681_laser_pointer_dog_crotch_bite.webm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 17:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Source](http://www.bamz.org/conservation.php?id=2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The green turtle has been protected in Bermuda since 1620, only eight years after the island was settled. (x-post from /r/obscureknowledge) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 17:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The green turtle has been protected in Bermuda since 1620, only eight years after the island was settled. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 17:09:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 17:04:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Popular posts on TIL have a very specific type. I love the idea of this sub because it's sort of a /r/mildlyinteresting version of it. You could put TIL in front of a LOT of factual posts on Reddit and it would work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 17:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Journalist here. 

WE. DON'T. WRITE. THE. HEADLINES.

Feel the need to make that extra clear because every time there's a sensational headline, it's the author that gets blamed for it. 99% of the time we HATE the headlines our stories are given.

Call out the sub-editors, not the authors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 02:48:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Teddy Roosevelt - the original hard-ass romantic. The duality between his inner suffering from his personal losses, and the person he projected to the world, are infinitely fascinating to me. 

He sorta had this need to assure and remind everyone of his heroism, but at the same time was aware of his own limitations and listened to what his heart told him. Rare you find those qualities in the same man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:32:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anderson Cooper is a stellar journalist. He fucked off to Africa in his teens IIRC (bankrolled by his family, but still...). He started in journalism by answering telephones, before he made a name for himself by forging his own press pass and getting into Burma to interview the students fighting the government. After that he began stringing from war zones all over the world.

He may not be a Marie Colvin, or a Philip Gibbs, but he's legit. I dont find any reason not to like the guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 05:21:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My family would totally be worthy of the show if it wasn't for my cuntrag sister shushing everyone.

FUCK YOU KATIE I HAVE QUIPS TO MAKE AND I WILL NOT BE SILENCED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 21:50:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I came across that many morons in my field of work, I'd get pretty angry too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 17:59:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. You wouldn't notice the Canadians, you'd just be dead. 

"If I had Canadian Soldiers, American technology and British officers I would rule the world." - Winston Churchill

EDIT: Oh. Just noticed your flair. Howdy neighbor.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last I heard she was an Eagle Scout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:37:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> STORY TIME!

Freshman year in high school, my buddy got a hand job from a girl named Davina. 

She basically clapped her hands around it and rubbed up and down like she was trying to start a fire with a stick and some tinder.

Thus 'Dolphina' was born. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:12:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Already spent on rum and hookers. Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's not a bad idea, but it'd be damn near impossible to sell. I might give Elon a call though, just for good measure.

The Guardian has a long and storied history of breaking earth-shattering stories dating all the way back to when the Bolsheviks leaked documents exposing the Entente's imperial interests of WWI. That kind of history attracts supporters, so it's no wonder benefactors favour them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 18:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The point is that reliance on advertising for revenue creates that conflict of interest. Hence the BBC. NPR would've been the same, and in fact started out the same IIRC.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love that people still expect separation of church and state in the media. Of course they banned their reporters from doing that. Of course, it's also wrong, but the public doesn't want to pay for news. Don't want to pay, don't expect the tenets that journalism once espoused to remain.

Signed,

Severely disgruntled journalist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 19:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was really hoping this would be an America's Cup reference.

For those that don't know, the Brits invited the Americans to sail against them, with the Queen looking on.

America proceeded to detroy the British by a massive margin. Thus the "America's Cup" was born.

It would take almost 180 years before anyone else beat the Americans, when Australia did it in 1981 (I think.)

So... yeah, the Brits aren't too hot on sailing against the Americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mutu....

Now that's a name I haven't heard in a loooong time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 22:08:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I... don't get it. What a waste of a meme. A hipster cop would obviously go around arresting people for breaking archaic laws that nobody knows are still in effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 20:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> #JusticeForColby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 19:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> AYYYY LMAO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 21:52:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, I love moments like this purely for the quick little glimpse it gives into a person's real nature. I live in a majority black country and grew up thinking all my white friends weren't racist. But over time, every now and then, one of them would let slip a moment like this, and I'm grateful every time. I don't say anything, just make a mental note, then slowly eek them out of my life.

EDIT: I'm not talking about wee little moments of prejudice, or politically incorrect views. I'm talking about flashes of outright racism. It's something I hate with the core of my being and it fundamentally changes my view of people to the point that I don't want to know them anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 16:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/quityourbullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 18:42:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This girl had her life ruined over this video when the guy she sent it to uploaded it to the TOR site Pink Meth. Guilty boner....... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This happened to me in London. Travelled from one end of the city to the other, getting off and changing at all the same spots as a really cute girl. I was thinking I'd say something to her jokingly and we ended up getting off at my stop. She looks back. I go to say "heh I swear I'm not stalking you" but she bolts before I can. Shaved my moustache as soon as I got home... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 15:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Goats? Psh. My dog killed geese. GEESE. Lovely little black lab taking on dozens of 3-foot honking pieces of hell. It was a bloodbath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 20:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being seen as a "trusted student" by a teacher the rest of the class dislikes puts that student at odds with their classmates, fostering distrust among their peers. In the hyper-social setting of a classroom, this can be severely detrimental to the student's social standing among the group. 

"This kills the ____" is a meme, in this case applied glibly to signify that such an action by the teacher would leave the "trusted student" figuratively "dead". 

In comedy, hyperbole is often used to "play up" a truth. In this instance, "This kills the student" is referencing the social strain being labeled a "trusted student" would induce. 

While one could have commented: "This would severely hamper the student's social standing among his peers", such matter-of-fact comments often go unnoticed on forums such as Reddit, where one-liners and popular references tend to generate more reaction and, in turn, karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 19:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Send a trusted student

This kills the student </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:59:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Repost or not, I love seeing this. It's really the simplest advice you can give. I write for a living, so I get a lot of people asking me "how to become a writer" etc. The answer is literally in the job description.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:24:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A wave hit it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 22:32:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://media.giphy.com/media/awRutawdcWLJe/giphy.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 22:02:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 21:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention Suzuka 2006. Put it on pole then gave the lead to Schumacher, who would've won the championship if his engine hadn't blown on the final laps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:56:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I may not have ever seen a Whitmarsh car in person, but we in Bermuda are super fucking stoked to see what he can come up with for BAR racing. [Here's](http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-LlGp21ZReTY/VMGTeYMQmkI/AAAAAAAAdCg/WdQ5Pt6eBWs/s1600/Nacra20ACBARBermudac.jpg) what they are sailing in our waters right now. Gorgeous, frankly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 12:18:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make it hail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  JayZ Wentworth 

My sides.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 17:28:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These boots were made for scissoring?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:16:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [For that bitter taste.](https://boots.scene7.com/is/image/Boots/10136964?id=VhVah0 fmt=jpg fit=constrain,1 wid=504 hei=548) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 12:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Thine network is Telus

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 02:58:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Welcome to the fucking show.](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=b22_1422986532) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 01:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being the best at the second most popular sport on Earth is probably worth bragging about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 20:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quite a posh accent too. She'd do well in Parliament. 

"What Mr Cameron was meaning..."

DC: "POINT OF ORDER, MR SPEAKER. I'M NOT MEAN." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 18:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good thing he's better at football than chewing gum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 18:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/ComedyCemetery  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 17:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_burn_centers_in_the_United_States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 17:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's just calling two black men monkeys. There isn't even an attempt at making a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:54:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not offended. It's just not funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More of a response to low effort racism that isn't remotely funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:20:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/Bermuda here

Legend has it that if a corn-rowed white girl shows up before the end of May, summer comes early. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Snort it back up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:04:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol black ppl are monkeys right guise?

/r/shitpost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 14:57:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sarong is so fucking fetch I literally can't even </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 14:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hold the fucking phone. 

There's a girl named Kate Micucci?

Is her mother named Munch?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Come to Bermuda. 20 minute swim from my dock with a spear, and you'll have one in no time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 06:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fuck you say to me, paragraph? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 04:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They used the local media and now they're beating you. This is called being outsmarted. Nothing to do with a pussy pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:43:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best of luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:38:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well telling them they just don't get it, or explaining things in a condescending and dismissive way, is how you make sure they never get it.

Clinic defenders protect abortion clinic workers and clients from protesters who try and shame women as they walk in. IIRC you get some training and they call you up when a local abortion clinic is being protested for whatever reason. It's a great cause that always needs more help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perhaps try taking your activism beyond the internet. Volunteer as a clinic defender. You'll find no empathy here when you come in guns blazing with lines like 

 The only people that think women don't have issues in the US are men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:18:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really hoping you're a troll. Ignorance is not an indicator of intelligence. You have a flair for the kind of melodramatic rage that makes everyone think feminists are perpetually triggered cuntnuggets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:09:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lolwut? 

"Feminist" work differs wildly from country to country, according to how much work is needed to be done for the rights of women IN that country. American feminism, as the average person sees it, looks like Tumblr. Turkish feminism looks like a woman beheading her rapist in the fucking street.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:28:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "American feminism" would imply feminism in America is different. 

"American feminists" implies feminist women in America are different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know saying you complain about feminism = spouting off about feminism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:01:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doubtful. Quotes but no name is a pretty big indicator that the story is bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 01:54:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the new Brangelina!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 01:15:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Talking about how Superman makes us question our priority in the universe? Yup. That's exactly who is talking. Has to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 01:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just did a quick google. In California alone there are five different endangered fox species, five endangered species of rat, two species of endangered mice...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:53:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Lindsey works for the Washington Animal Clinic in Brenham. In the comment section of her post, she wrote no I did not lose my job. Lol. Psshh. Like someone would get rid of me. Im awesome!

lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also indigenous and endangered species. I live in Bermuda and have to keep a constant eye out for my cat getting its paws on a skink, one of world's rarest lizards. He's killed 4 already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:31:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All great advice until

 take the story to a sympathetic media outlet.

I hire a lot of freelancers. While I sympathise that you are working at an unethical company, I wouldn't trust you further than I could throw you if you quit your job because of the reasons you've listed then told another news outlet about it. Unless it's a story that has real value, like interns being forced to pay for rec letters, you'd be shooting yourself in the foot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:17:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please don't do that.

Lovingly, Bermuda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 23:33:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doubtful. It's one of my many pet names for him. Haz, Hazzy, Jazz Haz, Hazmat, Hazdribal, Hazilla, Hazim Zalabim, El Hazerino (if you're not into the whole brevity thing). Sometimes I just refer to the entire left side of the pitch as Hazpilicueta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 21:57:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not with that attitude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:24:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'keepers don't tend to get worse until their physicality REALLY drops off. Even then that drop-off can be compensated for with wise positioning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You must be watching a different player. IMO he's been excellent in those positions. His presence in a melee is precisely why I'd choose him over Cech.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 16:33:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weird. I remember a very boisterous chorus of "Adebayor, your dad washes elephants and your mum is a whore" echoing around the Emirates for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 16:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try using Colgate Xtra Fresh mouthwash. Excellent for getting rid of lingering bitter taste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:48:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's probably his only weakness. He can get overzealous. With Haz on that left wing I don't blame him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is one uncanny airplane impression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:29:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His distribution, primarily. He's had a number of shoddy throws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was a TV reporter for a while. Got pulled over for speeding with a girl I was dating and she says to the cop: "Do you know who he is?" Never been more mortified in my life. We broke up a few weeks later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has any of your work shown up on /r/wheredidthesodago? Any good stories? I worked in advertising for a hot second so I KNOW you've got a few... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 16:22:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whoring out my hair for karma is better than whoring out my mum though, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 15:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tropical islander here. Have to deal with this most of the year. All the advice here is spot on. I'd only add that I've found the best underwear for this in Banana Republic's Untra Pro sport trunk. Toss some Gold Bond in there and you've got yourself a smooth, dry coinpurse for the rest of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 15:43:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You paint with words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 05:04:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I CAN DO A REALLY GOOD WOOKIE IMPRESSION ^^^sorry ^^^I ^^^panicked ^^^and ^^^didn't ^^^know ^^^what ^^^else ^^^to ^^^say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 03:48:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a fucking sandcastle mold you numpty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 03:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have lived in the US, Bermuda, Canada, and the UK. In a bumfuck nowhere town in Canada I'm having a smoke on the sidewalk by a traffic light, outside a bar. Truck pulls up. Rolls down window. Guy looks at me: "How ya doin'?"

Um, fine.

"Don't look like you're from around here."

No, just here for my sister's graduation.

"Oh! Well give the little lady all my best!"

Light goes green. Truck drives off.

NOWHERE, and I mean NOWHERE, has that ever happened to me. Canada has earned it's reputation. Now siddown and eat your poutine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 03:29:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Smile big and walk fast. Nobody will notice. Unless you get obese. Then everyone will notice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 00:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ITT: the exact kind of speculation Funny or Die wanted to stir up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 00:13:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's SOP to film multiple takes of a scene from multiple angles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:16:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:58:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's from PinkMeth, a TOR revenge porn site where they doxx women on social media and make them write apology letters to get everything taken down. Remember coming across it a while ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 17:29:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Found the purple. 

#Grey4Lyf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 14:36:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's always sounded like bullshit to me. Do we have any proof that being fat was once found attractive? I don't see any beautiful statues of fat people... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 05:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not trivial at all, especially since the DP was [Shane Hurlbut.](http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0403397/) So, not exactly like he's going to ruin the guy's career.

I've done really small time broadcast news, and I'd get super pissed if anyone, let alone the director of photography, was walking around in front of me during filming. Everyone knew not to do that. 

How the fucking DP of a major motion film doesn't know that is actually pretty astounding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 05:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a really shitty version of a smoker's retort to people on high horses telling them how much money they'd save if they didn't smoke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 03:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Smoking a joint as I read this. Have I just been sorted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 02:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/zoophilia

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 22:49:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God fucking dammit. This sub is hell. Ducks, not chicks. Capybara, not guinea pig. Jesus. Someone get the oncologist, this post just gave me lymphoma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 06:13:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YAY. Does this mean I can finally use the term "Malthusian Catastrophe" and people will know what I'm saying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 06:08:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having your girlfriend of two years leave you because she's a lesbian is not quite the same... But Eh for Effort? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 04:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [K](http://www.reactiongifs.com/r/ktf.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 04:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YES. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a club!? GOOD. Because I'd really like to discuss how fucking confusing it is thinking about the woman I loved having lesbian sex. The dichotomy between a man's heart and his dick has never been more apparent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuckit, I'll jump on this downvote train. Fuck that show. Fuck Chuck. Fuck sitcoms. They're all terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure Reddit is comprised of a wide variety of people from all walks of life with similar taste in pop culture. But what do I know, I'm just an outcast loser neckbeard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take it from a guy who fell deeply in love with a girl who was questioning her sexuality, you dodged a bullet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:04:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Sigh.](http://thatmarriedguy.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/j002e3d.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 20:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The request and fulfilment of said request are too perfect. I think we need to bring in /r/KarmaConspiracy on this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 19:48:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be happy to if there's an actual interest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 18:23:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Night court????? I didn't know there was such a thing!

And honestly, if you haven't ever been to plea court (dont know what the American equivalent is), you need to go check it out. I've always referred to it as the most fun you can have for free with your pants on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was fine, except that he kept trying to explain to the magistrate that he and his cousin (the owner) had sorted it out. The magistrate kept telling him if they had sorted it out, he wouldn't be here. That was hard for him to understand. Here's the article. http://www.royalgazette.com/article/20131113/NEWS02/131119909 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's much more succinct than I've been putting it. I hate this new trend of looking at the world like it should be a crime free paradise. Should the Ferguson kid have been shot? Of course not. Should he have obeyed the law? Of course. Did Charlie Hebdo deserve it? No. Should they have seen it coming? No shit. Should women get to wear whatever they want? Sure! Should women know wearing certain clothing will elicit certain responses? Fucking duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:42:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Court reporter here. Can confirm. Especially in plea court, these idiots are a dime a dozen. Once [wrote a story](http://www.royalgazette.com/article/20131113/NEWS02/131119909) on a guy who kicked in a restaurant's door because he had to pay $3.25 for some bacon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 17:23:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  There's not very many automatic weapons

Quite the opposite. Automatic weapons dominated trench warfare. The machine gun is responsible for the brutality of WWI. Jump out of trench, get mowed down, repeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:33:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dear America,

Sort out your pansy ass college students. We didn't help you fuck up the redcoats so cry-baby college kids can waste their time banning a goddamn film from being shown to whoever wants to see it.


Sincerely,

/r/bermuda  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 15:34:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the NATO Tigers patch, IIRC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 13:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  freakshow

Tagged as deep closet homo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:04:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YES. Islander here. Happened to my parents' friends. I go full panic mode whenever I see a kid sitting like that now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Chickensaurus is already in dev.](http://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/paleontologist-jack-horner-is-hard-at-work-trying-to-turn-a-chicken-into-a-dinosaur/2014/11/10/cb35e46e-4e59-11e4-babe-e91da079cb8a_story.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Grab some popcorn.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/2c9ida/recap_unibanned_a_recap_of_the_fallout_of_reddits)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey fuck you, buddy. Who died and made you Conductor of Assumption Junction, eh? Society dictates what's "normal" or not. I mean, sure, there's the whole thing about normality being established by statistical representation of sex and gender identity, but the implication is you're calling non cis NOT normal, and that's mean. Also accurate. BUT MEAN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:24:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really wish there was a large group of black people watching this go down. I'd pay handsomely for that commentary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 02:08:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So... WERE YOU THERE FOR HER? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 01:19:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was waiting to read this. Former court reporter here. Cameras are shown to have a significant impact on the judge's sentencing. Doubly so considering judges are elected in America, leaving them prone to handing down harsher sentences to please the public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dead_cat_bounce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 23:25:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A school is using perfectly legal means to reduce interest payments! Burn it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 19:06:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Am I the only one that would like to see confirmation that this is OP's mom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 17:11:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FUCK. THAT. NOISE. 

My balls just retreated quicker than an arctic glacier on rollerskates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 04:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd have to be certain I had something worth saying. Otherwise you're just asking to be haunted by the disapproving gaze of the president of the united states the rest of your life. "Yeah, I met the President," you'll tell your grandkids, trying your best to forget the way his eyes belied precisely how disappointed he was that you were even in the room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 04:51:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fuck is everyone angry at then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 04:32:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. Only a fucking moron or a genius would speak up during something like that. I'm the loudest cunt in the room 90% of the time but you couldn't get me to give my thoughts in a situation like that in a million years.

EDIT:[ Thank you.](http://i.imgur.com/86etTSn.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 04:21:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait. Really? Did a gay couple ask them to cater, or did they just say they wouldn't cater gay weddings? Maybe I run with a different crowd, but a pizza place announcing they're not going to cater a gay wedding is a bit like me announcing I'd rather not make out with the hottest girl in school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 21:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's precisely what I meant by "solution". Apologies that it came off differently, I agree 100%. My point was that the public doesn't understand that the "solution" to addiction is in mitigation, not eradication, and that our current way of dealing with the problem only ends up costing everyone more money and ruining more lives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very much so. The most interesting aspect of drug treatment court for me was that it's more like a therapy session. I'm of the opinion that if you enjoy using drugs, you should be free to do so until your drug use infringes on the rights of others. That's when your addiction becomes a problem for the state and community to address (although that's not to say it shouldn't be addressed sooner). I'm a big advocate for the "it takes a village" approach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:10:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cassie???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 16:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I appreciate it, but I'm only a conduit doing its job. Covering such stories is to my benefit. It just so happens that what benefits me also benefits the public. It's impassioned people such as yourself that really need to be thanked. Without people like you I wouldn't have a story to write. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 16:07:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Funny you mention it. I'm looking at Ross Perot's cigarette boat "Blue Thunder" as I write this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 15:45:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's actually astounding how much push back there is to the idea that sticking a badger in a cage is the best way to make it nice. Alongside the public perception of addiction, I think Americas biggest difficulty will be taking capitalism out of the prison system without plangent screams of "socialism" from the right. We've already seen how hard it is to take capitalism out of health care.

EDIT: clarity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 15:28:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weird. The religious people I know are some of the most positive, genuine, and selfless people I know. I'm as athiest as they come, but still... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 15:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've reported on the rehabilitation of non-violent drug offenders for a while now. Was given unprecedented access into a drug treatment court, which is not open to the public or press. Wrote a solid 15+ articles on the subject for my country's national daily paper. Was interviewed by a PhD student studying the same thing for their dissertation. Was thanked profusely by the lawyers involved in the process (who are some of the most genuine lawyers I've ever met). Basically, everyone who knew anything about the subject was super stoked that it was getting coverage, and a lot of it.

Every article I wrote received little to no attention. The comments came in on the web version were derisory, often along the lines of: "Yeah, I'd fake being 'rehabilitated' as well if it meant getting out of jail."

I can't speak for other nations, but to me the problem is clearly with the public's perception of drug addiction. There is still the prevailing mentality that people do this to themselves, and they get what they deserve. Up until those articles I was as gung-ho about drug reform as you could get. After seeing how much the public actually cares, I've lost every last bit of optimism. My only hope is that enough countries begin taking such approaches, so countries like mine can see just how powerful this kind of rehabilitation can be.

EDIT: THANK YOU FOR THE [GOOOOOOOOOOOOOLD](http://i.imgur.com/86etTSn.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:10:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Betty probably said the same thing about her dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 23:44:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've seen it matter firsthand working in a single industry for more than 10 years. You're not even out of high school.

There are times when diversity can be of value, and times where it's not needed. Saying point blank it doesn't matter just shows a total lack of understanding when it comes to workplace dynamics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 23:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  ...placing diversity over skill is clearly counter-productive to the bottom line.

How you managed to interpret the exact opposite of what I said is a miracle.

My point was only that diversity can be a positive thing when it's not prioritized above skill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why not? Having a gender diverse workplace is shown to have a number of advantages. If you have two equally skilled male and female candidates in a workplace that is largely comprised of men, there are plenty of reasons for why the female candidate would be a better option.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:05:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to be contrarian, but [workplace diversity does have its advantages.](http://newsoffice.mit.edu/2014/workplace-diversity-can-help-bottom-line-1007)

Obviously, placing diversity over skill is clearly counter-productive to the bottom line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 15:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably risks having the whole cave collapse... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 14:58:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Skeets Miller" is possibly the best journalist name ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 14:55:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glad to see this sub going back to its roots. That "bathrooms should be pull to enter, push to exit" nonsense rustled my jimmies a bit too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 14:53:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess people don't care when it's TIME magazine. Unabomber, Gaddafi, Bin Laden.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 05:13:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rolling Stone is hardly the first magazine to put a terrorist on the cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 00:09:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A total pisshead is who.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 20:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solid plan. Let's run with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 15:20:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't realize /r/showerthoughts had become /r/commonsense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 11:29:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spot on. No idea why I keep clicking on the comments section. This is the ONLY time it's ever paid off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 06:10:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We need more women like you commenting in this sub. Dear lord that would be so refreshing. Like a paper daisy on a cum-stained corkboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 04:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of the few times I'm glad I got the titties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 03:48:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was piss my pants or dash for the bathroom. I chose wrong. And yeah, they sell beer inside the stadium but you cant bring it with you to your seat. Hence the chugging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah, Essien's famous screamer against Arsenal in 07/08.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was far and away my favourite player, which made it all that much worse. But yeah, he was crucial for us for so many years. Won't ever forget the Ess Express and his love for naps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:12:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know. It'd be like having an Army badge as well as a Green Beret badge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 23:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever I watch a game with the English side of my family and we go down a goal, they all tell me to go take a piss so we can score. Its worked a solid number of times actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 23:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SO fetch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:36:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just being pedantic and I love WWII history. The creator clearly just threw on as many Nazi logos as possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:16:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would be a bit difficult to be a part of the Schutzstaffel, SS-Totenkopfverbnde, AND the luftwaffe...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:12:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh man. Almost feel sorry for him. It takes one hell of a falsely inflated ego to flip out over something like this. Even if you WERE lying, I've had plenty of dates "reschedule" on me then never follow back up. I'd rather sit at home a watch a movie than go on an awkward date where one of you doesn't want to be there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:08:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $10 says "Easter dinner" comes in scare quotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:01:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a hope in hell that is Courtois' fault. Jog on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LOL a bedpan? With that kind of money I could just pay someone to piss in their mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 20:53:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You try holding it in after chugging as many beers as possible before the whistle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 20:48:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of ham did you use? And it better have been whole wheat bread. Hovis, preferably.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know nothing. 

My first Chelsea game I went to take a piss. Walked up the stairs back to my seat and the crowd goes nuts.

[This was the goal I missed.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kl1L67rzuEk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Called the whole family into the TV room for this one. Jesus Fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 18:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know "heads up" was shitting on someone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 15:29:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ugh. Yeah, that's the ticket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 15:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh man. I saw these chicks in London and this song had me DYING. I want to marry them both. So glad they're making it big time. Only person to make me laugh that hard at a show was John Stuart doing stand up.

(If anybody has a clip of his closing act, where he talks about trying to fuck his wife while his dog is puking outside his bedroom door, that would be great) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 14:41:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Live in one of the world's largest green turtle sanctuaries. Our country has protected them since the early 1800s. Not sure where you are, but where I'm from this picture would get you in shitloads of trouble. Highly illegal to even catch them. Just a heads up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 14:11:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's pretty fucking stupid that Jesus needed to roll a giant rock out of the way to escape the tomb when he has teleportation powers, but you bet your ass I'll be chompin down on some candy bunnies this weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 13:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HA! Thanks for pointing that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 02:37:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I posted this same TIL to Archer a while back. Most people on the thread pointed out Hiroo probably wasn't the guy as there were lots of "hold outs." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 23:16:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really, no. So just putting it out there. Bring me a puppy, you've got yourself a free stay at Chateau du Weiner!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 22:49:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean... it doesn't HAVE to be an aussie. How hard would it be to get a puppy to Bermuda? I am so down for this trade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ummmmmm that can definitely be arranged </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:26:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Bill Cosby's thoughts on the subject](http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/84/83/f9/8483f904e67132d9251c6c720422bdf1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is. Fun fact about the house: Adam Driver married my cousin 2 summers ago on the front lawn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:18:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The racism in this thread disgusts me. Clearly this woman is hedgehogkin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:50:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If puppies result you've got yourself a free week at [my rental cottage](https://www.flipkey.com/sandys-cottage-rentals/p522705/) in Bermuda in exchange for one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:42:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ugh.... I've wanted an Aussie for so fucking long. Directions to Jelly school, plz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [A humble token](http://i.imgur.com/PvNJZgI.jpg) of my broke ass's appreciation for that comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 13:21:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait. Who is Alex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 13:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why even bother? Or are you that much of tool to think you can get laid because a girl posted a picture of herself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Far crazier things have happened... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:05:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have no idea what's going on, but clearly you've ruined it. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 15:22:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait... did they recently release an album that sold like 4 copies in Australia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 15:18:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's because you can't get in trouble for saying two grown ups had sex. Try saying a major celebrity fucked a 14 year old and see how that goes down with their lawyers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 14:27:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's my cousin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 17:53:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is PRECISELY how I feel after missing an easy birdie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 17:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ONE link I click on thinking it might be real. Fuck you OP. I had the biggest freedom chub and you ruined it. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wasn't just for you. I've had a few messages and there are other similarly themed comments to yours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah... I get that my comment came across that way. But there are a lot of circumstances to my personal relationship and how it ended that has resulted in me being a lot more judicious with who invest myself emotionally in. No sense going into them, this isn't /r/relationships, but for clarity's sake it's not my trust in women that has gone specifically, it's the realization that the person I choose to give myself to wholeheartedly can at any given moment turn around and leave me with my dick in the wind. I doubt that person would ever be a man, so it's not a leap to say that relationship has left me wary of any woman I should want to spend my life with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mixed, but close enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go ahead and check my post history. I'm all for remaining with England because of the advantages it offers us. Carry on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spoken like a true member of the Empire.

Since you clearly can't pick up on colloquialisms like "readins", I guess I have to explain.

Bermuda was settled by people on their way to settle in America. Therefor anti-British sentiment was strong circa 1775, since many of the people fighting in the Revolutionary War (sorry, "The War Of Independence" in your parlance) had close ties to Bermuda. Famous figures like John Rolfe, for example, had been wrecked in Bermuda (he even named his child with Pocahontas "Bermuda Rolfe.")

Seeing as those who settled in Bermuda did so for the same reasons the colonists settled in Virginia, it's only natural that they would side with their American brothers and sisters in their fight to gain independence.

Subsequently, we have attached our own dollar to the American dollar, become the darling of your biggest corporations, and underwritten the majority of your insurance. We are the oldest self governing colony in the British Empire, and have made shaky steps towards independence on a number of occasions, each push ultimately failing because no longer being a part of Britain would deprive us of valuable education and work opportunities both in the UK and the wider EU.

But what do I know, I'm just a Bermudian journalist with more than a decade worth of experience and research into Bermudian history to draw from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:19:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was more savage than that. Literally stopped responding to me when I lost my job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:41:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck. It's not a joke when this has actually happened to you. Completely erased my trust in women

EDIT: the women I have intimate relationships with. Obviously not all women. You don't get hit by a car then not pay more attention the next time you cross the road.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:36:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Found the professional comedian everyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:32:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sisters are good friends with him. Went to school together. He's hilariously self deprecating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:23:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either the mods are morons or this is a really bad April Fools joke... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 16:53:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totalling a car? Check.

Driving fast and annoying neighbours? Check.

Eggings houses? Check.

Being late because video games? Check.

Pissing in inappropriate place? Check.

Distain for authority? Check.

I did every single last one of those things as a kid. You've only made me feel sorry that Justin Beiber has to live his life under such scrutiny that regular teenage hoodrat shit qualifies him for being vehemently hated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 16:30:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd still hit it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 16:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What makes him so twattish? I know nothing about the kid except he has a face I want to punch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 16:05:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Found the Belieber  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 15:24:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually I had no idea. Thanks! Growing up on an island, we don't get much readins done, but when we does its awlays good to learn something new. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 08:07:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /u/trollabot EvilBrent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 07:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  a nation of naked knee school lads on a scouting trip

I ain't even mad. That's the best goddamn description I've ever heard.

And if you want showy, try lying on that pink sand and being able to stick a little flag in it every time your $12 daiquiri needs a refill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 06:00:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honorary patriot* 

/r/Bermuda reporting for duty. 

When it comes to helping Murica fight off red-coat scum, let alone the wand waving kind, we've [got your back.](http://www.revolutionary-war-and-beyond.com/the-bermuda-gunpowder-plot.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 05:46:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree, although I found her more annoyingly stubborn and pompous. The way she walked over the house elves really irked me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 05:43:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What makes you think Hermione would want a domestic life?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 05:36:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel compelled to say sir, yes sir right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 05:31:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually, my last name is double barrelled. "Spicy-Weiner" just sounds too weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 01:34:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah. TIL. Good for them. Must've been fun. We in Bermuda had a Cat 4 hit us dead on last summer. One of the coolest things to experience, so long as nobody gets hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 01:29:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IIRC that picture was photoshopped or taken at a totally different time to the hurricane. Did they actually, or was that just more Facebook bullshit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 00:26:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well Muslims born and raised in the west usually ARE like every other muslim. Regular people.

The media is responsible for a lot of things, not least of which is the total confusion over what is going on within Islam right now. You're right in that it's helped spread xenophobia and racism and prejudice. I totally agree. You're right in that plenty of other religious groups have practiced the exact same things from time immemorial.

But Islam is in the middle of a massive ideological battle right now that is spilling over, costing hundreds of thousands of lives. Should talking heads be wondering on national television if the guy was a muslim? Of course not, if there's nothing to suggest that. Of COURSE that is wrong.

Is it prejudiced to wonder if a muslim who has carried out a violent attack was doing so in the name of Islam? No, because prejudice is by definition a pre-conceived notion not based on actual experience. If 20 people have been bitten by sharks off of one beach all summer, and a body washes up with chunks taken out of it, you're going to assume a shark did it.

EDIT: #notallsharks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 22:07:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1 + X = 2. Assuming X = 1 is not exactly rash.

It's not prejudicial to assume that if a Muslim commits an act of mass murder, especially in the West, it's usually in the name of ideology. And when it comes to killing people with planes, it's not like there isn't a history. It's irresponsible to use a label such as terrorist without knowing the motive, absolutely, but questioning whether an act of violence was ideologically motivated these days is only natural. 

Just to be clear, I lived for three years with kids from Jordan, Saudi Arabia, and Iran. Some of the best friends I ever had. I'm not trying to shit on Muslims. Hell, the most devout Muslims I met were the most morally upstanding people I have ever come across.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 20:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm one of those people. Worked in journalism from 16 onwards. Went to college. Realized in my first month that it would be way more beneficial to stay in the industry for three years instead of spending money on getting a 3-yr degree. Going to get my masters next year, and the newspaper I work for is paying for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 18:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you misread my comment. I wasn't saying that. And it's not just a dick on a motorcycle that thinks this. There are plenty of economic studies that advocate for flexible speed limits, especially on rural roads where noise pollution is not a factor. [Like here, for example.](http://docreader.readspeaker.com/docreader/index.php?jsmode=1 cid=bqcrm lang=en_au url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bitre.gov.au%2Fpublications%2F2003%2Ffiles%2Fwp_059.pdf v=Google%20Inc.)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 18:09:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm puzzled too. It was at +10 one second. The next it was at -14. Either way, I'll happily take the downvotes on behalf of /r/motorcycles. I don't know a single rider that isn't extremely cautious with their driving. I ride to avoid traffic, but I also ride for the exhileration. At no time do I mesh those two desires. If I want to satisfy my craving for [power](http://www.instantclarkson.com/) I go to a long stretch of empty road near the airport where I live. I even dated a girl that loved the whole motorcycle thing and pissed her off every time she rode with me because she wanted to go fast and I refused.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:49:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spot on. I've had a handful of crashes, all but one of them have been because of someone else in a car. The one that wasn't, I ran over a nail that popped my tyre. I've got a theory that a lot of road accidents could be avoided by less restrictive speed limits, and the same logic applies to riding vs driving. In a car it's easy to switch off because of the feeling of security a car provides. If you're on a bike, you're acutely aware that you could go flying 50 feet in the air and land in a ditch if anyone makes a wrong move. Now who is going to be the more cautious driver? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:30:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On behalf of bikers everywhere, we know. The last thing the majority of riders need is a lecture on their own mortality. The majority of us are respectful and safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:16:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My ex's exes were a Rockefeller and pro basketball player. Jokes on them though, because I'm the one she fell in love with. Until she became a lesbian and broke up with me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit this is so true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:50:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/im14andthisisdeep  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:41:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [You're not wrong.](http://i174.photobucket.com/albums/w108/Billtog/splittinghairs.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Went to tie my shoe. Fell off a cliff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm more concerned with that flapjack ass in sweats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:24:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for explaining a very obvious visual message. It really drove the post home for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fighting_words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:09:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Freedom of speech doesnt literally mean you're free to say anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 15:56:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd really like to introduce you to my friends. You can't have a glass of wine without being called a fag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 15:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tired of being a ham? Need a qualified shitlord to shame you into getting healthy? Come on down to /r/fatpeoplehate! You bring the jelly, we'll bring the shame! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 15:28:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit that is one good looking cat. Rock on Mr Jones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 15:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. Made me remember the time my ex bought me dinosaur shower curtains. That is true love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 06:35:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck me, people remember trig? I took it for two years and there isn't a snowball's chance in my ass I could do this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 06:27:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IIRC the russians conducted training drills down there during the cold war. Seems like it might be just an attempt to show the US Russia can have major influence within their immediate neighbourhood.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 05:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The way he just lets the natural momentum of his jump carry him back around when he realizes the shot is delayed... he's not just athletic, he's fucking smart. At least in that sense. Not everyone would have the presence of mind to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 05:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OH, yes. I hadn't thought about that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 05:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> crimping 

OOOOOOOOOOOOOH! That's a tinny word.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 03:56:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *are dotted ^^^^I'm ^^^^really ^^^^really ^^^^sorry ^^^^but ^^^^I ^^^^can't ^^^^help ^^^^myself ^^^^it's ^^^^a ^^^^problem ^^^^and ^^^^I'm ^^^^trying ^^^^really ^^^^hard ^^^^to ^^^^overcome ^^^^it ^^^^pray ^^^^for ^^^^me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 03:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> _ 

I don't follow... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 03:49:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, that's what really confused me. I've never been self conscious but I sure as shit never thought ol' Reptar was anything to write home about. Can only assume she was a size queen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 02:57:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/quityourbullshit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 02:53:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As someone who had a one night stand recently with a girl who said "Oh, I heard it was bigger", that shit stings. I'm not even small, but that's a surefire way to give a dude a complex where there wasn't one before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 02:36:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's really interesting. I'm guessing the principal is that by not trying to make the software perfect, you get it out early and keep developing it from there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 01:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yessssss. Exactly. Although as a former court reporter I might point out that it's not really tip-toe language, it's just factual. And while libel is a concern, media oversight groups are the main concern. I'd have seriously put my job in danger if I didn't use the proper language.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 01:12:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/FloridaMan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 01:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone never read Stieg Larsson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 00:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /u/trollabot train_subject1208 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 23:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get why I'm being downvoted, but I was just pointing out that you don't have to be rich to sleep with people from around the world. My m'stake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 22:02:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is the historical context? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:52:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Giving up that karma would be... criminal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel so bad for laughing but fuck that was funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:45:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I don't care that you think it doesn't deserve to be there. The whole point of reddit is that the users decide what is good content and what is not. Downvote and be on your merry way. I'll upvote and do the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your mastery of sarcasm blows my mind. Look out Cicero! Where did you learn to use such a rhetorical device?

Your ebullient use of the English language aside, my point was that it was clearly not the most amazing content, but the story behind it connected with me in a way that I could appreciate.

Could it be that the things people find interesting differs wildly between individuals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:24:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was more thinking of the post where OP used his dead father's last fiver to get a beer when he was legal. It was just a picture of a beer and a fiver, but as someone who lost their father as a teen, I appreciated the post. Begging for donations is different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:19:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unless that girl was Elle Woods. Then she'd dump your candy ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:17:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait. I thought this was photoshopped. Is it not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:14:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing humble about it, except I can't afford to go any of those place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 20:53:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've dealt with an unfair amount of tragedy in my 27 years. Don't have a problem with this at all. Whatever helps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 20:31:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was in an emotionally abusive relationship for a while. Got out of it when I realized things weren't getting better. Turned out the entire time we were dating she was living undiagnosed with MS, which played a big part in her craziness level. Anyways, this won't be a popular opinion, but I think it takes a particularly weak person to internalise the emotional abuse they're getting. Both men and women. I couldn't ever take a word she said seriously because she was so clearly trying to say the most hurtful thing she could imagine. Why would you give a person like that the time of day? Why let their comments affect you? It never made sense to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 19:40:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dunno, living in a major tourist destination, I could probably make my way around europe and america crashing on the couches of girls I've hooked up with. Tourists love the local boys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 19:23:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Need a sauce on that please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:46:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I definitely know that hair and booty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:41:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've heard that joke. Seriously en pointe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 17:49:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a Palace fan, in which case I'm sure she'll be a lot more happy in about 28 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 07:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what the fuck has happened in the last few weeks? why is shit like this making the front page now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 06:05:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I take it you're not the safe guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 01:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Calling him a journalist is doing him way too many favours. He writes about games. Call me when he's writing about gaming in South Sudan.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Father and son share a moment at a football game. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 23:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 17:13:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An ex of mine did a photo project similar to this. After three years of taking intimate photographs, a junkie isn't going to care if she's there when they start fucking. A bit ethically grey to me, but that's why I stick to words not pictures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 17:09:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/quityourbullshit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 17:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drug treatment courts for non violent drug offenders are some of the most effective courts in the world. Their recidivism rates are miniscule. The entire drug court team knows who really needs it, and who is trying to use them to get out of jail time. They spend a lot of time and effort making sure they aren't being played.

Signed,

Guy who has reported on drug treatment courts for, oh, 11 years now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 15:30:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ghost Kitty is our nickname for the stray we found stowed away in our car engine. Our last name is Stevenson, so naturally we named him Yusuph Islam, the artist formerly known as Cat Stevenson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 15:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're having content problems I feel bad for you son, I got 99 problems but reposting ain't one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 05:44:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Building a stadium that gives your team an advantage over the visitor is standard practice among most sports. A lot more of the new stadiums in English football do this, not to mention everything they do with the pitch to get an advantage. Also, it's not against the rules. You can't get busted for smoking weed then point out the guy that's drunk and say what he's doing is worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 05:35:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably because their shitty O-Line ruined what could have been a top 5 QB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 05:31:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is pretty common practice in a lot of sports. Wembley Stadium in particular. Playing fake crowd noise is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 05:05:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Technically according to [cat law](https://youtu.be/WGEGy21Yk9U?t=45s) you're right. The apartment is his now. But cat law differs slightly to human law. Kinda like bird law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 04:43:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did he have to wait?

I don't think it's that incredible he advanced through the ranks. I'm pretty cynical about most things, but I find it very hard to imagine the American military has come to a point where valour is no longer a core value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 04:30:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm ashamed to admit I got the year wrong, and somehow forgot about Palace making Suarez cry. My LFC Hater badge will be on the desk in the morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 04:22:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shit. Of course it's that match. That would explain why I spotted this. I watched it at least five times out of pure schadenfreude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 04:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I kiiiinda checked, but I'm about as confident as Rhodri Giggs at a family reunion. The only match between the two sides I came across in 2014, the score was 1-2. The 2013 fixture ended 3-1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 04:11:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair. But I was thinking in terms of content and the reddit community as a whole. Google+ and Facebook users don't get a goddamn fucking ridiculous doge meme on a NASCAR, then it into the All Star Race. It's shit like THAT that keeps me here. I lost it seeing that goddamn doge car, and I don't want that kind of stuff to stop happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 01:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, it's way too friendly. She's putting up fliers though. [It was hanging around outside the day before.](https://fbcdn-sphotos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfp1/v/t1.0-9/10858467_2822717327065_4298220802314223533_n.jpg?oh=a0b1480ae931d194c260b4d11ca9519f oe=5571DB34 __gda__=1437718069_d4bb51a56b02ecae4adb06b4e09abdb4) Guess he decided he liked what he saw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 00:56:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Reddit is far past masquerading as anything other than what it is: the most influential website in the world. This happens with a lot of cultural movements, of which Reddit can certainly qualify. They start out with upstanding value systems that people gravitate toward. But the more people gravitate, the harder it becomes to uphold those ideals. Reddit gets more and more popular, requiring more and more money. In order to keep making that money to service the users, values are sacrificed. Goes for political parties, religions, you name it. I'm disappointed but wholly unsurprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 00:37:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is my friend's business! Big up Evan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 00:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, but no. Boston. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know of many F1 drivers that haven't practiced from an early age.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:28:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. Definitely going on my letter to Santa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bermuda, the land of pastel shorts, pink beaches, and nonexistent triangles.

That's pretty much what I had in mind. This is in the far off future, mind you. There's no way I could afford flying out to a driving school any time soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, unfortunately. Her apt complex doesn't allow pets :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THAT I can understand. Obligatory brush with death story:

 My days riding 50cc scramblers saved my life a few years back. I was going too fast around a blind corner and there was a van parked in the road. I swerved to avoid it but another car was coming in the opposite direction. I hit the brakes hard, locking up my rear which put the bike sideways, skidding straight toward the car. The moment I realized I was going to hit it head on, I let go of the rear brake and the bike popped up and straightened out, grazing the driver's side of the car and sparing my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh dear god no. Definitely not planning on jumping straight into an F1 car. I want to take a proper course and everything. And yes, I drive every day, but only ever under 60kph in beat up Opel Astra. Doesn't exactly hone your driving sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:40:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately not. I live on a 21 square mile island where the speed limit is 50kph. Having a burp in an F1 car is high up on my bucket list though. I'm dying to know if I have the balls to give it some real welly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alonso might disagree there. Or Stirling Moss........ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:13:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That makes a lot of sense. Sounds similar to MotoGp. I guess what's tripping me up is just a general lack of knowledge for how it feels going fast on four wheels. I've always gotten my kicks on two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 21:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like that's probably a good thing. I've only ever seen a fedora worn well in magazines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 21:05:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ? am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This ferocious beast followed my friend into her apartment today and now refuses to leave. He loves snuggles, sour creme, and laying claim to apartments that are not his. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 20:49:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 20:12:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like he's about to dingle his dangle on the rim... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 20:07:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to be SUPER into swords as a kid. Went to Toledo for them and everything. I still fucking love swords, but man oh man have neckbeards ruined them for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 18:05:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mother of god. what tard kard put this report together? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 16:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Journalist here. Same thing applies, although it's not so much crying over really horrific shit, more the slow, painful realization as you slip deeper into the rabbit hole of life that nothing is going to change, and there's nothing you can do about it. That said, we do see some pretty awful road fatalities. I didn't think journalism would teach me what a kneecap looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 14:41:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They were actually the OG truthers. Well, them and the sinking of the Maine. We've just forgotten about that particular conspiracy theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 14:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. I never understood this about fans wanting athletes to be upstanding moral paragons of sportsmanship. Players dive. They flop. They do anything they can to win. It's up to the people making the rules to ensure the integrity of the game is maintained despite this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 13:24:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean... That's kinda exactly how America started </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 12:24:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or... y'know. [Get a cook book holder.](http://static.eatwell101.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/CUCINA-RECIPE-HOLDER-e1353950059213.jpg)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 14:37:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> something something, Cotton... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 15:59:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same goes for writers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 15:11:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DEAR GOD. How did it get there???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 14:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is Sir David's mortality a problem? Really? You don't see the problem there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 07:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya'll need to learn how to bullshit better if you're typing single words in at the end of sentences. Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 07:13:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooooooooh dat thudding doe. Jesus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 07:08:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It got a decent "heh" out of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 07:04:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is a huge fucking difference. Words are just a fraction of the ways we communicate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 07:04:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm the same way. I saw a thread about a guy wanting to commit suicide the other day and my first instinct was: "What a cunt, posting that online. I should go tell him to do it". I didn't, but I still wanted to... that's disturbing to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 06:10:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can confirm.

Signed, a criminally charming hobo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 05:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you'd like to boil it down to which measurement is used the most, I'd be willing to bet the entire trade and commerce industry might beat out the average number of Americans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 05:35:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now you just need to have JJ block a field goal... Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 05:24:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Remind me how a few movie stars worth millions of dollars asking for my money to make another movie is important? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 04:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fun fact: the "official" system of measurement in the US is actually metric.

EDIT for clarity: the metric system is "the Preferred system of weights and measures for United States trade and commerce". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:54:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fact that she, armed with only a bachelor's degree in early childhood education, took over an entire magazine when her husband died suddenly, and not only kept the business afloat but managed to cut all our debt, rebrand the magazine, launch four more magazines, publish 12 books, find the most awesome, caring, creative man to love, and raise two kids all at the same time. She also rips mad bongs. Mom's an OG4Lyf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct me if I'm wrong, but that's kinda the fucking point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 21:48:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait, why? Because other people are writing the material, or because no roast material will ever come close to what Kat had for Flava Flav? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 21:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly what I thought. Running up to the big guy like "He's scared! He can't fuck with you, dude!" Probably going to be yammering away next to him for the rest of the day, pointing out other skinny kids: "You could take him, Mike! Is it cool that I call you Mike?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 17:25:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ugh. I mean, I get as much of a kick out of the fat acceptance movement as the next guy, but I sure as shit don't hate people for it. It's just flat out hilarious. "Look at me, I'm beautiful!" Ok sweetheart. Keep telling yourself that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 16:34:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had no idea we didn't like her. Quick, someone tell me why I should hate her too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 13:35:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rolling Stone doesn't shy away from stories easily. I'm very curious to know why they didn't publish this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 13:33:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your definition of "high quality journalism" is a little different to mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 15:17:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I literally have AIDS now. Fuck this sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:50:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When did the Marine Corps get involved? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 16:45:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whaaat? I thought this was fucking fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 16:37:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EVERY GODDAMN TIME.

"Honey. Honey. Go gown on me."

"Have you showered?"

"Yeah of course."

*sniffs*

"Nope."

Damn you, ball sweat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 19:49:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. That's why I consider it a very poorly executed good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 18:53:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends on what kind of writing you want to do, but for most creative stuff you'd want to **start simple**. 

I started with American lit, Kerouac, Thompson, Twain etc. Their stories are accessible, entertaining, and well written. Diving straight into the REALLY good stuff, especially writers like Vonnegut, tends to discourage beginner writers because they are such masters of their craft they make it appear dead easy. So easy you think there's no way you could ever fucking come close it what they do. It's not easy. And if they had felt that way, they wouldn't be the writers they became. Writing is fucking masochistic when you get down to the nitty gritty, and the best writing will convey the exact opposite. I can't tell you the amount of times I've put down a book after reading a sentence and thought: "Well fuckit. Guess I'll be a teacher now."

After that, I'd say stick with writers that are generally praised for good writing. For masterclasses in novel writing, my top recommendations are Gravity's Rainbow by Thomas Pynchon, Heart of Darkness by Joseph Conrad, Lolita/Pnin/Pale Fire by Vladimir Nabokov, anything Dahl (seriously), Hero of a Thousand Faces by Joseph Campbell, Slaughterhouse 5 by Kurt Vonnegut, and probably many more that I can't remember right now.

OH.

And A Farewell To Arms. Hemmingway. I have a first edition and it's far and away my favourite book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 18:17:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is great advice. Also, never ask a writer to edit. I was constantly asked to help with people's papers in college. The guys never took my suggestions seriously because it assaulted their pride, the girls just fucking cried.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 18:09:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In novel writing this would apply. Depends on whether you want to go down in history or make a buck. As a reporter, you're doing it for the history. You are providing your society with a fair and accurate account of events (ideally). You have no place in deciding what the people want. I've published a few big stories in my time and they've resulted in fundamental, tangible change for the better. But you can bet your ass I was dragged through the coals for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 18:04:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely. I was a hockey goalie for a season. Lots of contact. LOTS of hate. Few things as satisfying as a sneaky slash to the back of a guy's calf as he's screening you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've found that this ESPECIALLY applies to writing on a deadline. In fact, writing on a deadline is where I learned this the most. "Don't be afraid to write a shitty lede." Chances are if you're writing on a deadline that requires such precision, you're already a good writer. So "shit" is relative. If I have to have 1800 words in quick, I disregard all thoughts of structure or my lede, parcel the story out, then arrange it in an informative and, hopefully, captivating structure. Then go through and tweak each paragraph so it has a smooth, logical flow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:50:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That never worked for me. Personally I prefer to write sober, edit stoned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes x1000000. He puts it way better than I do. I wrote a screenplay called "101 Banditos" in my teens. I shudder thinking about it. It was.... I can't. It was bad. Really bad. BUT. It was about a former slave turned bounty hunter in the wild west... Now I look at it as one of the best ideas I've ever had, just a very poorly executed one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hire an editor or bed a comp lit major. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ehhhhh. I dunno. There's A LOT of shit out there you could do with avoiding. My mother comes to mind. 

Me: "Mom, have you read 50 Shades of Grey?"

Mom: "I don't have enough time to read crap, let alone 50 shades of it."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:36:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always loved it when a team had a good striker that I knew I had to be on point for. I suppose being made to score good goals is just as challenging and rewarding as being made to make good saves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:25:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too......... How bout them Yankees? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I outline HEAVILY to avoid exactly this. I also smoke. And outlining and smoking go well together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nabokov's wife fished Lolita out of the trash. [I always defer to Ira when I hear this.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PbC4gqZGPSY)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:13:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You'd have to be a fucking moron to send something that reads like it's been written by one. The point is that you go back and make it better, ace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:10:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Precisely! When I was in advertising, my boss wouldn't allow us to present an ad unless we had literally sketched out a thousand ads before it. He'd plop a fresh stack of printer paper in front of you and tell you to have drawn an ad on every sheet by lunchtime. The point isn't to sit around and think carefully about each ad. You scribble an idea as quick as possible and move on. Once you're finished, sift through the paper, pick out the best, repeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're right. I wish that wasn't the case though. I had to read a lot of academic literature as a newspaper reporter and quickly realised I had no objective way of judging what I was reading. It was just too bogged down in a jargon I was totally unfamiliar with, and I didn't have the time to become familiarised. I think that's the problem with science and media right now. Neither industry makes much of an effort to communicate with each other in a way everyone will understand. The stuff that IS well communicated is usually the stuff scientists complain about getting stupid amounts of coverage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 16:49:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fun fact. My friend banged him in Vegas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 16:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Pretty soon, you and your audience will like what you've written, as long as you have good taste.

FTFY

Pro writing tip #2: Read good shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 16:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean dont be afraid to write poorly. Don't worry about spelling mistakes (god knows F Scott Fitzgerald didn't. His editor was a goddamn saint for transcribing his scribble into books), finnicky grammar, poor sentence structure, insufficient conveyance of an idea. If it's slowing your progress, don't worry about it and move on. The most important aspect of writing is writing. Anything that stops that pursuit should be scythed off like a wart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> LPT: When writing anything of consequence, don't be afraid to write like shit. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 15:54:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've written professionally in television, newspapers, magazines, PR, and advertising for more than a decade. My number one piece of advice to writers (and this applies to all forms of writing, whether it's a cover letter on your CV, a college essay, or a novel) is don't be afraid to write like shit. 

Worrying over whether it's "good" or not is an exercise you save until you're done. Write an awful sentence. Shit, write an awful chapter. Mark it. Go back and change it later. 

This has served me better than any other writing tip I've ever come across.

EDIT: Do not write drunk and edit sober. Hemingway didn't do that, and besides, he's fucking Hemingway.

EDIT 2: Do what you want. I'm not sure I like the front page. Tis a silly place. 

EDIT 3: I'd love to respond to all the messages for advice and feed my ego, but the sausages popping in the kitchen are more appealing right now. Everyone asking for tips on how to get into writing, there's a reason that word is a gerund. Writing is something you do. Do it. If you don't know what to write, read. Simples. Stay gold, ponyboy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 15:27:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All your mothers were seriously lax on manners. I'd get crucified for not greeting people properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 15:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, so very true, but those were the greatest compliments! I'd get a half chub if a striker refused to shake my hand after the match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 14:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As in players give keepers respect for good saves more than you might think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 13:46:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was a keeper through college. Nothing beats the satisfaction of this. Happened more than you'd expect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-18 00:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I seem to remember hearing or reading somewhere that he had a writer for these kinds of speeches. Can any confirm or deny that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 19:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's exactly how the best interviewers do it. See: Robert Durst.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 17:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The all boy's middle school I went to would suggest otherwise. Nobody is stopping you and your buddies from gathering peacefully.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 15:56:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And now single! Hiyoooooooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 15:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit. Kenny vs Spenny.... now those are two names I've not heard in a long, long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 15:52:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone rang? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 15:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a one night stand the other night and once the willy came out the girl gives me this disappointed look and says: "I was told it was bigger." 

Long story short, there's a rumour going around that I have a large penis. I don't. Really not sure how to feel about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 15:14:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well shit, that's a lot better than I usually get. Once was told I'm like an autistic Brad Pitt... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 14:38:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On YouTube, if anyone find my news presenting skills funny enough. I'm going to be a news anchor! Look out, Robin Scherbatsky! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 14:32:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow. you DO realize that hasn;t been taken away. like. at all. right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 06:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is one dedicated novelty account. Have all the upvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 06:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jib) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 06:05:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have to get it cut in a few month for my new job (I'm gonna be on the tv!) Really, really not looking forward to it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 05:56:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is fabulous, at times. Other times it's fabulously annoying. Dont get me started about driving with the windows down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 05:55:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will be the bouffant whore Reddit craves. Not because I want to. Because I have to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 04:40:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course. But again, meet anybody involved in feminism beyond online flame wars and they'll agree men need better treatment in family court. I'd refer to RBG again on this issue.

...gender discrimination is bad for everyone. It also ends the stereotype of women as givers of child care and men as solely breadwinners. [We need to] tear down those barriers so a woman or a man could pursue whatever path in life they had the G-d given talent to pursue.

Also, it's "per se" not "say" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 03:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, a little teapot. Not that short. Kinda stout.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 03:43:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fahd had just died and Abdullah was the regent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 03:10:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the cut of your jib </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 02:43:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yissssssssssss. Fuck yeah TAL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 02:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously. Can we get a source on that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 02:01:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big props to the pastor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 00:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean this in the kindest way possible, but please, try and reserve your opinions for when they are informed. I'm not from the US either, but I went to school there. One of my best friends is as gung-ho feminist as they come. She's a clinic defender, someone abortion clinics hire to help when people protest. What you see on the Internet is NOT feminists. They are people who talk about feminism. There's a big difference. Every gender studies, women studies major I've met has a firm understanding of the challenges men face and agree with me on all the standard MRA points. First wave feminism most certainly did not fix the outmoded gender stereotypes men face, just as it didn't do that for female gender stereotypes. I'd really encourage you to speak to real women who are actually on the ground doing feminist work rather than sitting on Tumblr complaining about cis male privilege.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 00:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Outmoded gender stereotypes? Have you ever met an actual feminist outside of Tumblr? RBG has done more for men in America than any other person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 00:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My asshole dad refused to go to the doctor about his heart pains and died at 41 of a heart attack. Asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 00:01:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What "right" has been taken away from you because of women? I'm genuinely curious. They are men's issues. They deserve to be discussed, absolutely, but the idea that women are leading the charge against us is retarded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 23:28:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boss would have thrown a book at me. Or whatever hard object is in his immediate vicinity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 22:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ugh. I wish I had an asshole dad. Well, any dad would be nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 20:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only when my mother is pissing me off, for some reason. Usually though I just take it out on some fish or lobster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 20:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's really discouraging to see so many male-oriented subs go the way of women bashing. Even Men's Rights. I subbed because I thought we were going to discuss issues that effect men. Nope. It's a giant bitch fest about the women they all can't get. Even RP had an initial edginess to it, like you're approaching life as a predator. Nope. Bitch fest.

Can there be a sub for guys who like talking about guy things and have no problem with the women in their lives? Because right now I really don't think that exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:50:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, that's pretty much how I react to stubbing my pinky toe. So I think mildly perturbed does it justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey. Let's not go allocating blame here. I think everyone is sorry, right? Right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anger and hatred? I'm mildly perturbed. That's all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:38:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I... I'm sorry. I got a little heated. You said some things. I said some things. Let's put it behind us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:37:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your personal experience does not equal prejudice or racism. Prejudice is literally a preconceived notion based on ignorance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EDIT: I have anger management issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 13:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What? C'mon now this is nonsense. I like the spirit of this sub. This is more RP crap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 04:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. Got detention as a kid for using it in that context. Didn't know it had an alternate meaning, so naturally the teacher wasn't too please I called him queer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 00:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's something oddly... non sexual about your pose. I have the most confused non boner. Awesome either way. 10/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 22:40:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shut up, Scott. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 18:58:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I respectfully disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 18:20:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah. So, like DBZ GT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 18:11:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, yes it is. Well done. And this is all from his wife, who has relayed it back to her uncle (my step dad) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 17:55:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh... Well I feel dumb. I thought the Star Wars stories went on, and these are just putting them into film form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 17:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I got the chance. They were supposed to come stay with us a few times now, but each time they cancelled because of filming etc.

From what I've heard, Adam starts out good, then turns bad, then becomes a Sith (I love Star Wars, just not that informed about it). Is that Kylo Ren's character arch?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 17:02:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just sharing what I heard. It's the talk of the whole company, obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 16:29:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 14:18:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm very curious to know how OP here has a pristine single page with an internet warning from the 90's... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 18:19:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not saying a lower rate is a magic wand. I'd imagine you could marry a number of policies with it to incentivise companies into coming back to America, though. It's a pretty big subject for us in Bermuda, being a tax haven, and everyone's asshole gets a bit tighter around election time and we wonder what it would take for us to no longer be an attractive jurisdiction. And frankly, I don't think it would take much. Companies are far from peachy here. The IB environment has only just gotten friendly again after the ousting of the Progressive Labour Party in 2012, so we're seeing an uptick in new company registrations, but honestly myself and others really don't think it would take a whole lot to sink our economy and start floating yours. Take that as you will, I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 16:39:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's nothing illegal about re-domiciling. That's why it's called a loophole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 15:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just the opinion of a guy living in the country where all your businesses domicile to avoid taxes, but I happen to think lowering the corporate tax rate would be the best way to start reeling in that lost tax revenue. They talk about closing the tax loopholes every election cycle and never do. Seems to me a good way to keep American companies paying taxes in America is to give them less reasons to domicile overseas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 15:28:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Colby 2012 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 15:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking prick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 05:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, well, coming from an island that is 21 square miles long and in the middle of the ocean, I was unaware of such things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 05:38:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer my women to be conscious when I disappoint them, thankyouverymuch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIFU by picking up a drugged girl in a slutty nurse outfit off the bathroom floor and taking her home safe and sound. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-11 14:55:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was Halloween at Western University in London, Ontario, and my friends and I were hitting up an amazing burger join just outside of the bar we'd been drinking at. 

I go for a piss after ordering my food and find an apparently very drunk girl lying on the bathroom floor. I sit her up and try to get her talking, but all she keeps saying is "I hardly had anything to drink." She's pretty much incapacitated.

So I help her to her feet and get her out of the bathroom and sit her down at a table, then return to my friends and ask them what I should do. The logical choice was to help her into a cab, so I helped her back up again, walked to the street corner with her, and flagged down a cab.

Cab comes, but the girl is too far gone to even remotely remember where she lives and the cabbie refuses to take her. She manages to communicate to me that her house is on the road we're standing on and that she can point it out, but the cab driver still refuses to take her alone. 

A bit pissed, I get in the cab with her. She starts slurring about how she barely drank anything again, and then starts trying to kiss me, at which point it clicks that she's probably been drugged. I push her off me and she tells the cab driver to stop and that her house is right here. Cab pulls over, I go to pay him, and she bolts from the door and begins running down the sidewalk. "Ok awesome," I think. "I did my best." Nope. She stumbles and face-plants right into the concrete.

So I pick her ass up again, pretty frustrated with the whole situation at this point. She's bleeding from her forehead and yammering incoherently, but says her house is "right there." We get to the door and there's a party still going on inside. Her housemate answers the door, I tell him I "found her like this" and she fucking belts: "HE ROOFIED ME." Housemate clocks me in the nose before I can respond, sending me down the flight of stairs leading up to the door. Bang my head on the concrete. Housemate kicks me in the stomach, lays on a few more punches, and leaves me there.

Now drunk, concussed and bleeding from my nose, I make my way back to my res, find my resident advisor and go to the hospital.

I've never hated a slutty nurse so much in my goddamn life.

EDIT: Shout out to Western. You may remember me as the guy who ran around Saugeen with a boner, or that guy who unwittingly punched the stripper at the Beef Baron. Go Stangs.

EDIT 2: Ya'll motherfuckers need Jesus. Where I'm from, we help people in need of help. Yes it was dumb to get in the cab. GEE, THANKS. I know I fucked up. That's why you're reading this, turdblossom. 

EDIT 3. Dear god... If you're a personal injury lawyer, I don't care. Go chase an ambulance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How much responsibility can William Randolph Hearst and Joseph Pulitzer REALLY take for starting the Spanish American War? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 15:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was the effect of 'yellow journalism' such that it truly convinced a nation -- that valued freedom above all else -- that they were justified in taking freedom away from others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Used my SO's "volumising" shampoo. Figured it was a marketing gimmick. I stand corrected. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-26 14:47:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the Japanese soldier in the season 6 premier existed in real life. Hiroo Onoda carried out his orders for almost 30 years after being given them in 1945. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 19:14:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dadjoked by a lawyer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-11 16:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Court reporter here. Was speaking with a lawyer and he was telling me about the time he had to represent someone accused of having sex with a horse. "Did anyone ask why THAT horse, instead of any of the others?" I asked.

"Actually yes," replied the lawyer. "He wanted a stable relationship." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jesus vs  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 21:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ber intense security agent chokes out a topless female protester. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-30 16:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My half brother and step-dad are both photographers. They decided to have a little fun out in Arizona. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-24 18:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Got fired. Had last, very petty laugh. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had an argument with my boss one morning. Was working in broadcast journalism and had set up a series of interviews with politicians to respond to a major story that broke over night. Except that those interviews I set up were being handed to someone else and instead she told me I had to go and talk to orphans and ask them how the economy was effecting them. I laughed, and said "No, Gary can do the orphan story, I'll do MY story, thankyouverymuch." At which point she launched into a tirade, belittling me and basically speaking to me like she was my mother. This has happened a bunch of times. I hung up and texted her. "Please don't speak to me like that again or I will have to quit." I got an immediate response: "Your fired." I was gutted. But as I looked at my phone again, a wry smile creeped across my face and my thumbs went into action....

*you'RE

We haven't spoken since.

**EDIT:** I suppose I should add that I was at my wick's end (EDIT EDIT: FINE. "WITS' END" YOU GLORIOUS PEDANTS) with the company and her as my editor. She was extremely unprofessional. What made this argument special was that she constantly told me I was not delivering enough stories of my own, that she was setting up too many interview for me. Naturally once I start doing this, she hands the best interviews of the day, set up by yours truly, to the chief reporter-- who has stopped talking to me after she handed one of HIS interviews to ME-- and sends me to do some filler about the economy. She was eventually fired and I have since been offered my job back. Twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Of all the weird pub names, not a single one is called the Go Go Gadget Arms... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:12:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the Bermuda Triangle mystery is nothing more than the result of bad/sensational journalism. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-02 13:40:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What do you do when your new cancer treatment kills all the melanin in your hair? Meet my hero and best friend, Captain White Beard. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-24 16:07:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What do you do when your new cancer treatment kills all the melanin in your hair? Meet my hero and best friend, Captain White Beard. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-24 16:06:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why do men have to hide their erections? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-10-10 17:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Frankly I think us men should no longer hide our erections in public. For too long now our erections have been oppressed by belt buckles and between our thighs, hurriedly tucked away lest anyone sees. Man will not truly be free until he can be proud of his erection, not ashamed and embarrassed! We get them all the time, for many reasons besides arousal. If a 'liberated' woman can walk around with hard nipples reading 50 Shades of Shit, why can't I walk around with a hard penis? I envision a new era, where penises are not judged by size or breadth or stamina, but valued as utilitarian assets-- a world where, when I get a boner on the train, I can stand with my erection proudly as a free man... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>