<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5680</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Music training in the teenage years may improve the teenage brain's responses to sound and sharpen hearing and language skills </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:19:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> University of Michigan opens test "city" for autonomous cars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:17:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Agriculture's next frontier? Growing plants in space </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 11:30:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 02:04:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It worked! Thank you so much :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:55:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't even listen to Beats 1. It just says contacting store and then nothing happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 00:47:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah that's the proof
Sorry Looks like I forgot to link it.
Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> voat's global website rank jumps 45,000 ranks in about one day </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:14:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 14:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a pledge by Queensland state government which is the labor government </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Queensland government (Australian State) pledges to reach 50% renewable energy by 2030 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 12:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 14:14:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. I have it installed on my PC and it runs every time I turn it on. It's very unobtrusive and you don't have to do anything. I'm just glad my spare processing power is going to contribute to making a difference instead of going to waste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 00:35:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know a great way to help.
[World Community Grid](https://secure.worldcommunitygrid.org) allows you to contribute your spare processing power on your computer or android device to contribute to scientific research.
Basically, millions of small data based computer tasks are sent out to volunteer devices. When the devices are done with the specific tasks, it gathers the data and sends them back to the researchers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Painless vaccine patches are set to begin clinical trails in 2017 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 09:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 15:10:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, it is Tony Abbott sadly.
Also, the chances of this happening under is leadership is basically zero. This government just [funded $4million to a climate change skeptic's think tank] (http://www.theguardian.com/environment/planet-oz/2015/apr/23/australia-paying-4-million-for-bjrn-lomborgs-flawed-methods-that-downgrade-climate-change) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 11:18:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. The article is exciting, but also kind of sad that we have such big potential, but the government just doesn't care. Hopefully, next election we'll have another government that will take action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 13:09:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. The article is exciting, but also kind of sad that we have such big potential, but the government just doesn't care.
Hopefully, next election we'll have another Prime Minister that will take action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Australia could have zero emissions and 100% renewable energy by 2050, new study finds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 12:14:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 13:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try Earn Honey. You can leave videos running there to earn money (just like PerkTV)
[Referral Link](http://www.earnhoney.com/home/?referrer=UqHtXaud) |
[Non Referral](http://www.earnhoney.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 12:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not that I know of, but it doesn't use much extra power anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Great way to think (x-post from r/yoga) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 12:27:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 13:14:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His real name is Alex Romano. I love how he got into character for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New Ebola vaccine provokes immune response in human clinical trials </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 08:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Costa Rica powered with 100% renewable energy for 75 straight days </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 09:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Well now that I think about it... ( cyanide and happiness) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-23 09:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Australian Newsreaders fight to the death- Anchorman Style </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 23:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> BEST BREAKING BAD SUPERCUT </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 23:31:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Were you lying then, are you lying now, or are you just a chronic and habitual liar" - Jason Clare, MP, slams the Tony Abbott for broken promises </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 10:00:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>