<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4010</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Star Trek Into Romance </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:52:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:19:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! Don't worry though - I'm totally with everyone on the annoying mouth sounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's certainly a logic to that, and it sounds like JJ's actual reasoning too (I quote him from the Star Trek director's commentary on this in the video). 

The danger that comes with filming it like this, is that you're going against a century of 'action' filmmaking - a cinema language that's developed with and for the audiences ability to read the onscreen action. Going off that path could be more likely to frustrate the audience by making it harder to watch then the more traditional approach.

As for gritty action films - MI3 is about as gritty as he's gotten and he did seem to do well with the action in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:22:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I actually have a bone disorder that has altered the bones in my skull, making them encroach on my nasal passage and vision. There's not that much I can do about the nasalness or the pitch, and little I can do about the mumbling. It's complicated is what Im saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aussie with an American father, though I did live in the states for a couple of years while learning to talk. Half my family sounds either or American or Australian, but only one of the 6 of us are actually born there.

As for the the topic - maybe a shorter video on how Brad Bird injects charm into his work. Another idea is a video covering the works of cinematographers Christopher Doyle, Conrad L. Hall and maybe Roger Deakins. The final idea I'm also keen on is spatial clarity in action sequences - comparing directors like Nolan to guys like Johnnie To. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:54:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I appreciate that. Unfortunately, I had cheekbone and jaw surgery last week and it's left me unable to talk properly. It'll probably remain that way for another month or so as I recover, and I didn't want to this wait on a shelf for a month. I'm trying to develop a flow of getting a video out every 4-6 weeks, and I didn't think that would help it.

Anyway, thanks for checking it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:38:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah i was having surgery the next day and really rushed through fixing that stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "A Touch Of Sin" and "Animal Kingdom" are both like that. 

More so "A Touch Of Sin" simply because it has much more violence. It's on Netflix and it's pretty great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was very well done, though i thought it could've ended a few minutes before it did. I think about 10 or so. I also liked it's production design. If it weren't for that clam-shell e-reader (What's the meaning behind that?) I would've sworn it was set in the 80's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Video essay - Star Wars: The Force of Abrams </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 05:12:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was gonna say either Wake in Fright or Mad Max: The Road Warrior, but then I remembered - oh yeah - Mad Max: Fury Road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, but look at the opening of District 9. That's also in a mockumentary style and that looks great, not just because of the set design but also due to the cinematography.

Better yet, look at Veep. Also by the same writers and creator. Great cinematography, identical style. I just think In The Loop has bad cinematography. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In The Loop has pretty pedestrian cinematography, but that film is all about its script. And that was one fucking great script. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a good article. Although one point I'd like to add is that George Miller, John Seale and Margaret Sixel storyboarded, shot and edited the film to achieve total spatial clarity in Fury Road's action sequences. Whereas spatial clarity in Ultron seems like more of an afterthought to the dialogue and character development Joss Whedon was focusing on. Like it was something that could be done almost solely in post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:50:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sinister has moments of genuine cleverness  - like the premise, and some of the 'films' you see. The lawnmower one for example.

It just fails to really capitalise on it's own potential. Both scare-wise, but especially thematically.

Great horror films play on people's insecurities and fears truly well. 'The Thing' revolves around paranoia and trusting others. 'Cure' - a Japanese thriller/horror I can't recommend enough - does the same and also makes the viewer believe even they might be capable of terrible things and not know it. 'The Exorcist' plays on a parents fear of helplessness in the face of physical/mental illness as well as ones doubts of faith in God or the nature of the world. There's probably even more than that - it's a heck of a film and it's been a while since I watched it.

All of those fears/insecurities are enough to make people stay up at night just on their own. This is a big part of what makes the characters struggles in horror films so relatable - even though none of us will experience anything they go through.

'Sinister' toys with the notion of the main characters ego getting infront of his families safety, but it does little with it.

Take 'The Babadook' -a recent Australian horror film that's on Netflix and has received massive critical acclaim (86 on Metacritic, 98 on Rotten Tomatoes, took home best film and direction at the Aussie equivalent of the Oscars). The Babadook totally drives home it's themes. Without giving anything away, it's almost impossible to come out of the film and not understand what The Babadook was 'really' about. Hence, it ended up resonating with a lot of people in ways I haven't seen Sinister resonate with anyone.

I feel like that's the reason Sinister won't be remembered as anything more than a pretty good idea, that didn't pan out like it may have deserved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 15:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was great. Thanks for sharing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 15:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wake in Fright is absolutely fantastic and everybody should see that film. 

It's got one of my favourite moments of sound design, where there's nothing but the rumble of the engine as the party is driving back home after the kangaroo hunt.

Just fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 12:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got a lot of respect for Robert Rodriguez. His work ethic and his skills across multiple areas of filmmaking are just... I mean, a guy who writes, directs, edits, produces, scores and even helps with the visual fx on his films. That's a lot of passion and love for his craft right there.

Just look at his credits on imdb for his own films. Nuts.

http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0001675/?ref_=nv_sr_1

Edit: AND lights them too. A guy who totally deserves the title of maverick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 18:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out this VFX breakdown of [Gone Girl.] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yvwS_E91fZA) Lots of great stuff in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 17:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to like Armagaeddon. I watched it again recently and ah... yeah I don't like Armagaeddon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 12:20:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This scene in Little Children is always a gut-punch.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zm7-Lg0kWfk)
Especially impressive given the context </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Directing - The Fine Arts of Blocking and Composition </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 12:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>