<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4000</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:41:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know this came out 24 years ago but I think it still applies, 1991's Career Opportunities. A nice little comedy i just saw on tv the other day starring Jennifer Connelly and Frank whaley, and written by John Hughes. Reception seems mixed to the film, but being someone who grew up watching John Hughes on vhs and dvd I'm surprised I never heard of this one because to me it's a good film. Not as good as something like Ferris Bueller but I'd still recommend a watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:33:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only way I can agree with that headline is if "hungry for more" is followed by "new games".  I just don't see how an improved framerate and resolution warrants excitement for a game that came out almost six years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:20:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like a rant than a review, and that's surprising since moviebob loves to complain about the videos of people like Razorfist yet he's doing the samething here abet with forced amounts of swear words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An in-depth interview of director John Carpenter (The Thing, Big trouble in Little China, They Live, ect.) by Robert Rodriguez. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:30:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think he's talking about the courtyard Smith fight scene In Reloaded, not the ending to Revolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:27:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Terrible reviews? It seems to have gotten critical acclaim... if that means anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:49:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel you, man. I just watched the new Terminator the other week with my dad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:47:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did that movie have such a big budget? I'll let the guys at [RedLetterMedia offer a reasonable theory.](https://youtu.be/fTOL-Ph5SQM?t=101) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:42:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have a good point, Columbus knows what's he's doing. I think it's just my bias against Sandler speaking. But who knows, maybe the film  will meet the production value of its budget. We'll just have to wait and see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:37:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I doubt a majority of that 110 million is actually going towards the movie. I say that because Jack and Jill had a **$80M** budget, and that film looks nowhere close to that figure. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They exist in the same franchise don't they? If not sequel then a successor I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's your favorite movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:12:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A part of me thinks they're talking about Sega just having the licensing rights to Alien video games, but I don't know legal jargon so I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me it's the Greasers theme. If I ever make a movie I'm gonna have a barroom brawl scene with that music. I love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:03:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's because Ubisoft delivered an inferior game than what they promoted. Bugs, downgrades, a story that's so meaningless that one of the "story" missions serves no purpose other than to introduce the multiplayer features of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:58:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know they've said this times before, but it's been almost ten years since Bully came out. I want another one. I know everyone wants another Red Dead. But Bully came first, and I think they should work on that. Ten years, man. I first played it in elementary school, and now I'm in college. I mean I know it's been five since Red Dead came out, but the gap between Revolver and Redemption was only like six years. I think the world can wait a little longer for some western action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 11:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are there really no challenge maps? And you can't play as the side/dlc characters outside their short missions? If so then wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 08:40:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well there was a Batman vs Spawn comic, that's the closest he's got to fighting the Devil/or a demon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Resident Evil 6/Lfd2/Borderlands 2/Payday 2] 18M/PST [Any voice chat option] Looking for some pals to have fun with. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 13:09:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi everybody, I'm looking for some people to play games with. My choices aren't limited to the games listed above, I just put down those four because they're the ones I'm most interested in. Here's a [link to my profile](https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198016939364). I hope to hear from you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is this being downvoted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:26:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Prince of Darkness isn't on par with in The Mouth of Madness, but still give it a watch. You should also check out Christine, John Carpenter did an awesome job with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:48:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know it's the first time, it's just that this time it felt awkward. Well atleast for me it felt awkward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:47:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We didn't need to see that scene because the story was about Furiosa and the wive's escape.

Ah okay, I see what you mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 06:10:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright, I seen the movie twice now and I'm still digging it. The only thing that stood out to me was after Max kills the blind warlord. After Max kills him and the rest of the party continue through the area it cuts to black. I'm bringing this up because it felt unnatural, like they cut out a scene. Did anyone else notice this? To be more precise it's exactly after you see those guys dressed like crows walking around on pogo sticks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For Lynch I would say Blue Velvet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rear Window? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:34:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hm... I'm conflicted, but I say T2? My second choice would be Aliens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright, Ima' say 300?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:29:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big Trouble In little China? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:28:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Batman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:28:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Barry Lyndon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watchmen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:26:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stanley Kubrick, 18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 13:13:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a big fan of the Breakfast Club I could actually see this working. Nice choices </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 16:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> * Akira 
* Who Framed Roger Rabbit
* Big Trouble in Little China
* Raiders of the Lost Ark
* Aliens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 14:19:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no problem, man. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 14:12:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... I didn't ask you a second time, some other guy did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 14:07:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 
Shakira

A Colombian singer gains psychic powers, destroys part of a city, and turns into a giant baby-fetus before causing her own Big Bang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 13:57:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2008's Alone in the Dark. The gameplay is kinda clunky, the voice acting and characters are not that great, and the story is cliche. But I love it because the game itself is fun to play. The inventory system is unique because you can combine all sorts of different items your guy is carrying with you and the game's set pieces are exciting. It's like a B movie if it was given the budget of a major blockbuster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 13:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you feel was over explained in Memento? I'm just curious that's all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 05:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> AHH! He got me again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [H] 3 tf2 keys [W] Payday 2 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-26 09:03:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-24 15:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fatal Attraction, with Michael Douglas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 08:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like I told OP I just posted a Shadowrun lfg on the sub and was wondering if you're interested as well. Here's a link to it http://redd.it/2n5ezn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 08:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi I just posted a Shadowrun lfg on the sub and was wondering if you're interested. Here's a link http://redd.it/2n5ezn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 06:42:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi i sent you a message a while ago to let you know I'm interested in playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [H] 2 TF2 keys [W] Kane   Lynch 2: Dog Days </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-12 01:24:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi guys, i'm looking for a copy of kane and lynch 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-18 10:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well the PC 2k sports game's have always been just a port of the console ones. What he's saying is that unlike last year we'll receive a port of the PS4/Xbone version instead of 360/PS3 version. I wish it wasn't just a straight port, but it's the most we are gonna get...

[here's a comparison of the visuals from last-gen to current-gen](http://unrealitymag.bcmediagroup.netdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/1381773388-media.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-05 05:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know Big Trouble is my favorite movie and I really tried to get into this comic, but it just doesn't feel right. They constantly have Jack shouting catchphrases trying to mimic the movie and to me it just feels... forced. And all the humor and jokes make the book sound like it's trying to be a parody of the movie instead of an actual sequel. Like look at the last page in the link, Jack's talk about that Kansas burger joint. It just feels like they watched the movie and was like "Jack Burton is an everyman who likes to make wise-cracks and catchphrases so let's just have him constantly do that. The readers will love it!"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 06:21:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe. It said that the Arkham Knight is as skilled as Batman and has his own army, and that army could be the League of Shadows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-23 04:15:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm excited we'll finally hear about Jason in the Arkham series. It was just something I felt wasn't touched upon at all in the previous ones. 

I think his design is alright. I prefer the comic version with his helmet. But I'm betting they have it as an alternate skin.

I also wonder if they'll have a third character. I know Origins only had 2, but that was a different developer, and City had three. If they do I bet it'll be Damian. With (Arkham City spoiler) [](#s "Talia and Ra's al Ghul dead") I think now would be a good time to have Damian introduced. It follow a similar pattern as the playable characters in City: Catwoman=Harley, Dick=Jason, Tim=Damian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-11 17:44:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you, have a nice day :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-10 02:35:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be willing to play with you if we have games in common, I'll PM you my steam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-30 10:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem, just helping out :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-30 09:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_rU04rsImtM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-28 07:57:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've only read the first 15 issues of All-New X-men but I'm loving it so far, so yeah check it out if you can. I also recommend checking out All-New X-Factor and Amazing X-Men. I'm liking both of those so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-17 02:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn min-maxers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-14 23:44:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VGy9zTDefvg Jiffy! 2:05:48-2:05:50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-10 05:29:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basically it's where they send the people who ditch all the time and never do their work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-09 20:41:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah they don't sell sodas. But things like ice-tea and coffee are sold. Coffee during zero period and ice tea at lunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-09 20:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where I'm from there's a continuation school based out of the mall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-29 05:55:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It helps to mention what game you're playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-29 05:25:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was around 15 or 16 when he first went to the camps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-22 07:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice. I'm thinking of setting up a Mass Effect game too so now I might get this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 08:16:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First I need to ask, Why are they going after the bad guy? Are they getting payed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 08:00:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While I don't have experience with the game you're playing, I do have a little bit of GM experience.

1. Don't freak out if things don't go according to your plan. There's four of them and only one of you, so expect to be outwitted sometimes.

2. Plan ahead. Keep some spare encounters on the side just in case something happens. It takes a little bit of the fun away when you have to prepare encounters in the middle of a game.

3. Improvise. There's been times when my players have had lucky rolls that flipped my entire encounter around. You just have to go with the flow and react accordingly.

4. If you or the players aren't 100% sure about a rule don't waste time going through the rulebook. You're the GM, you decide what the ruling should be at that moment.

5. Don't give your players too much slack. There's no fun in a game you can't lose.

6. Just Have Fun. It is a game after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-15 06:24:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy crap! I always thought of the idea of making a Warriors Rpg too! Having the players play different classes like scout (Fox), tagger (Rembrandt), and muscle (Ajax). If you ever have a playable version post it here Because I would love to try it out :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Online] LFP Star Wars Edge of the Empire New-ish GM looking for 2 players to join a group of 2 on Fridays PST (GMT -8) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-04 00:06:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, My name is Ryan and i'm looking for 2 players to join this game I'm starting on Fridays at 4:30pm PST. I'm still a beginning GM so bear with me as I learn to play the system. I'm looking for new or inexperienced players, but experienced players are welcome if you don't mind playing with newbies. So send me a message telling me a little about yourself , why you'd be a valuable member of our group, and your Skype name so we can talk more. Thanks and have a wonderful day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-02 04:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm, you're a little late to the party :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-01 22:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you'd have a better time over at /r/rpg, but that's just my opinion :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-01 15:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely yes, and at this price it's a steal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-25 01:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For Jedi Knight: Jedi Academy, make sure you check out the [Knights of the Force expansion mod](http://kotf.com/main.htm). It adds a whole lot of stuff to the game and it's fun as hell to play with. Here's the list of features on the website.

KotF includes 100 new Star Wars characters, 150 skins, 70 lightsabers, 40 vehicles, 50 new stages, 130 NPCs, around 40 new and upgraded menus, 70 multiplayer maps and extraordinary CD menu. All these new features are in 2 GB and KotF requires 3.5 GB space on your hard disk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-24 09:41:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This could work better if you replied :p

Yeah I was confirming with you that those days would work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-24 09:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can only do Mondays and Tuesdays after 4pm PST. That's about 6pm your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-24 09:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm currently the GM of 1 going on 2 games and I'm dying to play, my only question is what day and what time would we be playing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 08:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no problem :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-23 08:22:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What game are you talking about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-22 06:13:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes you can buy ranks in the skills as if they were trained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-19 03:25:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes you can :)

Hey I remember you from my [Lfg post](http://www.reddit.com/r/lfg/comments/1xn44v/online_star_wars_edge_of_the_empire_new_gm/) last week. Did you ever find a group that fit your schedule? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-13 02:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey man, I got your message. Are you sure you can't do Thursdays? I changed the listing to Thursday's because I'm now occupied for the the other days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Online] (Star Wars Edge of the Empire) New GM looking for three players. PST (GMT -8) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-11 21:19:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, my name is Ryan. This is my first time GMing an rpg. I'm looking for new or inexperienced players, but veterans are welcome if you're willing to be friendly and patient with new players. For schedule I'm thinking weekly games on Thursday. Games would be about 4:30pm PST. Session time I guess would be a few hours, I have yet to try the system so I'm not sure. If you're interested send me a message with a way I can talk to you (preferably Skype) so we can discuss things and I can get to know you.
Thanks for clicking and have a nice day/evening. 

Edit: I changed the game date to Thursdays. As of now I'm just not able to do it any other day.

Edit 2: Party's full. Thanks for the help guys :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-11 01:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He didn't, he was the property of Princess Leia. She just gave him orders to find Obi-Wan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-10 04:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure. Could you message me some kind of contact info so we could talk more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-09 09:27:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! If I don't get any hits on this I might just GM one myself. I've never done it before, but there's a first for everything :). And if I do do that you'd be welcome to join. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Online] LFG, Star Wars Edge of The Empire. Fridays and/or Sundays PST(GMT -8) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-09 07:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello! I'm looking to be part of a Star Wars game. I've played a couple of sessions of 3.5 and Pathfinder so I'm not new to Rpgs, just this one. I have yet to try out the game but I understand the dice system and the character creation (apart from the obligation point system. I need someone to help explain that to me.) For Fridays I can anywhere from 4:30pm PST to late into the night. Sundays I can go from 1:00pm to 7. So post a comment or send a message if you'd be interested in having me. Thanks for the consideration and have a wonderful day/evening.

Edit 1: Friday is filled. Sunday is still open :). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-08 12:54:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-06 04:12:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alrighty, I'll send a message on skype. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-06 04:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I could do that. Could you message me some contact info so we can go into more detail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Online] LFG Pathfinder. Fridays, Saturdays, or Sundays (PST, GMT -8) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 11:23:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello! I'm currently looking to join a weekend Pathfinder group. I've never played Pathfinder before, but I have played a few sessions of 3.5 so I believe I have the basics down. I'm open to playing any role that I'd be needed in (I don't have much experience with magic but I'm willing to learn). I'd say anytime after 4:30pm PST works best for me, and for Fridays and Saturdays I can go late into the night (I usually stay up past dawn so if you guys are operating in Europe or Asia I can be available). So just comment or message your information, and thanks for the consideration.

Edit 1: For Saturdays I'm available from 12pm PST to whenever, if that helps :)

Edit 2: Alright so it looks like I've found some groups, so unless anything happens with them I think this post is done. Thanks for the help everybody :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 00:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> child PCs? You've had someone really roll up a kid to go adventuring?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-31 00:44:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They got rid of their entire history... Dick Grayson was never a Titan, Beast Boy was never a titan, and neither were Raven, Cyborg, or Starfire. In the New 52 the Teen Titans are a newly established group.

...Also Beast Boy is now red instead of green. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-30 09:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They wanted a fresh start. But while the New 52 does have a lot of good things going for it, there's a whole lot of bad decisions like this. Don't get me started on the things they did to the Teen Titans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-30 08:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes they abandoned his Origin story of trying to find a cure for his sick wife. In the New 52 he never met his wife Nora. Instead she's just a sick women in cryostasis that Mr. Freeze became obsessed with while working at Wayne Enterprise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-27 03:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old are you?


What's the most expensive thing you've stolen?


Tell me about your fence, the guy you sell your stolen goods too.


Why are you a thief?




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-24 08:42:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man I love that gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-18 08:39:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a few B horror movies

Dude, she starred in Halloween 4 and 5! :p 

But you're right, she is fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-15 09:30:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old were your victims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-15 09:30:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did you kill your victims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-15 07:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And to think I pay these people a thousand dollars in premiums!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 07:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would't say Jack is a Redneck; he's more of a cowboy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 07:51:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Carpenter said the film bombed because of bad marketing on the studio's part :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 05:27:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Her mind and spirit must be goin' north and south. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-01 18:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is gonna take cracker-jack timing, Wang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-30 14:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should only worry if you haven't paid your dues, Jack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-30 07:34:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You press 'caps lock' to speak. You should she a little microphone icon pop-up in the lower left corner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-26 16:33:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol, everyone thinks my name is from Naruto. I just like killerbees... :p

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-26 11:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To me this is when the series started to become great. Don't get me wrong, the 1st season wasn't bad, it's just surpassed by all the other ones. Plus I freakin' love Mr. Turner; I was sad when he left the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-26 10:42:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's Humans. I think you're thinking of the place you grew up in.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-26 05:54:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no, no, no [Spoiler](/s "kids do talk like that, I'm in High School now and kids talk about the same things in the same way and act the same [besides the assaulting part :p] I just didn't really see the kids in the story progress into madness. I mean you had the pencil scene, the girl talking about her first time, and the fight... holy shit, you did see them go crazy overtime.  Now I believe the ending.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-25 10:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Rage, but to me the ending is just... off. [Spoiler](/s "The kids all assult Ted, and that just seemed weird. But hey, it's memorable.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-25 00:52:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> have you paid your dues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-24 12:44:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> come on man! I'll admit High Life isn't the best song, but beneath Night Vision? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-24 10:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothin' or double </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-22 12:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> May I ask what fanfic? it sounds familiar to one of my favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-10 08:09:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP should quit being a wussy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-29 22:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah but have to realize those remakes were 2D. I can see turning [this](http://ps3maven.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/06/final-fantasy-iv-super-nintendo-snes-064.jpg) into [this](http://i.imgur.com/vdCcz.jpg?1), but [this](http://snackedup.files.wordpress.com/2012/09/final-fantasy-7-cloud-model-up-close.png)? With something like  FF7 which is in 3D they would have to create new character models, create all-new non-prerendered backgrounds, and new animations to match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-29 01:46:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they should bring back the battle system from 10; It was so good I can't believe they took it out of 10-2. But make the battle party 4 people instead of 3 and set the game in a setting like IX. That's how i think Square can make a comeback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 10:48:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bad, I meant 15 not 14 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 09:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why its take on the "rag-tag group of rebels fights evil empire" cliche is so special

I think it's because at the time that type story wasn't cliche yet. Besides Star Wars i can't really think of another example like it. Also at the time, and I emphasis time, this was still a new idea. It's like Citizen Kane. If you compare it to modern day movies most would say it's average. But you need to realize when it came out no one told stories in a flashback/interview way like it did, no one did make-up like it did, and no one used that style of cinematography (with it's use of deep focus lens and low-angle shots). 

In FF6 we had a large group of at least 14 main characters with their own personalities and we would switch to different parties at certain parts of the game. No one did that, at the time. 

So I'm saying If you compare it to the later entires like FF7 it's not going to like look a masterpiece. But if you dial back the clock and look at what came out before it and around it, the game is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 07:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was goin' good in the beginning... but they had to do the drop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 06:53:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  "annoying FF7 fans" that never actually appear...

Yes they do appear and I think that's whats making people mad. Don't get me wrong I love FF7, but ever since the PS3 tech demo came out people have begging for a remake. I want a remake too, especially for the rest of the PS1 Final Fantasy's. But it's not gonna happen. Square is no longer Square Soft, it's Square Enix. And since the merger things haven't been looking up for the series. They can barely develop the games they're already working on, aka Versus 13/XV.

So yes those fans do appear. And it's not that people think the game is overrated, it's just that people are tired of hearing people beg for a remake.

*edit 1

I meant to say 'XV' not 'XIV'
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-27 21:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the vid :). At first I wasn't too fond of Oliver but he's grown on me, especially when he took over the Daily Show over the summer. I heard he might get his own show so that's good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-27 20:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was hoping XV would go back to roots like IX did. IX is my favorite game in the series and that's because, like you said, final fantasy works best in a setting without ultra-futuristic technology. It can work with that setting, but not at it's best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-27 20:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're right there was nothing memorable. For example in most of the other Final Fantasy's we were given a, I don't know how else to say this, memorable villain. In 13 we were given fal'Cie and even after playing the game I still don't know if they're good guys, bad guys, or just guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If history was a TV show what would be a running joke? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-27 13:46:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-07 05:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> original DragonBall or Z?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-07 03:41:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What did you think of the new remake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-07 03:37:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy Cake-day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-07 03:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy Birthday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-07 03:34:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Big Trouble in Little China](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0HEitZ06oRY), an awesome 80's movie that's nonstop fun (seriously there's like no boring parts) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 02:46:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Growing up. I know I'm 16 and that's considered an adult in some places, but I just like being and want to stay a kid. That's why I need to become Peter Pan, so I can stay young forever :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 02:43:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A jumped-up pantry boy, Who never knew his place :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 02:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would go out tonight, but I haven't got a stitch to wear 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 02:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/AmPUHgu.jpg?1

found this a while ago and really liked it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 10:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 10:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I first read it I really liked it and I still do. But after rereading over the past couple of years I just feel really sorry for Holden. That's because if you really get down to it he's lazy and cynical to the world around him, and it's saddening knowing he lives with that mindset. That's while I don't understand why he's such an ideal. I'm not saying he's a bad character, I'm saying he shouldn't be looked at as someone you inspire to be or put on a pedestal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 01:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't give up on skateboarding. I just started doing it the past couple of weeks and it's hella fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 01:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit! AP calc! What did you take in middle school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 01:20:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In 7th grade during my third day of woodshop my teacher pulled me infront the class to try out one of the machines. I actually cut the line he drew pretty straight and felt pretty good. My friend said I was shaking the entire time until i sat back down.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 01:09:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would go out tonight, But I haven't got a stitch to wear  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 00:56:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It makes you feel really good. I've always thought people exaggerated the effects but the first time I got high it was really fun. I don't get high regularly though. So if you still want to know why it's 'celebrated' so much, I don't know what else to say but try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-05 00:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I visited my sister in Shanghai last year and went to an Elton John concert. It wasn't that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 13:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well if it helps i woke up at about 4 in the afternoon, so i don't need *that* much sleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 13:44:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im about to go to bed. Gotta wake up in 3 hours :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 11:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol thanks, that give my night a little boost. Now I must buzz off and do some PreCal homework :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 11:35:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem :). If I came off negatively I didn't mean to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-03 14:54:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/tipofmytongue/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-31 07:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last November I went to visit some family in Shanghai. And I got to tell you that when you're walking down these crowded streets in the middle of a freezing downpour with neon lights flashing all around you, you forgot you're in the present: it feels like your in the middle of a Cyberpunk adventure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-30 05:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only thing that comes to my mind is Knights of the Old Republic. I know it's a comicbook and not a book, but I really enjoyed it and would recommend it. The only problem with it is that near the last couple of issues the story gets jumbled a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-30 07:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did your family respond to you voluntering for this experiment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-02 09:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The cover system in Max Payne 3 was much better than the one in GTAIV and since the shooting in V looks like the one Max Payne i'm guessing they're are using the same cover system too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-22 02:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I thought it was Franklin at first because of the clothes he had on. But since the bar in the lower right is blue I guess it was Michael in the bike race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-21 13:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If that since the game is split between 3 protagonists, there won't be a large amount of missions for each of them. I know there is a shit load of stuff to do outside of missions, but I would be disappointed if they all have small campaigns that just add up together to match the previous games. Also I hope they bring back checkpoints and mission replays from Ballad of Gay Tony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-21 13:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably Franklin, because in the trailers he's mostly seen as being the athletic one with the cycling, parashooting, and dirtbiking. I never really feel in love with CJ or his gangster story, but Franklin and his story to me seems interesting. Also I love driving and its been shown that he's the best one at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-18 08:48:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Kingdom Hearts 1 I agree that they were bad and I think a waste of time, but in Kingdom Hearts 2 I felt that they became pretty fun (especially that "death star" one that lead to twilight town).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 21:50:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While I do like the look of the multiplayer, I'm mainly wondering if this means Robin will also be playable in the new challenge rooms, because I loved playing as him in Arkham City and the talk of more skins is really getting me excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-26 00:21:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was bugged that Red Robin was hardly in Issue #19, him being there just seemed weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some good stories featuring team-ups within the Batman Family? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-25 07:31:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Books that have any of the Robins and Batgirls working together, with or without Batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-07 10:40:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  slightly off topic

O_o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-20 10:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> try it, I already have 26 hours on it (and two playthroughs for the single player). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-12 00:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Riffs leader: You Warriors are good. Real good.

Swan: The best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-12 00:02:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fifteen bucks little man, put that shit in my hand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-12 00:01:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Son of a bitch must pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-12 00:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just remember what ol' Jack Burton does when the earth quakes, and the poison arrows fall from the sky, and the pillars of Heaven shake. Yeah, Jack Burton just looks that big ol' storm right square in the eye and he says, "Give me your best shot, pal. I can take it."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 0na5200, The Youtube Home for Titus </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-09 10:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-08 20:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QKPvEfBCPSk
Jiffy! 0:00-0:08 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-08 15:36:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> O_O..... Just kidding. I can actually believe he did something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-02 13:09:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> roll again for crit confirmation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-01 09:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've played it and I got to say it's really good. The shooting is fun and it has a nice story. I also thought the first one was ok but I love this one. You should check out some gameplay or the demo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 10:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [I know this is a right hand but....](http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=2gSf5UMZ8ms#t=131s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-29 09:59:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friends and I disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 10:14:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you give her the old Pork Chop Express? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 10:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know if this would count but I would like my feet similar to an Ape's. So I could climb faster and just pick up stuff. 

If not a tail, so I could hold stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-26 12:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god, same here. I first watched MST3K when it was on Netflix a year ago and when I saw the Arrested Development cameo I searched to see if this subreddit existed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-26 12:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw your earlier post and I couldn't believe it either. They made sure to have a lot of cameos this season :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-26 12:04:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The movie is The Fantastic Four, the one from the 90's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I was just watching the new Arrested Development when .... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-26 11:59:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-22 09:23:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm beginning to write a Cyberpunk novel and the thing I'm having trouble with is describing my characters and the world they live in. For characters I'm wondering if I should go into detail (clothes, facial appearance, etc.) or leave most of it up to the reader's imagination. And for the world I'm trying to find a way to describe it without going into long stretches of exposition. I'm just an amateur writer in High School so I only have a small amount of experience with creating anything beside short stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-21 09:27:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A whole bunch of pain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-17 00:52:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Jesus lifts up Muhammad and does a Cross Piledriver!"

"Can I get two hallelujahs and a amen!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-14 02:14:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish my D D group had females :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-09 03:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [relevant](http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=4m2WutlqBk0#t=56s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-08 08:06:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> was? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-08 06:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ultimate Spider-Man is my favorite too. The game-play and music were good and it felt awesome playing as Venom. I was a huge fan of the comics, but I haven't read them since Ultimatum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-02 09:48:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boy Meets World? 

Here's an episode where they go inside the girls bathroom and the walls are pink, and there is a couch. http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=kudFmxVoLFU#t=328s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-01 08:18:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> independent contractors too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Clerks of Reddit, What are some strange or interesting conversations that have happened in your store? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-01 08:14:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-01 08:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg. I've been searching for the name of this game for nearly 9 years. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-30 01:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually started playing it again this weekend, and it still plays good :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 10:37:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't heard about this. But I doubt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 09:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who knows, in the future it might see the light of day. Personally, I hope after GTAV they start working on Bully 2, if one of their studios hasn't started yet.

Edit: Sorry for the redundant title in the second sentence. I copy and pasted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that Rockstar had planned a spiritual sequel to their game The Warriors called We are the Mods. The game was to be titled We Are The Mods and was to be set in 1960s England during the Mods and Rockers brawls. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 09:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-28 12:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm replaying The Warriors. It's still awesome. I wish Rockstar did make that spiritual sequel I heard about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-28 09:03:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "you're tearin' me apart!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-28 08:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Play the game Bully, by Rockstar. I always feel better after beating up some punk kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-28 08:11:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to say Drawing too. I can write stories, but I think it would be better to tell them with visuals, like a comic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: Why is it easier to learn your first language as a kid, then to learn your second as a teen/adult? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-17 03:38:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You would think since the brain is more developed it would be easier. But is it easier to learn your first language as a kid because your brain is still developing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Growing up who were the crazy/weird people in your neighborhood? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-16 05:24:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-15 06:37:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh i just noticed that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-14 17:57:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've done this too many times.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are your best all-nighter tips and stories? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-14 17:53:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-14 10:28:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like Abrams, but Star Trek and Star Wars are one thing, 2001 is another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-14 10:24:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing. I love Big Trouble in Little China, the same goes for Kurt Russell and John Carpenter, but i think it's meh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who are the video game characters you will never forget? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-14 10:12:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-14 10:10:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Without Kubrick.... I'm sorry, Meow_Goes_The_Kitten. I'm afraid I can't let you do that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-12 09:21:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me its kids who die driving drunk or texting while driving. I just cant feel sorry for people who do stupid stuff like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some things people find sad or depressing, that you just can't/don't? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-12 09:10:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 11:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have some pretty good points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 11:55:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always do this, and It keeps reminding me of Taxi Driver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DAE stand in front of a mirror and come up with comebacks for future use? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 11:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 11:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 11:17:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Come on man, we have to survive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 11:15:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 11:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh that's one too many, I'm sorry but you got to cut one loose. Unless you want to go.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If a zombie apocalypse happened and you could only have a group of 4 people, including yourself, who do you choose? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 11:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Family, friends, celebrities, whoever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 10:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Star Wars jedi power battles? http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Star_Wars_Episode_I:_Jedi_Power_Battles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 10:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> man,  if only she had been in Showgirls instead of Elizabeth Berkley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 10:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a kid my family had vhs copies of the karate kid and Adventures in babysitting and I was in love with Elisabeth Shue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who was your first celebrity crush? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 10:13:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 09:44:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Titus. Best sitcom Fox ever had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 09:35:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I miss Atton Rand and Mira :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DAE feel that something epic is happening somewhere when it's raining heavy? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-09 04:30:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 07:16:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> true that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 07:13:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> who doesn't hate it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 07:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too, I always sing it Time After Time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What popular followings have you not caught onto? past or present </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 07:03:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a movie, book, tv show, clothing trend, whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some things you've been meaning to finish but just can't? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 15:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DAE create movie-type trailers in their head when they hear music? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 15:12:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 14:50:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> stories, some sci-fi and fantasy. I'm not making money or anything, it's more of a hobby. I always wrote good stories and speeches in my English classes so that's where I started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 14:44:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its premise might sound weird, but it really is good. Some kind of plague wipes out every male mammal on Earth, except for this guy and his monkey. And they have to travel alongside this government agent and this scientist to find out why the plague happened and how to fix it. I think it's pretty good because it doesn't just focus on the characters, it shows you what the world would be like without men, the good and the bad. It's well written, well drawn, and since it was planned with only 60 issues in mind it doesn't feel dragged on, and by the end all plot threads are tied up. The only thing bad I can say is that the ending might not be what you want, but it's ending that leaves you satisfied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 14:31:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Final Fantasy 9. It showed me how powerful fictional characters can have on you and that helped inspire me to start writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 14:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its ok, I was touched by Airborne and Encino Man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 13:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Y: the last man

Even if you don't like comic books you need to read this. Buy it, torrent it, whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some things that you think were ahead of their time? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 13:50:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> gadgets, movies, people, ideas..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 12:03:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'll help you out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 11:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's attractive when they show self-respect. For me it's a major turn-off when girls complain that they are fat, unintelligent, or too skinny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, What are some of your non-sexual dreams that could be adapted into a movie/tv show? They don't have be Oscar worthy masterpieces. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 11:49:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 11:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 11:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> source... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Parents of Reddit, What are some times you've purposely embarrassed your children? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 11:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: How Australia operated as a prison colony </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well now they have that new show coming out, Hannibal. But the guy playing Lecter is the bad guy from Casino Royale so I don't know if it's gonna be good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Harry Potter could have been a tv show, maybe not better but still. I don't know how long kids in the United Kingdom have off for summer break, but in america its 3 months, so i'm guessing a Hogwarts school year is about 9 months. That's a lot of time to sum up in about 2 hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What movie do you think would be better as a tv show? And vice-versa. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:01:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> even though some will call this a cop-out, you can answer with what you think would be better as a mini-series, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 09:45:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to see Catcher in the Rye as a movie, but at the same time I don't. The reason why is that I can't think of a good actor for Holden. If only they could have made a movie in the 80's, I think Anthony Michael Hall could have been a good pick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 09:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this and Kids next door were the reason I always watched cartoon network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 09:33:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had a similar experience, when I was a kid my older brother used to always come back from his friends house smelling funny. And I always wondered when his friends came over why he wouldn't let me hang out with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 09:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was just playing Star Wars: Shadows of the empire the other day. I was surprised how much I found it difficult compared to when I played it years ago as a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I was watching Willy Wonka and the chocolate factory earlier and when the Pure Imagination song came up I got teary eyed thinking of my child. Reddit, What makes you feel nostalgic? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 09:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *childhood, goddamn I need to proofread more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's your stance on movie remakes? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 13:36:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you love em, hate em. What's your opinion on this growing trend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's the farthest you've gone to maintain a lie? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 08:49:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 08:40:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I blame peter molyneux, he just kept over-hyping his game, setting the bar too high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 08:38:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a fan of Final Fantasy, I don't think FF7 is a great as everyone says. Apart from graphical improvements and stuff like mini-games, it played just like the others. The magic system was creative but not that special and open world aspects had been in the other entries. The story wasn't bad, it was good, but not that special. I still think its a great game, I still play it to this day, but I don't think it's as game changing as others have called it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What video games do you think don't meet up to their reputation? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 08:31:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 15:25:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And now I'm afraid I have somewhat of a mess on my hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 13:49:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude the people who look at you with disgust, fuck those guys. When i was 15 i used to have a small red-afro, people used to call me carrot-top. You just have to learn to ignore it, and then you don't hear it anymore. I used to be introverted too, I'm still afraid to order a pizza over the phone. You just need to realize your special, there's no one like you, and there never will be. Just knowing that will help you be more outgoing. I'm doing this, and the girls are starting to swoop in for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What was the beginning of promising trilogy... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 13:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 12:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buck Naked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 12:27:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah make society your bitch, if you're into that sort of thing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 12:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While I do think it's a shame they shutdown LucasArts, that doesn't mean the end of Star Wars games, they can still license. Some of the the best games were developed by others. Jedi Outcast, Jedi Academy, Empire at War, Battlefront, and Knights of the old Republic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 12:09:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While you make good points, I still think it is. The license system is deep and while it matches the sphere grid I think it takes the idea to a new level. But I don't think it's perfect, example is Vaan. You could take him out of the whole game and it wouldn't change much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 10:25:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why'd you delete FF12? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 09:27:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> holy shit you're me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 09:14:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I won't lie, Bioshock is a great game, so are the sequels. But I never understood all the hype. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some movies where you are rooting against the main characters/protagonists? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 09:04:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and it doesn't just to have to be movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 08:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shenmue, if you don't it you really should youtube it. Final Fantasy series, even though I don't favor the new entries I do respect how amazing the graphics are. Knights of the Old republic, one of if not the best series of Sci-fi RPG's. Heavy Rain, while I liked Indigo Prophecy I actually cared about the characters in Heavy Rain with all my heart, so much so I had trouble getting a sad/"bad" ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 08:32:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "you will sit here, and you will f*cking watch this!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 08:15:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Star Wars:Jedi Knight. the old games still have the best lightsaber action so I would love to see what they can do now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 08:08:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine is about my dad. I wanna love him, but he wasn't and isn't part of my life that much, so I have trouble loving him. I think he's trying, but i'm not the first kid he wasn't always around for.

P.S. I know the title should be "What's" not "Whats" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Whats a horrible truth you have in your life? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 08:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 07:07:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [dude those it just suck being you?] (http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aeFuq5Q0OXo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 06:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2001: A Space Odyssey. There's so many interpretations out there ranging from the minor details to the overall plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 06:37:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At first i was like, yeah! Then it asked for money and I was like, Sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 01:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Topher Grace? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 00:57:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4, 5, 2, 3, 6. You don't need 1 because the elevator scene in 2 I think brings you up to speed and almost no plot is carried over. And with this you don't lose the shock value of the Darth Vader father reveal in 5. After that you can consider 2 and 3 a long flashback for how Anakin become evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 12:44:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was/is your dream job? Unless you always wanted to be a security guard, I'm not saying it's a bad job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 12:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> relax bra, :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 12:27:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sequel to Office Space </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 12:12:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Parenthesis, Exponents, Multiplication, Division, Addition, Subtraction. Solve in that order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 12:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "PC LOAD LETTER? The fuck does that mean?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 11:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Queen - I Want to Break Free </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, What superstitions do you believe? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 09:56:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 07:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just wish more people would realize this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 06:38:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep Shenmue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 06:34:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I once owned a dog that was smarter then you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 06:22:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> side note it has some bad language, i don't know if that would make it NSFW so I'll just leave the post as it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A funny/mean review of VIII. I know it's been out for a while but I still think it's funny. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 06:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 03:21:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Adventures of the Taxi Dog and If You Give a Mouse a Cookie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What books were read to you as a kid? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 03:19:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 00:36:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Halo had a remake.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 15:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kingdom Hearts series. It may look kiddish but if you really get into it, you'll never be the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 15:21:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my dad gave me his old laptop he had lying around, the Google search bar was full of mother son porn. weird stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 14:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1biedv/people_of_askreddit_what_are_some_questions_you/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 14:35:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> would it be too much to ask if you could send those people our way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 14:26:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just don't forgot to upvote :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 14:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> man, i just remembered that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 13:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> herbie... you poor bastard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 13:50:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a change I noticed was in Episode 2, when Obi-Wan is talking to Yoda. While they are talking Obi-Wan says he was trained by Yoda, but he was trained by Qui-gon. It's one of the ways I think George Lucas made it so you can ignore Phantom Menace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 13:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think we can add this to the list of terrifying N64-era enemies. Something about the graphics back then make things scarier than in games today, I think. 

Edit: I forgot Dark forces wasn't on N64, it was just in that generation of games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 12:53:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't think it's that much of a spoiler, but you never know with some people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How were you introduced to The Galaxy far, far away? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 12:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it doesn't say its against the rules to ask questions and this question didn't pop-up in my search so I would like you to share how you discovered Star Wars, maybe with some interesting stories :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 11:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry, my fault, just spur of the moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 17 years later and this guy still scares me (Shadows of the Empire) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 10:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 10:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but you'll always know...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 07:31:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I was frozen today!"-Suburban Commando http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nC8zz95rm8s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 07:29:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never liked Lord of the Rings. Mostly because I don't like old medieval type settings, I love futuristic Sci-Fi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 07:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Star Wars Jedi Knight. Mainly because I love Star Wars and I would like to attend the Jedi academy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 06:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/yqui2mR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 05:54:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/Fnm4qMO.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, What has ruined a part of your child? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 05:49:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 05:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always wanted to be Robin. I don't think I'd be able to fill Batman's role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, What cross-media character team-up would you like to see? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 05:34:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Characters from books, movies, tv shows, whatever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 08:44:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> care to elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 08:43:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you should tell your husband, "if you didn't look like my first crush, I wouldn't have given you a second thought." I kid I kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 08:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what is the value of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What was the last possession you lost, that you're still looking for? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 08:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> People of Reddit, What are the stories of your first love? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 08:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 06:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "you're my density" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 06:34:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol i wish. She didn't know anything about the movie apart from the title so she was surprised during the opening scene. This was the start of a childhood of R-rated movies full of nudity and swearing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 06:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom took me to see this in theaters.... when i was four years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 06:11:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> death by stereo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 06:01:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to have to check this out, it reminds me of Rad and Airborne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 04:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really like 16 candles, but I love Weird Science. Me and my by best friend are just like Gary and Wyatt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 02:50:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah i found that out about the "indian" guy in short circuit. At first I didn't think the movie was racist... til this scene http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=2rxlidAR3Fw#t=2s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 02:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disney should make a proper sequel. Like 2000, but without pointless celebrity cameos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 02:44:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> which one overall do you favor most? As a kid I loved VI but now as a teen I love V </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 02:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same here, got to love Corey Fieldman and Kurt Russell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 02:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have to agree, i watched it on vhs when i was 7 years old and it stills astonishes me with the music and visuals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What movie defines your childhood? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 02:22:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 11:32:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://24.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ls6yd1ndRI1qeo6bto1_250.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 11:31:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for some reason I love the stuck-up professors that only like things to be done traditionally. Basically the "antagonists" of Robin Williams movies (Dead Poets Society, Patch Adams). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What movie character stereotypes do you love and hate? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 11:26:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 09:18:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There wouldn't be that many teenage girls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 09:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> everyone always criticizes FFX's voice acting but i think its good, most of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 09:06:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For games i would say Final Fantasy 9, I was drawn in by the characters and story. Movie wise would be Big Trouble in Little China, because Jack Burton is awesome. A comic i recently read was Y the Last Man, and i have to say everyone should give it a read, its really that good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What movies, games, comics, etc. have sucked you in and made you feel like you were on a real adventure? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 09:01:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 12:57:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sister was talking to a friend about it, I asked what she was talking about and she told me to go to reddit. Life's never been the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What types of mixed signals have you been given pursuing a romantic interest? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 12:55:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We've all been through it. We've been interested in someone else but it's never clear whether those feelings are mutual. So I would like you to share some tales of confusion and/or frustration going after someone you liked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-20 23:51:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the article, more people should be aware of crimes like these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's the strangest thing you've done or seen done in a movie theater? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-19 09:42:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-12 00:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grim Adventures of billy and Mandy, courage the cowardly dog, and American dragon jake long. Man I miss those shows... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 14:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Limbo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 14:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Y:the last man. 60 great issues of pure amazing, if you haven't checked it out you're missing out big time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 14:22:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "It". If you don't believe me watch Nostalgia critics review, it makes it hard to believe this stuff was scary. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aFcC5xi2W1o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 14:18:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mind-reading. I just imagine people who you think are friends just constantly hating on you in their thoughts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 14:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll say Judge Doom from Who framed roger rabbit. Everytime his reveal scene after the steamroller was going to come up I would shut off the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 13:58:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everybody in "The Phantom Menace"
Blame George Lucas writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 13:52:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You got a point. But while we're on the subject I have to ask, what do you guys like about the original Star Trek? I'm not saying its bad but I was always a Picard guy.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 13:47:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big Trouble in little china. Gotta have my six demon bag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 13:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom always cooks something special like a Pot Roast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 13:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I kind of think it had more than a cult following, it seemed popular back in its day. But I was a kid back then so I don't really know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 12:45:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was a sophomore in high school I met this Junior girl and it was going great. We were talking, laughing, I even got her phone number. But I noticed this red pimple looking thing on one of her breasts, and I pointed it out to her. Never heard from her again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 12:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn, beat me to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-11 09:43:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jak and Daxter: The Precursor Legacy

I never get tired of the victory fanfare that plays when you get a power cell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>