<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2259</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it was amazing, minus just a few tweaks. It was very moist while still holding a good shape. The only two things Id change were:

A.) add more lemon flavor than I did

B.) wait until the cake was completely cool to pour the frosting over so it didn't just roll down the sides. 


Overall, great cake and definitely worth a try.  The sweetness of the cake was a great offset to the tart blueberries! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:24:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the tip! I'll try that next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Guide to a Delicious Lemon Blueberry Pound Cake! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:00:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Guide to a Delicious Lemon Blueberry Pound Cake! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:59:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey! Crazy, I just saw this on my facebook feed this morning. It happened in a super small town in Georgia. That's awesome though, don't mess with off duty redneck fireman, you'll get rekt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 10:59:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very. She had diabeetus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 12:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god. Maybe. That is too accurate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay. I live in the South, and once knew this girl who was a totally weeaboo(spelling?) and also a gigantic redneck. This is basically what she would draw and have as her phone background. *cringe* Her playlist would go from anime theme songs to "She Thinks My Tractor's Sexy"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 21:04:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Enemy.

In 1944, thats all we were told. The Nazis were enemies to the United States and had to be eliminated. Our generals never spoke about the families they had, the dreams the sought, or the way they bled just like us. No, they were enemies. 

Now, I stare into the eyes of a man who took my last breath; a man who beat me until I screamed for mercy yet he would not deliver it. This same man, he now stood in front of me handing over a two Euro coin for a carton of milk. 

His once rigid face and sharp eyes had aged into a sad, helpless stare. His hands shook, and his legs struggled to hold the weight of his aging body. The hands that once delivered a bullet into my head, were now outstretched handing me a coin. 

After staring for a moment too long, I took the coin and handed him his milk. I knew him, but to him, I was just another supermarket clerk. 

I watched him walk out the door, letting my grudges escape me.

A painless bullet took my life, but pain and suffering by the hands of age would take his.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 00:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [bruh.](http://imgur.com/YoYcGjv)

Just a little sketch I did, hope you enjoy it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [it's deer season y'all](http://imgur.com/k6YMIG4)

Growing up in the South this is all I could think of.

Apologies, I'm out of town and didn't have a lot of time or a sketchbook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I am a big burly man who loves you. Look at my picture. 
https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/7c/3e/6c/7c3e6c50d78259d530b7d703501c8c99.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now it just sounds like you're calling a random man on the internet darling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:09:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should probably go to the doctor, pal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Boyfriend and I dressed up as Link and a Hunter a couple years ago at Dragon*Con, draw us? :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:01:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 23:16:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god yes. even better
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 23:08:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know that, it was just a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bruce Jenner's female name should've been Jenny Bruce. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 22:59:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no I'm sure you do! I just haven't met many and those who are don't really seem to like to talk about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 08:26:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suppose that is true, women do seem to respect men and women the same. 

I'll be your friend! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 08:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hm, that's really interesting. The upper body strength makes sense, but I wouldn't expect the jalapeo thing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 08:12:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's all good! It's related to my question and it is still very interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 08:09:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That actually really fascinating. Especially from a psychological standpoint. As a woman I think (especially about emotional things), we do the same thing in assuming the other woman knows the feeling we are talking about. Thank you for sharing that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 08:08:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I assumed it wouldn't be the exact same, but I've always been very curious about transgendered people and this shed a lot of light. You don't meet many here in the Deep South, if you remember the subs let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Transgenders of Reddit, what are some effects of hormones and transitioning that helped you understand physical struggles the other sex has that you didnt understand before transition? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 07:41:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Edit: or emotional struggles
Edit 2: it also doesn't have to be serious struggles, anything you just weren't expecting or didn't understand before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:20:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This looks delicious! I don't love eggs but this looks really great.

Side note: My dad went to Mexico once and stayed at a resort, ordered room service for the following morning while intoxicated, ended up ordering 3 different plates of this, among other things. He ate a bite off each plate lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 20:35:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/Zh5cg0r

Pretty sure I nailed it. A++ Art Skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 19:20:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LOL, this is fantastic. After that scene I could only picture that pitch as Don just picking up a gun and shooting himself in the face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: Why are car year models a year ahead of the current year? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 17:15:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Example: the 2014 Honda Accord was sold in 2013 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 06:53:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Call me Dahlonega because I'm always 30 minutes from Cumming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-13 04:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/QA1bHc8.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Zelda Wall Mural - all freehanded (WIP) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-13 15:44:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-13 15:25:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've completed part of it, and next I'm going to add the moon from majora's mask, and maybe skull kid. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Zelda Wall Mural, all freehanded (WIP) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-13 15:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-13 15:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow dude, great job!! I frickin' love it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-12 18:47:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! And I will most likely, these fuckers are just so butthurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-12 18:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! :) nice to see some positive comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-12 18:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey asshole, I only made an account because SO really likes reddit. I wish I could really just jump through the internet sometimes and punch people in the dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-12 12:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Geez, fuck off. Leave him alone. 

Spoiler alert: you're the cunt, and you never going to get any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-12 11:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, girlfriend here. Thanks to you guys who defended me. When I handed this to him, I flat out told him that it wasn't my design, so I didn't pass it off as mine. Second, I did what I did out of love. I had an extra canvas and I knew he liked that poster, so I wanted to paint it because what does just buying a poster really say about how you care for someone. I had one day to do it, between work, school, and driving an hour each way to see him, and it's hard for me to be creative under stress. Because of that I didn't really have time to do my own design but I wanted him to have something I painted. So for the record, I fucking love that kid, and all this is meant to be is a gift :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>