<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject517</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Norwegian Version seemed much more valuable than the others, so that's nice to know i guess. Thanks ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, it's a good book so far, so rarity isn't much of an issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought so until i found out all Nordic versions were printed the same year. Well, if it's not rare, i do not care, the book is really interesting from what i have read already. Well, thank you for wanting to help, Sir and/or madam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:04:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are in Swedish, Printed in 1957 yes, but after the ones in Norwegian. I was a bit unclear , but yes mine is in Norwegian, sorry about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:59:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm Reading **Aku-Aku The Secrets of Easter Island, By Thor Heyerdahl** when I am at the Cabin, and at home **A Man Called Ove, By Fredrik Backman** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not in the original language though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Purchased a cabin, found a few interesting books </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:04:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey here /r/books ! My Family Recently pruchased a cabin here in Norway and we found some books left by the previous owner. There was one book that made me wonder how rare that book was. I love books so i would never sell it, but knowing the rarity of the books i own is nice. The book was Aku-Aku the Secret of Easter Island, First edition 1957, written by Thor Heyerdahl. All other first editions i found online were not Norwegian, so not printed in 1957. It seems to be in a good condition and i already started reading it. i was wondering if any of you guys know how rare it is? My bookshelf is sorted in Year, Rarity, Author. So knowing where to put it is also nice. Thank you on beforehand !

And i also found a bible from 1871 which was quite interesting, made with what seems to be made with a Hectograph. For some reason i put it in the closet where we keep the wine glasses. 

Sadly i cannot provide pictures of the books, as i left the books at the cabin where i keep my books.

EDIT: Took the well used bible home, some photos: http://imgur.com/a/GFBcH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:48:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Push space to jump, then push R after releasing space. That works for me atleast  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 14:15:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never give up on good games, sometimes i just need extended pauses. I'll try finding some better people to play with :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Poetry] PS4 / War Thunder Ad Parody </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 23:45:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-17 10:25:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Sandvich make me strong!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 08:25:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [wat](http://imgur.com/za20pvR) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-16 08:19:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Long time since I've seen one of these self-promoting Minecraft players, who in their head, are better than anyone, and different from everyone else. Sorry, man, this shit's getting old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reminds me of an Italian Who owns a Pizza Restaurant </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-21 19:10:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 21:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> heh, thanks :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 21:05:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's good, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 21:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! :D Means alot ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 20:56:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, heh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 16:00:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :D Never Be afraid to embaress yourself a little bit ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 15:58:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 15:36:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Remember, This is supposed to be a joke. Don't Take it seriously
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 15:27:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is what it's supposed to be :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Honeydewyeayea - In Real Life! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 15:12:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Eye of the Fox </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 13:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fox in The Snow </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 10:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Aerosmith </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-13 15:37:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>