<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3590</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cooking with accordion! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:04:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My band's secret to making great Shakshouka </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:25:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yup there's a list! http://www.nycrgb.org/html/resources/zip.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NYC Legal Stabilized rent when hidden from landlord </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:15:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi All, looking for some advice on the following situation:

Landlord never informed me that my building is rent stabilized. No preferential or legal rent was mentioned on the lease. No rider was attached.

I've been paying 1450 for just under the last 2 years. After a year the lease expired and went month-to-month. It was never renewed as is legally required. 

Landlord now wants to raise rent $50. If this is still preferential obviously I don't want to cause trouble. If it isn't it could be too much of an increase, but I don't know the legal rent. I told him I need a new lease, but at the moment he still doesn't know that I know that the apt is rent stabilized. 

What's the best course of action for me? Should I sign a lease for the additional $50 and then once I get the rent history from the state confront him if it is too much. Or should I wait until I get the history and then have him rewrite the lease if the increase is illegal?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 22:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you rather clean up the poop of 100 duck sized horses or one horse sized duck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 16:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yo mama.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:48:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you should know Turkish! Seriously... Way too many expats leading isolated lives in Turkey. You can't "learn how to bargain" unless you speak Turkish. If you start in English you've lost the game already.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 05:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dinosaur is nothing compared to Hometown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 05:10:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Goto Hometown BBQ. Best in NYC as far as I'm concerned. Actually wait, don't go. More Brisket for me...

http://www.hometownbarbque.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Up. Wind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have them and like them. Obviously the bass response isn't as rich as a larger speaker...  when I went to the showroom to listen it was between these and the Adams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 23:38:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> explain for the uninitiated... does this address venom somehow?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 06:05:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's hard to explain... something in the middle. I was hypnotised as a teenager during a very large stage show. I didn't forget the experience. I wouldn't say I was being mind-controlled like a puppet. If I was asked to do something I was truly not ok with I don't think I would have done it. It's more that I was hyper relaxed / meditative  and there was a kind of unspoken agreement to do what the guy suggested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tipsy Oxcart -- Tipska [World / Balkan / Ska] (2015) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 07:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thursday: Global Throwdown w/ Tipsy Oxcart   Background Orcs (Funky Balkan   African) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 05:40:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:29:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you can also disable whatever you'd never use... for instance if you're not working in surround, or don't need 20 Mid-Side plugins etc.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Global Throwdown w/ Tipsy Oxcart   Background Orcs this Thursday (Balkan/African Inspired funk) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 19:01:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 04:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's very not true seor wombat. 
With more speakers the chances of alignment issues significantly increase, causing phase cancellation and ultimately unintelligible dialog + muddy music.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 05:01:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ONLY good software for drafting signal flows is "Omnigraffle" as far as I'm concerned. All serious theatrical sound system designers are using it these days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WMMusic [Balkan] Tipsy Oxcart - Honey Dripper (NYC) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 06:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Honey Dripper - Tipsy Oxcart </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 06:18:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 06:45:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> agreed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 00:33:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Def sounds like Spat to me! http://www.fluxhome.com/products/plug_ins/ircam_spat-v3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who are the creepy figures above your left and right shoulders?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 21:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't take the video, a friend did, but it is most certainly the Brooklyn museum, not BAM.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 16:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe could be a midi conflict? Protools thinks it's getting a signal from a control surface and it's interfering with what you're trying to do. Just a guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dog vs Fountain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 16:19:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 17:17:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha I literally just did a film with the exact same perspective shift. Design aside, build the effects chain for your "deaf effect" and put it on an aux channel that returns to your main output. Then insert a send on any of your tracks that you want to morph into deafness, bussed to your new aux channel. Set it to "prefade" then you can fade down the main volume of the track, but fade up the aux send to reroute it through your effect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 07:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I need to check but I suspect that indeed the master volume acts as a DCA for the output fader as stated. When outputting just 1 stereo output this seems redundant, but if you have multiple outputs (IE: 5.1 surround sound or more complicated output routing for monitoring) it affects all of of them which is potentially useful, although honestly I don't see why you would ever want your output at anything but unity assuming everything is setup properly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 01:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a pro sound designer. Use logic and protools. Actually prefer logic to protools for pure sound design work for its bundled plugins, quicker hand-drawn automation (curves) and since I can experiment and then bounce the track in place. Prefer protools for hardcore audio editing. Would never dream of using it for anything midi based. 

If you're a true pro company you gotta stick with protools as your main DAW though if you expect to send sessions around to other places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 01:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like apple's Space Designer so much sometimes if I'm forced to use Protools, I make an effects return to logic or mainstage with soundflower and use that. Cheaper than altiverb. . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 01:05:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  r e c o r d  i t !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, def a useful step in the right direction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nope. Doesn't work, this adjusts the whole track OR if a selection is made adds too many nodes and a hard bump which is exactly what I'm looking to solve.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Finetuning automation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:02:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi folks,

Been using Logic for 10 years but also use protools professionally. Still catching up a bit and have a quick question. (not interested in a debate about which is better). 

When fine tuning automation lanes by hand is there a way to:

Raise or lower (probably w/ trim tool) JUST the segment of automation that lies between two nodes. Currently it either scales the automation of the whole track or if I select that area it adds new nodes interfering with my preexisting fades. (In logic this would just be dragging a segment, stretching the fades before and after it to achieve a new level. )

When I select an area and the use the trim tool to adjust its level, 4 nodes are created (2 on each end) creating a hard jump to the new level. Is there a way to switch this so only two nodes are created essentially creating a fade from whatever nodes are already immediately lbefore/after the area?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:09:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> +1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 21:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you can't run directly from your interface to the speakers. They're passive which means the need an amp in between. I don't know the specific specs of your speakers so can't recommend an amp. Once you have one though, you could then run 1/4"-Speakon cable from that to the speakers. 

I think you could benefit from hiring a professional  though to fully address your needs. There are different kinds of 1/4" (TS vs. Balanced TRS) and different kinds of speakon (NL2 vs. NL4 for a bi-amped system) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 18:59:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure why not you just need an amp. All that said, these speakers aren't really going to give you a clear mix if you're doing serious audio work up close. They're more geared towards loud playback in a large entertainment venue, not precision. 

Your signal chain would be: 
Computer--firewire/usb--interface--very small mixing board*--2 channel amplifier--speakers

*like a Mackie 402VLZ4. Technically your interface could function also as your mixer but it's probably safer to have a mixer in there to gain stage everything correctly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:04:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wav absolutely supports surround sound. . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:58:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree, but it's more complicated than that. Anyone with great ears who doesn't have a properly treated room won't actually have an accurate sense of what they're hearing. A fine engineer is going to charge more than $50/track because of the overhead involved with running a professional operation where those good ears can be put to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:12:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> at $50 a track you're gonna have trouble. Even if they have decent ears, anyone working on that budget isn't going to have the expensive outboard compressors/limiters and room treatment that makes mastering a valuable step in the process. It's expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 00:06:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know we're past your deadline but I usually prepare 2 stems for theatrical gigs... a wet and a dry. Then when I get to the space I'll mix in the wet as needed.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe traditionally just tacks or nails/needles/pins on a hard surface have been used. But there are no rules. . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:17:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would use a combination of:
An additional track of hiss/crackle sounds that's sidechained with a compressor  to your main auto to help "glue" them together
A distortion plugin on your main audio
a very very slow flanger. You can also use a tape delay with feedback set to zero and then modulate the delaytime to give it that warpy sound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 21:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe compress everything to glue it together/blend and then fade certain clips up into the foreground strategically. There are no rules though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 06:17:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like all these movies portray the Roma in a fairly romanticized unrealistic way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-02 06:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd advise you to goto one of the folk-music seminars/camps like the Plovdiv seminar, Ross Daily's thing,  Macedonian pearl seminar,  Amala School, etc... Without connections or language skills you'll have  a very difficult time arranging things on your own in only 10 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 07:26:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In america speaking 3 languages is the equivalent of a PhD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 07:22:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DOWNVOTED. Here's why
User "Kristinchen" only shares links from this website.
The Article says: 
 ITS NO LONGER ABOUT PORTRAYING AN IMAGE THROUGH EXCESS AND LOGOS. MODERN DAY LUXURY IS ALL ABOUT INTEGRITY.

Well then why is Absolut's 'handcrafted hard to find luxury Elyx brand mentioned at every turn? 
THIS IS AN AD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-26 05:30:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Read this. Everyone has slightly different needs but this article is pretty good. http://michaelkammes.com/audio/prepping-and-exporting-for-post-audio-in-final-cut-pro/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 16:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in NYC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for your help! It's a doc so there isn't really much subby material so I think I'm probably fine in that dept unless I'm overlooking something? Theater speakers are full range and the LFE is literally for LFE(?) Is there crossover that I'm overlooking and need to account for?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:06:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Room isn't treated but I have a pretty good understanding of its deficiencies. Mixing LCR so 5.1 minus 2.1...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mixing for theater in small room </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 16:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi Folks,

I'm mixing a film that got picked up for a festival. My small room is loosely calibrated to -79dB on my nearfields. When I print the stems I want to make sure this thing is going to translate decently to the theater. Are there any steps I can take from my room to make absolutely sure there aren't any surprises when it gets to the theater?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-23 05:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've rarely had a problem with my big guerrini which I know fits perfectly in the overhead of a large transatlantic flight. That said I know professionals who will actually take the instrument apart into its two halves and have separate cases for each.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 22:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chalga. Love it? hate it?... or love it after 2 drinks?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 05:35:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fish sauce and shallots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 05:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> np- still learning the basics myself. 
If you can't find kafir lime, you can dilute normal lime juice with a little mayer lemon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:02:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You want the little fresh or pickled "bird's eye" peppers used in Thai and Indian food for CHILLI PASTE.

 However what you are making is CURRY paste, which is different. For that you're best bet is **dried** puya peppers. You mash them up in a mortar and pestle with all the other stuff. Some trouble-shooting tips for 'ya are: 

* When making your curry, first sautee the paste alone in oil for a bit until fragrant to cook all the raw shallots/garlic/other stuff. 

* You are correct to add sugar. Best bet is to dilute **palm sugar** (not white granulated cane sugar) in a mixture or lime juice and fish sauce. Then add that to the pot to incorporate it into the paste.  Add coconut milk after. 

* The boxed coconut milk is better than the canned. 
* finish it all off with some unsweetened coconut cream once your protein is cooked (not cream of coconut or creamed coconut). 
*I've never used it since my city has access to thai stuff, but you could try http://www.templeofthai.com/ for ingredients. I'm guessing you may have also been missing galangal and lime leaves too which makes a world of difference.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What The Hell Do Sound Mixers Do? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 06:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 19:38:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do it all the time for live theater, and have never had a problem with hair noise. I usually use 2 toupee clips, hiding the cable under a part of hair, securing a loop of cable to the back of the neck with skinprep+transpore. The mic sits centrally right at the hairline, best situation are bangs to hide it. You can match the cable color to the hair with shoe paint, just be sure to cover the element with a little e-tape first so you don't mess it up. You can color the element itself with a paint marker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 19:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mic + pot of hot oil + something frying in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Accordion Clap </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-18 05:12:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 21:47:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are a bunch of video on youtube of how to do it. I just seasoned mine yesterday and it worked fine:

 Basically, scrubbed the waxy stuff out of it with warm water, detergent, and a scouring pad. Then I heated it up on my range  REALLY HOT. Next rubbed oil all around in it. Then burned that in occasionally rotating it around to hit as much of the surface as I could- you're going for a smooth burnt black finish on the inside. 

 I've heard of an alternate method using salt to get the same effect but I don't know much about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-11 17:50:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could it be some kind of metadata or a copyright marking trick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-07 21:26:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> actually paying far under the stabilized rate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> stabilized lease renewal legal question? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-07 02:36:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> According to NYC housing code my landlord is legally obligated to renew my lease after it expires. He also never disclosed that the apt. is rent stabilized and I found it out later (illegal although I don't really care). Should I continue to bug him to formally renew it, or in the eyes of the law am I safe and still covered. (see below) 

The catch: My lease has a clause that it's good for a year (which has passed) and "thereafter it shall become a month-to-month tenancy."

Later it says, "TERMINATION: After expiration of the leasing period, this agreement is automatically renewed from month to month, but may be terminated by either party giving the other a 30-day written notice of intention to terminate. Where laws require "just cause," such just cause shall be so stated on said notice..."  

Am I safe from sudden eviction or is he legally permitted to kick me out after a months notice? (a bad situation to be be in) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-06 21:47:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CHEESE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 20:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dried oysters   fish sauce *are* MSG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 20:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here is a GREAT article about everything you ever wanted to know about MSG, it's flavor, its myths, relation to "umami", etc..
http://luckypeach.com/on-msg-and-chinese-restaurant-syndrome/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 22:44:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bunker is great and $1000/a day including engineer and assistant is very reasonable for a professional place in NYC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 15:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is obvious. Tarracotta soldiers in Xi'an China!! http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Terracotta_Army </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-03 22:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pour it in the sink? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Serving salad as an hors d'oeuvre </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 22:09:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm making a northern thai herbal salad for a party (from Andy Ricker's book). Anyone have any creative ideas to present it as a bite-sized hors d'oeuvre? Was considering using a cabbage leaf, but that's kind of like wrapping a salad in a salad :-/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Recipe Management? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 04:12:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-26 19:33:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well if I had to have only 16 spices I would get:

* Black Pepper
* Cinnamon
* Nutmeg
* Cumin
* Paprika
* Cayenne  
* Turmeric 
* Saffron
* Cloves
* Red pepper Flakes (preferably Aleppo)
* Coriander 
* Sumac
* Curry Powder
* Cardamom
* Dried Mint
* Dried Thyme
* Dried Oregano

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Impeach Taylor Swift. Lets recruit this fella' as the new NYC spokesperson! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-05 00:19:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Band offers orig. cookbook to accompany music </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 18:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tipsy Oxcart brings Mediterranean madness to Radio Bean - Fri July 11th. 9pm </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-04 03:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Tipsy Oxcart Official Site](http://www.tipsyoxcart.com)

Friday July 11th. 9pm-10pm

[Radio Bean](http://www.radiobean.com)

[FB Event](https://www.facebook.com/events/1463670323866314/)

Join Tipsy Oxcart for a night of funky Mediterranean madness at Radio Bean. All the way from Brooklyn, Tipsy Oxcart plays electric, sweaty, bumpin' Balkan music, channeling the spirit of 36 hour weddings to keep the crowds dancing until the sun comes up. Serving up originals and fresh, upbeat arrangements of urban dance tunes, the band deviously infuses the sounds of South-Eastern Europe with elements of jazz, funk, and more. Dig naughty violin solos, atomic accordion grooves, freak-me-out clarinet, and the baddest rhythm section this side of the Mediterranean. A party with Tipsy Oxcart is guaranteed to shake the dance floor all night long! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-03 16:07:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jackalopes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: Why milk comes in a box? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-02 06:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is milk pretty much the only drink that comes in a box? (Other than 2-buck chuck of course) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-01 20:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried both on some really tricky dialog in an active port recently. No comparison -  RX3 is the way to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-30 04:05:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are your thoughts on [Tom Brown Jr.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tom_Brown,_Jr.) and the controversies surrounding the story of his upbringing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Interview with WWII sound recordist </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-26 22:48:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 03:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And petition here: http://www.thepetitionsite.com/470/217/554/reinstate-the-tony-award-categories-for-sound-design-now/#sign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sound design categories nixed from Tonys </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 03:02:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-12 03:00:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Petition can be found here: http://www.thepetitionsite.com/470/217/554/reinstate-the-tony-award-categories-for-sound-design-now/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-08 04:53:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Evernote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-08 04:48:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and one fact THEY don't know is how to use an apostrophe. . .   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-24 17:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like every weekend last summer in Istanbul... #BiberGaz. Sounds exactly like pepper spray\gas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-22 03:38:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's plain. Add whatever flavoring\nuts you want. http://ozlemsturkishtable.com/2012/06/home-made-turkish-delight-lokum-and-they-go-so-well-with-turkish-coffee/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-22 03:36:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two ways I like:

* Cut in half, where the pit was drizzle some nice olive oil and handsomely season with S\P.

* When I have a little more time, I love to caramelize some shallots with cumin, paprika, lime juice. Throw in some almonds at the end. Put it in a bowl, and make some toast in the same pan. Then I take an avocado, mush it up, add salt, pepper, olive oil and a little bit of balsamic or rice-wine vinegar. Spread that on the toast, and add the shallot\almond on top.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-22 03:08:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Inclusion or exclusion: Perhaps a normally loud atmosphere grows suspiciously quiet. Or maybe some element of the atmosphere starts in a rhythmic fashion, like water dripping or a rusty fan.Or maybe it's nature and the animals that inhabit the enviornment start making alarm sounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-20 15:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think of not only where you are, but what's beyond the walls of the scene. 

* What time is it? 
* What season?
* Is it tense? 
* for your restaurant is it fancy, is there also a bar? where is the kitchen?
* How does the environment react to what's goin' on?

If it's a tense winter night, chances are there aren't going to be crickets in the background or children going to school for instance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-11 23:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mysteries is vastly different than Job - I encourage you to see it. It's 50 different playwrights' individual interpretation of a given Bible parable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Entire Bible onstage in 1 night... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 18:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The entire Bible onstage in 1 night [NYT] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 18:26:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-22 06:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I still say "Alblum" instead of "Album"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to *really* end a concert... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-19 23:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-03 18:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is lower brooklyn south brooklyn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sambusahs in Bulk? (like samosas\empanadas) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-03 06:58:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi All!

I'm having a Sambusah party in 2 days (Iranian pastry empanadas). I've made them before but need advice on making A LOT in the most efficient way possible. This is for around 20-30 people so figure I'm making around 100-150 total sambusahs. 

I plan on making my 5 fillings on day #1.

Day 2 will be all about stuffing and folding them. Then baking some and frying some so that they'll be fresh when people start arriving in the evening. I have 2 questions:

* What is the most **efficient way to prep** so that I can do as much ahead of time but keep them fresh. Can I stuff some day-1 and refrigerate, or will they got soggy? Maybe freeze the ones I'm frying?

* **Folding** them can be a time consuming process. Any tips to speed it up?

*  I was also considering other forms some could take, like an **open cup**. Any tips on how to make puff pastry mini cups? Could I make these day 1 and then fill them right before? Should they be refrigerated or room temp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 22:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nope... it actually seems like a marketing stunt for ABC to promote it's new show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-29 06:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> on new years day there's the "polar bear swim" there which is probably pretty fun to check out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-29 06:17:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah they're great! If you like them make sure you check out the [Golden Festival](www.goldenfest.org).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-29 04:38:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Native Brooklynite here. Use [HopStop](http://www.hopstop.com) to figure out trains once you know your destination. 

I would suggest either walking across the Brooklyn bridge to DUMBO or you could take the F to York or the A\C to High St. Walk around [Dumbo](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DUMBO) and then go up the hill (or squibb bridge) to [Brooklyn Heights](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brooklyn_Heights) to see some really nice tree lined brownstoney streets and the [Promenade](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brooklyn_Heights_Promenade). 

Some alternatives: Walk the length of **5th Ave in Park Slope.** You could either take any train to Barclay's Center or 2/3 to Bergen.  Cool things to check out there:

* [BierKraft](http://www.bierkraft.com/)

* [Skyice](http://www.yelp.com/biz/skyice-sweet-and-savory-brooklyn) good Thai food that's a bit better than standard fare. Casual. Really interesting icecream flavors

* [Gorilla Coffee](http://gorillacoffee.com/) Strong Stuff!

* [Barbs](http://www.barbesbrooklyn.com) Amazing music every night of the year. 

* etc...  

Or take the B\Q all the way out to **Brighton Beach.** Get lunch at [Cafe Kashkar](http://kashkarcafe.com/) or one of the [Russian places](http://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=Brighton+Beach+Russian+Restaurants find_loc=Brooklyn%2C+NY)  and then walk down the boardwalk to Coney Island which is erie but kinda cool in the winter. Good if you're adventurous and like Russian stuff. 

Don't goto Williamsburg. It's just an extension of Manhattan and full of people trying too hard to act like what they think of as "real New Yorkers"    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-29 03:33:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I spent some time this summer interpreting from my non-native second language (Turkish) into English for some friends I was traveling with. When I was in the thick of it, doing it daily, I started dreaming in both simultaneously. It was as if I was interpreting the dialog in my dreams as it occurred.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-28 04:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah you're right. I had the impression that she wanted to explore authentic East New York to see "what the city is really about..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-28 02:51:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> * **The Staten Island Ferry** You don't need tickets, don't worry about it. 

* **Ground Zero** No idea, but I'm sure you can just show up. 

* **City pass....** I'm a native New Yorker and never heard of this. The MET is free and you can give them whatever you want at entry so a "discount" seems silly.  

* **Subway** Get a weekly pass. That makes sense since you'll be jetting around all week. Every station has a machine where you can get one. 

* **Tickets** Goto TKTS. Like u/SilverMarch said the one in Downtown Brooklyn is the easiest. From there you can easily walk and see the Brooklyn Heights promenade\DUMBO\Brooklyn Bridge


* **Central Park** Like anywhere in New York, **the best thing you can do is just walk around, get lost and find your own little surprises**. The horses are pricy but easy to find. 

* **Bus Tour** No clue. Be a real New Yorker and walk! 

* **The Projects** Don't be an idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-23 02:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Folks have already suggested Kalustiyans and Sahadi's as I was. I'd also add Patel Brothers in Jackson Heights to the list for anything indian. Go there to be inspired: there will be plenty of stuff you don't even recognize.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-23 02:18:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also check the places across the street from Sahadi's or Damascus next door for middle eastern goods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-23 02:05:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is become even less sparsely populated to due to migration after the late 80's onwards. People in the East came to the Istanbul \ the cities seeking work and refuge from armed conflict between the state and the PKK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-23 02:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems like the most popular was answer was "I don't think anything about it!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-23 01:54:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great! Def. my favorite lokum flavor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-23 01:30:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm guessing this is Rose flavored? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-21 22:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Conflict resolution  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-18 22:36:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pun intended  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-18 21:37:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, you're thinking of the dream house! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-18 16:33:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ruhlman's  20 is all you need!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-18 16:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lemongrass also has a softer "heart" that you can find if you shed away the stringy bits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-17 01:26:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ecofriendly heaven excluding the toxic waste site that it's built upon. .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-16 04:55:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you tipped the band! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-15 06:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you encountered any foreign elements offering to support  your efforts or pay you to deliver specific goods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-10 04:00:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone can agree that their mother's cuisine is the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-09 02:27:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Advieh is just persian for "spice mix" and can take many different forms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-09 02:26:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cardamom is more indian \ subcontinental  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-09 02:25:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As others have said it's a mix. What's in it is up to you but I'd say cumin is generally dominant. When I make lamb kfte \ merguez I use:

* 1 1/4 teaspoons ground cumin
* 1 1/4 teaspoons ground coriander (toasted)
* 1/2    teaspoon ground cinnamon
* 1 1/4 teaspoons fennel seeds (toasted)
* 2 tablespoons harissa or ac biber salas
* 3 garlic cloves, minced
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-08 05:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like sorel a lot - http://jackfrombrooklyn.com/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-08 04:59:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> myst + simcity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-07 04:23:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> agree that it's mastic. Try [making a pudding](http://ozlemsturkishtable.com/2012/09/milk-pudding-with-mastic-gum-and-rhubarb-compote/ ) from it instead of making Turkish Karanmaras dodurmasi as others have suggested which, at least when I've tried it in Turkey, doesn't really have much mastic flavor. oh and also Sahadi's is the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-07 03:57:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> visa versa = why does a sponge become a brownie?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-01 01:17:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> uh, it would be kaleidoscopic and beautiful!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-01 01:11:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ramen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-01 01:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least on my instrument, that issue wouldn't make a sound. it would just be leaky and perhaps make the note out of tune. The reeds only sound from one direction and the leather prevents air from going through when the bellows are going the other way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-01 00:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry I misspoke, I was referring to a putty knife not an offset spatula. Great for omelets, anything on a skillet, cleaning your cutting  board. I'm not professional but recently I've noticed one in every single professional kitchen I've peeked in. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Putty_knife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-01 00:29:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess it was an unintentional pun ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-29 21:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> * Paring knife should def be on the essential list. 
* You don't need a million pans. I'd say one large frying pan, a smaller cast iron skillet, stock pot, medium sauce pan, and an enameled dutch oven will get you VERY FAR. 
* The one thing you're missing is a lot of small assorted containers\bowls\dishes for  mise en place 
* i'd also add a palate knife (like what painters use for spackle) for scraping things around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 07:47:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First by watching mom. Then in college I got to practice when the meal plan sucked and I just craved Turkish food! I made friends with the cafeteria workers and they would give me ingredients from the store room :-) I learned to cook non-Turkish food when I then lived in Turkey and craved thai food and more :-p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 07:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with ostones and would add to always focus on making your left hand more stacatto for clarity. Also try playing repeated notes in the melody with different fingers on each one. It's a good habit to get into now for when you start playing super fast later. A great exercise is playing triplets on one note 321 321 321 321 or 123 451 234 512 345 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 07:23:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Logic, but i've heard good things about reaper. Maybe it has the best bang for its buck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 07:22:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorta reminds me of a CZ1000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 07:19:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a friend when I was living abroad who was female and stood out (she was blond). Whenever guys would stare and drool at her on the bus she'd start picking her nose... and then slowly eat it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-27 03:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Find a place that sells "Hot Bread Kitchen" like RUSS   DAUGHTERS 
179 E. Houston Street, DAG HAMMARSKJOLD PLAZA. It's worth it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-27 02:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In bacon grease!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bon Bons w/o Molds? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-26 07:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I make bon bons without molds by dipping the ganache in chocolate or dripping the chocolate over it? Can someone walk me through any  common mistakes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-25 18:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Smoke Joint in Ft. Greene or Hometown in Red Hook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-25 16:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brooklyn is big and it will take a long time to get from parkslope to Williamsburg for brooklyn brewery (plus Williamsburg sucks). Instead of brewery take him to krafthaus (or maybe it's with a C) on 5th ave right near superhero. Skip wisk and just goto the Bowery when you're in the city </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-24 19:27:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do (or would) your team-mates  feel about you talking out to the public either in your book or something like this? I've heard that it's pretty much frowned upon in the culture. Is that true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-19 19:43:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I second Damascus!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 17:39:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know this guy - his name is Eliano Braz https://twitter.com/Elianobraz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 23:15:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> looks like someone read Ruhlman's 20 ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 23:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But once you brown them shallots get nice and mellow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-07 02:51:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's funny. I'm actually having the issue with my own accordion now. The reedblock probably isn't properly seated is my guess. Open the bellows up to check it out if you know what you're doing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-01 05:31:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kebap is the turkish spelling. You misspelled kebab in your language. . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-01 04:28:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hotsauce in a glass of dark beer. Try it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-29 03:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes - Here is an eclectic concert-party in Williamsburg. Music-wise it pretty much has it all ranging from psychedelic soul to high-octane Balkan party music. 

Muchmores 9pm-1am on Friday 
https://www.facebook.com/events/402089213253765/   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-23 20:49:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> downvoted - Not in Brooklyn!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-10 02:54:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trke nasl biliyorusun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-07 04:18:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  As for spices I think you would be fine if you just goto to the store and buy the following:

* Cumin
* Paprika
* Cayenne
* Cinnamon 
* Nutmeg
* dried mint
* oregano
* Bay Leaves
* thyme \ Rosemary 
* tumeric 

Perhaps also:
* Coriander
* Cardamom
* Saffron
* fennel seeds
* mustard seeds
* Cloves
 
I hate buying spices in America because you can't try them first. As far as I'm concerned they're all terrible so it doesn't make a difference if you get them from one place or another.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-07 03:04:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> amazing left hand! The guy is clearly a huge virtuoso but I missed the ornaments that really make Balkan music what it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-07 00:31:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My advice (as an accordionist) is wake her up with a home cooked breakfast, not accordion music. . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-06 22:10:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they're doing a thing over in IAMA - http://redd.it/1nus49 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tipsy Oxcart -- Pauline's Kyuchek [World ] (2013) Balkan party music from NYC </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-02 02:36:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Exciting Balkan tunes from Brooklyn, NY. USA </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-02 02:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-29 20:06:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's probably a cop who was on his way to the Tunnel to Towers run. . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Order-of-events for mushroom filling </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-24 23:54:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi!

I'm making a minced mushroom filling for Iranian "sambusas" kinda like baked samosas. I'm wondering if I should sear the mushrooms whole first or if I can mince them first raw and then cook.

What I did this time:
Minced shallots   browned in butter\oliveoil 
Minced 'shrooms and added to the pan and seasoned 
I was also going to add walnuts but forgot! (woops...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-23 20:27:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Floyd in Bklyn Heights - Bocce! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-23 18:22:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> www.tipsyoxcart.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-16 00:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ruhlman's 20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-04 03:17:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sound designer\accordionist here. Feedback suppressors, if you're *very* lucky address the symptom but not the overall problem. When you get to the venue you need to consider your placement in relation the speakers. Are you playing in front of the speakers? This will create feedback in nearly any system. Perhaps you're mics are gained to high. If you address these two things and it's still a problem, then you can look into some EQ - For this individually raise each band until you find the one that corresponds with the root frequency of the feedback. What band enduces feedback. Once you find it, you can bring it back until the feedback is reduced. It's much better to manually counteract it like this than to use a feedback suppressor in attempt to address it automatically (which probably won't work). I've never met a sound professional  who uses one of these devices.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-04 03:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hanon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 17:58:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The other day I saw what looked like an engine but it had writing on it saying it was "Squad Company 5" or something like that. What purpose do these companies serve?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Neighboring landlord blocking fios </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-31 00:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Long story short i had a FOs install apt today and mobilyan showed up. After 7 hours of calling customer support I finally reach the executive support line where I'm told that fios isn't available in my building dispite prior notices of availability. 

Later I get a call from the guy in the truck who tells me he actually came but the neighboring landlord refused to give permission to run the line past his building! I went to the restarant downstairs in the building next door where they refused to give me their LLord's contact info and mentioned that I'm not the first person to complain. I did some detective work and found the guy's address and associated phone number. I tried calling but nobody picked up. 

What should I do!?
Isn't he in violation of section 228 of public service law by denying a utility? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tipsy Oxcart </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-10 06:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-03 19:48:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've travelled to the furthest reaches of [Svaneti](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Svaneti) and yet the biggest culture shock I've ever faced is in LAS VEGAS. It's like Mars. Last time I was there, I witnessed an interaction between a young girl who had just gotten back from a rave at around 9:30 am and and older gentleman in the elevator of the Luxor. The girl said "I too so much E and now I can't remember my room number." Then she asked the older man "are you rolling?!" and he said "Have you every heard of Jesus Christ?"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-27 03:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tipsy oxcart. Balkan party music </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Custom backpack/luggage/case alterations in NYC? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-26 15:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi all

I'm looking for a place that can add a padded hip strap (camping style) to a heavy-duty cordura instrument case of mine that must support approximate 35 lbs. 

Tips?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-20 02:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe ask the folks at the chelsea garden center? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-05 04:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Red Hook is a laid back freelancer who makes metal sculptures on the side and  is always 15 minutes late... fuckin' B61  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-09 07:24:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FOOD HERE IS AMAZING! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-09 07:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or Nice Green Bo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-09 07:23:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's probably Uzbek? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-09 07:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> these are guidebook "best NYC eats" and not the true hidden gems. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Def not serbs. He is probably talking about the very very small handful of radicalized muslims in post-conflict former yugoslavia who were in conflict WITH orthodox serbians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-09 15:30:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's a greater-than sign. . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 14:53:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Macerate away!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 14:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If its only changing the color it's probably not real or at least not fresh. To use saffron properly you need to grind down a few threads and then dilute the powder in water, or sometimes rose water or orange blossom water. Then add the liquid to your dish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 03:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alice Ct maybe ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-26 20:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best I've ever gotten was when I was stuck in traffic on the Bklyn bridge. The cabby looked into the mirror towards me and squinted. He said "You are Jewish... yes?" Trapped in the moment, I wasn't sure how to proceed but I decided it was best to be truthful and after a moment I replied, "Yes..." There was a long pause.

Finally, he looks back into the mirror and simply declares. "At home we fight, but here we are friends. We have the same food."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-24 22:58:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would do this:



These could be in any order:
1 day devoted to the museums others have mentioned and central park.

1 day starting in Union square, walking down through the west village, crossing over to the east village and then perhaps down further through soho for dinner in chinatown. You could also do that all, get a late lunch in chinatown and then continue across the brooklyn bridge and see dumbo, bkyn bridge park, brooklyn heights and get dinner around there. There's great middle eastern food that's cheap on atlantic ave. and many other options on smith st. 

You could easily split the above day into two and make that the third day. Instead of wasting your time in the tourist wasteland that is timesquare, what about finding a theater experience more true to downtown NYC? Check out the Saint Ann's Warehouse in dumbo (you could walk there over the Manhattan bridge from china town after your lunch!) Look in the village voice or timeoutNY for listings. Or sleep no more. Or The Flea Theater. 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seamless Tips? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-21 19:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone know if the typical delivery man in NYC actually receives a tip if you list one on seamless? I usually hold off and tip cash because I'm not sure...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-18 13:31:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brooklyn is a VERY big place. Where in brooklyn are you looking for takeout? Your best bet wherever you are might just be going to seamless.com and choosing from your local options there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-16 23:54:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's total bull. It's Tahini-based!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-15 17:15:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There isn't really any good food or shopping on SOHO or the Village. . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 15:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4 days is NOT ENOUGH AT ALL for istanbul! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-11 05:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there are some places on canal in the around broadway\chambers\etc.. that offer gear  that I suspect is on the level you're looking for although if B H doesn't satisfy you, I don't know what will. Some of these places have speaker rooms, but then again so does B H  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-01 17:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> craigslist, trulia
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-22 16:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no no. The best torta is from the folks who sell goat ones from a little cart in Red Hook in the spring\summer!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-02 22:27:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate when people pronounce istanbul "eeesshhhtanbul" in an effort to seem worldly when in reality they are just wrong.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-17 20:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Listened to it. I don't think it's arabic. The only thing I can say confidently is that it's DEFINITELY not a Turkic language. Some of the sounds seem reminiscent  persian to me but I don't think it's farsi. I wonder if maybe it's Tajik?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Trains Officially Shutting Down at 7pm.  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-10-28 15:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL there are bees that make blue honey by harvesting waste from M Ms manufacturing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-10-07 18:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-21 13:06:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wendel once approached me as I was waiting for a friend and gave me a one-on-one tailoring workshop as I helped him re-pin the hem of his dress... I remember him complaining that the fabric he uses is becoming too popular and is selling out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-06 14:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's also a new place in Gowanus that's similar to 3rd ward, although I forget its name    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-25 00:39:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't even consider staying in the Sperdorm! Live somewhere where you can live the life, learn Turkish, etc...

If you have a decent budget (maybe up to 700 lira a month) try Cihangir, galata, etc... You can also try living  in Tarlaba for a different experience if you want full immersion  (IE living in a Kurdish\Roma ghetto).It's cheaper there and in a few other places like Kasmpaa than in the trendy neighborhoods but requires some more street smarts and Turkish skills. Student-oriented places can also be found in Bekta or, of course, near Boazii.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-08 18:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've heard that the CIA uses colonial williamsburg as a kind of practical field training ground for agents headed on assignment to foreign countries. Practicing how to follow people, dewdrops, and the like. Did you ever witness this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-20 00:30:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went to high school with the creator of this site!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-19 21:28:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is new york, not Berlin... I don't know if you'll find a squat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL how to make kim chee </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-18 04:04:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-16 18:27:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> quite a common sight in Istanbul too:
 http://mw2.google.com/mw-panoramio/photos/medium/3515933.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-16 05:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where did your family live before the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-14 02:02:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As far as I'm concerned the best brunch is at a place called "Home Made" in Red Hook (bklyn). Only open on weekends

http://homemadebklyn.com/home_made_bklyn/home_made_bklyn.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-30 08:59:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trke konuan bir Amerikan'm (Trkiye'de okudum). Yani tabii Trkiye hakknda ok eyler biliyorum, arkadalarm diyorlar ki onlardan ben stanbul'un sokaklar daha iyi biliyorum.  Tamam. . . Trkiye'yi dunuurken kafama ilk geldii ey. . . . .  knefe ;-p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-14 18:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about "Cok Duydum" - I'm full! that's the most useful turkish phrase I know, although I'm also partial to "Dil dile deemeden dili renilmez"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-16 18:49:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> couchsurfing.org! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-16 17:11:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Key tips from someone who has lived in Turkey...
* Do not stay in Sultanahmet, which is a giant theme park for tourists. Stay in Beyoglu. I've heard good things about the "World House" hostel and also "Neverland," which was the cheapest and attracted the most quirky and interesting guests at the time.
* the couch surfing network in Istanbul is great. Use it. At least goto a meet up  
* Your budget will be greatly reduced if you don't drink. Alcohol is heavily taxed and very expensive. 
* Immediately buy the "Istanbul Eats" book or visit their blog (same information). Use this and you won't have a bad meal. 
*Spend more time in Turkey\Istanbul than you think you'll want to. 
* From the airport you will save a lot of money if you take the "Hava" shuttle instead of a cab. Just make sure it's going to the right place (probably "Taksim")
* Goto the following neighborhoods: Taksim, Galata, Tnel, Cihangir, Balat\Fener, Kadky, Karaky, one of the islands if the weather is nice, perhaps Arnavutky or Rumeli Hsar\Saryer. 
* Save money by taking public transit. The bus system is great as are the trams, metro, ferries. The *Dolmu*es, a kind of shared taxi, will especially save you money and time
* Bargain 
* Try to go elsewhere in Turkey... Kapadokya. The Coast. If you are really intrepid and adventurous perhaps the South East. Skip Ankara.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-09 21:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> college "circus" scenes are very different from professional circus and especially from studying clown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-03 23:57:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why, when you visited my highschool to read from your book several years ago, did you start the talk with degrading comments about the student body and then proceed to cross out lines from your book as you read it to us?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-02 18:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brooklynite #2 here... "The Nelson Mandela" projects are a fictional name given to the Gowanus houses which are hardly "deep" in brooklyn (they are in cobble hill\Carroll gardens). 

There was a raid there though from your friends in the DEA... http://www.brownstoner.com/blog/2010/10/huge-drug-bust/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-02 07:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> head to jackson heights. best indian food in the city (--jackson diner) then check out the patel brothers supermarket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-10 21:00:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Twisted Soul? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Film Addressing Transphobia in Turkey </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-10 20:48:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-22 06:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1: Trke biliyor musun? 
2: What city do you teach in? Is it in the US (aka Paterson) or somewhere actually in Turkey? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>