<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6794</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What movies or series of movies should everyone see in their lifetime? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:34:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:05:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LARPing just got extreme.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:55:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any time a girl has talent. Like they can dance, are a good athlete, plays an instrument...  I'm a goner  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 08:32:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The original Mad Max movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 08:12:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The rotating hallway fight in Inception.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 04:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has no one said April O'Neil?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 18:19:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know I'm probably in the minority with these people but: Nick Swardson,  Greg Giraldo, Aziz Ansari, and David Cross. I like both David Cross and Aziz as actors... Just not comedians.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:01:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My biggest problem with the film is the fact they changed a major theme of the book, which is fear of the unknown. 

SPOILERS 

In the book the buggers attacked earth because they thought that humans were an inferior race and kind of stupid, only because they could not communicate the way they did. In the film they say they attacked because they ran out of resources and needed water or something which means that humans have some sort of knowledge of the aliens. 
The whole war is started because they could not communicate and did not understand each other. That's why Ender feels remorse and takes the baby bugger. 

Feel free to correct me if I'm wrong. That is what I got out of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Flash vs. ToonBoom? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Cabin! From what I have heard most animators continue to use Flash since they are familiar with it and have been using it for a while. Zach and Chris said they recently started using ToonBoom. What would you recommend for someone just starting out in animation? Is ToonBoom the way to go since it's geared towards animation specifically?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 19:12:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Speaking as someone who lives in California there a few things you/she need to know. Yes, everything here is much more expensive. I live in the south Bay region and pay around $860 a month for a studio apartment. Fairly big enough but still. Also, there are good areas (redondo beach, marina del Rey, Irvine, Glendale) and there are bad areas (LA, Compton, Hollywood). Moving here won't give you any more opportunities unless you already have your foot in the door. If you have already been talking to some of these companies and are interested in giving you a job, go for it. But if you come here looking for a job you will probably fail. LA is full of people hoping to "make it" and only around 13 percent actually succeed. Look at your current circumstances and decide if that's the best decision for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 05:01:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sub here. The teacher said to specifically have the students sit in their own seats. A student asked if they could move and I told them that their teacher said to stay in their seats. The student actually responded "no she didn't". I was like really? I have the paper right here!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cory translator </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 05:11:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are some words Cory has used and their actual usage. 

For example: prestige - pristine 
Stunt devil - Stunt double 
...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Question for the Cast and Reddit </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 22:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey gang, I am just curious as to why you started a company together? What was the reason that led to this decision and how has it helped you financially or otherwise? Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:01:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have them on while on long car rides. Makes them feel much shorter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 04:02:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where's pigpen?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:11:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kenshin Himura  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:01:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not necessarily weird but I find women who are talented very attractive. Like if you are good looking but also can sing, play an instrument, are good at sports, or can dance... You rocket to the top of my charts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 21:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here are some great gems on the DS: Ghost Trick: Phantom Detective, 999, Dragon Quest IX, Robocalypse, and Elite Beat Agents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 08:14:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd love to see the Drunk Cory/ Bacon Story! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 03:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Flip it and rip it. 
Diving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 17:38:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beni Benimle Birak by Manga.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 21:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At my church there was a kid named Grinnen Barret. Pronounced grin 'n bare it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 18:31:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's alright. You might want to check out some prov videos though and see what really good looks like. Might I suggest NachoTHPS and then click on links from there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Um, I'm not sure if this is a joke... Considering the day. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 19:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Avatar. Once you get past the special effects, it's a goofy story with a bunch of clichd characters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:43:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Google Thugpro. You're welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Google Thugpro. You're welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:42:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Google Thugpro. You're welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's actually a mod to THUG2 called THUGPRO that's takes all the levels from thug1 and 2, thps4, thaw, and more. The community is growing. Check it out! Just Google it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 02:56:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you to the team for making this! I am reliving a huge part of my first gaming experiences. I hope the community builds again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 02:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember Create-a-review. That's was the place for the community! I remember hanging out with the Tho guys. Tek was really cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 01:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just some beautiful animation there. I love how Quagmire just stands there stone faced, unblinking. There's so much liveliness in the characters, especially if you remove Peters mouth. Walt Disney would be proud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Katy Perry Superbowl </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 00:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-02 01:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We did! He signed it "all my love" and his signature :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 09:09:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was for the premier of his new movie Suburban Gothic. He encouraged everyone to come in their pajamas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Look who my wife and I just met... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 05:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 03:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Mcpoyles go clubbing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-18 21:26:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Driving in San Francisco is HORRIBLE! There are one way streets everywhere. If you miss your turn or your entrance to the grocery store, you have to go up two more blocks, turn left, get on the highway, merge to a different Highway, take the exit, and left turn, just to get to the turn that was 3 feet behind you. Not to mention... It's all uphill  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-15 08:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shame. Also, spiderman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-23 00:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was this written by Charlie Kelly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 18:06:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I apologize in advance if someone has already posted this (I didn't read all the comments :/). But he strikingly resembles his own master (Ben kenobi). Foreshadowing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-30 03:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The same  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-27 14:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No joke. We have this in the men's bathroom at my university. It's a Christian College BTW  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 03:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Liberal Studies - Half the idiots in here will be teaching your children. Good luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-17 18:19:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When repairing a computer,
Have you ever come across a virus that looks like something from a movie. Like really evil looking and frightening? on the opposite side, have you found anything that was just downright hilarious? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-14 00:20:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like he's a padawan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it possible for there to be a Star Wars themed world in the next Kingdom Hearts? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-03 06:25:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Have humans slowed or stopped the evolutionary process? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-06 01:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-04 19:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The same goes with video games? Do you play them in chronological order or when they were made? Example:Kingdom Hearts or Metroid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When watching a series of movies for the first time, do you watch them chronologically or in the order in which they were made? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-04 19:03:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For example Star Wars. Do you watch New hope, Empire, Return and then the prequels? Or prequels first?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-02 18:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of my favorites is "graffiti is for fags"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is some of the funniest bathroom graffiti you have read or seen? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-02 18:12:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Graffiti found in the bathroom stalls or on the walls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-29 02:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of the Facebook girl meme.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This had to have been on purpose... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-28 15:56:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-03 18:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He must be writing the trombone part  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-28 08:03:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well..... welcome to reddit i guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Friend just posting this to Facebook saying "My son has some explaining to do when we wakes up..." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-27 22:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-20 07:30:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Zoids. It was a really underrated show on cartoon network and a lot of people I know have never even heard of it. Probably because it was on at like 5:30 in the morning. Maybe it could get some sort of following after being on Netflix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>