<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1885</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you ever ride RAGBRAI? Where in iowa are you from? When were you last back?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:16:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you seen everything a deer as ever done? Have you seen them poop on their children? I'm sure that happens sometimes. Have you seen then give birth? http://25.media.tumblr.com/ae7b461cb5634cbdbc0e61d731858649/tumblr_mjv01jjGTq1r9odzco1_500.jpg shit happens, twat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The prince of darkness has antlers that cease to stop bleeding, hail him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL species in the cervidae family, such as deer and elk, lose and grow a pair of antlers every year. When the antlers are shedding the velvet covering them, they drip blood for a few days straight. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:17:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay but honestly you should watch True Detective for the real plot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My man!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 04:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bee probably high as fuck too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:39:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DOOM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:15:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you have a protocol set up for if there were words written on Pluto's surface?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  ":c"

-that fish  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 02:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clean up on isle five.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This has Michael Scott written all over it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 02:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being at the front for Kendrick a few hours early,  I got to see Alabama Shakes real close up. Being that close, I also was touching the VIP walkway. I had been keeping my eyes peeled for a few celebs to maybe have their fame melt off onto me, but ended up forgetting about that for a bit. That was until a man walked by in overalls and a straw hat, a man I immediately recognized as Matt Shultz from Cage the Elephant, one of my favorite fucking bands. I screamed,  CAGE THE ELEPHANT after he had passed and he turned around and gave me a huge smile and pumped his fists. I also yelled I FUCKING LOVE YOU and he did another wave. That was pretty fucking cool. Then Chance the Rapper walked by and high-fived me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's the best/funniest way to unconventionally answer the phone? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 02:14:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 23:55:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Homie,  it could be THE Wrong Way Wooten!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 23:51:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HERE IS A VIDEO FROM 2009 https://youtu.be/JPaIEmiyG7o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As promised, here's the video of Backwards Bike Riding Baton Blackman, he's done this every day for at least 6 years. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 23:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 14:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like a damn water dancer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For about 6 years now, I haven't gone more than a week without seeing Backwards Bike Riding Baton Blackman in my local parking lot. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 12:17:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ant-man's main villain SHOULD be named Spider-Man </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You meet someone who says they're you from another reality. What do you ask first? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NSFW to be safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 08:19:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RemindMe! 1 day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What, in your opinion, is the best brand of microwave popcorn? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 18:44:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was an episode of the original Pokemon where Ash finds a group of Pikachu and decided his Pikachu would be better off with them. He essentially "Whitefangs" (Airbudding for the illiterate) Pikachu and cries as he does it. My mom wouldn't let me watch it because I would cry too hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 05:38:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did you get involved with Ninja and Yolandi of Die Antwoord? I loved seeing you in Ugly Boy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 06:31:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that's what this is, I was there too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 03:46:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We can go toe to toe on bird law and see who comes out the victor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 03:45:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the hell is nightcrawlers? It's not what it sounds like. It sounds like you crawl around at night like goddamn worms. I guess it is what it sounds like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 03:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mr Jon bon Joni himself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:28:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your ruining this for OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:49:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When rob trujillo played enter the sandman I lost my fucking mind  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is what showing up early for the Superjam gets you! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 09:53:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or just skip them, like world war 5 did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hm. I thought you were going to go with some like along the lines of hell actually being empty until the end of the first person's 100,000 years. Anyone snide enough to ask for the spoon got to help run hell from the inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 09:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't slept for ten days because that would be too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 09:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't slept for ten days because that would be too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If you could replace snapping with any other sound effect, which would you choose and why? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 03:49:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:46:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is probably the most 2010's thing you'll ever read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 08:37:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your home bar is the exact same as mine. I had been tapping your back button for more than I would like to admit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 04:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Smarter Every Day! How did you start doing your show, and how did you get access to so many fantastic facilities? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Jesus Is My Anchor" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My little brother's (3) daycare lady had on a shirt that sported proudly, "Jesus Is My Anchor." To my amusement, I began to think about what an anchor *actually* does. It hold a ship back from going anywhere. Just like closing one's mind with religion holds back the possibility to learn anything new. Jesus was the anchor holding her back from an open mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 00:47:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The time warp episode on skating is really cool too. https://youtu.be/rjScAVh7q0o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I don't know what happened, but that mouse didn't stand a chance. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 17:09:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 02:32:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm getting real sick of these naked but covered ladies. Its like smelling candy bars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 09:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love your Trale Lewous character! How did you find Brube and does he still think you're a trailer louse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 09:23:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is kind of haunting. Watching this toy makes me realize how immense the real one was...and how there are still people in the rooms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 20:22:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Flush the fatties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:39:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait, that's NASCAR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I would buy the game Super Race Brothers; opening the Mario Kart universe to the levels and characters from Smash Bros. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:35:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 06:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I lined those pages with $10,000! There's always money in the porn box! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 18:48:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't you think it was unfair for Amy to get mad when she was stuck for 30 but you waited for 2000 and didn't complain? What's it like to kiss another actor with such passion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 19:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "That sucks" or "sucks to suck." As a writer, there's nothing more infuriating than lazy, thoughtless, uncreative sayings when I have an actual problem. To be honest, it really sucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 19:18:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "That sucks" or "sucks to suck." As a writer, it's infuriating when people cop out say something as lazy and as thoughtless as this. I mean, it really sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 04:02:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait, they haven't banned you? I thought using any proxy would cause Netflix to ban you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:40:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you started doing your high-voice interpretation of the audience during your show, were you afraid of how they would react? The real audience, not your voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:50:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And that's how I met your mother  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see you've played knifey-spooney before! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 19:45:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to think of it as sharing what I have to offer (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 19:15:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I posted this at like 3 am last night but thought more people would see it if I deleted and reposted during the day. So you're right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If fucking only. This was my friend's conversation actually, and he said the most they ever talked about was homework. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lol be my sperm donor lol </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 05:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Nick! I was lucky enough to be in the audience in Bloomington, IN last month to hear you lay it to our governor for an hour and a half. I laughed/clapped my ass off. I've been trying to apply paddling my own canoe to my every day life. My friends and I actually waited in the lobby to try to get you to read part of a script we were working on. My question is, how can someone make an impact on people they don't know? How did you know cancelling your Indianapolis show would make as big of an impact as it did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 19:04:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought of myself as a big macho scary movie fan until I watched the canal alone at 3 am. The final scenes had me with my blanket up to my eyes, which were as wide as they could be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 20:53:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Prepare yourself. [Eric Wareheim's CREEPIEST music video.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aV7VNhzFLOQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 14:38:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay don't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spanish Book Snapchats </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 05:24:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What my teacher wrote could be the grade and the number. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 21:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it possible for someone [19F] to become addicted to my [19M] orgasms? [3 months] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it possible for someone [19F] to be addicted to my [19M] orgasms? [3 months] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it possible for someone to become addicted to orgasms? (X-post from /r/sex) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:31:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it possible for someone to become addicted to orgasms? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:21:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 01:35:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if i'm both? por que no los dos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 06:37:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did you scare the shit out of me as a child? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do I get rid of the virus on my computer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you think I'm stupid? Hostess had the blood buy back system implemented immediately after twinkies came back into business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:17:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll use your children's umbilical cords as straws as I drink your blood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Redditors who are at least semi-famous on a social network site, (ex. twitter, vine, instagram) how do you deal with the hundreds of replies directly to your phone? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How would you finish the sentence, "If I've said it once, I've said it a million times, --"? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How would you finish the sentence, "If I've said it once, I've said it a million times, --" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 18:52:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I knew what this was immediately, this is that weird egg movie where they fly logs like planes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-19 19:07:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Gordon, why didn't the duck cross the grill? He didn't want to be a roast duck. Also, how do you feel about using cream of potato in gravy for biscuits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:40:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Over the summer off the coast of South Carolina, my father and I witnessed a red ball appear floating miles at sea from our condo balcony around 11:30 at night. Of course we thought it was a flare and wondered what we could do to help this lost ship, but the red ball remained visible for a few seconds until going out. About 15 minutes later, the same red ball appeared, then split into two floating balls out at sea. Have you ever heard anything like this before?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Me peeing into the shower stream to hide the sound of me peeing in the shower has the same logic as money laundering </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:39:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 20:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eating biscuits and gravy covered in mustard changed the way i looked at both individually. Imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-14 01:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I may or may not have went through a phase where I would create fake pizza coupons, then when the driver shows up i tip them and they don't know the company well enough to not accept it. I also created a bunch for drive throughs and would say i took an online survey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can already feel the welt from reeming my knee on a brass jawbone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 19:54:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no! It's "idle-glass-of-water girl!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spider-Man sounds like the perfect villain for Ant-Man if he didn't already exist. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 19:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 21:49:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mr. Nobody. I know sometimes when a movie is overly complicated just to be complicated it adds the feeling that the producing team is trying too hard, but with Mr Nobody I felt as though i was trying to solve a mystery called what the fuck is going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 19:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did you quit Franklin and Bash, besides the fact that every episode is essentially the same? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Things You Wish You'd Say To Your Ex </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 19:38:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 09:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was eleven I wrapped my pecker in scotch tape, starting at the head and spiraling down. Once I got to the base and the now purple crooked toothpick was beginning to hurt, I knew mistakes had been made. So um, scotch tape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 00:57:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Riff Raff. I bought my girlfriend a ticket for her and myself to see him 2 Christmases ago, thinking he was funny in anything I'd seen him in. He had FOUR OPENERS, then I realized I thought he was funny because he was joking with his routine and lifestyle but when he came out and danced in his dumb clothes it wasn't a joke anymore. Plus he poured Croc into my underage girlfriend's mouth. Riff Raff if you're reading this I hate you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 19:15:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh shit! Now I have to clean my closet to look for them :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's a past fad you still stand behind? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 19:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-28 06:20:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On toga day of my senior year, a strange autistic kid asked me if togas were flammable. He then asked the teacher for a lighter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thanks, I wouldn't want to slip </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-27 01:55:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was it like going through that woodchipper? Were you okay?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 15:01:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rick and Morty season 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 21:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you know William "Bill" Robinson? He was my great grandfather from Indianapolis, and was also a Pearl Harbor surviver.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-21 04:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you know your city is a level in Sniper Elite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:42:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ohai johnny, how did you get into making YouTube videos? Also what country are you from? Thanks, you're my favorite customer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 21:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want to move shoes from one place to another, it looks like lifting shoes will be your only option </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-14 18:01:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If me creating an earth in my head and imagining life on that planet is the same as us existing, do the people I gave free will to in my brain fall out of existence as soon as I think of something else? Are we just waiting for someone to forget about us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 20:17:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Working in the year 1 AD probably made this way less special  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why, what is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-10 20:08:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your arms fling up like a happy dandelion of love, good work pal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 16:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I watched her eat a plate of pretzels out of the bag with a little cup of ranch next to her to dunk them in. I had looking past her chubbiness until then. I'm shallow guys hi  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 15:29:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As far as I can tell, its always. Maybe its just consistent enough for me to imagine its always. The tone haunts my dreams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 15:05:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What we're actually watching is a hate crime in the making. The turtle radiates contempt for the cat and will stop at nothing to see him fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mystery Notification Sound Every Few Minutes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-05 06:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is driving my absolutely crazy, my notification sound goes off every 5 or so minutes with no new notifications coming through. I can't seem to find the place where notifications are reminded, so that may fix it. I have Flow Lite and Twilight running always, so if anyone else with these apps has had something similar please help me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-04 09:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Salty Spittoon episode. I'll have you know I stubbed my toe  while watering my spice garden last week and I only cried for twenties minutes. Plus there was a place called mega weenie hut junior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 20:23:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard a recorded Demetri Martin standup routine where you played a piano or sang in the background or something like that. How did he get you for that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-27 07:15:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> woo iowa! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-21 19:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What were your inspirations when you were younger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 19:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is Gillian Jacobs as dope in real life as she is at Greendale Community College? Followup question, when you gave your show at Bonnaroo, did you kick it with Hannibal? And I think i gave you a perfect handshake in passing on the farm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 20:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chris, was the tattoo of the kid urinating on an FM radio and a television drawn on in sharpie? Thank god the AM radio was floating on the magic carpet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-19 20:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you ever get a lawyer for the boner police? My real question is, could you please please please disclose any and all information regarding Rick and Morty season 2? I'm almost half way sick of rewatching the same ten episodes. Down with FM radio and thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's one sentence that always ruins your day? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-18 23:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is Pepsi okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> On planets that speak English from movie universes like Star Wars and Guardians of the Galaxy, are we to expect they have a vast collection of music completely different than ours? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-18 18:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-18 17:20:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is how I Am Legend started </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 05:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fuck yessss, then Zombino spits some mad lyrics for 40 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Donald Dies in the TRAILER of The Lazarus Effect! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 03:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not only do they kill him off, they show it in the TRAILER!! Olivia Wilde throws him into a metal cabinet and you hear him screaming as it bends inward, then Even Peters is seen later begging to know what happened to Niko, Donald's character. I don't know why Hollywood feels the need to kill off black characters first, but this time it hits a little too close to home. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=90GKwd10KRc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-14 19:55:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Roses are red
Verne is awesome
If you give me bacon
My butthole will blossom 

Too graphic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-14 19:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was 14, I was at Long John Silver's for the first time and had been checking out a high school girl in a small black skirt for 10 or so minutes. When her and her friends got up to leave, she leaned over facing away from me to show she WASN'T WEARING UNDERWEAR. LJS's has never been the same for me. 
EDIT: This story seems fake even in my own memory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey David! I'm Matt. 

After AD got cancelled, what was it like realizing how big of a cult following you had? How did you even find out how popular it was becoming? I mean, i imagine Netflix had some type of online data report that said something like, hey this kid in Iowa just watched all three seasons in two days. Hypothetical example. I remember seeing jokes about a fourth season 4 years ago and thinking they were as crazy as Firefly having another season. Unrelated story, i found the first season of Firefly on box set in my dad's closet and asked why he had it. He said his buddy let him borrow it a few years ago but never gave it back because he liked it so much. He then said he forgot about the show and can't wait to watch all of the new seasons. 

I know you had nothing to do with Firefly.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:22:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The crocodile was going to be in a commercial for a fire sale but they gave the part to the purple boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:16:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who the fuck ate your hard boiled eggs? Even if it meant taking a chubby, would you suck it up? 

Also Megamind is one of my favorite animated movies and deserved more recognition, you were my favorite space step mom from any Dreamworks film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for Cheap Cardigans </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 06:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm talkin' $10 or less. Single colors are fine, i'm just going to wear them open over a tee shirt anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-12 00:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sweet jism, look at that prism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mixed Feelings on Brixton Sew Cap Snapback </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-08 04:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.brixton.com/brixton-products/brixton-mens/brixton-mens-headwear/snapbacks/cavern.html

I was really into this snapback since my friend has a Brixton snapback I've worn and loved, but I scrolled to the right and saw how it fit that model's head and was swayed away from it. I'm a low budget college kid just trying to look good, i'm usually in loose cardigans and tees with skinnies but I think a hat like this will really pull the look together. So my question is, do any of you have any knowledge with this type of hat? What color would look good with a darker palate?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 19:45:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *chaos..... reigns* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-05 19:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Note to self: Use mew and mewtwo's birthdays from Cinnibar Island every year, instant fame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 16:00:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> South Park did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 06:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Back when the gamecube came out, I used to bite myself until the skin would break because I couldn't beat the fucking fantasy worlds in super Mario sunshine with the giant spinning blocks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-01 23:28:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But the laugh track tells me when to laugh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-01 10:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, the rare picture of a Japanese person from in the 1980's, when they were all 8bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 12:51:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Director George Romero? Who's that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-30 17:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Maisie, what's it like walking around with the same last name as me? Do people ever ask if we're related? I bet you get that all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Laptop companies should put one USB port upside down, so whichever way you try will either work or is right next to working. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 14:52:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 07:10:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those rodeo clowns will never know what hit 'em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 06:41:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The internet has newly informed me that Red Bull is two words\_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sideways, the Redbull bull is tiptoeing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-22 06:36:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-19 08:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is how i am legend started </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-08 17:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to think i knew, but now i'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 06:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Streetlamp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-30 16:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll forgive you this time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 22:22:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hell yeah, life after beth was really enjoyable for me but it's more of a black comedy than a horror movie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 07:58:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is normal in Peru  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-19 07:54:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe this to be fake  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 06:28:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 08:08:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pabu! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-15 21:43:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've seen Planes enough times to know this is El Chupacabra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-14 21:41:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've said this many times to many people, but The Walking Dead isn't even about zombies. My parents are disgusted at the idea of an undead show, but the antagonists are the humans. That's when it's annoying when they STILL try to make a suspenseful fight scene with walkers. No main characters will die in some bullshit 30 second beef with 2 walkers, stop pretending that's what's going to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If temperature is raised in an environment slowly, will natural selection create a heat-withstanding species? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-14 03:09:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:56:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kid's eyein that piece  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why are there no big canine species besides the wolf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-12 22:42:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See, I don't get it either. Maybe I've just known of her for too long. I didn't think she was hot when she was 14 and she still reminds me of Jackie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-09 23:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally there is an elegant, comfortable mitten... for cats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-07 22:55:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The hardest I've cried since I was a child was two weeks ago when I learned my best friend, the first person I met in college, took his own life. He went back to his hometown one night to go to a dentist appointment the next morning and never came back. When I texted him the next day his brother called me and said he saw I texted Anthony's phone and that I deserved to know what happened. Turns out his mom came home that morning to find him crying in the shed with a gun in his mouth. After she tried to pull the gun away, he put the gun in his mouth and pulled the trigger. I don't even want to be at this college anymore, the only person I spent time with is gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-04 06:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Threw a kitchen knife modern warfare 2 style and it bounced back off the wall, hitting me in the eyeball with the plastic handle end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 19:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How could Dexter spend 8 seasons becoming more human, connecting to his son only to leave him with a different murderer? And do you think Deb shooting you at the end of season 7 would have been a more bittersweet ending?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 19:04:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Michael! 

I've read that many of the scenes from Dexter had little improvisations you put into them, were there any memorable instances where the directors told you you went too far with yourself and crossed the line between Dexter and you? 

Also are John Lithgow's eyes less creepy in person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 16:49:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the earth's thruster, it'll push us off course if you light it too early! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-03 00:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had bad whiskey before, should I call someone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-02 16:38:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But if you mess up once it breaks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-02 07:35:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey man don't knock it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-02 07:31:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Am from iowa, can claim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The food came off the spoon in the shape of a spoon </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-01 16:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 14:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tan Ashley Tisdale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 14:44:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But this post is indeed about ferguson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 14:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dem layers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 13:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are indeed spoilerS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 22:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always imagined closed-off hollow mushrooms like this would hold some type of hallucigenic air inside  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 03:42:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trale Lewous, or trailer louse  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:02:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My best friend shot himself in the head in front of his own mother this morning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [image] Go sailing once in awhile </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-20 00:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 18:32:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Acura Ebola sounds like an Italian person saying I cure Ebola  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 16:53:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My hypothesis was that they all lived in the dorm's basement, but the temperate drop caused the humidity to disappear. Then they crawled up through the pipes to get to warmer territory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 16:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually know the answer to this! Their wings are the shape of a human ear when fully extended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 16:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> During high school I took them every night for a couple of years to counter the ADHD meds I was on. They work because they make you want to be tired, they feel like natural sleep is on its way if you lay down and relax. When I got to uni I stopped taking adderall except for special occasions so I stopped taking melatonin every night, and I can still sleep and I can nap like a fuckin' champ too. No insomnia my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 09:54:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hehehe there's a dick on your dog's forehead  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The quote is a bit off, "A ship is safe in harbor, but that's not what ships are for." -William Shedd </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 09:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 08:29:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Read curry 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 03:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Way ahead of you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> These are crawling all over my dorm </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-19 03:23:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-18 16:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If something like this did wash up to natives hundreds of years ago, white people wouldn't believe the stories anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The strength levels of my sleep pills happen to spell REM </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 06:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 03:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 07:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take to the seas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If earth was a simulation, what would the "overall stats" page look like? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 19:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 17:23:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 01:35:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exit Through the Gift Shop- A film edited and directed by Banksy about street artists. We watched this in our journalism class to prove how much a director's opinion can change the sense of a movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 16:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Princess mononoke ninetails </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-05 16:37:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But just remember if you ever wanted store bought weed, the furthest possible state from you now legalized it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 19:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 18:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sister is the baby in the ultra sound, 19 year difference in ages </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 18:52:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No,,,,, my sister is in the womb. My dad married a 25 year old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My sister's ultrasound </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 17:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 17:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I meant to mention in my post that whether it's true that fapping has anything to do with testosterone, I've placebo'ed myself into the position I'm in now. And I love it and hate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 16:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely, the benefits are fantastic. Usually. I don't want to sound like one of "those people" but working out, even at all, will help you let that energy out and sleep much better, I promise :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 16:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why didn't Helen Keller scream when she fell off the cliff? She was wearing mittens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The super powers exist, switching to hard mode </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 16:10:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been on easy mode for a about 2 months now, and I'm going to have to switch to hard mode. The super powers are real, and I've known for a few years but I seem to forget until after going over a week without an orgasm. I don't know about you guys, but I've known about the super powers for about 4 years now, ever since I saw one picture that said not orgasming for a week can double your testosterone levels. It's as if reading that picture made that a real fact. I've tried telling people about how horrible and weak I feel the days after fapping, and they've told me they fap with no such feelings. So whether this feeling we get after fapping is real or just made in our heads, one thing is for sure. The super powers are more than real. Orgasming in general has begun to make me feel weak, and casual sex with girls I'm not into is beginning to lose its thrill because I know how weak it'll make me feel. I'd rather go a week without an orgasm and lose my social anxiety altogether rather than have one night flings every week. Right now, right now is the first time I've hit the week mark without an orgasm, even if I haven't fapped in 2 months. And this is the first time I've felt the powers of testosterone. I hope this helps you fapstronauts who aren't feeling the super powers yet but haven't switched to hard mode, it's worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 05:02:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I had to do for karma was take a picture of my zune.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 04:51:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuckin hate yahoos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-01 17:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then who was phone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-01 10:03:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to need that back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-01 10:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey I think you might want to turn your belt upside down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 20:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If someone could link me to the iTunes version of this app that would be grand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The waffle on the fork isn't from the waffle on the plate </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 00:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lightning storm (x-post from /r/pics) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-27 03:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-22 01:15:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your mom is so dirty and stupid that when she was told to do the robot R2D2 got aids  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 17:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That scene doesn't make any sense. How would her leg getting crushed make blood come out of her mouth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 17:13:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Paper planes by MIA makes me feel like a rich drug dealer running the South American border countries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 16:14:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Season 5 still had the original Dan Harmon feel to it... Now we only have Jeff, Abed, Britta and Annie left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 07:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what mine was like, did you wake up feeling the anxious feeling that follows a relapse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 07:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is he okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Accidentally Had a Wet Dream </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-20 06:55:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a girl sleep in my bed last night; We didn't do anything sexual but I spooned with her until she left around 10 AM. Once she left, I fell back asleep and dreamed I ejaculated which lead to me cumming in real life. I know it wasn't on purpose, but when I woke up and realized what happened I felt as bad as if I had reset my badge for real. I feel weak and disgusting, and I know it doesn't count as fapping but it sure felt like it. Has anyone else experienced this after a streak of a few weeks? What mindset can help me feel less weak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-17 08:33:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see a praying mantis  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 04:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hehehe he thinks he's people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 17:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Ebola Cakes!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If we built a pipe along the circumference of the Earth's equator touching the ground at all points, what would happen if we added a meter to the pipe? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-09 17:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-08 16:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm confused. Did you use your brush as a way to turn the second dog into nothing but hair or what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 05:13:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, he's super dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 05:05:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's way less funny in real life than in Ace Ventura:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 22:07:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By the garden of Zeus give me a link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 21:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just somebody trying to get laid, nothing to worry about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-06 18:56:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 08:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay did Bill Murray get AIDS in that movie? Because he got some disease from a chimp's mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-04 23:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shark fin never fails  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 17:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I meant like, killing animals or having sexual urges at a very young age  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 17:25:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Decorative fruit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 09:32:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Come on, son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 16:21:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god my step grandma fucking screams so loud every time my half brother falls, she's ruining that child.On  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 15:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Throw EVERYTHING into the closet. Why would she look in there? On the off chance she does, have a backup pan because that you have to run off quickly and probably can't live there anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 15:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always wanted to be able to run into the woods all day during the 60's and my parents not call the police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-01 15:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those Facebook attempted spooky stats that say 80% of the time you wake up at night you're being watched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 17:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't look up, she doesn't like to be seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 16:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking scantrons. We can make computers navigate on Mars but they can't read pen on paper instead of pencil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-24 19:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Donna noble has left the library
Donna noble has been saved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 16:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is one of those attempts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 16:12:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine being down there exploring when a tsunami wave hits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 17:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was just getting something to eat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 15:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've seen your boobies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-15 01:33:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Michael Cera anytime he gets sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:08:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much can one banana cost? 10 dollars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-10 20:21:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Find me this without the upvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 20:16:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do I take my badge away? )': </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 05:28:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No self caused orgasms all of September, I can do this. Every time I break my anxiety triples and I don't leave my dorm, i've watched every LOTR and Hobbit in the past 3 days. Going 10 days feels so empowering, does going a month make it better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-04 05:24:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you stop yourself during the first week? WHY DO I SUBSCRIBE TO SO MANY PORN SUBREDDITS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Best Steam Games with Wired Xbox Controller? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 20:47:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 13:37:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I do cuz my asshoke friends tagged me in it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I saw Satan's face while passing some granite, for some reason the eyes bore into my core for sure. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-23 05:19:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-21 18:40:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Say hi to your mother for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-15 17:17:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice, I was using alien blue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-15 15:18:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can someone link me to a sticky page for the wiki or bible for this sub explaining the difference between easy and hard more please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-13 08:36:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BONESAW IS READYYY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-08 22:09:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What would getting a lawyer change?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Iowa OWI Advice, Leaving State Next Week </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-08 21:40:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First offence OWI, I'm 18 in Des Moines and blew a .134 outside of my house. I spent 12 hours in jail and the bail was $1300. I'm really worried because I'm moving to Indiana for college this Wednesday but my court date is next Monday, will I have to take classes in Des Moines or can I do those in Indiana? Also should I get a lawyer? My charges are Operating While Intoxicated- 1st offence, and driving left of center line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-06 22:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did they really? That seems somehow illegal... What if you just stood in the back, would they hold you there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-06 22:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you could put money around 50 or so. We bet my friend he couldn't eat 15 single hamburgers in 45 minutes but him winning meant he didn't have to pay for the hamburgers. It was a lose lose situation, he only got 10 in and had to pay $15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Have you ever been in a restaurant and realized you had no way to pay after you've eaten? How do the workers react? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-06 22:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember watching cartoons where the restaurant would make them go wash dishes in the back, but I think it's more of a "just leave" type situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-05 09:38:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want this to last, need you by my side  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-01 09:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't believe you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-30 03:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I go so hard they call me Mr. Go So Hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 19:23:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our old high school  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 02:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 02:11:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you go down the slip-n-slide? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-28 02:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's obviously a bee keeper biking to his job getting caught up in the festivities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-27 23:38:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was a very easy first year, my buddy has ridden it a few years though. It was mostly about the day drinking though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just rode across Iowa river to river with the /r/bicycling jersey! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-27 20:37:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-27 01:17:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I was as brave as you, you'll just leave home wearing anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:12:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me llamo t bone la araa discoteca </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-18 18:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just be homeless, scrounging through dumpsters and eating whatever you find. Also nibbling on walls and dry wood to dull down your incisors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-15 07:38:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does this cat remind me of David Duchovny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-02 23:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where were you when Pied Piper needed you most? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-02 21:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Rake scares me pretty good and plenty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-29 04:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My jaw can wiggle left and right about 2 inches on each side. I thought it was normal until I started getting horrible TMJ and my dentist said it wasn't normal, I guess jaws are just supposed to go vertically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-27 01:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sister Wives </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-26 01:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But they're paying to go to class, why not just go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are unspoken but vitally important rules for freshman going into a state University? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-26 01:19:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've read that after a test it's a very silly thing to sit back down, but I never would have known that. Any advice would be helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-23 16:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Zackeffron69me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-22 07:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I couldn't believe he was stopping his songs just to point out to everyone how many people liked him. I thought it was planned at first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-22 07:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I AM THE GREATEST FUCKIN ROCKSTAR IN THE WORLD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-22 03:37:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I read that too, which is why all of my friends called me stupid for mourning his death and that I shouldn't believe every death I hear on FOX news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-21 23:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Necessary  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-21 23:29:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ryan Dunn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-21 07:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is usually overlooked, but to this day there isn't a more scientific reason we sleep other than because we get sleepy. Why can't we go days without sleeping? Why do we get sleepy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-20 01:05:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When Kat dies in Halo: Reach. That was completely unexpected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-20 01:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god I thought I did something wrong when it was up in my face but I guess that happens for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-18 04:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually for awhile they put foot ringers at the end of caskets so people could push the levers with their feet if they were alive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-18 03:51:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When people say "in a minute" when they mean a large amount of time longer than a minute. "Hey man I haven't seen you in a minute." It's been like a year, I don't understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 07:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly this was the best show I've ever seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 18:24:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The movie Dragon Wars from a few years ago, utterly unwatchable. Not in the good way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 13:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 03:46:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you make a tissue dance?
Put a little boogie in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-07 03:10:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are..... Are they okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-27 06:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw an episode of friends like this once </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> These two things can't be done at the same time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-22 17:31:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-15 15:46:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you ever heard the theory that everyone is every person, when we die we live another's life somewhere else in time until we have lived every life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-10 06:44:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm watching Community on Canadian Netflix with the Hola Chrome extension, like right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 22:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How can people make posts like this? Does no ones family members have facebooks? That's all mine is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-07 05:22:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Her arm is a strange shape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-05 05:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Water charmander is the way to go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-23 00:27:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone know a subreddit full of actual fight videos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-19 00:54:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have any of you actually seen Birdemic? Second best worst movie of my time behind The Room. I'm Facebook friends with the lead guy, he has a whole 200 fans! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 19:37:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it "eye-la" or "ice-la?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-15 06:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bam Margera in the brown hat is too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-13 19:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I had a dollar for every frame in this gif, I would have 4 or so dollars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-10 04:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Chaos... reigns." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-08 15:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought this was Bob's Burgers on a tiny plastic tele </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-03 17:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think there's a line to find. I once pulled my ex girlfriend's pants up to hide her thong from the rest of my high school and we got into a fight  because she should "be allowed to show as much skin and not be sexualized by men in society," but sexuality is definitely needed, if not in small amounts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-02 16:55:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Calm down, Kit Walker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-01 21:03:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guess who will pay for one? This guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-01 04:33:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This reminds me of the onion ponds on the top of the devil's thumb in Holes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-25 05:59:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is there a 12 on her head? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-20 16:19:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Way to go, Portal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 04:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got tears in my eyes, I felt the love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My scruffy old man </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 03:25:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-02 19:40:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Her face looks a little ditsy in this picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The best desk graffiti I've seen </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-06 16:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-03 03:53:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *there's*
my Skate 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-30 01:49:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Paleasseeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-27 23:43:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to watch more things go into this machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I always saw a sloth on this cupboard when I was little. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-27 19:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-25 21:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine when THIS post gets 1776 upvotes, instant karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-11 01:04:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How terrifying is it on screen with Jeff Goldblum? Also is it Gold-blum or Gold-bloom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-11 00:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My favorite Important Things with Demetri Martin sketch you were in was at the little Shenanigans restaurant as Ben Franklin, yelling "Fuck you, Cathy!" What would yours be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-10 01:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do this every time I eat one of these, all I had to do was take a picture for Karma? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-06 22:01:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Raggedy man, goodnight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-06 18:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How does one proceed to buy such an artifact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-03 00:33:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yiss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who's helping bi lions? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-02 21:31:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-20 03:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Real^heroes^live with us^forever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-18 03:07:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take to the seas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-15 22:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The feels I feel  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This golf club wants me to use him. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-14 23:13:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-14 20:43:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's Dul Hill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-11 02:39:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dante's Peak has taught me that you need to leave your town immediately  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-10 02:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're gonna need to see this pornstar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-08 23:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are all the socks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-08 08:55:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> B82rez 2g4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-06 03:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're supposed to streamline dummies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 18:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Rake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 17:57:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If Stan Smith was Superman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-28 17:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got the results of the tests back, I definitely have breast cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-26 13:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I just watched the whole thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-23 23:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> David Spade wants his hair back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-23 22:11:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the purple patch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-23 16:25:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ghost of mole erhmentraut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 04:47:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Black ice is ruining this country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-21 01:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one where he changed a $1 to a $100, these 4 black guys just screamed and sprinted down the street and didn't stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 23:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck you Cersei. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-20 04:06:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Frederick Diggery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-19 15:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus, the memories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-17 05:41:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chaos reigns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-15 05:12:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...did he get blacker since Space Jam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-14 00:56:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dante's inferno is a severely underrated game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-13 15:29:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Each individual source </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-13 15:28:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely haunted  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 04:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those gifs just raise so many more questions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 04:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My grandma has the exact same thing. Somehow the ears were always better, you're right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 17:28:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh, barracuda  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-08 16:02:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate when I have gifs saved and then they get front page, I was so close </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 14:11:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look, look with your Portal eyes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 06:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do cats normally puke the much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 06:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Portal cat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 01:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's cool how the seat got more defined from you sitting on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 01:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The big toe on the right foot isn't shaped right, you could try to make it look more three dimensional </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 01:07:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bad Company 2 will forever be my favorite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 00:17:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was seriously on the front page maybe 4 days ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-04 00:10:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I met her when I saw her naked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-02 17:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chaos reigns  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-02 17:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck that shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-02 17:09:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where's Geatland? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-02 16:19:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's Nathan Barnett. Once you know what he looks like you'll start seeing him as extras in a bunch of commercials. Also, his skittles commercials are fantastic, I would recommend a search. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-02 04:02:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cry

pick up cat

karma </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-29 06:33:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rango- Untangled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-29 06:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya heard, with Perd. I'm Perd Hapley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-28 05:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone wanna give me a link to that Patagonia coat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-27 16:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would love to go up to him as a Boondock Saints fan instead of the regular WD fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-25 19:22:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never fully understood what that thing they hold and snap is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-25 07:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's getting used to sitting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-23 06:38:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One tiny blade of grass through my jailcell crack  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-23 02:13:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tell me why I just watched that whole video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-20 14:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trailer louse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-20 02:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is...is this a real person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-18 21:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can feel them on me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-12 19:22:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo DJ High-Tek, where you at my niqqa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-12 18:08:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deshi deshi basara basara  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-10 14:11:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Draw JFK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-09 06:50:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This makes my heart hurt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-06 21:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm okay with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-06 18:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oww ow ow ow ow owww </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-06 18:46:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Caaaaaaaarl! that kills people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-05 16:37:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not my fucking mother! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-05 16:37:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me underwears </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-05 08:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $55??? I got that poster for free for preordering it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-04 17:20:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then he ate his insides and said chaos reigns  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 21:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will write down your username and if she dies in the fourth season I will down vote every picture and every comment you ever make for eternity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 07:24:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chaos.... Reigns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-02 14:03:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/glitch_in_the_matrix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-29 17:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought that was a polar bear exhibit or something  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-29 09:44:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so long it took Goku a year to run from one side to the other  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-28 19:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> John lithgow is perfect for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-27 19:21:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look at those clavicles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-26 17:18:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I came here to say I'm pretending this actually happened  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-23 04:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jack's building is a giant swastika ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Had this as my background for a considerable amount of time. [slightly NSFW] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-22 04:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-21 07:22:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a version where someone recorded in a Russian accent "I am going to take some of your food now don't be scared eh eh eh eh" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-21 07:21:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got that reference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-08 19:07:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think about this; half of unlimited could still be seen as unlimited. The number you spend keeps going up, without end, as does the amoun for charity. No downside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-06 05:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And it came out to an even $9.50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-04 05:53:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you a little purple dog named Courage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 18:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Despereaux? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 03:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I seriously just went through this maybe 15 minutes ago, I get a snapchat from my buddy who I know the girl I'm crushing on likes, and he likes her. And the snapchat was just her face, meaning they were hanging out together. Identical reaction as the gif. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-24 08:12:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your girlfriend is 12 congrats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-24 00:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It does seem they are trying to trick us into thinking Vogel is the good guy, but I think she's the true villain over all. She is so okay with the killers, and she was the one taking Zach home, Dexter had some sex, then Zach was dead, and it showed Vogel with the brain. I think she's a bad guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 22:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-23 05:23:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I came here to make a Tangled reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-20 03:26:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If someone would make this into a iPhone 5 wallpaper I wil supply the snacks and karma </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-19 18:47:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How come when a cat walkes over the orange cat, it acts like its totally cool, but when I touch its paws ONCE, it runs and hides for 3 hours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-18 07:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Desmond, Juliet, and Jacob are missing. Why leave them out and put in Ilana on the left?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-18 07:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha Vincent looks silly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-18 06:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did anyone else find it weird that they had sex? Like I couldn't forget that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-16 00:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She fucked her brother  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-15 18:47:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I AM THE NIGHT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-15 05:08:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jennifer Anniston has a 2 or so minute strip scene, plus a scene where she and Emma Roberts teaches the fake son of the family how to make out. Plot galore! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-15 04:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except Relicanth  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-10 05:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Chaos reigns" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-08 07:08:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like FunnyJunk instead of facebook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-07 18:11:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's actually taking off his headphones, they just put the little sunglasses over his hands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-07 17:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you The Waitress? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-06 04:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lets stop and think, Ass Fuck 25 is the TWENTY FIFTH Ass Fuck in the series. The series is *so good* they made 24 additional movies after the first Ass Fuck. I have made it my duty to find and view the original Ass Fuck, and then hunt for the encyclopedia of Ass Fucks for the remainder of my lifetime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-05 17:06:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That stair glitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-05 15:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Baby cloud  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-04 08:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a freaky movie, Fire in the Sky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-04 00:25:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Maisie Williams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-04 00:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> \3 Charlie I miss you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-03 22:49:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They sure dress up nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-03 11:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Immediately thought of Grandma's Boy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-02 05:55:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disney channel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-02 05:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP's Michelle, she just met some kid and put it on /r/pics for karma </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:02:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that Micky? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-30 20:57:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Appa! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-30 20:54:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You just stole this from Sunday's episode of Dexter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 05:14:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sansa looks pretty hawt here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 05:14:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god the hotdog  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 03:52:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait, all I needed to do for karma was screencap Garry's Mod? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 03:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's my favorite season 4 episode, always has been </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-27 03:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why are you okay with letting Redditors oogle your mother? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-27 03:03:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My family walked into this exact restaurant. The waitress said we would be dining with another group of seven, at the same table. As we walked in we saw napkins and trash strewn about the restaurant. As a naturally anxious person, I was against sitting with people I didn't know, so we left. Easily the strangest place i never ate at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-25 21:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We all know the library planet episode was freakier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-25 15:40:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did OP take the picture  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 19:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pour a drink out for my niggas resting in peace  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 18:08:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where's the pizza </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-24 17:17:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine how many hours could have been saved in Skyrim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-22 02:56:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I'm biking through small towns across Iowa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is really dark for a poster at a gas station... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-22 00:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-20 07:49:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This guy looks like the beard version of Blake from Workaholics  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-19 10:24:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cooking Mama doesn't count </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-16 15:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't see you at the convention! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 18:36:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to also relate to David Duchovny  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 18:04:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They feel like sandbags </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 04:48:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anustart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-12 17:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm here to make a Rio joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-11 06:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't think of willem dafoe the same after seeing his dick and balls in Antichrist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 16:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As did I my friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-28 23:05:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I immediately thought of Lapras </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-28 18:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's still Cordelia in my eyes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-26 22:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The capital letters spell POOT USA down the side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Like has anyone passed this? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-26 07:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-26 06:47:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you dumb, that's the point of this fake video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-26 06:34:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chicle yum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-26 04:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice funnyjunk bookmarks my friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-26 00:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His arm looks severely long and deformed from the shadow... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-25 15:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I see this damn picture one more time, I'll call Zach Braff and make him unfollow me on twitter  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 21:27:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey! Who turned out the lights? Hey! Who turned out the lights? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 06:58:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That fuckers face is so accepting, like that shit happens to him every week  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 03:54:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice 10 year old repost  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 03:37:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We also have them in Iowa, OP isn't special </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-18 20:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Booker DeWitt is still my fave  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-18 02:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever I hear popped corn I think of Ned's Declassified 
*edit: which is incidentally also said by Lincoln  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-17 17:13:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice stain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-17 04:24:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't go through this stress again, I just can't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-17 00:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I sense some Jonathan Coultan in my future  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-16 18:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They actually did take South Park off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-11 05:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, Matt Smith already shaved his hair and announced he's leaving the show by the end of the year. So after John Hurt has his season or two, Matt Smith will use his regeneration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-10 16:31:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I see this stupid gif one more time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-07 05:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's up, teefury friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-05 04:19:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm confused, why is there a tardis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-04 04:45:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She doesn't even know about it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-04 01:45:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I LOVE TO FUCK I GOTTA FUCKIN PROLLEM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-01 05:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had at least 3 reddit stories in my local news. The Hitler teapot was on it today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 05:09:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm intrigued... But how would this get back at the husband at all? He's just slowly I investing bones, nothing happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-29 23:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excuse me OP, I've seen Homeward Bound 14 times, Chancw got hit by a porcupine and this didn't happen. We caught your little game, time to throw in the hat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-28 22:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Change temperature to match temperature outside, rake in the votes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 03:25:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're never too old to do heroin this morning  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-24 00:47:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fact that he recently shaved his Doctor Who locks means Season 8 will be only about John Hurt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-19 07:46:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I grow up I want to want to be rich. I don't want it now, but I hope soon I will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-18 22:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too bad he's still Sylar in my eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-13 14:15:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last night's Game of Thrones made it apparent that bears aren't pussies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-12 18:07:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably the same one getting raped on Tosh.0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-12 05:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Teefury swag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-09 22:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm gonna need some sauce good sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-08 22:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I AM LRRR, RULER OF THE PLANET OMICRON PERSEI EIGHT  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-07 23:20:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your name is too great, spacedong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-05 00:30:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-02 02:19:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you do acid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How about super nope </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-01 19:52:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-27 18:44:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did everyone come here to make a Khaleesi reference?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-27 02:29:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> David Luiz! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-26 03:32:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have that same phobia, I used to have this nightmare where I would fall into an Egyptian tomb and little bugs would crawl into my skin and leave holes all over my body  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-24 19:49:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you like spacesticks, in your mouth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-21 21:31:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But seriously sauce 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-18 02:24:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was a torture type in Amnesia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>