<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5126</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I grilled halibut with some potato and veg </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:56:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've seen this in NYC too, at a Japanese place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:37:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had sex once. Then operation and pills. Now I have two sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:20:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This looks like a cut scene from the walking dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:09:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Such great opportunities for public shaming/learning are being missed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:12:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. Did no one say anything to J?  Or at least hint that he was being selfish and rude? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIL Movie rental stores still exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:37:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She looks like that droopy dog from old Loony Tunes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My thoughts exactly. Just imagine a guy going to a bar, having a bit to much to drink, stumbling about, and taking a cab home. It's silly and funny. Then there is the drunken degenerate on the street who's life is consumed by alcohol. That's dark and depressing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:54:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I fluctuate but I tend to get just under 7 according to my fitbit.  I do notice that during times of more intense training I require more sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 19:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, personal amusement. Seems legit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 18:48:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You obviously don't like Weeblyn. Why allow her over in the first place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:14:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think finding new ways to short American education debt will be HOT in pretty soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:26:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6.5 you're pretty and looks like you're in decent shape. Your acne doesn't look very severe bit Accutane worked wonders for me. Acne + fix your hair up and you're an 8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3.6 get in shape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6.1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People using my height as a conversation starter. Usually starts with me being informed that I'm tall. Like, cool story, I hadn't realized.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 16:56:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like she eats a few apples a day. And by apples I mean some pies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 16:53:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eggs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 16:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. One breast is like two cup sizes smaller than the other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 03:19:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Little floof!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 20:13:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed. A key is to hollow out one half of the bread, stuff it with cheese and rosemary, dust with olive oil, and bake until toasted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bacon egg   cheese. Goat cheese, rosemary, thick cut slab bacon. On Ciabatta bun. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:07:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 23:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8.75 You're a smoke show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 23:36:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is true but many of their products are organic so those calories don't count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:18:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blonde. The red looks way fake and nowhere near natural. At least the blonde looks somewhat natural.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I see is duck face. Please repost without duck face.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:04:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you look ~20yo. Maybe just a bit younger. Nothing to be insecure about, especially considering that any bit younger you look will play out to your benefit in the future. 7.5/10  Would try to smash. Might not fit - you're itty-bitty

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The price *was* right. And they had all those different colors and patterns. Like pink leopard. I'm all stocked up on duck tape so no buy for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:15:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Duck*  It's the name of the brand that's on sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:43:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is NOT eggs 101 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Guitar strings!!! Guitar strings for everybody! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems that Jeb is missing something that is very obvious to me. Americans work hard and are labor force is productive; relative to other developed markets. I look at myself, and my coworkers, and we are so productive that we can use technology to cut thousands of manual labor hours out of our lives by creating programs to automate day to day functions. This lowers costs for our company and in economics is known as 'gains from productivity.' The problem with these gains is that they are not distributed to those creating them; they flow almost entirely to the capital owners. And this is the problem. Jeb is a capital owner. He was born into that. It is not so easy to build a large capital base these days; with stagnant wages, increasing costs of housing and education, and tight credit, it is unfair that the productive only serve to enrich the already rich while being robbed of the fruits of their labor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think about if I was armed at what distance I could accurately hit targets. By targets I mean random people on the street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:30:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What? No one was happy with the six pack of duck tape? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:22:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be too curious to see what he'd actually do than to contact HR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow OP. He seems to know a lot about her. Ask him what that snatch tastes like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8/10 - you look great. Please don't try to get more "curves" as I've read in other comments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fat logic is deciding to buy this thing instead of dropping down to a human weight. The "big guy" reviews are hilarious. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:33:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's bewildering that fat people think they're in a position to give advice on positive body image or health. Dumbstruck is the natural reaction to such a fat logistician.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:17:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You definitely don't *need* to lose weight. But you would be sexier if you were a little more toned. You're like a 7 but were an 8.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 00:54:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6/10 - would smash but probably not call again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:16:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This whole story makes me angry. What a piece of shit. I'd have wanted to kick his ass. Did you say something or were you left dumbstruck by the sheer ignorance of what was said to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll be on the lookout for these come next Olympics.

But still I wonder; what is a "great length"?  According to my gf it's just 7 inches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone told me that whisker length was a sign of intelligence. If true than this must be a very wise cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Time to get another girlfriend. I'm not saying that you have to give this one up, just get another. And explain to this one that you need a person in your life to meet your sexual needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:09:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ew, I bet she smelled awful. That's ironic though, a church charity organization directly facilitating gluttony.  It's sad that those nuns were put in that situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:05:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like wieners.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one time she's not sticking her tongue out her kid's picking its nose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is **SO** sexist! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:36:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guys don't just want curves. And please don't confuse curves for fat - don't go trying to put on weight because you think that's what guys want. Fit is attractive. If you want to be hotter, do squats. Being fit and doing squats are the biggest things girls can do to improve their attractiveness. That said, you're pretty. 7/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 9/10 - You're very pretty but I'm sure you know that. You have really nice lips and eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:46:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds like a quote from Bender Bendington Rodriguez.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is nice having an active and diverse sex life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Skewed in my favor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:02:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basic ass bitches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bad dude. Work out more. You'll appreciate looking young when you're older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:01:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brooklyn. And they will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10/10 - out of my league  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look like a lesbian.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trying to help my longest friend be anything other than a bigoted scumbag.  If someone doesn't want to change than my help is useless. Dude will probably be homeless in five years but had every change to succeed.  As a white male with two middle/upper middle class parents, free school optional - he's always the 'victim'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8/10 You're very pretty.  I love your cheeks. The ones on your face. You'd be hotter if you did some squats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:26:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your face looks asymmetrical.  Your nose and your cheek bones specifically. Maybe it's the angle? Right now you look like a 4.5.  Would not smash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:19:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My lowest recorded was something like 10 pounds 4 ounces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:06:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. It's also sort of judgmental if you think about it. Like, I'm Ok with hookups, but you're not? What, are you too good for casually enjoying some of the better things in life? Are you judging me because I'm more promiscuous. Either way it's bs; girls will always hookup.  That's like some dude selling a car on craiglist saying "no lowballs." Show up with cash in hand and you're taking that car for way less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:53:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha yeah, she lost me when she started talking about her 'old soul' and the played out museums in NYC. + no hookups. No hookups = get off Tinder; this isn't an old soul mate search engine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:50:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6.3/10. You're not that pretty but you're good at finding flattering angles. You also wear way too much makeup. I dare you to post a no makeup smiling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Summer comes first </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:36:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:25:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Based on other things I've seen on this site I can conclude two things from this picture: the driver has sex with his trucks' tail pipe and is hung like a baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:24:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did you fry this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spring rolls are not sushi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:20:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let me guess; you're a New Jersian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:09:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure you were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You douching?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:48:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or comments.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:20:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6 or 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to run distance in some hot areas, like Guam and Singapore. During long runs (typically anything over 45 min) I'd have to consume salt packets to keep my muscles from seizing up.  They have 'sport gels' for this now, but salt is basically what you need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I concur.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:12:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> looks pretty ~~cozy~~ douchy.

FIFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:52:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's 2015 - gay jokes just aren't cool.

[edit] Unless you're referring to Hawaiian's. Is that the case?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't get it. Is that a gay joke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:43:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a bit. It's just such a douchy look. I see all these hipsters rocking their wool caps over here in Brooklyn and it's like mid 80's and humid. Uuugh. And they SMELL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "for pages"

Hope it's not an English test. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone else in the photo is wearing shorts and a sleeveless shirt. Short sleeves. Sleeveless. I bet the girl sitting down is wearing shorts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:13:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, I'm not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:35:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> www.youtube.com/watch?v=xyl5H5a09f0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously, it's not like that's even a good beer, it's made by Inbev and it's very basic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:16:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea, I've tried wool caps. They and their effects on your hair aren't a big secret. People who wear them during the hot summer are tool bags; evident in the image of a man needing help from a group of lesbians to muster some hope of success on Tinder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 20:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh it's summer? Why don't you wear your wool cap and a hoodie.

I hope this guy never gets laid, ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 20:33:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah, ginger is naturally soothing to the stomach.  It's actually used as a natural treatment for acid reflux.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 16:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A bit longer than 15 minutes but "The Situation."  He's going on about building his brand up when now it's a brand that no one can sell. Clubs in NYC won't even put him on the guest list b/c it's so synonymous with douchbaggery. And the clincher is that the IRS is into him hard now. If he'll avoid jail time he'll have to pay out until he's in the poor house. Good for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 16:49:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've know NattyFat too! She's such a health expert. And since everything the eats is healthy, the more she eats, the healthier she becomes! Duh, it's SO LOGICAL.

I dropped this story into rant wednesday on rFitness; but she lurks in my works kitchen too.  When I make peanut PB J she'll let me know that almond butter is much healthier and ask why I'm loading up on the protein. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 15:34:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If that were my Goat server, he wouldn't be getting a good tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 15:24:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This totally makes sense. It's just a very very specific bit of wisdom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 15:22:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't mind girls in tattoos but a bad tattoo's really bother me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 15:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Horny, then lonely. Than bored enough to finally look for love. The internet *is* beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 15:12:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  All I want for Christmas is my two front teeth ~ () </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:07:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it was more for the knots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:07:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can use less salt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 21:41:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rabble rabble rabble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crystal updating her OKC profile </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 21:25:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 20:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but she owns it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crystal got her hair did </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 20:23:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Made some miso chicken and snap peas </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 20:22:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Nobody not lying about anything"

Does this mean he's lying about anything?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 05:36:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it food? Do you have free will? Don't come to me with your silly questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 22:30:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG you're right! I've had that at a bunch spot. Admittedly I was skeptical but damn was it good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 20:09:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the nice thing about humor; there is a flavor for everyone.  I'm more of a Louis C.K. fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:28:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bet it still tastes like freedom!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Went all America with my oatmeal this morning! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, no offense taken.  It's funny how you go on hearing and saying things without ever really thinking about what it is that's being said.  Like that old McDonald's jingle, "two all beef patties...blah blah...on a seseme-seed bun."  I'll start saying in from now on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:11:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think he's throwing gang signs.  Kids these days... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a grown ass man and this shit's funny. Get off your high horse and get a sense of humor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:08:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can kill a sub, but you can never kill what that sub represented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:57:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This scientific study proves it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As do I  _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:53:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here in Murika we use stupid units of measurement... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:52:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't add that factorial and didn't notice it until now. Good eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:47:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're right. I'm so used to hearing "on a bun" or "on rye" but it really is *in*, isn't it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bacon egg   cheddar on croissant </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 15:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't have enough fucks left explain to you the point of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:59:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Slow clap] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:32:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree.  I cook and make cocktails with lemon.  Also, lemon has plenty of sugars naturally. 

Side note; Liz Lemon is alright by me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:31:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Before 5pm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:35:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hurray! and Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  /r/fatpaohate

Oh wow, my first time being the first poster to a sub. I feel honored. 

Time to update the 'ol resume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This wil do. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YISSSSS!!! They're GRowing BIggerrrr! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Could use a derpy floof break from all this mod mayhem </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:30:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 21:28:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm thinking fork lifts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 20:45:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let's go for circus sideshow fat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 19:37:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know their fatter than this.  Should have made the measurement in stones. Or maybe included the weight of their ego. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 18:03:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thin privilege is making the rest of Wildwooders feel disgusting by comparison.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ----- Weight in pounds of average Admin supporting Pao </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 18:02:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:40:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the most disgusting thing I've heard all week. It's like a gross coffee smoothie. I hate it when fat people try to act tough. It's like, we know your T count is low af and your bones are weak. Who are you trying to fool? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:24:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crystal is one with the rug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:59:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I asked: Confirmed Sith </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:59:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds really good. I think I'm going to make that into a cocktail actually. But here in America; without adequate sugaz we go into starvation mode and get fatter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:19:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a trashy good time...when you're in high school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:40:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIL again. The Beetus thus forth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The betes is strong along the jersey shore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a good honest slogan.

[edit] but I think Seaside heights holds that crown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The floof is strong with Crystal </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:41:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, any time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:11:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well the rides and water park are still fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:10:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try visiting Japan. Their candy is only a little sweeter than American bread. I think 2/3 of Americans have an undeniable sugar addiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love how this is turning into a mixology thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like a Gin   Ginger.  And if you're feeling nuts; 

Gin + Ginger soda + Fresh Ginger = Gin^3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:05:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think added sugars is one of the biggest problems in our economy.  Our government regulates everything but allows food produces to add what basically amounts to poison to almost everything in the grocery store.  Makes me sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:01:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't argue with this type of sound reasoning. It's *science*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not fat, cultivating mass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:43:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's sound logical science. Drinking is like breathing and breathing burns calories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:34:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sure about that? Last time I checked water had chemicals and chemicals are bad.

[edit] but Popeye's still OK b/c chicken = protein = good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:29:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, great map. 

Yea, Wildwood has really gone down hill.

Also, I grew up on the Jersey Shore. And it's not like the TV show.  Sure, I used to go to Seaside Heights (where the show was filmed) in high school, but we all knew it was a trashy good time. I spent my summers on LBI though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> According to documentaries and articles I've viewed, the early 80's is when the US obesity population began to blow up.  Combine this image with the recent presence of meth use just inland along the jersey shore and you'll have a more current view of the boardwalk. It's pretty sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:59:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a late bloomer. I didn't finish developing physically until I was ~25yo. [31M now] It was around 29 that I realized I was hot. It just sort of hit me. Like I have had girls telling me this (sometimes guys too) but it didn't really sink in for a while. It's one thing to know you're good looking, being called "pretty boy" growing up, but all the sudden you're a 6'4" blonde male with the body of a stripper and it hits you.

I don't think it effects my personality too much because I don't view myself in terms of beauty but I am cognizant about certain things that are effected by how I look. I'm more aware that people will try to take advantage of me sexually and vie for my attention. I'm also more aware of the effect I have on women (some men I suppose too) as they can tend to become nervous when I approach them or talk to them. I also notice that some things in life are just handed to me and I'm attributing this to looks. Also, access to parties/clubs is much easier for me I'm noticing.

The one notable change in personality for me is that my standards for girlfriends has increased a lot. Now, I won't even have a drunken one night stand with a girl who's even a bit chubby.  In general they have to be tall, beautiful, smart and educated.  My standards were not that high when I was 21. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:40:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIL Gerd wrote der bible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:27:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You'd think this answer could be found with a quick googling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tiki floof in all his majesty </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:11:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tis a magical place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:08:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wonder what study it's citing. I'm sure it's true if you count overeating as an eating disorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're hot. 8.9/10

Is that hair color natural?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 16:58:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It *has* fruit in it so it's healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 16:40:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're right, I deserve that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL where Diabetes comes from... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 16:21:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I'm at the the Jersey Shore - this place called Wild Wood.  Once a year my friends and I like to go to the boardwalk there to ride all the rides and play all the games.  I'm walking around with a friend and we see a lemonade stand selling giant (1L?) lemonades. We're thirsty but these things are huge so we decide to split one.

We walk up to the stand and order. We get our drink and each have a turn taking a sip. Both of our reactions are the same; our faces scrunch up and we're a bit overwhelmed by the amount of sugar in our drink. You could literally crunch the sugar with your teeth. But whatever, we're thirsty, we'll drink it.  

As we're drinking, we're standing around near the lemonade stand and I watch this very large couple waddle up to the stand. They're pretty big, even relative to the population found in Wildwood, which is on the larger side to begin with. They each order a lemonade as I'm watching them. They start to walk away and take a sip. They each made the same disgusted face my friend and I made when we had our first sip!

Plot Twist! This couple, after taking a sip and realizing it is not to their liking, turn around and walk back to the stand. I'm out of earshot but I can see clearly what happens. They ask the kid for more sugar. They open the lid and he pours a full scoop (probably a tablespoon) of sugar into their giant cups. They look at him like, "come on, really?" and he pours two more scoops of sugar into each of their cups! That's some sweet ass lemonade + 3 additional scoops of sugaz! Wtf did I just witness!?!

They walked away, pleased with their purchase, and at that moment, I realized that that lemonade stand in Wildwood, New Jersey was where diabetes came from.

[edit] spelling of "lemonade" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:49:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know what your mission is right? You MUST hide its chair for every class.  Better yet; loosen up some of the bolts so that it falls apart under her weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:08:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8.6/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 15:49:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know your breeds! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:27:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The white one in the middle is full loaf and the one in the back is at least half loaf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 01:30:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perfect/ Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Costco baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:07:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What you have to eat today?  

"Oh, a salad, I went for a walk and treated myself with a cookie. I'm SO bad!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:37:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:58:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The floof is strong in this group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The loafs are abundant when visiting my mother </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:47:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Made my own sliders at favorite brunch spot. Pretzel bites + eggs + bacon = yum </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:45:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6/10 - pretty basic looking but cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And having big man breasts and low testosterone is super manly and straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:34:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll have to look into that. Barnes   Noble has a great reference section I'll be able to use to do my research.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tikiloaf on the sofa </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:54:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If four years is "entry level" what's two years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made it a point of not turning down interviews I got from attending on campus recruiting events close to graduation.  There were many booths for "Financial Advisers" that were open to all majors. Being open to all majors is a red flag on its own but I did research into what they actually did.  Some houses are more legit than others, but most get you to resell life insurance to family and friends.  As soon as they started asking me about my network of fam and friends I politely excused myself and walked out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:46:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Barnes   Noble. I don't buy anything there but I like sitting in their chairs and reading magazines.  If only there were a place similar to B N that I could visit and perhaps borrow some books or magazines, take them home for a bit, or read them there, then return them at my convenience.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> VII / X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:19:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a tough call because you're making a duck face in both pictures. 

In the second photo, the larger zoom makes it harder to see your duck face but it also reveals the large urine stain on your mattress. 

It's a really hard decision. Personally, I'd go with #2, as the urine stain is less embarrassing than the closeup duck face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Physical attraction trumps emotional connection. (In most cases involving males) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This sign in front of Jeffry's in the West Village </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:38:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those calves... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:37:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm no expert on lady attire but it looks like you have nice legs and I'm assuming a nice butt - so anything that would highlight that?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:35:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look at her legs; she definitely does some kind of sport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't do English breakfast, this is Murika. It's also missing the beans. And blood pudding is gross.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On the left.  I used purple potatoes so their camouflaged.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:30:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're those little purple potatoes with onions and rosemary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:38:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Math is hard sometimes. Forgot that betes multiplier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thick cut slab bacon with eggs and home fries. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:46:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6/10 - You look older than 18. You also look like you're pretty fit but your clothing isn't complimenting that at all.

Teeth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solid 9. You're fit and pretty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But 2,000 calories *is* 2,000 calories.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:29:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Low and slow. Like for 30-35 min at 225. Spice to taste.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Roasted salmon with kale, rosemary, and skillet potatoes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This kind of ignorance makes my skin crawl. I had some idiot on Yelp! message me saying that the racist bar tender that wouldn't serve me wasn't racist because I'm white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy to report I've only bought beer from Whole Foods.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:38:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try steal cut oats!!! Sorry I got excited.
I add blueberries and a tiny bit of cocoanut oil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Almost everything I make has onions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:45:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:31:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 5.5 / 10.  You'd do very well to get in shape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look like a young Peter Griffin. It seems like there is a handsome young man hiding under all that fat. The biggest improvement you can make is to get in shape. I can give you tips there if you need, otherwise, there are plenty of subs you can use for knowledge and motivation. Current rating: ~2/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 19:15:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have some things I do that help me maintain.
1. NEVER eat in front of TV. This robs you of the sense of satisfaction you get from food as your senses are being overwhelmed by light and sound.
2. Learn to recognize when your body is not hungry. 
3. Be aware of your sugar consumption. Read food labels of things you eat and notice the addition of sugars. Taper off of sugar. It's basically poison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 18:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really awful tattoos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:40:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> McDonalds because that shits gross. + basically any fast food burger place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No prob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:26:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 5/10
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 03:41:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been tracking my drinking habits in Excel since 06 April.  My average daily consumption is 4.8.  My Max consumption in one day is 14 drinks.  A side note: according to my fitbit, which records my average calories burned, I consume ~4,300 calories a day, which is more than twice the human average.  There you go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 19:40:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's comforting to know that as a sociology major with bad grammar she'll be unemployable if/when she graduates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 04:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so true. People try so hard not to offend. And this obese culture has turned 'being fat' into something that's offensive to talk about, when really, we should be talking about this issue openly in society. It's not like they're even a minority, they're taking over, we need to fight back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 23:35:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't "hate" god. I hate that ignorant people chose to do in the name of god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 22:08:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. Looks. DISGUSTING.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 19:43:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 19:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But what if she's on top? And I'm handcuffed?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8.5/10  You look tall and you're pretty.  I love your smile.  If I were to guess ethnicity I'd say Vietnam/Chinese mix.  I've spent a good amount of time in Asia/South East Asia but I'm no expert.  Have you considered one of those spit based DNA services; like ancestry or 23andme? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:54:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're definitely pretty. You have a good bone structure, your face is symmetrical and you look thin/fit.  8.5/10 - would totally smash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 00:40:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6.5/ Cute.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:50:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 9/10.  You're sexy and pretty.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:53:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't forget about taxes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea, it's hard to cheat up from a 10.  I just saw that arm hair and was like, Whoa, I knew we had the right to bear arms but this guy took it too literally.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi. Full disclosure, I've not been overweight for about 20 yrs now, but I do have a solid command over my body weight and composition.  Over the past 7 years I've had 35lbs worth of weight fluctuation while maintaining a body fat of 10%. 

I see diet and exercise discussed a lot on this/related subs, but there is a powerful tool that is not often discussed here. I'm talking about the mental/psychological/spiritual aspect of controlling your body. I've been regularly meditating for over half my life now. Along these lines, fasting has been used as a tool to reach a higher plain of consciousness for millennia. The key here is to understand that your body and your consciousness (soul to some people) are completely separate. Once you begin to deny your body, in controlled periods, this becomes more apparent. I fast for spiritual reasons, and also I'm very active and eat well, but there is that added benefit of running a controlled drastic calorie defect - you shed fat quickly.  Other benefits of sharpening this tool include avoiding that 3 week on/off cycle of self control. 

Note; techniques like this aren't for everyone and meditation, I've been told, is hard for people to just jump into. But if you're interested in hearing more, feel free to message me or comment back.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:53:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look much bigger in one of those pictures.  Also the lip rings aren't doing you any favors.

Almost a 5.  (4.5/10) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're beautiful. 8.5/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:46:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of times people cheat because they're insecure.  
[edit] I'd be insecure if I was so hairy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10/10 - you're also exactly my physical type.  Tall, beautiful, fit blonde. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:05:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the tiny minority; it's the tail of the distribution.  The huge majority of fat people are fat because they're addicted to sugar and are totally ignorant about nutrition in general. Sure, it's not fair that food companies are allowed to put sugar in everything we eat and aggressively market their drug to children, but the most powerful way to change what corporations put on the shelves is to change societies demands. If society is bullied into believing that things like HAES is legitimate, there is less incentive to act responsibly as consumers.


As a young person, this is a very real problem that your generation will one day have to face. Today I saw a morbidly obese ~10 year old in the supermarket.  Her mother had a cart full of sugary cereal, ice cream, and soda (or as referred to on this site, a cart full of genetics). She was born into that environment. This problem has deep roots. I'd love to hear any constructive ideas on how this problem can be solved, but right now, what you're witnessing with FPH backlash, is a pushback against the censorship of something that should not be taboo to discuss openly in society.


And just to bring home the gravity of this epidemic; 
some people are fat because of diseases

 

The word 'obesity' has literally been changed to a disease according to modern medicine.  Some some people have a disease because they're diseased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 19:54:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True. I feel like it's rude and shallow not to eat bc it's weird looking. I mean, it's not like your looking at it while you're eating. And I'm a big fan of the finger test before I go down there. Vegans taste better.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 17:07:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6.5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 16:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6/10.  You're pretty but at 22 you should not be so heavy. I bet you know your way around a potato.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 16:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8.5/10 - You look a bit more mature than 18.  Personally, I'm a fan of natural.  If you're a brunette, be a brunette, because you can *try* to look blonde, but you'll never really be blonde. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 16:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weird looking vagina's are a huge factor in attractiveness.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 16:43:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think it's "funny" to hate people because they're ~~big~~ **fat**.  I think it's necessary to have an outlet to pushback against "fat acceptance," which is really just a phrase describing fat bullies forcing society to accept their irresponsible, gluttonous, and destructive lifestyle.  It's nice to sit here and say, "oh, everyone's beautiful and healthy and a product of genetics" but the stark reality is that if we continue on our current fat path, society is doomed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 15:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bars are where insecure "Alpha males" go to mate.  If your not there to fuck   fight than it's not a real bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 15:39:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Acting stupid/childish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 14:44:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never asked but I'll let you know.
[edit] No, it won't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 14:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True.  Personally, I live in a city and bike mostly everywhere so it's not a huge sacrifice to give up an auto.  The problems I'm seeing are in deep rural areas where there might not even be strong enough grid support for charging stations.  On the bright side; the way technology is progressing, I think I'll see the fix in my life time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 14:40:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It could have stayed there.  She escalated the situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I need an outlet to express my frustration about the tyranny of fat culture. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 14:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, you look SO much better.  7.5/10.  You're thin now, so you can tuck in your shirt and look good.  Thin people privilege.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:11:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Facially; you are marginally attractive but you'd do well to update your facial hair and haircut.

Body wise; get in shape.

You're like a 6 but you could work that up to maybe an 8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:06:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What % of the world population is willing to give up driving their petrol cars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A bit off topic, but when I was in the Navy, just getting out of boot camp - SO MANY people got tattoos of inspirational words in other languages (Asian languages).  Later on, when I was in Asia, I learned from snickering locals that many of my shipmates' tattoos did not actually say what they thought they said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:51:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adjustable dumbbell set, a bench, and a pull up bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use mine for a seat when meditating as well.  And to prop up my window.  And a pillow.  It basically does everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice ass.  9/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:35:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this....it's mating call? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:32:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously.  Like, they know they're not going to get any positive attention out at a bar so they have to bully people into acknowledging them by being boisterous and larger than life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:05:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ha, thanks.  Yes, I forget about this sub sometimes.  Good call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously.  It's like they're wearing their character, or the lack there of, on their sleeve; not *really* knowing what things like integrity and discipline are, just insisting that at their core, under their fat exterior, those traits exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:56:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You've made the right call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:56:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:02:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a fan of BSN Syntha - 6.  It's whey better than others I've tried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This whole FPH backlash has triggered me to speak my mind more freely in the real world. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:58:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This happened last night.  I'm at a bar for a happy hour after work with some coworkers.  It's getting later, most people I work with have funneled out, leaving just some good friends.  There is an attractive girl standing at the bar, looking bored, so  I walked up to her and struck up a conversation.  This is where the story starts.

I did not notice that she had a friend with her.  Her friend (let's call her Fatty for short) had a pretty face but was probably 70-85 lbs overweight. Fatty kept on interjecting into the conversation I was trying to continue with attractive girl (Fit Girl for short).  It was *really* annoying.  She'd respond to questions I'd pose to Fit Girl. She'd interrupt Fit Girls responses and even answer questions that Fit Girl asked me. Fit Girl was annoyed, you could tell, but you could also tell that she was probably used to this kind of treatment from her friend. 

As I grew increasingly annoyed with the situation, my frustration became visible through my tone and body language.  Fatty challenged me with, "Oh, so you don't want to talk to me?"  

"No," I said, "I was really trying to talk to [Fit Girl]."

Fatty asked "Why?"  Fatty asked if it was because I didn't like "nice girls with good personalities."

I said I didn't like her personality.  She retorted with, "You don't even know me!"

This is where I became a blunt shitlord.  

I explained to Fatty that I did know her and I knew that her personality did not meet my standards.  I knew she lacked discipline, self control, and fore site. I knew we couldn't participate in certain activities that I enjoyed. And then she asked, "why? because I'm a big girl."

"A big girl."

I said, "Yes, it's because you're FAT."  Fatty was SHOCKED.  Like it's some secret that everyone knows but can't talk about and I broke that golden rule to speak that unspoken truth and the sound of it just blew her mind. 

I left.  I didn't get to finish talking to Fit Girl. Fatty was butthurt. 

TL:DR - I explained to an obnoxious fat girl at a bar why I could tell from her being fat that our personalities would not align.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:26:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can we consolidate?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:12:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice beer choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:35:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are BEAUTIFUL.  9/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you're about to make that decision, reach under your shirt, grab your fat, and tell it that it does not make the decisions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you please teach them to harmonize and post a video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:25:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FINALLY!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They know.  They know when it's quiet time.  Furry little rebels.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:52:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please stop doing duckface.  6/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:48:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love it when they chirp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might I suggest peanut butter.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:48:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This seems like a problem that kitten mittens won't fix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And eventually, you'll feel like shit if you don't exercise and feel amazing during.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, does your cat make too much noise!?! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:03:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People who put raisins in cake should be prosecuted by cake courts.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:00:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a solid vice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm literally at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:00:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That took a lot, didn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:59:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two for cake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice.  I like it.  I have one of the flagship year Mazdaspeed 3's but I'm not super into fixing it up...probably b/c I live in a city and almost never drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of cake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Books! Now I'm picturing Johnny-5 tearing up a library, shaking a bit from the large dose of books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hey Reddit, what is your vice? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:33:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is a proper full sentence.  Please learn English, bot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's your vice? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:26:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 00:51:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're doing great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's the M0D's name before they're triggered; turning into a furious, putrid, lump of blubber? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 00:07:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bruce Banner   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:36:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got in trouble for throwing an apple core into a heavily wooded apple on school property because I was "littering."  It isn't literally littering.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who orders soda?  Beer please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:00:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ( ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 00:39:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/fatpeople is also decent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 00:38:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was all the obese mods being butthurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can just crush arugula.  It's a vegetable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIFU

The titles are always misleading that anyone can relate to.

TITLE: "TIFU by going to the grocery store"

TEXT: "I walked around with my cart of groceries, texting, and didn't see the guy on the ladder who I bumped into causing him to fall and knock over a case of soda!"

REALITY: You fucked up by bumping into some dude because you weren't paying attention.  The fuck up was NOT going to a grocery store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was so *underground* then! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:21:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you're beautiful! 9.5/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If a tree falls in a forest and no one is around to hear it... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will a hipster still buy its album? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi. I spent 4 years in the Navy.  During this time, I was required to do a lot of swimming for my job and I also did long distance running (halfs   fulls) in my spare time.  I also lifted heavy.  

Generally gains   distance do not go well together.  I found it almost impossible to keep on weight from lifting.  I was eating A LOT and still, weight would just fall off. I'd be waking up several hours before a race to consume a crap load of high hypoglycemic carbs to fuel throughout the run and dumping on proteins afterwords.

If you're going to prepare for this, know that you will likely lose mass.  On a side note; it's not very good for your joints to carry a lot of mass when doing distance.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:46:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful. Fit. Tall? 10/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:47:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You do not look 19.  Currently 6/10.
Some suggestions: Your skin looks dry.  Try cocoanut oil, this might help you look closer to your age too.  You look sad.  Smiling, even if it's forced, makes us happy.  Try it.  And don't just smile with your mouth, smile with your eyes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you actively seek a girlfriend?  What kind of girls are you going for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:01:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 9/10 - so hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:29:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The odds of me contracting a severe STD, based off of the demographics that I date, are roughly 1 in 100,000.  I'll take those odds.  How's your personality treating ya?  Can't get a bf but you're not fat or ugly?  Good luck with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 21:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, yea man, thanks. Keep being awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude, when I was your age I used to think of all these things I could do to look older.  Be patient really is a virtue and it *will* pay off.  

I'm m31 living in NYC. I didn't stop growing until I was like 24 and didn't get my true confidence until maybe 27 but now, it's like I can have any girl I want. I love it.

Keep up the gym, stay active, stretch and above all, just believe in yourself - life can get SO awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6.5.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look very young and as a fellow young looking late bloomer I can affirm that you can definitely benefit from this later in life.  7/10. Get in shape and you'd be more like a 9. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:53:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 7/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:50:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha! Personally I think monogyny is overrated anyway.  Don't let society pressure you into having to have a bf if it's not what you want. But you're hot, so I'm sure getting what you want shouldn't be a prob! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're young and beautiful.  Please don't go putting on a lot of makeup.  You don't need it and I see so many girls killing they're natural beauty by wearing paint. Also, at 6'4" - I can really appreciate a tall beauty.  9.5/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're hot. 8/10.  Why do you think you've never had a bf?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're so cute! 7/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:05:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this thing the size of a truck or is that guy just *really* short? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:14:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That wasn't a question. It's not efficient to work employees to the point where they kill themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:54:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8/10 - I'd smash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:34:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're a company making your employees work 100hr weeks you need to create two jobs and hire two people.  Gah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:53:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really. You are a joke and you're hilarious. In a sad way. The other comments ring true and honest. The fact is that I have very high self esteem, I frequently get requests to model, and I'm drowning in pussy. Maybe a slight narcissism exists but there is nothing 'quite tragic' about seeking approval and showing off ones hard earned abs in this sub is to be expected.  Btw; you're full of shit with your obvious contradiction:
 I wouldn't say you're ugly because that is unfair

vs

 you can't accept that you're ugly

You're pathetic.  Get help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 15:04:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard work pays off.  Good job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:51:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Enough about some president that was before our lifetime.  Are you on Mount Rushmore?  How will you be forgotten?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 04:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6/10.  Do some squats or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 01:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Velcro wallets: age 10

Drinking too much: age 25

Not caring about your health: age 30 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 00:37:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're a handsome fellow.  7.5/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 23:57:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Athletic high (runners, swimmers, fighters, etc). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 23:32:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Carb filler: Brussels Sprouts.  I just eat them raw.  They have a ton of fiber, + some protein, and they fill you up fast and keep you full. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 22:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're hawt!  Nice thigh gap.  9.5/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 22:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Porn magazines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 22:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree.  That can't be working for her.  She'll either have to be less of a bitch or be hotter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 22:26:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stop making a duckface.
That piercing is not flattering at all.
Go with your natural hair color.
6/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd eat your ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 15:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It must suck being fat, ugly, and generally unattractive.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 21:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Undercover shitlord.  I get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 19:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't as for honesty if you can't take it.  You're fat, ugly, and age terribly.  Honesty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 19:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3/10.  You look like you're in your late 30's.  And you're fat.  And this picture is of horrible quality.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:32:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi.

The website asoftmurmer.com works wonders for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:57:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're beautiful.  9/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Step 4: Get new glasses. Those are too small on your face.

OR; get a smaller face.  Your face is too big for your glasses.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:29:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look like you're 40.  Are you balding?  
I have a fix: Consume less than you expend (talking calories here).  Repeat this behavior consistently until you are no longer obese.  Then consume as much as you expend.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why you Russian, are you late for something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8. I like the bangs but that just might be b/c I live in BK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good at Google. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>