<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2466</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help me find a hobby for my dad. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello!
My father is 49 years old and lives at home with his parents due to three suicide attempts.  He has been diagnosed with a mild case of schizophrenia, depression, anxiety, paranoia, and a mild bipolar disorder.  With his latest suicide attempt he had a minor stroke and now has difficulty speaking (slight stutter), and his hands shake.  He used to go bowling twice a week but insists that the people there talk about him and don't like him so he doesn't want to go back.  I am desperately trying to find a hobby for him to add more meaning to his life.  He doesn't like being out in the sun, he doesn't like crowded places, he can read but doesn't remember what he just read, and he doesn't have to motor skills to draw or paint (according to him).  He has a truck and can drive, and he used to go fishing a lot but doesn't want to do that anymore due to being out in the sun.  Please help me brainstorm potential hobbies that would be within his comfort zone!

*note - I am in the military stationed overseas, so spending more time with him isn't an option right now :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 03:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is the word "up" used in relation to the earth, or in relation to yourself? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-02 02:52:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For example, if a person is laying down and someone asks "what's up?" Is the ceiling still up or is above the person's head up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Independence Day miracle. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-06 02:03:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Adventure Time pottery piece I made! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-08 03:44:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some fun things to do in Lincoln that not many people know about? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-08 03:16:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-05 17:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may have more luck posting on r/rateme (http://www.reddit.com/r/Rateme/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-04 06:59:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait...most people don't do that?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Courthouse in Nebraska - photo by Tim Vrtiska </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-04 02:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-01 10:26:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Violin!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-19 07:04:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do I have a television and electricity?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-16 06:13:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try just putting eye liner on the top...I think that would work well for you.  I also think the curly hair looks better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-16 06:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the rectangular glasses, but not the "nerdy" ones, I like the tattoo on your arm!...and btw, where is the right side of your face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-16 06:00:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're very pretty...try sticking to the eye brows in the last picture! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-16 05:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Close enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-16 05:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My anatomy teacher told our class that a marathon runner has miles and miles more blood vessels in their lungs than an average person does.  I'm sure lots of other things happen too, but other than that, I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-16 05:30:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Are you a boy or a girl?"  I'm actually a girl...but I told them I was a boy to try and add some humor to a bad situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-16 05:23:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a girl...if a guy were approaching me at the bar he would need to be sober enough to hold a conversation with, and simply asking me for my name, and saying that I look familiar (or something dumb like that) would be enough to grab my attention.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-16 05:08:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "the front page of the internet" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-14 15:14:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A re-occurring dream I have is that I'm a kid playing on a playground with the Rugrats (yes the t.v. show), and I find a hidden doorway at the bottom of one of the play sets.  I open it and it's full of lava.  All of a sudden I see my mom coming up out of the lava asking me to come with her.  That's usually when I wake up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Van Gogh Puff Paint! (cross-post from r/crafts) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-14 07:38:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-14 07:30:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the general population views me as nice...and for the most part I agree.  At the same time people can't read my mind, so they don't know what I'm actually thinking... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-14 07:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read in my (fairly old) statistics book that more men are born than women, but focusing on the same group of people, by the time they are middle aged there are more women than men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Van Gogh Puff Paint! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-14 02:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 2009 Mercury Grand Marquis question. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-03 06:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For those of you who own this car, how well does it handle in snow?  Also, what are the positive and negative aspects? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Good morning human! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-30 03:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Opera dog! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-25 02:40:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Come at me, brow! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-25 00:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-15 16:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Detasseling corn in Nebraska. I started doing this every summer when I was in sixth grade. This job consists of getting up at 4 in the morning to catch the school bus that leaves at 5, riding for an hour to some random corn field, getting off the bus, putting on safety glasses and gloves, walking through the dew soaked corn field freezing cold to pick the tassels off the tops of the corn stalks.  Then in the afternoon it gets killer hot (since this takes place in July), and it wouldn't be so bad but you have to wear long sleeves and long pants to protect yourself from the corn.  Then you go home, wash off your crusty mud shoes, through your clothes in the wash, take a shower, go to sleep, wake up for supper, pack your lunch, go back to sleep...and repeat for about 2 weeks (no days off). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-14 21:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you guys have a falling out with the members of My Chemical Romance, does the song "Pretty Handsome Awkward" have anything to do with Gerard Way....or is all that drama just rumors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-01 05:48:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nope...he lives with his parents and has tried killing himself three times since the divorce (12 years ago). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-01 05:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cheating on my father and divorcing him all within a short time period.  Not because it hurt me directly but because it about killed my dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-01 04:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hear you...I'm graduating in may and college didn't seem like my cup of tea (at least not right now).  Travel sounded good but I knew I'de never actually go anywhere on my own.  So I joined the Navy...now I have to go places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-09 04:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks!...I think...skatest?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-08 02:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> August 26th 2014 - EA (Engineering Aid) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does A school start with the basics? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-08 02:40:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was sworn into the Navy and am on track to be an Engineering Aid.  My main concern is if I'm going to be able to keep up with the course work at my A school with no background knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Curious Annie peeping on the neighbor's dog. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-31 06:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-28 08:58:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> moron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-28 08:57:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I met my best friend detasseling in the corn fields of Nebraska.  Getting on a bus together at 5am and walking rows of corn until 2 in the afternoon = bonding time.  We knew each other's life-stories in about 2 days. 
("Detasseling corn is removing the pollen-producing flowers, the tassel, from the tops of corn plants and placing them on the ground.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 04:44:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got saline implants under the muscle...while I was in the recovery room waking up from my anesthesia, the nurse kept asking me what my pain level was and if I wanted to take a pain pill.  I refused.  After I woke up some more they moved me back to the room where I changed into my gown before the procedure and I slept in there for a while.  The nurse came in quite a lot to ask me if I needed anything...all I wanted was water.  After a few check-ins with the nurse I finally accepted a pain pill because yes it hurt, but it wasn't unbearable.  Upon returning home I was sore but again, nothing unbearable.  They prescribed me a bottle of 30ish strong pain pills and I only took 4 or 5.  They also gave me a packet of pills to put under the tongue for when the pain pills made me feel like vomiting.  These were a life saver more than the pain pills were.  I don't even want to think about how much it would have hurt to puke right after a breast augmentation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 02:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That we are going to have to break up when I go active duty in the Navy this coming summer.  Don't get me wrong, I love him and all...but I don't want either of us to be miserable the whole time I'm gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 01:20:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They set the guy free while investigating further?!  If it was a full grown adult found encased in concrete instead of a baby would they be letting the home owner go?  I don't think so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An important lesson on self respect brought to you by my little sister. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-07 05:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 07:10:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not. even. kidding.
https://www.facebook.com/tyler.creek.37?hc_location=stream </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 07:02:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YES! Today I was looking through this guy's profile and he is obsessed with diapers.  By scrolling down his news feed he had multiple pictures that said "share this if you're an adult that loves wearing diapers"...and then I looked through his profile pictures...big mistake...he had a picture of him in a diaper...never again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 06:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "You wasted $150,000 on an education you coulda got for a buck fifty in late charges at the public library." - Matt Damon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 05:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Since you don't use your degree at your job, do you regret going to college? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 05:13:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you regret going to college and spending money since you're not using your degree? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What did you get a degree in while attending college, and where do you work now? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 05:05:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a high school student writing a paper about the effectiveness of college and I'm curious to see how many people actually use their degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do any of you have a college diploma and work at a job that doesn't require a degree? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-03 04:49:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-02 04:36:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Shut up! There is no laughing in math class!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 06:41:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WHY DON'T I EVER SEE FOXES?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-01 05:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boyfriend was always on reddit so I decided to get an account to see how pointless it was.  That didn't work out so well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-30 04:48:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mom -  "I'm disappointed in you." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-27 18:16:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A few weeks after my dad tried committing suicide, when I was about 9 years old, he looked at me and said "you're the reason I hate myself." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-27 17:04:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom and step dad were fighting and it was time for me and my older sister to go to sleep.  My mom tucked us in and when she left our room I heard my step dad yell from down the hall, "the next time you see your mom she will be in a body bag." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> People are so hateful. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-27 16:19:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>