<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3431</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: During World War II, Germany and Japan due to certain atrocities ranging from mass rapes (e.g. Nanking), genocides (Jews) and human experimentation (Camp 731), they can be viewed as evil while the Allies can be viewed as good. Is this view correct or is there a reason for their cruelty? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does everyone downvote me the second I post something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> To avoid the fear of death think of it like this. We were dead before we came into this world so surely, we can do it again! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:38:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alcohol helps me become less anxious around new people. Should I take a few glasses before orientation tomorrow? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:24:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alwaaays things relating to mental health huh.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The most depressing piece I have read in a long time: "Mariana" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do you make friends? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 12:12:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Orientation is kicking off day after tomorrow and I, as an awkwardly shy guy who struggles to hold conversations with everyone both friends and strangers am fearing that I will not be able to make friends... Help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 10:04:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why not? When I first learnt the piano I didn't find super fast double thirds or clean scale runs that impressive and now that i'm older, I do! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 07:31:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I call BS on OP. Who the hell names their worker just Employee? Ever heard of names to avoid confusion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 02:11:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Knowledge of something only adds to the beauty! I paraphrase Feynman on physics of course! Take a look at this video to see what I mean! (I highly recommend it) 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cRmbwczTC6E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:36:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes of course! But I don't see how that relates to the picture of a piano! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well to be fair, his 1812 overture did require live cannon fire!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just read from /r/classicalmusic that these pianos would usually be trapped with bombs that were sometimes trigged by hitting a certain key. Terrifying to think about it. Sad to see how even traces of beauty and humanity can be manipulated for grim purposes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:22:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reposted this and made note of it on /r/pics so that more people hopefully will see this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Repost from /r/classicalmusic: Russian soldier playing a piano in Chechnya, 1994. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:22:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 17:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Makes me wonder if there were any pianists who were soldiers at the time who were lured to the piano and were killed or had their hands incapacitated as a result of the trap :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:07:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Edit: Here are some breathtaking pieces I have discovered recently!

[Anton Rubinstein - Piano Concerto No. 4 \(1864\)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l3tS05YROlY)

[Anton Rubinstein - Symphony No. 2 "Ocean" \(1851\)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4YBu5QzHPoo)

[Charles Villiers Stanford - Requiem \(1897\)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PfHi6rfHiEU)

[Norbert Burgmller - Piano Concerto in F-sharp minor, Op.1 \(1829\)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jKX8NXOH55I)

[Franciszek Lessel - Piano Concerto in C-major, Op.14 \(1810\)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b4N95zeJugM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rant Alert: Music is scary. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So it's pretty late where I am and amidst my state of half-sleep while listening to [Moszkowski's Piano Concerto](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V1dDAs0fZic) I just realised something.. 

Music.. is huge...

I've been playing the piano and cello my whole life and i've had my fair share of music classes and performances. However, I just only realised that MUSIC IS SO GODDAMN MASSIVE. 

I'm just sitting here in awe just looking at these random youtube channels that have posted hundreds upon hundreds of masterpieces that I have never heard of in my life with composers I have never even seen or know how to pronounce! There are entire operas, gargantuan symphonies, oratorios and masses by composers, basically entire worlds out there that have eluded me for a lifetime! Composers I discovered recently include Marx to Giere to Beach to Spohr to Scharwenka to Walter to Elmas to Martucci... the list goes on and on and on forever! 

Admittedly I always thought I was the classical geek who knew tons about music but now... I think I know nothing and am completely aware of my ignorance. 

When I was much younger, when I learned that our massive planet was just one of trillions in our universe and how there are more stars than there are grains of sand on Earth, I was overcome with a feeling of both awe and fear of the huge scale of things. Once again, I feel this feeling again but now, for music. 

"Music is enough for a lifetime, but a lifetime is not enough for music.' - Rachmaninoff

I know now what Rachmaninoff meant. 

Sorry for the rant but I just had to let this feeling of euphoria out! Music is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As an international student heading to another country for college, how do I mingle and make friends with the "locals" and avoid being stuck in my nationality's asian bubble? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 09:29:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 04:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been looking at every bit of information on my college's website/handbook/guideline/etc. for the past 5 months, even before I received admission so I think i'm at least providing all the info.

There are other classes in the informatics department which would fulfil the requirement but... it's restricted as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 17:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry, I should have specified. I'm not in an American college and thus there are no differentiated COMP courses in the beginning!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 15:05:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You see, the problem is that the intro classes listed as a COMP class which I am, according to my major, not allowed to take. This is where my confusion stems from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 14:04:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the initial one:

Dear Prof. X,

I am a prospective student intending on majoring in X for the 2015 intake. However I have but one concern with the course. The breadth restrictions state that I am not allowed to take any COMP or INFO courses outside the core and thus, may I ask why this is the case?

I ask this because our Database Systems course later on requires a COMP courses outside of the core and I do not understand how I can counter this problem if it is a restriction. Could you please advise me on what I could do in this situation?

Regards,

Rumitative_Lychee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 11:28:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just need insight as to whether this app is legit and safe, never used something like this before.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 11:07:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here is one of them:

Dear Prof. X,

I am currently a prospective, incoming student to the university intending to major in X and have one question to ask if you don't mind answering.

One of the breadth restrictions are any courses labelled as COMP. If I would like to take a COMP breadth in my first semester as I have a deep passion for programming and have read that a COMP course is a requirement for the required INFO course later in the major, will I be able in any way to take the COMP courses as a breadth/diploma?

Thank you very much,
ruminative_lychee

To which he replied with a single "yes" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is my college prof. being an ass or is it just me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 05:44:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So one of my majors requirements is a 2nd year programming course. On the website, it states that to do this course, I need to take at least one 1st year programming course. However, my major restricts me from taking programming courses so I shot an email to the professor in charge of coordinating the major, asking him why this is the case and then gave details about my problems.

He then replied days later simply saying that he found my email offensive and that it was the case because they actually planned their major. I was taken aback but politely resent a rephrased email which was just ignored. Weeks later I ask a similar question in great detail about my plans and he just replied with a single Yes. 

What's happening? Was I really that rude? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A very under appreciated composer and work: Szymanowski - Symphony No. 1 in F minor, Op. 15 (1907) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 05:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Im mostly straight but want to try fucking a guy once, is this a bad idea? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty much straight but i'm just sexually curious to try it out one day. I've downloaded Grindr a few hours ago and have a page full of messages sent to me but i've never used these kinds of apps before.. help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Schumann's Final piano work -"Gesnge der Frhe" Op.133 (Songs of Dawn), perhaps one of the most incomprehensibly beautiful yet lonely piece I will ever hear </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 04:52:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Need some help finding a video/recording of Tan Dun's Piano Concerto </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember seeing a very brief except of the concerto with Lang Lang as the pianist a long time ago on Youtube but I forgot where I saw it now. Does anyone know where I can listen to Tan Dun's Piano Concerto (The Fire)? Can't seem to find it anywhere on youtube! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Selamat Hari Raya! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:32:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 11:37:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah I know but isn't making friends and networking a part of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:13:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not actually in "the industry" yet! I'm just a student who's done a handful of industry and academic internships! I'm a major in Geomatics/Spatial engineering which is really IMHO a black horse field. Basically, I work with GIS related projects as well as remote sensing and also do programming work with SQL and Matlab related to the GIS stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 09:34:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work with drones/UAVs for mapping projects :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> College orientation is next week and me, as a super shy and awkward student is afraid I won't make any friends D: </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 09:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:18:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unless.. you want to work in banking, finance, law, etc.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: How exactly did the price bubble for tulips occur in the past? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:31:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Melbourne University vs RMIT (This can probably be extended to every country) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:56:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Theresa May to force foreign students to leave the UK when their course ends </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 11:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> LEFTOVERS - Melbourne Uni vs RMIT </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 09:22:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> LEFTOVERS - Melbourne Uni vs RMIT </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 09:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 06:29:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what people tell me but whenever I look at myself in the mirror, all I see are fats! Even when I touch my body, all I can feel are fats.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm a 181 cm male who's a bit fat and if I do this, will I lose my fats quickly? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 06:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Currently I go to the gym 6 times a week but am still on the heavy side. I'm 19 and 181 cm tall and I weight 75 kilos and i'm planning on fasting from all food except for broccoli and water for the next one week. Will it help me lose fats fast? Or will it cause me to lose muscle mass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The concept of a "true present" in time does not exist for when we think about the "true present", it has already become a part of the past, embedded in our memories. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 05:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:21:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is it not worth it? I don't get it. Would it cost that much to install a security guard for each plane?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but I read that with the low amounts of Marshals they have, no every flight has security for the US anyways. Not sure about other countries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:09:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just curious, Malaysian?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: To prevent hijackings, why doesn't each flight have at least one security guard? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:07:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't see how it would be a bad idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it was an Australian.. huge blow up down under. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are the funniest posts on Reddit? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 08:07:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some movies about artistic and genius murderers/killers (e.g. Silence of the Lambs)? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 07:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: Do Siamese cats that are born and bred in Australia speak the same language as Siamese cats born and bred in Norway? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 12:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do Siamese cats that are born and bred in Australia speak the same language as Siamese cats born and bred in Norway? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 12:03:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Very noobish question... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 06:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello! I'm currently trying to learn the guitar by myself and am attempting Villa Lobo's Etude no.1. For the right hand, initially I only used my thumb, middle and index finger to pull the strings but videos on the internet show that you are meant to use all your fingers. How is this possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some pieces that sound very impressive but are actually easy to play? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some pieces that sound very impressive but are actually easy to play? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 18:46:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just shooting in the dark here, you a psych major? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 18:31:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He deleted it! What was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone take governing environments before? Was it a fun and difficult subject? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:23:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Twinkle twinkle little star has the same melody as the ABC song. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5:Why are there no third world countries with white people being the majority of the population? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Downloading this game now, whats the population? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:19:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is COMP10001 Foundations of Computing full? It says that there are no classes that are on today or in the future for you to register. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:44:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 02:21:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was young, silly and had some problems. I couldn't stand to hear more than 10 minutes of a Beethoven symphony and would just want to run outside the concert hall. I think it might have been because of my youthful impatience and naivety. I did however, one day stumble across my grandfather's huge collection of classical music and played 
some Schubert on the record player which made me feel emotions I never knew existed in me. Needless to say, after that moment my entire perspective was changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love how "The Nation" implies we're all American.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 12:46:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Assuming the camera was super advanced and could take clear images of our streets even. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If there's a satellite with a camera pointing exactly at Earth around 1000 million lightyears away that could take a picture of Earth and send it back in less than a second, would we be seeing the past if we looked at the images? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 12:45:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 12:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm assuming that if it could, the minute would be different than here on Earth. Thus are we viewing history? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 10:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found a dusty collection of Karajan conducting the 4th on my grandfather's shelf and am going to play the recoding tonight. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:58:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you soo much for your detailed post! I've just heard the piano quartet and the third Symphony that you suggested and it is absolutely remarkable! Your comments on him really opened my mind to his music and i'm currently trying to appreciate him more. Thank you once again.

Schumann really is a unique gem! 

I'm currently listening to his "Gesnge der Frhe" and it is to say the least, intriguing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know! The final passages of the third movement just strike home for me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As someone who hated classical music with a passion a long time ago, learning to appreciate it made me realise that it is the things that we find boring and incomprehensible that often holds remarkable beauty and wonder. To extend on that, I once hated Mozart and Bach but over the years have come to love them! With Schumann, I feel the same and simply wish to love and understand him more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:53:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's just... incomprehensible to me. The way he writes his music and structures it is just.. foreign...

I think this work really sums up what I mean. It's gorgeous! But at the same time, I don't understand anything!

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pcmO4AKmeDc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Worried student here, what exactly are my career options? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:49:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello everyone! I'm currently a student studying Geomatics Engineering (accredited) with geology and CS on the side as minors and am worried about my career options. Most posts i've read here say that GIS is mainly a desk job, no field work, etc. and quite a few posts expressed disdain in their jobs. While I still enjoy doing GIS related projects in class, if all else fails, do I have any other options?

Just for clarification, some things covered in education include:

- Engineering Computation (Basically programming with Matlab)
- Engineering math, calculus I,II,III, linear algebra
- Engineering risk analysis
- Database Systems (Programming with SQL)
- Python, C++ and Java
- GIS, GIS and more GIS
- Some remote sensing 
- A handful of geology courses 

I apologise for any inconvenience I may cause but thank you in advance for offering your insight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a student who's doing a GIS focused degree (Geomatics Engineering) with geology and CS on the side, i'm worried.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Update please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Someone help, I just can't appreciate Schumann! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:59:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been listening to him my whole life and have played a few of his works including his Kinderzsenen, Kriesleriana, Piano Sonata no.1 and Symphonic Etudes. However, I cannot for love of god appreciate and love him as much as I do for other composers like Schubert, Liszt, Beethoven, etc.

Any advice? He's an amazing composer that I know but what am I missing here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:39:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's basically a field that focuses on spatial analysis and visualisation and uses stuff from GIS to remote sensing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Planning to get the "ASUS UX501JW-DS71T Touch" for College/Gaming, is it good enough? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 13:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm gonna do an engineering degree with a fair bit of CAD, ArcGIS and programming work like Matlab. I'm also an avid gamer and would love to be able to play demanding games like Deus Ex Human Revolution, Far Cry 4, GTA 5, maybe even Fallout 4 when the time comes? Just wondering whether the specs of this laptop would fit the bill. Thank you for your time! 

- 15.6-inch 10-point touchscreen IPS 4K UHD display
- Core i7 processor and NVIDIA GTX 960M
- ZENBOOK aluminum uni-body design
- 512GB PCIe x4 SSD and Thunderbolt connectivity
- Premium sound design with Bang   Olufsen ICEpower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 08:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh! It was on my flair! It's called Geomatics/Spatial Engineering! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can I call myself an engineer? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 07:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean my engineering course isn't really the standard like EE, CE, SE, etc. and while I do graduate with a few engineering accreditations, is my field really an "engineering engineering" field? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Since college is coming soon, what advice/lifetips do you have for incoming freshmen? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:00:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I enrolled in some course already but the lectures clash with each other. Lectures can't be changed so does this mean I will need to withdraw and make amends? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 02:17:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For instance, my geology course clashes with my reshapping environments class so, I need to make changes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:07:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *GHOOOSTT CALLLOORRRIIEESSSS~~~ OOOO* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For one of my classes, it says there are no more spaces available when I tried adjusting my timetable. Does this mean it's completely full and I will be unable to take it for this semester? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is the best way to take notes in college lectures/tutes? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:46:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should I be using a laptop or my pen and paper? What are the pros and cons of each?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Should I be taking notes with my laptop or paper? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:55:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, my college has around 40-50k students which I find baffling! I was in a school with around ~150 students prior and to be thrown into a school with 50,000 students just boggles my mind. I'll definitely be joining cubs but if i'm entering mid-year, will I be at a disadvantage? Will social clicks be formed already?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some of the easiest Environments courses for first years? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Starting college next month and i'm completely introverted and somewhat antisocial. Will I really be able to make friends? How? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 21:26:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wait.. I hear people collecting thousands of relics.. HOW? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:55:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been playing for a month and have 100... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone take reshaping environments and mapping environments? How was it and how hard was it to get a H1? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:27:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really want to take Mapping but i've heard only negative things about the lecturer so far :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some not-so-obvious movie plotholes? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 13:53:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey! Ex-Foundie here! Don't worry about the first maths exam, it only counts for like what, 25% of the overall grade? You should definitely focus on getting a better score on the other test which is going to count for ~70% so it can definitely pull your grades up.

Also, try to focus on other subjects! Economics especially starts to get significantly more difficult later on when you are introduced to SAQS/LAQS which makes the first MCQ exam seem like a joke. Other subjects like HOI and Lit/Drama are really easy to score in if you follow the guidelines and ask teachers for help and participate (very important, it accounts for grades) in your classes. All in all, just relax and work harder! Good luck. PM me if you have any other questions. 

Finally, while it's awesome to respect your parents wishes and dreams (and I totally respect that and can relate) you should also come to realise that College is a time when you realize that at the end of the day it's YOUR life. Not your dad's, mum's or whatever but YOURS. So think carefully about what you want to really do. It may feel nice to honor your parents wishes in the short run, but after you've graduated it would really suck to be filled with regrets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How exactly are cockroaches able to survive the radiation of a nuclear bomb? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:49:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:55:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let's just hope that in the future the professor - who's probably backed by the dept.- doesn't start going against you and intentionally gives you unfair treatment in tests and assignments that would mess up your grade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:59:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How about constructing environments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Has anyone taken the following courses and has advice/reviews to give? They are: Designing Environments, Natural Environments, Understanding Planet Earth and Introduction to Programming? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 04:59:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 12:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure it'd dead already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If I want to increase the number of views on a website, will using a ddos like Loic or Hoic work? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 07:31:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:55:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it's the building next to a church then yes! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Melbourne Central sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone heard of the new Urbanest building in Central? What do ya think about it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 21:12:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I for one really want to study architecture! Advice would be appreciated. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's the population? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 00:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Warning:Very very eccentric but beautiful, just listen to the intro] Hahn Bin playing Sarasate's "Gypsy Airs" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:43:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Have an economics exam in 35 hours and I only know like 50-60 percent of the material. I'm planning on doing an all nighter to study, any advice? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 19:50:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If the Earth was united into a single country, would it be good or bad? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 06:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I either want to major in Music (been building repertoire for the past 15 years) or major in an IT-related major like Spatial Systems or CS... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crow says "Fuck you" to a guy who tries to mess with it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 09:18:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 03:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 18:04:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When companies usually state a BS as a requirement, would a degree like MEng, MPhil or PhD be overkill? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google is currently recruiting a Geo Data Specialist! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 12:29:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, who were the most underserving Nobel Prize recipients? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 07:06:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm soo friggin horny and can't stop thinking about sex with my GF! I can't get pass day 4, help? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 05:23:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 04:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in a destructive relationship with my girlfriend who had a terminal illness and I just wanted to give up because I couldn't bear to see her slowly fade as the days went by but I persisted and was at her side even during her last moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If you're in an incredibly heated argument with someone, what are some things you could say that would just make them laugh uncontrollably? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 15:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is runescape dead? Too late to join? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 14:18:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> While the human imagination is a mighty force, we cannot imagine a new colour. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 13:57:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, what are the MOST POPULAR browser based online games like MMORPGs? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 13:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why isn't 11 pronounced as onety-one like 21? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 13:08:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If women are gold diggers, how come I don't see any in African gold mines? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 12:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I want to start the violin but i'm 19... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 04:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey all, I really love the sounds of the violin and have tons of friends who are amazing violinists and i'm kinda inspired to be like them and learn the violin but... i'm 19... I feel as if i'm too old.

Now, while I don't have any unrealistic goals of ever reaching their level considering how they're already breezing through pieces like the Bach Chaccone, Mendelssohn Concertos, Caprices, etc. I don't know if it's the right move... will I forever sound like crap and be bounded to Suzuki-like-pieces? :(

I have some musical experience, i've been playing the piano for 15 years and have done my FRSM in music theory so I hope that can help a bit. I'm open to all advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 17:50:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She got tired after her laughing fit and went straight to sleep, leaving me alone, cold, lonely and very horny :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Completely new to the guitar, any tips? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:54:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey all, i'm going to go get a classical guitar to learn soon and was wondering if ya'll had any advice! 

I'm 18 and i've been playing the classical piano for 15 years and what I found with the piano is that at the beginning fundamental exercises like Czerny,Hanon,etc. are essential in building technique. Is there a similar thing for the guitar? 

I'm open to any advice, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIFU by trying to talk dirty to my GF </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 12:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So we were having a really hot make out/foreplay session and I (who was super horny), trying to be fucking suave, decided to just look her in her eyes to ramp up the hotness.

Our eyes lock on to each other and it was incredibly hot and beautiful and I decided to talk dirty. In the heat of the moment I said: "My tits are waiting for you". 

Let's just say the night ended there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone know of fugues that have more than four melodies or a ridiculous amount of melodies? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 06:05:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 05:58:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Impressive research, however through using Flaigocol mathematical derivations whereby the Hilbert spaces denote the Barnarch-Tarski paradox in equilibrium with the Fredhold theorem whereby the Erdos-nagy is 0, were can derive the Farrel-Markushevich in light of the Malgrage-Ehrenpresis if we denote the ZJ and Z* as the consant found in the Talor-Proudman. Thus:

Rasputin - Rasp[berry] = Utin[erry] 

Your mathematical rigour, though elegant, is flawed.

QED.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 07:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One year! Damn :(, so no hard boners during sex for a year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:20:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How people often allude Patriotism to the military. 


I mean come on, I love my country and feel that there are tons of other ways to show this love OUTSIDE the friggin military!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My great grandmother calling me fat when I was already anorexic and around 49 kilos as a 175 cm male. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 18:17:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah thanks for the input! I'm just a confused first year wondering whether to continue my degree or just switch out completely to something far more general like CS or Civil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 16:58:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to add, my Geomatics Course requires a range of courses from programming in SQL/C/Matlab, remote sensing, GIS, Linear Algebra+Calc, etc. (It's also credited by a couple surveying and engineering organisations) 

Will surveying degrees have this too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's the difference between a degree in Surveying and a degree in Geomatics Engineering? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 12:12:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is Geomatic Engineering a dead field? No one seems to talk about it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 06:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone did CASA's MPhil/PhD in Advanced Spatial Analysis care to share their experiences? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 05:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Definitely not your standard repertoire but this giant has to be introduced: Louis Spohr's "The Final Judgement" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 18:05:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 18:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do NOT attempt to take beta blockers for the first time if you aren't used to them!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone been to the Environments O-Week camp? How was it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 16:19:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rapists/Murderers/Criminals/Dictators who aren't executed benefit society. They stir up controversy, generating more views on youtube which nets more money for the site which gives Google more money to improve their services which eventually benefit the internet and society as a whole. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 11:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Question] I jack off too much and cant cum during sex, what can I do to fix this? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 11:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 07:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please show us a sample D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For every positive number, there must be a negative number. How can you prove this? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 06:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 06:02:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If anything, I think companies will usually value diversity over speciality so long as you have the necessary skillset.Just my 2c, one employer I talked to once told me that when he goes through job applications, it is the masters/phd degree that makes you who you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Because farts catch fire when lighted, if we force feed beans to prisoners in prisons and collect their farts, would we have solved the energy crisis problem? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 17:59:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 17:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *in a very soft voice*

g-g-geomatics? b-b-because... m-maps... can be u-useful for e-evil stuff too...

*goes back into hiding* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What jobs sectors could I enter if I continue my BEng/MEng in geomatic/spatial engineering? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to give an overview of what courses we have to take:


Using SQL to program (also learnt C, C++, Java and Python), SDI, GIS, GNSS, Geodesy, Standard math (calc+lin. algebra), land administration, ER Modelling, relational algebra, remote sensing and some geology courses like applications of geophysics, tectonics   geodynamics, field mapping and sedimentary geology.


Are GIS careers really my only option?


To open more doors, I have the option of switching to structural, civil or environmental, should I do it or stick with what I have?


I'm really open to all advice so thanks in advance! :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 11:22:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That attributes to the nature of the invisible hand not the accumulation of wealth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An Orchestra being a badass recording Beethoven's Emperor concerto during WW II with a bombardment outside. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 10:04:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [High School Economics] I don't understand this line from wikipedia, someone help? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 09:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this is the quote: "An "invisible hand" directed individuals and firms to work toward the nation's good as an unintended consequence of efforts to maximise their own gain. This provided a moral justification for the accumulation of wealth, which had previously been viewed by some as sinful"

I don't understand how this accumulation of wealth can be positive and a good thing. Someone help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 04:44:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you alright?

"yes!"

No! You're all, all left!!11!!1!1.1!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You cannot pronounce "xkcd" no matter how hard you try. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-14 04:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surveying is something that interests me but it would be nice if there were other options as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 13:05:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes I feel as though my engineering field isn't "real" engineering compared to ME,EE,CE,BME, etc. I really really love stuff that involves GIS,GPS,GNSS,Geodesy, etc. Was really inspired after using Google Earth for the first time and used to handmake crude maps of my countryside and local forests when I was younger so I decided to go into Geomatics. However... while employment isn't a real problem, i'm considering changing to Civil or Environmental just for added breadth as that's what my peers tell me I should do... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What jobs sectors could I enter if I continue my BEng/MEng in geomatic/spatial engineerings? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 12:40:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to give an overview of what courses we have to take:

Using SQL to program (also learnt C, C++, Java and Python), SDI, GIS, GNSS, Geodesy, Standard math (calc+lin. algebra), land administration, ER Modelling, relational algebra, remote sensing and some geology courses like applications of geophysics, tectonics   geodynamics, field mapping and sedimentary geology.


Are GIS careers really my only option?

To open more doors, I have the option of switching to structural, civil or environmental, should I do it or stick with what I have?

I'm really open to all advice so thanks in advance! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If a north korean civilian were to run across the line separating the north and south in the DMZ, what would happen to the person? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 12:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [OT] Wrote this piece when I was ten years old, how is it (haven't edited it at all)? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 10:56:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Aqofm231EO34o(C34^2? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 09:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 08:19:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bottled water. 

I mean, everyone was like who the heck would want to buy water at the price of softdrinks? Look at them now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Redditers who broke up with their SO, why did you do it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 08:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's sad to hear :( how can I widen my skillset then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:39:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the input, could you provide more details please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:32:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's an Australian degree for the bachelors in engineering and masters in engineering. Right now I could switch over to either civil, structural or environmental but i'm not too sure about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:29:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was actually called Geomatics Engineering but my university renamed it for some reason. It is accredited by Engineers Australia, EUR-ACE and RICS and material we cover include:

Using SQL to program (also learnt C, C++, Java and Python), SDI, GIS, GNSS, Geodesy, Standard math (calc+lin. algebra), land administration, ER Modelling, relational algebra, remote sensing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:31:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes on first dates I like to just stare into the other person's eyes, hold their hand and tell them: 


"Did you know Ho Chi Minh used to work as a baker in London"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I take out the white cream in Oreos and fill them with white toothpaste and leave them on the counter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:28:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can for a while then your body gives in. Try refraining from thirst and hunger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Freewill doesn't exist, we are controlled by our bodies. We eat because we are hungry. We play videogames because our minds demand it. We procrastinate because we are bored. We have sex because our bodies desire it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:26:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:21:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like.... *drumroll* ... BONERMAN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm a freshman majoring in BEng/MEng in Geomatic/Spatial Engineering and have no idea on what to do after graduation. Any advice on what job sectors I could enter and what to do while still in college? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to give an overview of what courses we have to take:

Using SQL to program (also learnt C, C++, Java and Python), SDI, GIS, GNSS, Geodesy, Standard math (calc+lin. algebra), land administration, ER Modelling, relational algebra, remote sensing and some geology courses like applications of geophysics, tectonics   geodynamics, field mapping and sedimentary geology.



Are GIS careers really my only option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hey Reddit, if I structure a mini, no-interval recital with this repertoire, will it be okay? (Suggestions are welcome) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:46:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey all, just planning for a not-to-serious performance for my residential college and picked some pieces out that are somewhat entertaining both for classical and non-classical audiences which are as follows:


1) Palmgren - Snowflakes (Fitting, it's almost winter right now!)

2) Bartok - Allegro Babaro 

3) Schubert Sonata no.14 - Movement I or III

4) Liszt Legende no.2

5) Prokofiev - Suggestion Diabolique

6) Aaron Copland - Cat and Mouse


What do you guys think? Too many "short" pieces? I'm open to any suggestions and advice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, what was the first post on Reddit? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If object X produces a sound at 50dB and object Y produces a sound at 50 dB, will having both sounds together produce a sound of 100 dB? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 14:08:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If object X produces a sound at 50dB and object Y produces a sound at 50 dB, will having both sounds together produce a sound of 100 dB. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 13:55:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some of the toughest truth questions you can ask? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 12:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Serious] Reddit, what were some of the limitations of the invisible hand? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 10:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Historically, was the Invisible Hand useful as an idea? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 08:44:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, compared to other bio-sciences majors, are pharmacology majors seeing a grim job outlook as well? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 17:40:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is the title Champion Slayer hard to get? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 10:31:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 06:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP UPDATE PLEASE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 06:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better safe than sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 06:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't even know you get an engineering ring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What were the pros and cons of Greek Direct Democracy (In context of Ancient/Classical Greece)? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 04:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So far, i've been reading to no avail. What i've found is that some limitations included:
- Women, Slaves, Foreigners were excluded
- Men, regardless of education, were allowed to vote so some uneducated people could be making important political decisions
- Unpopular but necessary decisions would not be likely passed (can't find examples though)

Pros:
- Allowed a representation of what the people want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 18:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> About writing music, i've composed a few musical pieces, mostly for the piano like double and triple fugues and etudes though i've sketched out an incomplete symphony (only the first movement)

I don't think i'll ever be a band leader, not really interested in leading, I just want to play music aha

And about the type of prog, i'm still relatively new to prog so i'm open to everything right now :)

Thank you for such a detailed reply! I'm going to watch those links now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hey, need some advice! How do I transition into Prog Rock? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 16:40:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey all! For the last 15 years i've been playing as a classical pianist and did dabble a bit into jazz and was wondering what advice you could give me if I wanted to move into prog rock? 

For a sense of ability, my repertoire included Chopin's op.25 (Full), Debussy Preludes Book II (Including no.12) and the Shotakovich Concertos.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 16:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two worlds one sun... If only the warring nations of this world realized that we all share a single sun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 03:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds cool! Thanks :)

One more question, how long after you submitted your materials did you get invited for an interview? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:11:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much money do you make monthly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If gravity makes things go down how come air and clouds and birds don't go down? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:57:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you soo much for introducing me to Palmgren! I have never heard of him or felt this way about music for a very very long time. :')

edit: Just sightread it after printing the score from IMSLP and played it on my piano with my windows open close to midnight and I am soo happy right now, thank you soo much Catt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If we know all the elements that make humans, why can't we create another man simply by mixing all those elements? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 13:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never said any of my pieces were easy :p, yeah that prelude was a monster! I included it in my fellowship recital a few months back. Loved the quote of La Marseillaise towards the coda xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 13:27:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Listening to it right now and I am in awe! Can't believe i've never heard of this gorgeous gem before (esp. the third one!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, i'm looking for some piano pieces that are relatively unknown but are beautiful and not too difficult (limited time)! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 12:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! Just to give a sense of my ability, here's some pieces from my repertoire:
Chopin Etudes op.25 (Full)
Schubert D.960 Sonata
Beethoven op.110,109 Sonatas
Debussy Preludes Book I and II
Shostakovich Concertos I and II
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My College's motto is "God as Guide, the Word as Light". Are there any biblical references? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 12:24:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, what are some critiques of the Invisible Hand? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:09:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly 666 comments, how meta- ops I spoiled it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For people living in residential colleges, how was the interview process like? Any advice? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 15:52:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 14:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I can just buy a plane ticket right now with no preparation whatsoever and fly straight into South Korea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If I want to go to South Korea for a holiday for less than 20 days, how can I apply for a VISA and what documentations do I need? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 14:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-05 16:27:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's freezing down here in Melbourne! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:54:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A high school friend of mine did a research essay on Nobili's Rings and Liesegang Rings which I thought was subtly beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Without high school chemistry, can I still major in chemical engineering? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 11:28:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who is the Chemistry equivalent of Feynman and Sagan? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 11:03:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, how in the world do I write a stunning, one page, personal statement? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 06:46:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jaw dropping video of an improvisation of Beethoven's Moonlight Sonata in the style of Khachaturian </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 18:11:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it legal to own a personal, home-chem lab with chemicals? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This North Korean Piano Concerto sounds very Rachmaninoffian </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:48:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 03:22:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't actually get karma from upvoted selfposts th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 02:37:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't actually get karma from upvoted selfposts tho...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 02:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was the fucker who went around open, unattended laptops and loaded porn websites on them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, if you could tell the leader of ISIS just one thing, what would it be? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 02:21:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, if aliens were to visit our planet, what's the weirdest thing they'll find thats normal for us? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 02:04:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 16:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are fucking amazing. KUDOS TO YOU. HAHHAHAA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 16:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Grave of the Fireflies. 

Had me crying like a little bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 15:59:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sprayed some pepper spray in front of me to test it out. Problem was, the wind was blowing in my direction so it came right back at me.

Long story short, pepper spray HURTS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 15:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dildo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIFU because I was unintentionally molested by my parents and molested my relatives when I was young. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 15:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guys I have a couple of cringe-worthy experiences to tell...

1) When I was younger, around 8 - 10, my mum used to grab my butt and say how jealous she was (especially when we slept together) of how smooth it was... this continued until I was 15 and eventually I started to feel weird out and politely asked her to stop.


and...


2) I used to love playing around with my mum's nipples when I was around 5 and found it cool that it grew hard when I bit it and touched it enough (FUCK MY LIFE). And when I tried to do this to my grandma and dad, they gave me the trashing of my life.

Someone please shoot me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 15:21:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GUYS SERIOUSLY, WHY DID YOU DO THIS TO ME. I HAVE REAL LIFE FRIENDS ON REDDIT WHO NOW KNOW THIS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 11:26:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wasn't watching some porn flick intentionally! It just "popped" up on the telly and then BAMF!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIFU by thinking I actually had superpowers. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 04:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, so this didn't happen today exactly but a relative of mine mentioned it to me and refreshed my memory and now I am burning in shame.


So, when I was around 8 years old I had this obsession with superpowers, superheroes, the works, and really wanted any power regardless of how lame it was, be it the power of super strength, super hearing, growth, etc. 


One day, when I was watching TV, this really hot steamy sex scene suddenly popped up and for the first time I saw a woman's nipples. Instinctively, I started to touch my crotch for some reason because it felt weird... I then noticed that I had a raging bulge in my pants. I was amazed. I grew?


At that point, I convinced myself that I had a superpower and was eager to show the world. The next day was my birthday and in front of all my friends and relatives I proudly announced that I was a superhero and told them that I had the power of growth. One of my friends didn't believe me so I showed them a demonstration. Right then and there, I grabbed my crotch area and started rubbing it - hard - in front of all those little kids who's parents were rushing to cover their eyes. In about 30 seconds I managed to "get it up" and gave a proud smirk of achievement to my audience. 


God, I fucked up.


edit: Real life friends on reddit are now calling me bonerman...

edit2: On front page... expected this post to be drowned but no...

edit3: The irony is that I kinda have ED today.... guess my nemesis, ED-man got me :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL During the ice age, 32,000 years ago, a squirrel buried a seed. Now the seed has been used to grow a flower </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:52:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL The first image of Hydrogen Bonds has already been taken </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 11:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some manga/anime that focus on Chemistry? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 11:36:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 07:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I posted this last time and no one upvoted it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chinese citizens of Reddit, what do you think about the censorship program? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 17:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's for a ... urm... school project, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 17:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was this the incident in Perth, WA?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 17:27:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in Australia so uh-oh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 17:27:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 17:27:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lesson learned: Chemistry kills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, what are the most terrifying chemicals known to man and what do they do? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 17:11:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Have there been any records of training child soldiers from when they were young/genetically modified soldiers? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 15:09:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 10:54:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every account on reddit is a bot except you. please.Every account on reddit is a bot except you. Every account on reddit is a bot except you. help. Every account on reddit is a bot except you. Us. Every account on reddit is a bot except you.Every account on reddit is a bot except you.Every account on reddit is a bot except you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, what's the most creative thing you can say? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 10:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are the most popular websites/browser-based games out there? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 10:40:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What advice would you give a freshman chemistry major? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 10:27:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 06:08:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing! Was just curious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If I'm a student studying in a foreign country with a student visa and committed a crime there that deserves death in my home country, will I be extradited back to my home country and sentenced? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 04:33:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For the Invisible Hand to truly work, is it true that you must have a perfect market situtation? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 02:57:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Need to write an essay arguing whether the Invisible Hand was good or bad but I can't think of any points aside from definitions, help? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 00:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's the most beautiful word you know? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:09:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:00:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 11? Wow! I must be really behind the times haha. Had no idea children were already aware of the references to economic theory, Reinmannian manifolds, Debussy's La mer and such!

Jokes aside, who cares about age?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [WP] You're listening to the greatest orchestral performance of your life. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 08:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, how do I get over depression caused by a book? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 08:29:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just read "Flowers For Algernon" and for the past two days i've never felt this depressed before... help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If my nationality is a country that gives the death penalty and I currently study overseas in a foreign country that does not, will I be sentenced to death if I commit a crime that would deserve death (in my country of nationality) in the foreign country, will I be deported and charged? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 00:19:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 13:58:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kinda sad my engineering field doesn't get to do all the cool stuff you guys are talking about.. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 10:51:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in a non-US high school atm! To be honest, at this point I don't really even know what it means to know a concept... I mean, I can answer the questions after practicing them for a while but I have no idea what you mean by understanding the concept. Like, i'm going through geometric distributions right now and I could say that if X was the number of failures before a success it would look like Pr(Xx) = (1-p)^x so maybe that counts as understanding?

Thanks for the pop book suggestions! I'll definitely look for them. I've actually read Frenkel's Love and Math too and would recommend it to you, it's great!. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 06:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm currently doing high school math and the topics we're doing are stuff like volumes of solids of revolutions, differential equations (at a hs level of course),  markov chains, hypergeometric distributions, density functions, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, I think i'm terrible in math so how in the world can I improve if I think the subject is boring? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 05:31:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm trying to study for my math test but find it incredible dull and boring. Many people have told me that math is as beautiful as my other interests like poetry and composition and that the beauty is analogous to a stark sculpture where beauty really is in the eye of the beholder but I can't seem to find any remote sort of beauty. I mean in Physics and Chemistry, it's much easier to appreciate the science because it's applications and presence is soo much more observable to the average person but mathematics; I am aware it's the language of the universe and without understanding it we would be blind, etc .but I can't seem to find any sort of accessible beauty or appreciation for math.

Any suggestions as to what I could do or see or read to gain an insight into this mysterious world?

edit: By dull and boring, I don't mean math! I'm referring to the test. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5:What exactly is Amnesty International and what do they really do besides making online petitions? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 01:20:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Want to major in Chem in Uni but haven't done high school chem? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey all, so I have a bit of a dilemma. I've recently just realized that what I really want to study in College is chemistry, now the problem is that I haven't taken any AP/IB/A-Level/ etc. Chem in HS (only did one year of IB SL chemistry). As of such, i'm required to take a bridging/foundation Chem course to make up for my lack of Chem. Seeing how I lack basic chem, would it really be a wise decision to major in Chem even if I really enjoy it?

Just for additional info, in terms of HS science, I only took AP Physics B, C, AP Calc AB, BC and AP CS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 04:36:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you mean by infinite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:10:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, but I find it admirable that he would face his worst fears to try to save someone he loved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL Enrique Granados, a revolutionary Spanish composer, died attempting to save his drowning wife after his ship was shot by a German U-Boat even though he had a deep fear of water and could not swim at all </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 15:52:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>