<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8471</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bernie Out of the Closet: Sanders Longstanding Deal with the Democrats </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 23:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 01:00:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just saw that one today.  They had a great one last Fathers' Day.  Something along the lines of Scotch helps a dad forget his disappointment in his children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:13:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mis-read as "fighting ISIS in your location." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the first document in the Project Gutenberg corpus is the Declaration of Independence. Happy July 4th! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 13:41:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tomgram: Gottesdiener and Garcia, How to Dismantle This Country </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:51:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Prediction: Bernie Sanders Will Win the White House </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just noticed that the ellipses in the crawls for Star Wars Episodes IV and V have four dots instead of the customary three .... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:10:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If you were a daemon, how would I start you? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 00:30:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL of kaiten-zushi: Restaurants with a long Conveyor Belt of plates of sushi. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 19:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Harvard engineering students devise ultimate BBQ smoker </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 14:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 02:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> High-end mechanical watches; you're supposed to get them serviced every five years or so.  My Omega just stopped working for no reason, and I had to send it in for $500 worth of repairs.  Seriously considering selling it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 00:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "A lawyer with a briefcase can steal more than 50 men with guns."
-- Don Corleone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Turks of Reddit: Why do you get upset when the Armenian Genocide is called Genocide? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-16 02:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously, I mean, you weren't even alive then.  You had nothing to do with it.  But the evidence is just irrefutable.  As an American I have no problem acknowledging our own genocide of Native Americans.  I wasn't there.  I didn't do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why do onion rings only come in one size? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-04 00:43:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, everything else comes in at least two sizes: fries, wings, drinks.  But I have **never ever** seen the option to order large or small onion rings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 00:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With apologies to Stephen Wright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just found out that McDonald's is serving all-day breakfast ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 00:07:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... all day breakfast?  I don't have that kind of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL China Has A 100,000 Metric Ton Strategic Pork Reserve. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-31 14:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WWJDrive? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 02:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I see what you did there, Onion :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 23:28:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-02 00:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it really my kid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-31 17:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The barber asked if I wanted my eyebrows trimmed :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-28 19:03:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either an egg, dumplings, or some sliced pork; mushrooms; frozen green beans or spinach added at the last minute so they stay crisp; maybe dried seaweed; and kimchi as a topping.  Sometimes I'll add Sriracha and Soy Sauce.  Quick, yummy, satisfying, and cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blizzard confession. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 21:17:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I knew he couldn't say it with a straight face! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 21:07:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-16 21:11:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess these aren't "real" Muslims either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL The "Apache Wedding Blessing" that was recited at my wedding doesn't come from the Apache. It actually comes from a Hollywood script. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-11 14:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-10 01:50:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been working at Tufts for almost two years, and I'm pretty sure they break out the good stuff for Spring Visit and Fall Orientation, when parents bring their precious snowflakes to visit/stay.  Otherwise we suffer with the see-thru TP.  Note, this is in the admin buildings that parents are likely to visit.  In the class buildings it's all suck-tp all year round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Selectmen clear way for young girl's 'Black Lives Matter' rally on Jan. 5 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 20:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL: "LEGO CERTIFIED PROFESSIONAL" is a thing. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 19:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-17 00:10:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would have posted about [Caffe sospeso](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Caff%C3%A8_sospeso) ... but then I probably wouldn't have gotten as many upvotes :)

" [A] pending coffee is a cup of coffee paid for in advance as an anonymous act of charity." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-13 15:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Useless!?!  Memorizing good poetry is never useless!  Case in point: one day I was walking with a friend in some terrible winter weather.  He remarked how cold it was, and I said, "If our eyes we closed, then the lashes froze 'til we sometimes couldn't see.  It wasn't much fun but the only one to whimper was Sam MgGee."  English Major friend was impressed, and it brightened our day a little bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-27 03:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or if you're actually interested in knowing [what happened]( http://blog.simplejustice.us/2014/11/25/the-ferguson-lie/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL The blue color of Peacocks' feathers (and many other animals) is caused by something called Structural Color. They're not really blue. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 16:55:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Former Prisoners of Reddit, how did you escape and what websites do you visit now instead? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-08 19:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, when I first saw [this post](http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/2lntrx/former_prisoners_of_reddit_what_is_something_that/) that's how I read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-04 15:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are right, they are super-protective of the brand.  I am actually paying royalties to Magister LaFleur and the Wheelock sisters :)  They are very excited about the app and it's linked from the [website](http://wheelockslatin.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-03 23:01:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... and of course the photo they show is Barnes   Noble, one of the chains that will be *closed* on Thanksgiving.

oh, wait.  I misread the title :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 20:49:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, the free versions only goes up to chapter 5.  The full version is $9.99 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 15:30:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, there's also an [Android Version](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.joelman.latin) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Salvete Omnes! Browsing Reddit instead of working on your Latin homework? Then check out my new app for Wheelock's Latin! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-02 15:23:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 18:39:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "In its majestic equality, the law forbids rich and poor alike to sleep under bridges, beg in the streets and steal loaves of bread."

-- [Anatole France](http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Anatole_France) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Is The Most Hilarious Bumper Sticker I Have Ever Seen In My Life! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-19 14:52:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The joy of reconnecting with your old high school english teacher </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-09 14:32:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 23:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Say "what" again, motherfucker! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 19:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this guy moves into a new neighborhood, and his next-door neighbor comes over to welcome him.  He says, 
"Hey, I'm having a party tonight, wanna come over?  There'll be plenty of drinking, drugs, and wild sex!"  
They guy says, "Sure.  What should I wear?"
"Wear whatever you want, it'll just be you and me!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-19 23:27:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Rick never said, "Play it again, Sam." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> To the guy who left a big soaking wad of paper towels in the urinal just now, "What the hell were you thinking!?!?" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-14 17:49:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, seriously, what is wrong with you?  How is this **ever** an acceptable alternative? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-03 22:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Boston Butt, St. Louis rack, and Baby-back ribs](http://imgur.com/UzUGjP7). It was a good day :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-02 02:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Binding U.S. law requires prosecutions for those who authorize torture](
http://www.salon.com/2009/01/18/prosecutions_2/)

CONVENTION AGAINST TORTURE:

Article 2

...

2. No exceptional circumstances whatsoever, whether a state of war or a threat or war, internal political instability or any other public emergency, may be invoked as a justification of torture.

Article 4

1. Each State Party shall ensure that all acts of torture are offences under its criminal law. The same shall apply to an attempt to commit torture and to an act by any person which constitutes complicity or participation in torture.

Article 7

1. The State Party in territory under whose jurisdiction a person alleged to have committed any offence referred to in article 4 is found, shall in the cases contemplated in article 5, if it does not extradite him, submit the case to its competent authorities for the purpose of prosecution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-31 03:40:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow.  I believe this is not actually satire! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 02:46:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [We're contagion!](http://www.bitrebels.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/Earth-Mars-Moon-Human-Destruction.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-05 17:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "And as a prudent man puts money by to serve as a provision for the material wants of his old age, so too he needs to lay up against the end of his days provision for the intellect. As the years go by, comparative values are found to alter: Time, says Sophocles, takes many things which once were pleasures and brings them nearer to pain. In the day when the strong men shall bow themselves, and desire shall fail, it will be a matter of yet more concern than now, whether one can say `my mind to me a kingdom is'; and whether the windows of the soul look out upon a broad and delightful landscape, or face nothing but a brick wall."

-- [A.E. Housman](http://www.chiark.greenend.org.uk/~martinh/poems/introductory.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Good biography of John Wilkes Booth? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-05 00:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I just watched the Drunk History John Wilkes Booth episode, and found it fascinating, particularly the fact that he and his brother Edwin were famous actors, and his strong identification with Brutus.  Is there a good biography out there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How can I weigh my head? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-28 14:57:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> White supremacy and slavery: Gerald Horne on the real story of American independence </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-27 19:55:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I got a Fortune Cookie full of Irony today. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-24 18:54:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-20 22:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't [fuck it up](http://prestowrites.files.wordpress.com/2010/09/velociraptor-free-workplace-21887-1283890097-7.jpg)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-19 17:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why shouldn't our top grade-inflating university not also start like-inflating on Facebook? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Schumacher knows. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 02:45:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Schumacher knows. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 02:25:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-15 02:18:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't worry if your subordinate clause doesn't agree with the subject of your primary clause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the computer cursor gets its name from the transparent slide engraved with a hairline that is used for marking a point on a slide rule, and that cursor is Latin for "runner". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-09 14:51:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Whom Will We Honor Memorial Day? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-26 15:04:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 22:27:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How exactly did Hundreds of Deaths cause Jindal to Refuse to expand Medicaid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 04:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, now that the real constituents are standing up for our (their) rights, We The Sheeple now have a chance to be sheared more enjoyably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-07 13:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't that all of them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-03 20:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [original site](http://gamersledge.com/its-that-time-of-year-again-time-for-giant-spiritual-dicks/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The majestic woodcock [fixed][nsfw]. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-03 20:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-03 19:18:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough.  In that case I'll settle for pointing out his promise to vote against retroactive immunity for telecoms, then promptly voting for it once he got the nomination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is Oracle's Larry Ellison going to pay Oregon back for the Cover Oregon debacle? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-03 19:15:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-03 16:11:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha!  This makes a wonderful companion piece to [Candidate Obama vs. President Obama](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7BmdovYztH8)  There's plenty of hypocrisy to go around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thousands of workers mark May Day </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-01 16:02:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-25 23:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An Englishman's way of speaking absolutely classifies him
The moment he speaks he makes some other man despise him.
-- Henry Higgins, My Fair Lady </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-23 00:54:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, but they're pretty strict about editorialized titles, and there's no current story that I could find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-22 23:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I [tried this morning](http://www.reddit.com/r/self/comments/23o5re/just_a_reminder_that_it_has_been_5_years_since/) but got no love.  Maybe I picked the wrong subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just A Reminder That It Has Been 5 Years Since Sean Hannity Promised To Be Waterboarded For Charity. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-22 13:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [The latest post I could find.](http://www.newshounds.us/sean_hannity_waterboard_weasel_1646_days_since_he_promised_to_undergo_dunking_for_charity_10242013) Enjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Britons of Reddit: After washing dishes, do you seriously put them in the rack without rinsing the soap off? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-18 15:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just got this Straight Dope in my inbox: [Do the British not rinse dishes after washing them?](http://www.straightdope.com/columns/read/3158/do-the-british-not-rinse-dishes-after-washing-them) which made me so glad we won our war of independence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-14 02:40:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or explaining the difference between effect and affect.  Oh, wait ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-31 16:23:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, except about that "ending the war" thing, if you'd carefully read the article, he notes that Obama did his damndest to keep troops in Iraq:

The war indeed ended in 2011. But lets not forget that before (most of) the troops left, Obama begged al-Maliki to let U.S. forces stay beyond the deadline set in the Status of Forces Agreement (SOFA).

And then later, he took credit for withdrawing the troops that he had tried to keep there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Obamas Iraq Fairy Tale </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-31 15:57:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-30 19:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One time, I was in a Babies 'R' Us, and they had these little phones that you could speak into, and it would play back.  I recorded "You're adopted," for the next lucky kid to come along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Parents of all ages will understand. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-30 18:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 17:04:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... not that there's anything wrong with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-08 20:33:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My wife: My urine doesn't smell different after eating asparagus.
Me: Yes it does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gettin' real tired of all your Goddamn Lies, Mr. Studfinder. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-22 18:49:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-20 19:58:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When a man grows tired of Reddit, he has become tired of The Internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-19 15:01:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel so much safer now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-14 16:10:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow.  Just don't read to the end ...
Wherever one stands on the "Jewish question," we think it would behoove our readers to applaud this particular Jew's open defiance of the ever-present white-shaming bully-brigade. Bravo, Jerry.

... or do a search for "Jews" on this particular site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-13 14:37:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> doh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So this duck walks into a drugstore ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-13 14:29:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this duck walks into a drugstore and gets a pack of gum.  The cashier says, "That'll be $1."  The duck says, "Just put it on my bill."

The next day, the duck comes back and gets a pack of condoms.  The cashier says, "That'll be $5.  I suppose you want me to put them on your bill."  The duck says, "No thanks, I'm not that kind of duck." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cornell Pair Introduce American-Chinese Food To Shanghai </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-12 13:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-11 17:31:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bless her heart! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-11 16:05:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see what you did there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL: The word "nice" used to mean "foolish, stupid, senseless," and comes from the Latin "nescire", meaning "to be ignorant." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-11 15:00:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As TPP Opposition Soars, Corporate Media Blackout Deafening </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-07 00:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lunch Lady Accused Of Threatening To Shoot Up Middle School Because Of Bad Cookies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-04 16:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-18 19:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So Captain America is left-handed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gentlemen: You're standing at the urinal in a pair of pants that has a perfectly good fly. Why do you have to Open Up The Whole Shop just to take a whiz? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-08 00:43:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pope Francis leaves New Year's voice mail for nuns in Spain: "What are the nuns doing that they can't answer?" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-05 18:25:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-05 03:36:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 21 Jesus said unto him, If thou wilt be perfect, go and sell that thou hast, and give to the poor, and thou shalt have treasure in heaven: and come and follow me.

22 But when the young man heard that saying, he went away sorrowful: for he had great possessions.

23 Then said Jesus unto his disciples, Verily I say unto you, That a rich man shall hardly enter into the kingdom of heaven.

24 And again I say unto you, It is easier for a camel to go through the eye of a needle, than for a rich man to enter into the kingdom of God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-03 15:37:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmmm ... and if I hadn't voted for you in 2000, Ralph, I'd have voted for Gore, and we never would've invaded Iraq in the first place.  Sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wiki markup to show total users/subscribers on a given subreddit. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-20 23:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would be nice, if you have a list of related subreddits, to have a way to show how active it is, i.e. show how many readers, and "users here now", next to the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-14 21:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Haters gonna hate!](http://kevinlepore.tumblr.com/post/16595115371/marcel-marceau-impersonating-a-man-walking-against) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-01 18:26:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Marsellus: I'm prepared to scour the the Earth for that motherfucker. If Butch goes to Indochina, I want a nigger waiting in a bowl of rice ready to pop a cap in his ass.

-- [Pulp Fiction](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0110912/quotes) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-25 17:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why was this marked "Not US Politics"?  ALEC stands for *American* Legislative Exchange Council </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Google: Doing Evil with ALEC </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-25 15:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why the Boeing machinists' fight matters </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-18 19:13:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 20:47:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://obsoletegamer.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/03/You-Wouldnt-Download-A-Car.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL: Buskers (street musicians) who want to perform on the Paris Metro have to audition, and there are only 300 permits to go around. I wish they had that here in Boston! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 21:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-06 03:23:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So apparently I'm going Straight to Hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Trans-Pacific Partnership: What's at Stake is Democracy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-27 14:16:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Much of JPMorgan's $13 Billion Fine Will Taxpayers Foot? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-23 23:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Triumph of the Right </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-23 23:17:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-15 17:50:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Or maybe not](http://etymonline.com/index.php?allowed_in_frame=0 search=nincompoop searchmode=none)

1670s, nicompoop. Despite similarity [noted by Johnson] to Latin legal phrase non compos mentis "insane, mentally incompetent" (c.1600), the connection is denied by etymologists because the earliest forms lack the second -n-. Weekley thinks first element may be a proper name, and cites Nicodemus, which he says was used in French for "a fool," or Nicholas. Klein says probably an invented word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-09 00:53:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Late to the party, but I'll add my 2 cents anyway.  Every iPhone I see in the wild is in a 3rd-party case.  There's a whole industry that has grown up around compensating for this basic design flaw:  The iPhone screen is apparently so brittle that it can't handle being dropped.  At all.  If it were produced by any company other than Apple, people would be losing their shit over this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-07 23:23:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to say this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> And when thou prayest, thou shalt not be as the hypocrites are: for they love to pray standing in the synagogues and in the corners of the streets, that they may be seen of men. Verily I say unto you, They have their reward. -- Matthew 6:5 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-27 22:13:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-21 20:40:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Kung Fu Grandpa in the Food Lion parking lot!](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gYvw68IneV4) Shake it off, homey, shake it off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-19 02:40:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When Rolex introduced the Oyster Perpetual, the [first waterproof watch](http://rolexblog.blogspot.com/2012/04/1964-rolex-fishbowl-ad.html), in 1926, they got jewelers to display their watches in fishbowls, complete with water and fish.  It was pretty sensational at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For all you students: Happy Back-to-School from Calvin   Hobbes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-02 19:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So in response to the question: "What is your dream job?" Isn't the real question: "What would you do if you didn't need to worry about money?" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-12 02:12:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This isn't an idle question.  As a society we're quickly approaching a state where there just won't be enough jobs, and we'll have to figure out what to do with people.  This is a scary question, but it should be an exciting one. [I propose that unemployment is not a disease, but the natural, healthy functioning of an advanced technological society.](http://www.deepleafproductions.com/wilsonlibrary/texts/raw-RICH.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm a madman who must be stopped. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-11 22:47:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-08 01:19:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a Sikh sense of humor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 01:54:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that a [Blancpain](http://www2.europeanwatch.com/froogle.php?id=18076)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-26 02:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the hell is wrong with you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Checkmate: somewhere a traffic engineer is laughing at me. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-18 14:30:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-14 22:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this white guy walks into Starbucks with a parrot on his shoulder.  The clerk says, "Where did you get him?"  The parrot answers, "Jersey". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> HOLY SHIT THIS IS THE MIC FOR YOU </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-10 23:02:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Temperature is Too Damn High! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-06 21:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-29 23:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When a man is tired of Reddit, he is tired of The Internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-27 01:07:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better image: http://imgc.allpostersimages.com/images/P-473-488-90/60/6067/OSZD100Z/posters/michael-shaw-gays-and-lesbians-getting-married-haven-t-they-suffered-enough-new-yorker-cartoon.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gays: Welcome to Reality :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-27 01:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-26 02:17:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Years later, Pavel was walking through the Chicago Zoo with his teenaged son. As they approached the bear enclosure, one of the creatures turned and walked over to near where Pavel and his son Pavel Jr. were standing. The large bear stared at Pavel, lifted its paws off the ground, and played with a plastic chair. The bear did that several times then roared loudly, all the while staring at the man. 

Remembering the his dear friend from 2011, Pavel couldn't help wondering if this was the same bear. Pavel summoned up his courage, climbed over the railing and made his way into the enclosure. He walked right up to the bear and stared back in wonder. The bear roared again, wrapped its arms around Pavel's chest and crushed his ribcage, killing him instantly. Probably wasn't the same bear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 17 Cooking Projects Ain't Nobody Got Time For </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-23 16:52:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-22 18:47:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But there [is hope](http://www.amazingribs.com/tips_and_technique/offset_smokers.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL: If you have a Char-Broil Offset grill, you're doing it wrong. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-22 18:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help! Why are my ribs never done? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-21 23:28:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm using a standard Char-broil offset smoker, and I'm monitoring the temperature, keeping it between 230 and 250 for 7, or even 8 hours.  I've also got a water pan in there to keep things moist.  But the ribs and boston butt are never done, and the fat isn't completely rendered, so I have to finish them in a 350 degree oven for half an hour to an hour.  How can they not be done after 8 hours? 

The only other clue I have is that I'm monitoring the temperature with a redi-check remote thermometer, which is an internal-temperature thermometer; is it possible that this is giving me an incorrect reading?

This is driving me insane.  I'd appreciate any advice, Pitmasters.

EDIT: OK, thanks for the advice.  It sounds like I need a new thermometer, and to learn about this newfangled "3-2-1 Method".  Depending on how that works, I'll look into heat loss.

BTW, I'm not using the thermometer for internal meat temperature, I'm using it for the ambient internal temperature of the smoker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-19 18:55:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isabella Acres </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-16 00:37:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Jason and the dragon](http://www.britishmuseum.org/research/collection_online/collection_object_details/collection_image_gallery.aspx?assetId=71393 objectId=1447632 partId=1) This is the one that got me started.  It's from a collection of Renaissance etchings that I bought a couple of years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-16 00:34:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [St Antony the Hermit](http://www.britishmuseum.org/research/collection_online/collection_object_details/collection_image_gallery.aspx?assetId=27233 objectId=764939 partId=1) by Drer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 23:33:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How are you planning on printing them.  For etchings/engravings/drawings, I'd like to find a service bureau with a high quality laser printer who could print on nice paper.  Any recommendations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Booz Allen Hamilton: 70% of the U.S. Intelligence Budget Goes to Private Contractors </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 20:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Did you know that on request, The British Museum will email you a hi-resolution scan of any artwork in their digital collection, for free, for non-commercial educational purposes? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-15 20:13:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-12 01:21:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't want to be his official food taster these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Not sure if you're on the NSA's watchlist yet? Here's one way to make sure :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-09 23:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wow. After just two tanning sessions, you too can be a slut! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-06 23:19:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-02 23:52:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Louis C.K. on being out of the food chain: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cCGVo3QTygI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL: The word "thesaurus" is derived from 16th-century New Latin, in turn from Latin thsaurus, which is the latinisation of the Greek  (thsauros), literally "treasure store". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-02 20:05:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My 9yo daughter is a huge Garfield fan, and the other day her art assignment was to draw something in the Byzantine style. Pure Brilliance! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-01 14:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-24 23:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Civil Liberties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Basic (bbq) Instructions. If it's a repost, reddit didn't warn me :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-20 05:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Don't tell me you haven't done it ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-20 05:18:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-20 05:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That looks like a good choice.  I have a similar Char-broil model that I got from Home Depot a few years ago for about the same price.  Go for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-19 18:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excellent.  Thanks for the link to the paints. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Painting a rusty firebox? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-19 16:36:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey all.  I've had a standard Char-broil offset smoker for a few years, and the firebox is getting pretty rusty on the top and sides, I assume from the heat.  Has anybody else confronted this situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-18 04:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I just added the "Add My Local Library Branch" link.  If you click on it, it then tries to determine your location. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-17 20:50:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fixed.  Thanks for the QA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-17 20:18:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet!  I'll get on that :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-17 20:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OK, done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-17 19:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good idea.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Found a couple small cans of "nope!" at my local Japanese/Korean grocery. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-17 17:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-17 13:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you share your location it will return results from your local library. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So I whipped up a little meta-search-engine for finding free ebooks, thought you'd want to give it a whirl. G'night! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-17 04:48:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Try this if you live in/near a big city </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-15 14:12:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> That feeling, after I got a hard kick to the nuts in Karate, but while wearing my cup ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-30 13:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-14 21:33:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [A little better] (http://funnyr.com/cgi-bin/funnyr.cgi?content_id=62):

Two Arabs are sitting in the window and middle seats on a plane. The Arabs ask the Jew sitting in the aisle seat to get them a glass of orange juice so they won't have to crawl over him. While he is up getting the drinks, they spit in his shoes. When they are about to land the Jewish guy puts on his shoes and realizes what has happened. He complains to the Arabs, "When will it all end? The hatred... the violence... the killing... the spitting in shoes... the peeing in orange juice..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-14 04:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try not to read this entire thread in a Scottish accent, I dare ye! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL about a strangely familiar 1814 poem called "The Defense of Fort McHenry" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-11 03:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 14:56:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excellent, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Photoshop skillz have atrophied, but my friend Chris is stuck in a Hotel in Nashville, and clearly needs some Sith Lightning coming out of his hands. Please Help. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 03:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your [job](http://imgur.com/jaYuobN), should you choose to accept it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 23:13:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Although I was only two years old when this happened, I just want to say, as an American, that I'm sorry for what my government did to your people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-28 01:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you give that in [Wales Units](http://www.sizeofwales.org.uk), please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> On Jim Cramer (Mad Money): "When people look at his record, the best thing you could actually do, is, the second he says to buy something, is to immediately short it, or bet against it." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-23 23:19:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-23 01:16:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bad.  I'll try to remember that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Topless Angry European Feminists: It doesn't get any hotter than this, folks! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-23 00:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-20 22:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to say this.  It wasn't a mistake, it was a crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-18 03:14:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Extra points for noticing the difference between the * on your keyboard and the one on your phone :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL: The dialog for Moe, the bully from Calvin   Hobbes, is always written in a childish scrawl </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-16 14:04:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-22 03:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Leaving the hospital with my daughter after she was born.  My wife and I just kind of looked at each-other wondering: "Are they really going to just let us walk out of here with this infant?  Don't they know we have no fucking idea what we're doing?"  Granted we were in our 30s, but it was still pretty scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-16 18:12:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, I was the guy who yelled out, "Is anyone here a doctor!?!".  I was with my mom and kids at the Topsfield fair, and she started feeling faint and sat down.  She had a bit of water, but I could tell she wasn't recovering.  We were actually sitting next to a kids' sing-a-long, so it was pretty noisy.  She slouched off the picnic table and I caught her and, I actually remember being a little embarrassed to start yelling, but I did.  There was a doctor and a nurse in the crowd who came to help, then the paramedics.  Turned out to be heat stroke, and she was ok, but it was scary, and it definitely felt weird to be yelling that out in a crowd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Don't Fuck With Bagels: in 2008 nearly 2,000 people wound up in the emergency room after attempting to cut a bagel </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-09 23:02:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-09 01:29:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OH COME ON!  WAKE UP SHEEPLE!  RICHARD C. HOAGLAND [BROKE THIS STORY](http://www.enterprisemission.com/spirit2.htm) YEARS AGO!  You need to spend less time on reddit and more time listening to Coast to Coast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-21 16:46:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the [company he works for](http://www.hargroveinc.com/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If you watch the Inaugural Parade today, you just might see some of these floats my uncle helped to make. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-21 16:38:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who will lock out the locksmiths? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-01 21:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So tomorrow is my birthday and I don't have a ridiculous number of facebook friends, but I'm always pleasantly surprised at how many come out of the woodwork to wish me Happy Birthday. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-01 03:53:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-24 23:23:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, Clarice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Facebook page did not live up to its promise. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-11-21 01:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You Might Be A Software Engineer If ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-10-27 02:07:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you start singing "Inchworm" to your kids, and you go all the way up to 1024. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-30 23:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Another fun event sponsored by the R.O.P.  Just like all those Mormons
who rioted over The Book of Mormon, and the Jews who burned embassies
over Egypt's broadcast of The Protocols of the Elders of Zion, oh,
wait ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Latin App </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-08 22:57:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Enjoyable discussion of Juvenal on the BBC </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-02 22:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I Accomplished Nothing Today But BBQ and Beer </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-09-02 21:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-22 16:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I'd rather talk about who the fuck brings a six year old girl to a Dark Knight movie.  I know it's tragic, but what the hell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-07-15 23:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry, but what exactly do you expect when you name your daughter after a state? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-27 16:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> AMA Request: The fucking stupid 18 year old son who racked up $15K in credit card debt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hey Bro!  Can I get a ... oh wait, nevermind. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-27 15:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-26 20:44:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough, but what I think of is the difference between code that's efficient and robust enough to still work after 35 years, 10 billion miles away, compared to 99% of the crap that we write today, that will generally be thrown out and rewritten in 5 years.  By way of analogy, think of the Roman aqueducts which still stand today, compared to bridges built in the last 100 years which are already falling down and in need of repair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-26 15:25:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Question: What kind of computers are used on the Voyager spacecraft?
 
Answer: There are three different computer types on the Voyager spacecraft and there are two of each kind. Total number of words among the six computers is about 32K. 

Computer Command System (CCS) - 18-bit word, interrupt type processors (2) with 4096 words each of plated wire, non-volatile memory. 

Flight Data System (FDS) - 16-bit word machine (2) with modular memories and 8198 words each 

Attitude and Articulation Control System (AACS) - 18-bit word machines (2) with 4096 words each. 

According to my calulations, that's a total of about 68KB, or small potatoes compared to today's microprocessors. We probably could perform all functions with one of today's boards and still have room for solid state data storage and much more fault detection software. We would still need a second unit for redundancy. Today's microprocessors are also much faster than the chips used on Voyager and a comparative system would use less electrical power. On the other hand, software might be more complicated as opposed to that used in an interrupt type system, but it would be much more capable and more flexible. 

Let's look closer at the CCS. The CCS has two main functions: to carry out instructions from the ground to operate the spacecraft, and to be alert for a problem or malfunction and respond to it. Two identical 4096- word memories contain both fixed routines (about 2800 words) and a variable section (about 1290 words) for changing science sequences. The CCS issues commands to the AACS for movement of the scan platform or spacecraft maneuvers; to the FDS for changes in instrument configurations or telemetry rates and to numerous other subsystems within the spacecraft for specific actions. Fault-protection algorithms are also stored in the CCS, occupying roughly 10 percent of the CCS memory. 

The main functions of the FDS are to collect data from, and controls the operations of, the scientific instruments; and to format engineering and science data for on-board storage and/or real-time transmission. The FDS also keeps the spacecraft "time" and provides frequency references to the instruments and other spacecraft subsystems. 

The Voyager spacecraft computers are interrupt driven computer, similar to processors used in general purpose computers with a few special instructions for increased efficiency. The programming is a form of assembly language. 

There is no clock chip, as such, in the spacecraft. The "clock" is really a counter, based on one of several electronically generated frequencies. These frequencies, based on a reference, generated by a very stable oscillator, are converted and fed to different locations in the spacecraft as synchronization signals, timers, counters, etc. The "clock" signal is part of the information telemetered to the ground and it is with ground software that we convert to day of year, time of day Greenwich Mean Time. 

Voyager was built in-house at JPL; the computers were manufactured by General Electric to JPL specifications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Voyager I: When Engineers Were Engineers who could code an Operating System for a Freakin' Spaceship in 68 Freakin' Kilobytes! 35 years later and still accepting commands. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-26 15:25:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Voyager I: When Engineers Were Engineers who could code an Operating System for a Freakin' Spaceship in 68 Freakin' Kilobytes! 35 years later and still accepting commands. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-26 14:54:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Voyager I FAQ](http://voyager.jpl.nasa.gov/faq.html)

Question: What kind of computers are used on the Voyager spacecraft?

Answer: There are three different computer types on the Voyager spacecraft and there are two of each kind. Total number of words among the six computers is about 32K. 

Computer Command System (CCS) - 18-bit word, interrupt type processors (2) with 4096 words each of plated wire, non-volatile memory. 

Flight Data System (FDS) - 16-bit word machine (2) with modular memories and 8198 words each 

Attitude and Articulation Control System (AACS) - 18-bit word machines (2) with 4096 words each. 

According to my calulations, that's a total of about 68KB, or small potatoes compared to today's microprocessors. We probably could perform all functions with one of today's boards and still have room for solid state data storage and much more fault detection software. We would still need a second unit for redundancy. Today's microprocessors are also much faster than the chips used on Voyager and a comparative system would use less electrical power. On the other hand, software might be more complicated as opposed to that used in an interrupt type system, but it would be much more capable and more flexible. 

Let's look closer at the CCS. The CCS has two main functions: to carry out instructions from the ground to operate the spacecraft, and to be alert for a problem or malfunction and respond to it. Two identical 4096- word memories contain both fixed routines (about 2800 words) and a variable section (about 1290 words) for changing science sequences. The CCS issues commands to the AACS for movement of the scan platform or spacecraft maneuvers; to the FDS for changes in instrument configurations or telemetry rates and to numerous other subsystems within the spacecraft for specific actions. Fault-protection algorithms are also stored in the CCS, occupying roughly 10 percent of the CCS memory. 

The main functions of the FDS are to collect data from, and controls the operations of, the scientific instruments; and to format engineering and science data for on-board storage and/or real-time transmission. The FDS also keeps the spacecraft "time" and provides frequency references to the instruments and other spacecraft subsystems. 

The Voyager spacecraft computers are interrupt driven computer, similar to processors used in general purpose computers with a few special instructions for increased efficiency. The programming is a form of assembly language. 

There is no clock chip, as such, in the spacecraft. The "clock" is really a counter, based on one of several electronically generated frequencies. These frequencies, based on a reference, generated by a very stable oscillator, are converted and fed to different locations in the spacecraft as synchronization signals, timers, counters, etc. The "clock" signal is part of the information telemetered to the ground and it is with ground software that we convert to day of year, time of day Greenwich Mean Time. 

Voyager was built in-house at JPL; the computers were manufactured by General Electric to JPL specifications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Getting Divorced? Choose Your Facebook Posts Carefully </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-22 14:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-19 17:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The article in question: http://well.blogs.nytimes.com/2012/05/16/coffee-drinkers-may-live-longer/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When I read an article about coffee being good for me ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-19 17:24:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-05 02:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... so where's her ring? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> James Cameron re-did the constellations in the Titanic re-make after "snarky email" from Neil deGrasse Tyson </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-07 21:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Good job on the timeline, guys, but you missed a major event! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-04-01 15:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It's not me, it's you </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-28 19:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 'This American Life' Retracts Mike Daisey's Apple Factory Story </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-17 14:47:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Asked, and answered! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-18 15:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Serious Prequel Question </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-11 22:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OK, so Anakin is hanging out with some serious players: He's training to be a Jedi, and his GF is a freakin' queen.  But nobody could scrape together a few grand to buy his mom out of slavery?  Sorry if this has come up before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Woody Harrelson's Devastated Reaction to his AMA Fiasco </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-04 15:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-02 03:42:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to say this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-01-23 01:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, if nothing is off-limits ... http://www.funnyjunk.com/funny_pictures/954506/The+interrupting+Doctor/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Witty headline?   When you post a link to mirror-finished DeLorean, you don't need a witty headline. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-01-19 19:29:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Floss usage explained </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-01-19 04:23:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-01-14 23:01:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought that was obvious: that the original meaning came not from one's victory, but from the fact that you defeated your opponent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that the word "trophy" has it's root in the Greek word "tropaios", meaning "defeat". </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-01-14 22:26:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My kids, when we're running late and I try to explain that there's no time for playing: </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-01-11 14:35:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-12-13 02:00:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who remembers the Seinfeld episode where Kramer sells the birthday card with all of the Yankees' signatures? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-12-13 01:59:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who remembers the Seinfeld episode where Kramer sells the birthday card with all of the Yankees' signatures? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AMA Request: Who here has Carl Kasell's voice on their answering machine or voicemail? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-12-04 18:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sound file or it didn't happen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Yo, Emacs, I heard you like minibuffers ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-14 20:12:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Beer is the mind-killer. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-04 20:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-03 01:17:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Snob post: I don't understand this because I don't know who/what a Kardashian is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's that new dance step loved by Pakistanis? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-27 14:45:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Punjab Square Dance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seems like The 99 is missing out on a real branding opportunity. After all, how many of the 1% have you ever seen eating there? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-19 02:19:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-08 01:20:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Something is happening here, but you don't know what it is, do you, Mr. Jones](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mjVXlPxkhMc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-09-28 01:40:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo Dawg, I heard you like reddit ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-09-10 13:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmmm. that looks ... [familiar](http://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/all5s/ummm_because_one_is_made_out_of_bacon_and_the/).  Upvote anyway! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scolding customer, teller thwart would-be robber </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-27 14:49:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Show me some ! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-26 14:45:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-26 02:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, Clarice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-25 15:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holly would if she could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-25 14:56:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for pointing out the false choice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Am I just a dirty old man, or is this cartoon character on my daughter's snack container a bit ... sultry? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-25 14:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Good morning Reddit!  I think you'll  my new nerdy T-shirt design. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-22 14:46:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Today I made a minor edit to Wikipedia that didn't get immediately undone.  AMA! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-22 02:12:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of the [Latin Conjugation tables](http://en.wikipedia.org/w/index.php?title=Latin_conjugation action=historysubmit diff=445979754 oldid=439022413) was formatted inconsistently, so I fixed it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Back-To-School warning for the kids:  Stay in school or you might end up working at K-Mart! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-20 13:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Iraq foots the bill for its own destruction </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-13 18:07:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-13 02:37:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> meh.  Nothing about China shocks me any more. [link](http://www.csmonitor.com/2006/0803/p16s01-lire.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Now I'm not saying anybody should go undercover and sabotage Mitt Romney's campaign, but ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-08-12 00:56:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-07-30 02:04:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm gonna need more upvotes here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This could not be more surreal: Ticketmaster parent company creates astroturf coalition to go after ticket resellers, resellers retaliate by forming astroturf organization of their own. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-07-24 03:26:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-07-18 01:56:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Everything's Amazing and Nobody's Happy](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8r1CZTLk-Gk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fuck You Disney Fast-Play </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-07-16 16:03:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, I don't want to watch your "selection of bonus features", i.e. COMMERCIALS.  I just want to start the freakin' movie as soon as possible so my kids can veg in front of the TV and leave me alone.

What kind of demonic marketing bot thought this was a good idea in the first place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-07-16 13:53:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey!  This thread is the opposite of [mine from a couple of months ago!](http://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/hbtc9/how_many_of_you_cant_help_making_a_lame_joke_to_a/)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-07-14 06:25:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's hooked! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I wear a fancy Velcro hat ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-07-14 02:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not too many people can pull that off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-07-04 01:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some [history here](http://www.gutenberg.org/wiki/Gutenberg:The_History_and_Philosophy_of_Project_Gutenberg_by_Michael_Hart) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 40 Years ago Michael Hart hand-typed the Declaration of Independence and released it on his university network.  Happy Birthday Project Gutenberg! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-07-04 01:32:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-06-28 02:48:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's an easy one: http://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/iaa5v/onion_news_editor_punched_kicked_as_mob_of_3040/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-06-23 03:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How about "A repost of redditors"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hey Reddit/IMGUR: why not put upvote/downvote links right on IMGUR that I could click and would take me back to Reddit and click the Reddit upvote/downvote link? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-06-17 12:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could instantly double my time-wasting efficiency! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-06-08 01:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe he'd be prouder if he weren't Irish ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gay Softball Team Tells Bisexual Men: "Sorry guys, we have enough Pitchers, we need more Catchers!" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-06-03 01:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Goodbye Liane, we'll miss you!  One thing though: Could you take Will Shortz with you when you go? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-05-29 14:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-05-21 16:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought we were talking about pool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I guess it's hard to find Fava Beans in Russia. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-05-19 15:29:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How many of you can't help making a lame joke to a professional, even though you know they must've heard it 1,000 times before?  For example ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-05-15 14:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The other day I was having an echocardiogram, which is basically an ultrasound of my heart.  I was looking at it and it looked like a pregnancy ultrasound:

Me: "I don't want to know whether it's a boy or a girl."

Nurse: _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Daddy, where do babies come from?" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-05-06 20:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well son, there used to be this awesome website called reddit, but sometimes it would go down, and I'd have to spend time with your mother ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NOTE TO SELF: When people change their profile pic to a picture of their mother in honor of Mothers' Day, the correct response is NOT: "I'd hit that!" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-05-06 03:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NYC Photobomb [fixed] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-04-19 23:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "That's what it feels like to own The Whole Internet for one moment." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-04-18 21:41:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-04-15 02:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't suppose anybody remembers the 1992 Republican Convention whose theme song was "The Best of Times is Now", from the gay musical La Cage Aux Folles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-04-14 03:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This woman goes into a funeral home to make arrangements 
for her husband's funeral.  She tells the director that 
she wants her husband to be buried in a dark blue suit.

He asks, "Wouldn't it just be easier to bury him in the
black suit that he's wearing?"

But she insists that it must be a blue suit and gives
him a blank check to buy one.

When she comes back for the wake, she sees her husband
in the coffin and he is wearing a beautiful blue suit.
She tells the director how much she loves the suit and
asks how much it cost. He says, "Actually, it didn't
cost anything.  The funniest thing happened.  As soon
as you left, another corpse was brought in, this one
wearing a blue suit.  I noticed that they were about
the same size, and asked the other widow if she would
mind if her husband were buried in a black suit.  She
said that was fine with her. So... I switched the heads" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-04-13 03:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [cite](http://books.google.com/books?id=J_P8xVdZzKsC printsec=frontcover dq=erasmus+adages hl=en ei=LOOkTcuBE--F0QGl2Z30CA sa=X oi=book_result ct=result resnum=1 ved=0CCgQ6AEwAA#v=onepage q=fart f=false) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-04-13 03:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Saw "impact" used as a verb, moved on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-04-13 01:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Suus cuique crepitus bene olet.*

Everyone thinks his own fart smells sweet

-- From the Adages of Erasmus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-04-13 01:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Suus cuique crepitus bene olet.*

Everyone thinks his own fart smells sweet

-- From the Adages of Erasmus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ebony and ivory live together in perfect harmony
Side by side on my piano keyboard, oh lord, GOOGLEIMAGESWTF?!? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-04-12 02:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So we're Bombing Libya. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-19 23:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to our latest Undeclared War: http://www.cnn.com/2011/WORLD/africa/03/19/libya.civil.war/index.html?hpt=T1 iref=BN1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-19 20:56:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is one well-hung cock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-19 01:13:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Q: How many Confucians does it take to screw in a lightbulb?
A: Many hands make light work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-18 23:26:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I applaud Microsoft for attacking the problem that they helped to create! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-18 02:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Lies I've told my 3 year old recently](http://www.mexicanpictures.com/headingeast/2008/03/lies-ive-told-my-3-year-old-re.html)

March 18, 2008

Trees talk to each other at night.

All fish are named either Lorna or Jack.

Before your eyeballs fall out from watching too much TV, they get very loose.

Tiny bears live in drain pipes.

If you are very very quiet you can hear the clouds rub against the sky.

The moon and the sun had a fight a long time ago.

Everyone knows at least one secret language.

When nobody is looking, I can fly.

We are all held together by invisible threads.

Books get lonely too.

Sadness can be eaten.

I will always be there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-18 00:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A knight of the Table Round should be invincible,
Succeed where the less fantastic man would fail!
-- C'est moi, Camelot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-14 01:26:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Why did he eat tacks?  He wasn't being careful?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A is for Amy who fell down the stairs, B is for Basil assaulted by bears. ... Am I the only one whose 3yo daughter picks this for bedtime? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-14 00:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Heyters gonna Heyt </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-09 03:49:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 52 Hertz Whale: Forever Alone :( </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-07 22:31:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-07 14:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I feel a great disturbance in the Force, as if millions of voices suddenly cried out in terror, and were suddenly silenced." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-04 02:49:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're surprised that our government would do this, may I suggest adding Necessary Illusions, Manufacturing Consent, and A People's History of the United States to your reading list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dear Image Uploaders: I have a slow computer and your stupid oversized images break it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-01 03:55:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not proud.  I browse the web on a (Dell Optiplex 770L)[http://support.dell.com/support/edocs/systems/op170l/en/ug/specs.htm].  You may laugh, but it was free and it runs Ubuntu just fine, thank you very much.  But every so often I click on a stupid oversized cell-phone picture like (this one)[http://imgur.com/FVQ5x] (only chosen because it's the latest culprit)  and it FREEZES MY COMPUTER FOR ABOUT 3 MINUTES WTF!?!  The picture wasn't even that funny and there's NO REASON ON EARTH THAT IT NEEDED TO BE 1,936px  2,592px.  No reason at all.  The resolution is crappy and there's just not that much information there anyway.  imgur provides low-resolution links, let's start using them, people!

Thank you for your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-03-01 03:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once I was waiting on the subway platform with a group of friends, and this woman was singing acapella.  She was *terrible*.  I walked over to her and told her I'd give her a dollar if she'd stop singing until we got onto the train.  She looked confused and explained that she'd been classically trained.  I said, "Well, I don't know much about music, but there's something very wrong here."  She accepted the dollar and stopped singing.  My wife was mortified, and one friend said, "You're either my hero or the biggest asshole I've ever met."

I report, you decide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-02-23 02:50:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> k.  I'm gonna jump in here.  Years ago I was talking with a gay friend over beers, and I asked: "What is **with** you guys?  Why are [your clubs](http://www.paradisecambridge.com/) always getting shut down over wild orgies?"  He explained, "In heterosexual relationships there's usually one party who wants to do it **all the time** and another who sort of keeps things sane.  Well, you get a bunch of guys together, and you pretty much don't have that sanity element.  Everybody wants to do it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Three Rings for the Elven-kings under the sky, </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-02-22 03:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-02-16 03:54:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If so, then wouldn't Sarah Connor have already blown it up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "What is SkyNet?" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-02-16 03:30:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just finished watching Watson run the table on the meat-puppets.  Anybody else feeling obsolete? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-02-04 19:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say save yourself $100 and get the Pandigital Novel.  It's still no iPad, but it's quite [hackable](http://www.slatedroid.com/wiki/index.php/Introduction_to_the_Pandigital_Novel):  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-02-03 03:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Non hic adsum ut amIcos faciam! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-01-30 19:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Am I the only one disappointed that this wasn't about making Cylons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The perfect Christmas gift for that bratty child on your "naughty" list. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-12-22 15:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> He Aint Marching Anymore: Happy 70th Birthday, Phil Ochs! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-12-17 15:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This story was just used as a quiz question on NPR's Wait Wait ... Don't Tell Me :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-12-11 16:56:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Calvin's Dad: the Original TrollDad </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-12-11 02:55:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now that I'm a father, I consider Calvin's Dad to by my personal role-model.  Thanks to the [Calvin   Hobbes Search Engine](http://reemst.com/calvin_and_hobbes/stripsearch) I managed to find these links; anybody got any more?

A lesson in polar coordinates:
http://www.gocomics.com/calvinandhobbes/1986/11/26

And structures:
http://www.gocomics.com/calvinandhobbes/1990/06/05

Anatomy:
http://www.gocomics.com/calvinandhobbes/1993/10/30 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that "OK" is a person sideways :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-11-12 14:01:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seeking fellow Halloween Grinches:  When everybody else is dressing up, DAE ever feel like Kyle at Christmas? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-10-31 00:09:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-10-20 03:37:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> McDonald's could use a guy like Andrew! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In Honor of National Fossil Day! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-10-13 14:01:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alec Baldwin: Don't Pledge to NPR! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-10-07 19:51:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-10-07 03:05:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to put your $400 in perspective:  The sysadmin and I put an incorrectly configured redirect click server into the pool, so it basically silently failed to redirect clicks to our paying advertisers, and not only that, it was logging the failures as 200s, i.e., successful pages served, so none of our Nagios alerts were fired.  Nobody noticed it until the next morning, so 1/3 of our click logs were lost.  The business is ALL clicks, and if they're not served, we're not paid.  Lost revenue was about $25k.  Our overlords were *not* happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> He liked to wear skirts ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-10-02 17:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is that sarong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-10-02 02:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or more practical, "Where are my keys?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sunday Morning. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-09-26 13:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If you're dyslexic, this URL is dirty. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-09-24 18:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-09-24 03:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This above all, to thine own self be true

And it must follow, as the night the day

Thou canst not then be false to any man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Well then, I guess it's a good thing we don't need roads ... you know, where we're going. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-09-16 02:19:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Planning on refusing a bag-inspection </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-09-14 00:54:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm planning to decline a role in our local [Security Theater Production](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Security_theater) at the South Station T-stop in Boston.  The cops stand by the turnstile with a little counter and ask every nth person to have their bags inspected.  If selected I will invoke my 4th Amendment right against unreasonable search and seizure, as politely as possible, of course.  What should I expect?  I imagine that I won't be able to pass, but what else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-09-12 03:26:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow.  Hadn't listened to this in about 20 years.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-09-11 21:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How sad is it that somebody from China has to show us how to stand up for ourselves?  I don't mind a few trailers, but the last few times I've gone to the moves, I've been subjected to numerous commercials.  It's ridiculous to buy an expensive ticket and then be subjected to advertising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-08-29 03:13:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Another First World Problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Forget Tiger Woods.  Meet Gaius Appuleius Diocles, the first Billion-dollar athlete. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-08-14 15:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-08-13 04:33:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... best served with a side of crow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-08-10 02:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, and for you home-brewers out there: never leave your hops out where the dog can get them.  Very bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-08-10 02:18:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really sorry about your dog, but ... I couldn't help thinking of one of those [Things You'll Never Hear A Redneck say](http://www.goofball.com/jokes/top10/talk_Top_36_Things_Youll_Never_Hear_A_Redneck_Say): "You can't feed that to the dog." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-08-09 18:38:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess I have it down pretty well.  It only takes me about an hour to fry up the bacon, make the weave, and fill it.  But the smoking does take a few hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dear Reddit: I had an epic Double Bacon-Explosion BBQ yesterday!  Sorry I forgot to invite you. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-08-09 15:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-08-01 16:08:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> vulgus vult decipi, ergo decipiatur -- The people want to be deceived, therefore let them be deceived. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-31 03:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this guy is telling his dad about his first time paratrooper training:

"Well, I was scared and said I didn't want to jump."

"And ... ?"

"The jumpmaster said, 'well, son, I'm gay and there's only one way you're getting out of this.'"

"So, did you jump?"

"A little, at first." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-30 23:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two things:
1. Eating fat doesn't make you fat, eating carbs does: http://www.nytimes.com/2002/07/07/magazine/what-if-it-s-all-been-a-big-fat-lie.html
2. Exercise doesn't help you lose weight.  It doesn't burn enough calories, and generally makes you hungrier.  This is not to say that exercise isn't good for you, it's just that eating less is the best way to lose weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-24 03:32:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So ... not one photoshop job on the group photo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-23 23:18:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's even a mighty poem about these poor lads:

http://schoonerfare.com/schoonerfare/8886.html

POWDER MONKEY
Words and Music by Steve Romanoff
Copyright 1985

In days of old, so the story's told,
Of boys who went to sea,
All of seven, eight and nine years old they say,
To serve upon the warring ships, their captains and their kings,
To serve the purpose they still serve today,
To serve the purpose they still serve today.
To carry up the powder from the magazine below,
From a hold too dark and crowded for a man,
The called them Powder Monkies, every schoolchild ought to know,
The price we pay to keep a promised land,
The price we pay to keep a promised land.

Send for the Powder Monkey,
Send him down into the well,
Send for the Powder Monkey,
He'll fetch us a pail o' hell
To keep out cannon burnin'
He'll fall behind the gun,
We'll just send for a Powder Monkey,
'Cause there's more where he came from.

They come from the city sidewalks and
They come from the family farm,
To trust their fragile futures to the wind,
They come from the Land of Plenty,
Through the evergreens and corn,
With more to lose than all the angry men,
With more to lose than all the angry men.
Was it the hunger of the family,
Was it the anger of the street,
That drove a lonely child to Satan's door,
Where death was all but certain and
Damnation near complete,
Save all for the holy innocent ashore,
Save all the holy innocent ashore.

From high above the gun deck
Ring the orders of the realm,
To roll out a battle cadence on the drum,
As forward into darkness
Sail the cowards at the helm,
And they shoot the stars to see how far they've come,
Look at their sons to see how far they've come.
In days of old, so the story's told
Of boys who went to sea,
All of seven, eight and nine years old they say,
To serve upon the warring ships, their captains and their kings,
To serve the purpose they still serve today,
To serve the purpose they still serve today.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIL that there were boys as young as 8 called "Powder Monkeys" serving on the U.S.S. Constitution (and other battleships of The Age of Sail).  Their job was to run between cannon recoiling at speeds of 30-40mph and fetch bags of powder from below-decks to recharge them. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-23 23:16:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-21 22:41:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It just occurred to me: she could've save a lot of trouble if she'd checked the state of his equipment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-20 03:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're asking "did I mean 'compelling' instead of 'compulsive', then no, I meant 'compulsive'", as in this definition: http://www.thefreedictionary.com/compulsive "Caused or conditioned by compulsion or obsession."  This is clearly the work of an inspired and gifted madman.  But the work is compelling, too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So last weekend I was at an art fair (ArtBeat in Davis Sq.) and saw this madman with the most astonishingly compulsive handmade Neo-Victorian Steam-Powered kinetic sculptures ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-20 03:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately I can't find any videos, or even a website, I'd just assumed that he'd have one that I could find later.  I think maybe he's too busy reinventing the past to upload stuff to youtube.  But I did find these pictures which of course do no justice to the experience of seeing them in action:

http://s579.photobucket.com/albums/ss237/Steamachine/?action=view current=DSCF2686-2.jpg
http://s579.photobucket.com/albums/ss237/Steamachine/?action=view current=DSCF2730.jpg
http://s579.photobucket.com/albums/ss237/Steamachine/?action=view current=DSCF0623.jpg newest=1

Oh, and it was a 90 degree day and I got to watch him tending his propane-powered steam generator! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-17 15:02:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess I just wish his story was less believable.  I wish my government didn't have a history of abducting people and holding them in secret prisons.  I wish it didn't have a history of fabricating evidence as a pretext for an illegal war.  Maybe he's telling the truth, maybe not; I just wish I could say to myself, "No, my government would never do something like that." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-17 03:41:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, you've clearly given up here.  You've got some preconceptions that you won't let go of, even in the face of viable alternatives.

After you've spent as much time researching homeschooling as I have researching public education, maybe we can talk.

Later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-16 21:29:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you have no research, just an anecdote.  I'd be more reassured if there weren't so many examples of people who didn't develop "thicker skin with everyone out there who tries to build themselves up by tearing you down", but ended up excluded from cliques, miserable, harassed, and sometimes bullied to the point of committing suicide: http://www.cbs3springfield.com/news/local/97624929.html

If public school is really supposed to teach people how to deal with that bullshit, it's not doing a great job.  In real life, you can in fact "bug out" if you decide you're not having a good time, you're not forced to hang out with jerks.

You should read some Gatto: http://www.informationliberation.com/?id=11375 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-16 15:42:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd love for you to cite the research that demonstrates that "forced socialization" is "crucial in developing fully as an individual", or that the lack of it has damaged the thousands of kids who have been home-schooled.  Home-schooled kids have plenty of options for socialization that are much more similar to the "real world" than the highly controlled, age-separated prison-like structure of public school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-16 02:24:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should seriously consider home-schooling.  It sounds like your wife has the time/inclination, and he'll just be held back by public school.  As many posters have suggested, you shouldn't try to force-feed him a curriculum, but there's no reason not to keep presenting him with opportunities to grow and learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-14 00:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guess I was expecting something more Looney Tunes-ish, you know, with the barrel looking like a banana peel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-11 01:56:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't believe I'm bothering to post to this thread, but there is a scene in [The Last Emperor](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Last_Emperor) when the former emperor is in the re-education camp, and is spoken to about this very subject, i.e. when peeing in the middle of the night, he needs to make sure to hit the side of the bowl so as not to wake his cell-mates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-01 20:28:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this woman's husband dies.  She says to the undertaker, "All my life my husband has worn nothing but black suits.  Just once I'd like to see him in blue suit, but I don't have one.  Can you help me out?"  The undertaker says, "Sure."

A few days later she shows up at the viewing, and there's her husband laid out in a handsome blue suit.  She says to the undertaker, "Thank you so much!"  The undertaker says, "No problem.  As it happens, on the same day there was a woman who wanted her husband dressed in a black suit, but all she had was blue suits."  The woman said, "Oh, so you ... ", the undertaker says, "Yeah, I just switched the heads!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> " 'The black man has never had the right either to keep or bear arms,' and that, until he does, 'the work of the Abolitionists was not finished.' " </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-07-01 20:09:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> More reddit juxtaposition fun (re: vaccinations). </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-06-27 23:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-06-27 23:00:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Removal may be surgical, mechanical, chemical, autolytic (self-digestion), and by maggot therapy.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Debridement).  Yum.  Oh, and an awesome picture to boot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-06-27 19:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, [Google]( http://www.google.com/search?hl=en q=72! aq=f aqi=h1g10 aql= oq= gs_rfai=)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Possibly more Hidden Valley Ranch Dressing than could fit into the known universe. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-06-27 19:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why do so many job descriptions require "the ability to multi-task" when there's so much research showing that humans just aren't good at it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-06-26 15:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> At 1,000 yards the Coriolis deflection is small but not necessarily trivial. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-06-25 16:46:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-06-10 00:40:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> motherfuckers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Like the attacks by Al Qaeda, the disaster in the Gulf was preceded by ample warnings  yet the administration had ignored them." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-06-10 00:40:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thanks, Internet, for ruining another innocent children's toy for me.  I present: The Elephantine Centipede Project! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-05-29 16:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-05-22 19:21:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While you're at it, compare the asterisks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-05-22 02:25:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then he said, "No, you don't understand, 'Chunks' is my dog!" ... oh wait a minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Am I the only person on reddit who thinks reddit gradually diminishes a person's personality?  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-05-21 04:29:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-05-19 03:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perhaps a caption contest is in order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-05-19 03:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I guess it's her business and none of ours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Me: "Looks like there's quite a story behind this."  My daughter: "No dad, there's really not" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-05-19 03:18:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-05-12 02:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "When I was a boy of 14, my father was so ignorant I could hardly stand to have the old man around. But when I got to be 21, I was astonished at how much the old man had learned in seven years."

-- Mark Twain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-05-11 03:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Them!](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0047573/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "More rogues than honest men find shelter under habeas corpus" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-02-13 15:31:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  -- Abraham Lincoln

Happy Presidents' Day Weekend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-02-11 01:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [How to Show off a Scar](http://basicinstructions.net/basic-instructions/2007/12/5/how-to-show-off-a-scar.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ooooh baby, now that we're in the mood, give me a second to put on my "English frock coat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-02-06 19:07:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Braille test for taxi drivers.  Really. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-02-06 17:19:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-02-05 03:28:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What has been seen cannot be unseen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to Survive a 35,000-Foot Fall - Plane Crash Survival Guide - Popular Mechanics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-02-02 15:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-31 23:47:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Obama Tells Nation He's going out for cigarettes](http://www.theonion.com/content/news/obama_tells_nation_hes_going_out) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You know, I really enjoy Rock Paper Scissors, but I just can't handle all that complicated strategery. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-30 22:44:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Let me guess ... the one ending in "o'clock"? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-30 20:07:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> baby </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-30 19:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it possible to loop or roll a 747 jet?  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-29 15:53:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why don't chain store websites use ip2location in their "find a store" feature?  Why do I have to enter my zip code? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-24 17:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, I know that it's not always accurate, but geez, in most cases it's a good first-approximation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-21 02:09:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My brain (too much time on reddit). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-20 18:32:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Jungledisk](http://jungledisk.com/).  It creates encrypted remote backups on Amazon S3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hitler Finds Out ... well, you know. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-20 18:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> " ... the greatest purveyor of violence in the world today -- my own government." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-18 02:05:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-16 22:22:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait ... what!?! I thought Jon Stewart **destroyed** him!  Reddit, you lied to me again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So you know the villain from Wild Wild West?  My wife brought home his girlfriend for my daughter.  Too creepy.  Of course she loves it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-12 02:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-09 14:23:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Next you're going to tell me that a 10yo girl can't hack into a Unix box and restore power to an entire complex by herself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-08 18:56:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kind of reminds me of the 80yo guy who goes to confession.  He says, "Father, I just slept with this beautiful girl."
"OK.  Let's start at the beginning.  How long since your last confession?"
"I've never been to confession.  I'm not even Catholic."
"Then why are you telling me this?"
"Father, I'm 80 years old.  I'm telling EVERYBODY."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-07 18:45:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just watch out for the goat, see? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-07 02:16:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Friendship: You're doing it wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looks like your design blog has run out of ideas. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-06 19:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-06 02:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's a free idea, in case you want to spend more time thinking you're accomplishing something:

HasSeanHannityBeenWaterBoardedForCharityYet.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-06 02:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh look!  It's [available](https://secure.dotster.com/DDS/?siteid=4798 domain=HasSeanHannityBeenWaterBoardedForCharityYet.com):  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ummm ... because one is made out of bacon, and the other is a puppy? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-05 02:24:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-03 02:28:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One night I was out with some friends, and we were waiting on the subway platform, and there was this "performer" singing.  She was terrible.  I mean really bad.  After a few minutes I walked over and offered her $2 if she would *stop* singing until the train came.  She agreed.  My friends were divided into "What an asshole", and "he's my hero" camps.  To this day, I really don't see the problem, but my wife is still embarrassed about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2010-01-02 15:03:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Manufacturing Consent is a close 2nd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2009-12-30 18:32:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Why choose just one?](http://xkcd.com/550/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Maybe I just have a dirty mind, but I'm sure glad this isn't what I thought it was. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2009-10-22 01:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's wrong with America, Exhibit #312225 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2009-05-19 01:10:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2009-05-12 04:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I second that.  After that, there are some good Wheelock's centered online drill tools:

http://people.hofstra.edu/Ilaria_Marchesi/text/list_exercises_101.htm
(sorry for the headache-inducing color scheme, but it really is the best online drill app).

And this one:
http://web.uvic.ca/hrd/latin/index.htm

And there's a great Latin study group: http://www.quasillum.com/latin/latin-activities.php

You'll also want to get Groton   May's _38 Latin Stories_ which I keep in the bathroom.

I've been self-studying Wheelocks for about a year and a half, and though it's slow going, it's rewarding.

Festina Lente, et Vale!
Joel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2009-04-29 18:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fact that reddit is filling up with all these stupid AskReddit posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Goodbye Bosom Buddy! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2009-04-26 04:28:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So THIRSTY [pic] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2009-02-28 23:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Audrey II </TITLE>
<DATE> 2009-02-25 19:20:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hmm.  Interesting book, but there's something ... familiar ... about that cover. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2009-01-22 22:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mr. Roarke Has Caught "De Plane!" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2009-01-14 22:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I come from a town called Obama. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2008-11-05 15:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why Can't Us? - Best rally cry Ever </TITLE>
<DATE> 2008-10-23 17:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Will eating tapeworms help you lose weight? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2008-09-26 16:58:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reading makes you Liberal </TITLE>
<DATE> 2008-09-14 19:21:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How Corporations Control Public Education </TITLE>
<DATE> 2008-09-12 15:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2008-09-05 18:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A couple of years ago I had the idea for a joke site where users could submit jokes and vote other users' jokes up or down.   Hmmm ... sounds familiar.  Anyways, I didn't do a good job of promoting it, but here it is: a href="http://funnyr.com/"funnyr.com/a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Wonderful Thing About Triggers ... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2008-08-13 17:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WTF the Pooh! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2008-08-13 17:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "When will it all end? The hatred... the violence..." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2008-06-22 20:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>