<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1805</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So what if Kanye did it, Kanye is a bell as well but doesn't claim to be a comedian.

Paul Kaye has done it, Sacha Baron Cohen has done it plus more I can't think of off the top of my head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really isn't, it's just been done before by far superior comedians rather than an attention seeking wanker clinging to his dying fame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ran out with city players on a warm up, jumped in photos with the England team jetting off, stormed the stage at Glastonbury when Kanye was playing and I'm sure there are others that I'm forgetting. All those he was chastised for as it was twattish, he's done the same here but he's been lucky that's why I said he lucked out that everyone is saying it's funny. If it wasn't blatter everyone would just call him a bell per usual like he is. He's also the "star" of one of the worst shows ever produced called The Lee Nelson Show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:22:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because he lucked out, he has done several things like this over the last couple of years and its twattish, it's just that us football fans have been desperate for something, anything which is why this is seen as funny. He is at the very heart of it an unfunny attention seeking bell and one good thing doesn't stop the rest of them being shit. Broken clock etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:57:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too right, he's an attention seeking prick who has lucked out with this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:45:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He been trying this for ages, sneaking into the photo with the England team jetting off for Brazil, getting on stage with Kanye at Glastonbury. He's a prick, he's ladbible in comedy form. Genuinely hope he gets locked away in a Fifa gulag hidden under the Swiss mountains forever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:41:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2 good things have come from this then, great photo of blatter and hopefully never have to see him do "comedy" ever again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> World first Manchester bionic eye implant trial to treat wasting disease is hailed a 'total success' by surgeons </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:03:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She was my ex's tutor for orthoptics and said she was really nice. Her daughter Rebecca always suffered with anorexia and she passed away a couple of months ago. Gail then found out that she had a brain tumour and sadly passed. Horrible really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 00:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meant same if not more as Stones but Shaw did play in the game against Costa Rica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:54:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love how much you hate United, it's top seeing a "Southampton" fan go on

Also Rio had played in champs league and World Cup and shaw had the same if not a bit more experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obligatory Ronan fucking up Ravenous from Annihilation
http://imgur.com/dRs25Hv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:26:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "You will make a big loss"

IF we do actually sell him and according to L'Equipe we aren't going to sell for less than 75 million euros which PSG don't want to pay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:50:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How unlucky for Crolla, thought he set the tempo and he was looking good even without the deductions. Not great. I am pretty gutted for Crolla though after coming back like he has  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quigg started cold in the first but holy shit what a 2nd round. Really happy for the lad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 07:29:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We subbed in youngsters as well, I'm not saying you were shit or flaming I was explaining why United didn't look great as well. Surprisingly not playing for 2 months can affect how a game is played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 07:25:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> K. Also it's you're. You're obviously just a troll, can't believe I've wasted part of my life with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 07:20:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The dirty American team who have played more games and are in better shape or a new team having to learn a new formation/philosophy. Easy isn't it making excuses. And Depay and Darmian and Schweinsteiger add a couple of youngsters like McNair and Pereira who are just breaking into the first team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 07:13:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only seeing an arsehole here mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 07:09:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok...it's still the very first game these players have played in 2 months with new players to integrate and the whole 11 swapped at half time, it's not going to be cohesive. Dunno what Chivas must be like first game of pre season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 07:05:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the very first game of pre season and we swapped our whole 11 at half time, not exactly going to be going full whack  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:57:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No he could be sold for 10p it's just that that's what Valencia will ask for as they don't have to sell and will want as much as they can possibly get for him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The legend himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:25:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah sachin nakrani, a man more famous for...other things than football reporting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 14:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh of course not but Fabian will more than likely still say it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 14:13:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If this actually does happen expect stuff like "Christian was my mate, I thought he was staying, there was a lot of broken promises" etc

The usual shite really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 13:43:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's his release clause </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 13:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeh we definitely should have spent 32.5 million on someone who will sit on the bench, definitely. Also for people who will comeback with Di Maria he was bought to be a starter not sit on the bench it's just not working out at the minute where as benteke wouldn't displace Rooney </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because he was only on loan and still a United player, save that for when he gets a permanent move not when United still own him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 00:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:29:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:07:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But we literally have nobody like schweinsteiger, we lost vidic, Ferdinand, evra, scholes, giggs (on the pitch) so quickly that we don't really have any leaders, we have Rooney who can drive us on but he isn't a leader in the mould of a Keane, Vidic or schweinsteiger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:37:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> England. No, they are inconsistent, seemingly don't actually care about the football being played or the fans one iota, easily bullied and just seem like bell ends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We aren't going to sign him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:56:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only post on mobile, United  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:35:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now they just have to sign him off us, Real and Arsenal according to the Chilean media </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:28:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> AD the Dutch paper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm assuming she told you to keep your foot raised and keep pressure on it and get out of her house and go to a hospital  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/3Ad0rD4

Should hopefully see the discolouration now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:12:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeh he has the white strapping but I wasn't talking about that, note the brown bandage underneath that further down the arm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 13:31:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look at the base of his thumb and you see bad bruising, add the bandage down the arm and would say he has an injury so pointless taking him to America when he wont play so let him stay at home and work on fitness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cole vs Antonio Valencia though wasn't for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:31:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Individual awards like team of the year are a load of shite, David Luiz got in world team of the year. He is brilliant though and will be remembered as one the greatest England has ever produced  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was good old dithering Dave thinking he wasn't strong enough for the league in the end

Can you also show me where he said it was a done deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ronaldo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:28:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trust me schweinsteiger is absolutely amazing and I genuinely still can't believe it but think it will be bigger than him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We will go for one massive thing which if it comes off would be huge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you mean wasn't going to be on the books this year? As in if we hadn't got him we wouldn't have spent the money, correct but we did so us now not spending the money is us saving it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:56:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahahahahaha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahahahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:48:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stopping us wasting money as you put it is still saving money as it is expenditure we aren't now using, before falcao came we lost vida, Ferdinand and evra who probably earned that amount so his wage was just money we had spent anyway so all in all yeh we are saving money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:26:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work at Manchester royal hospital and we generally use purple and clear bags for bloods, but the guy could literally have just grabbed a bag and used it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeh because he's saved us another 250 grand a week wages you weird bell, so he was shit it happens but with him, RVP and Nani gone that about 600 grand a week saved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:31:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Add falcaos wages to that as well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 20:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The article is a load of shit, apparently he told all this to a Milan fan who met him at Wimbledon who remembered everything fergie said perfectly and then told tuttosport </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 15:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We would not take a 20 million hit after one season, not a chance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:16:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've read a lot of shit in my life, but this right here is the fucking biggest steaming pile I've ever had the displeasure of letting my eyes witness. Day can only get better I suppose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:11:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a midfield 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:12:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We genuinely couldn't give a fuck about losing him on a free, keeping him this year would be worth more than what you are offering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:02:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Critters? Sounds similar can't remember the clown but not seen it for a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair play to him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:43:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for 20 RVP and for giving Fergie the perfect send off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 00:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the fuck is CMV? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No they aren't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 09:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeh we will definitely sell for a big loss after one season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He can still be a professional about it instead of act like a cunt, imagine if he was a member of your staff or someone on your team. I'm a united fan so couldn't give a fuck but he's still acting like a prick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus what a little wankstain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After he has picked a pug and gets asked why

"It's a bulldog innit?"

Kingsman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:32:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I watch other leagues and couldn't give a fuck who wins, it gives me true enjoyment as I'm a neutral who gets to watch great games but couldn't care less about specific teams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:30:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No because it's weird

Haha at bandwagoners downvoting me, I'm sure you support all the better teams in the different leagues because you feel a real "connection" with the teams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 01:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was only 20 then in all fairness so maybe couldn't adjust that well but since then he's been all over with the national team so he might be ok now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trust me mate he's painful at times because you know he can be an absolutely brilliant fucker but instead he just causes you physical pain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He has but he will never kick on, he will have a game where he looks like a world beater and you think fuck me what a player we have and then he will be absolutely abject for the next 6 games and you'll want him benched and then he will have a great game and then be fucking abject for 6 games etc etc time is a flat circle yadda yada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:57:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are right, he is too inconsistent. It's not so much bad work ethics I genuinely just think he has a bit of a mental block when it comes to taking the next step, he always seemingly sabotages himself by doing something stupid/infuriating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:53:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We've no idea how well he will do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yyyeeessss finally!!!!! Can't believe he is finally leaving and getting off our wage bill.

He was great in 2010-11 and one of the best in the league but fuck me he is probably the most frustrating cunt I've ever had to watch and I've had to watch a lot of them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:36:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Telegraph isn't paywall unless for people outside the UK it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-21 14:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good to see an actual professor state that even though so much was wrong he still enjoyed the film. If only the professors on reddit were able to do the same about other films... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 16:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was ok at the World Cup but everyone else playing for England were shite. It's not like he performed near the level Ferdinand was playing at either. Ferdinand was at the heart of the defence of a Leeds team that got to the semis in the champions league, it was of course a lot of money but he was worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 16:08:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And when he cost that much he had performed at a World Cup and in the champions league </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-20 11:39:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeh that one player...loads that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Danny Ings reminds me of a dwarf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 11:46:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thought Nasri was off as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 04:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 sick 7 me mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 04:10:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you joking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 03:52:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like falcao but just look at the Spurs game, he missed about 3 that should have been goals just in that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:32:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:15:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happily fuck off mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 23:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nerves maybe? Apprehension, just because he's the best doesn't mean he wouldn't feel them. Going out in front of 90 thousand and being expected to perform could do that to you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 23:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are the equivalent of The Sun on radio, bullshit and banter merchants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 22:58:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best thing you can do is try and catch Copa America games to see what he's like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 22:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bebe scored a couple of worldies as well and would look good in a YouTube video. Not saying Firminho is Bebe because he is of course a good player but can't go off YouTube videos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yet Evra is hated more than the average United player </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:19:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you hate him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeh completely understand and I can't be arsed with it all either, would love to just skip to the start of the season. I'm confident we will have a good summer though, everyone is on holiday, give it another week/two and reckon we will see it all start clicking into place  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:26:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just quite confident that we will get him, can't really explain why I am but I think because a lot of players are on holiday that's why nothing is happening and being said that seems like it's on the cusp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:23:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My Man!!! Didn't even know, definitely getting it now as a birthday treat to myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The rumours did come from seemingly nowhere but Canal+ or whoever there sport channel that tweeted it seemed certain we were in for him, have a feeling LVG would like him and sees him as an ideal Carrick replacement as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably schneiderlin I reckon is the most likeliest at the minute. Dunno who we are targeting for RB now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:53:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fowler, McManaman, Beglin etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dan Abnett and Andy Lannings Nova run especially now with the movies starting to show a bit more of the cosmic side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 23:49:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, it's a damn shame. My grandad said he was confident of us scoring whenever Law had a chance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 23:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've posted before about meeting The King on here and I'll just say it all again he was amazing, kept me talking about football, got pictures with him and just an all round great bloke and a pleasure to talk too and spend some time with. 

My grandad always goes on about him, Best, Charlton, Byrne etc but when he talks about the holy trinity he gets a glint in his eyes and you can still see the wonder. He says he's the greatest striker he's ever seen play football not just for United and my grandad has watched a lot over the years. He had it all according to him and could do everything you wanted in a striker, he is The King </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:32:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep Real doing what they do best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh of course they are pricks, I know he's leaving but can't be arsed with a new story every day with nothing in it till he leaves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:24:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Them and Real leaking loads of shit to their mouth pieces </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:16:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then they can do that and shut up this year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 12:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well having no defence until December is a tad troublesome... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 00:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The amount of stuff he posts he's bound to get ones right, a week or so ago he said Dani Alves was ready to go to PSG and the contract was done and then Alves came out and said PSG was never an option and Blanc denied everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And a lot of United fans wished Ronaldo all the best and still do, it's all down to the manner in which they are leaving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 21:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Roy Keane, his performance against Juve after knowing he won't be playing in the champions league final was astonishing, dragged us to the final. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 13:50:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Schmeichel - Denmark

Rafael -Brazil

Stam - Netherlands

Vidic - Serbia

Irwin - ROI

Ronaldo - Portugal

Bobby Charlton - England

Ryan Giggs - Wales

Best - Northern Ireland

Cantona - France

Law - Scotland


Just going with one from each country for a team, had to make sacrifices like Irwin in over Keane who is obviously the best player we have had from ROI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 10:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 94th time we have signed him in the last 4 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 11:38:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus my memory is better than I thought, good find  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 11:07:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last I heard and this was about 5 years ago it would cost about 114 million quid to go over the railway. They've said repeatedly it's not feasible at the minute but think it's because it would affect attendance for a bit so they don't want too yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 20:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have been chronically underfunded for years so we needed some heavy reinvestment, you can't expect brand new players to come in and settle straight away as you know. We got destroyed last year, had pretty much our whole back line leave and got a new manager with a completely new play style. This year was just bedding in, we got the minimum that we set out for, it's disappointing of course but after last year I'm happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 20:00:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In all fairness city came 9th in 07/08 then spent 125 mil in the summer and then finished 08/09 in 10th so wouldn't really be talking if I were you but I'm sure you know that was all building blocks for the club as ours is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 19:49:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it was Liverpool fans last year when they looked set for the title after City </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 01:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fellaini, Duncan Ferguson etc I want to play football not get the shit kicked out of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 16:28:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kevin Bacon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 12:50:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Supermans first flight in man of steel, it just makes me smile like a child and makes me really happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Went to school with him, he was so much better than everyone else and we all thought we were the dogs bollocks. He's a top lad and is a great laugh and hope he is doing alright with everything, it's absolutely shit when something like that happens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:52:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was thinking about that myself but I'm going with the experienced head, that and the fact my grandad loved Byrne and said he was our true captain and could play anywhere himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:38:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty much what you said, watch the original trilogy then move onto the prequels. After that you can watch the clone wars which will fill in a bit more for you and marvel are currently doing some comics to add more story. There will also be a book released in a couple of months with more story between the end of 6 and start of 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:35:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bioshock or Mass Effect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 03:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Schmeichel, Roger Byrne at LB, Ferdinand, Bruce, Irwin at RB, Keane, Robson, Charlton, Ronaldo, Best, Law

Bench - VDS, Stam, Vidic, Pallister, RVN, Tommy Taylor, Duncan Edwards

*Edit, changed it to bench instead  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-17 03:11:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Silver Surfer Requiem is a brilliant story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:27:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your all time is not great, should be best, charlton and then argued between law, robson, keane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 01:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sucker Punch, brilliant soundtrack for a sadly rubbish film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 05:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah you mean this one (sorry for shitty Instagram)
http://imgur.com/13jsmOn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 03:39:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/4tbM0AP
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 03:04:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tunnicliffe was touted as a rising star, not to the level of Pogba but people thought he would be able to do a job for us as a destroyer which we were sorely lacking in at the time. 

I don't know how many matches until he proved his worth because I don't watch Juve that often but as someone who goes to about 80% of our youth and reserve games (at home) I can tell you Pogba didn't deserve to be getting games for the first team. He got put in because of his complaints and when that happened didn't actually do anything to cement himself as a first teamer. We couldn't give in to him otherwise every youth player would do it like is happening now with us and pereira who once again is playing for the reserves and feels he deserves to play for the first team and won't sign a new contract but he doesn't deserve to be in the first team as he is playing quite average himself but no doubt if he leaves and starts playing well then it will be the usual "oh United made a huge mistake"

You argue obviously he was ready but with Juve he is in a midfield 3 where as with us he was in a 2 so maybe that's why he couldn't shine with us, maybe that's why he was able to look so good for you because he plays in a formation we never would have usually under fergie

He wanted a chance that's true but he can't just say he wants a chance and then continue to be bang average playing against people that were inferior to him, he should have been tearing people apart to prove he was ready

Also don't know who's down voting you and don't really no why, you're just putting your opinion across </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 02:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then he should have played better for the reserves that year instead of just moaning about not playing, the year before he alongside a youth team that consisted of Morrison, tunnicliffe, keanes etc won the fa youth cup. Pogba played well for us in that but still wasn't our best player in the kids hat year, tunnicliffe rivalled him in midfield and Morrison was the standout. The next year (where he complained about not starting) he was absolutely average for the reserves playing poorly at times and just doing enough so why would we play him when he wasn't putting any effort in? Tunnicliffe was playing better and we didn't play him either and he wasn't signing a new contract so why play him? The times he did come in the first team he didn't set the world alight and yes he was only off the bench but he still had time to try something and he didn't do anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 04:09:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After the great battle of the wounded knee massacre a lot of towns knew that there would be trained soldiers who would need a new job after being kicked out of the military due to severe knee injuries, so they contacted the empire to try and get a job for them with health benefits that included things like physio. This offer looked good to the returning soldiers and boosted the economy and the towns now had trained soldiers protecting them. 

Why that battle targeted knees however is still a mystery...

EDIT - Sorry the source is my friends dad called Thorin who was at the great battle of the wounded knee massacre and is now a guard in Riften </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 01:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which God? Several Gods?

Was it Gorr the God Butcher? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:23:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wahey. He was handing a check over as he had raised about 25 grand for the hospital. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Met Michael Owen when he came to our work (I work at Manchester Royal) and that was ok, seemed a bit dull and like he couldn't be bothered. 

Then met The King Denis Law as well and he was amazing kept me talking about football, got pictures with him and just an all round great bloke and a pleasure to talk too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 03:37:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know what he would learn, I'm just giving an opinion. I'm basing my claims on the fact the finding stuff out in 6 months would be easier than 3 so he could have more chance of exploiting weaknesses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 03:30:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would give him more time to get better materials, maybe research supes a bit more and find out about red sons etc. 3 months he might scratch the surface of these but an extra 3 would be a lot better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-13 03:25:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Build a suit that could possibly beat superman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 03:00:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To cook for themselves on a small budget, just in case. Would help countless people in the long run </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-29 02:58:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Hunger Games: Catching Willy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-08 14:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No you have to be 18 to be deployed by the British Army. You can join if your under 16 with your parents permission but you won't be deployed in a combat theatre till you are 18. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-28 21:21:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please be Rich
Please be Rich
Please be Rich
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-25 19:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Petr Cech Yourself
Baines on toast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-16 14:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because Cartoon Network have no soul.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-14 14:29:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pearl Jam - Ten - Fave song "Black"

Led Zeppelin - Led Zeppelin 2 - Fave song "Ramble On"

John Newman - Tribute - Fave song "Out of my head" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-14 14:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> MSN Messenger. Showing what music you were listening too, having a ludicrous amount of emojis and symbols and getting group chats going and nudging people if they hadn't responded in 30 seconds. I know we can do all this now with Facebook and others and whatnot but it's just not the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-14 08:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rosenknospe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-14 07:08:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Die Hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-12 08:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I know someday you'll have a beautiful life,
I know you'll be a star in somebody else's sky,
But why, why, why can't it be, can't it be mine?"
Black - Pearl Jam



"To shut out feeling lonely; I get out of my head
Lost everything around me
Not dealing with it well
To shut out feeling lonely; I get out of my head
Why would you want to love somebody when love hurts in the end?"
Out of my head - John Newman

Also pretty much all of wicked game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-12 07:37:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was also the time Ronan broke his hammer whilst smashing Ravenous in the face 
http://i.imgur.com/ing1Clk.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-12 05:25:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nova vs Annihilus and Thor with 2 Mjolnirs 
http://i.imgur.com/XrHv6tE.jpg
http://i.imgur.com/2FxBHu0.jpg
http://i.imgur.com/G7sKBf6.jpg
http://i.imgur.com/Um9p7rR.jpg
http://i.imgur.com/ZPVoTej.jpg

Edit: me no spell good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-12 00:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cook bacon naked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-07 06:56:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus Christ Marie they're minerals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-03 23:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone with a soul is my friend. Nearly everyone else who died during it has come back so we can hope and pray for the return of Nova Prime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-03 22:40:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think you would really like the whole marvel cosmic run by Abnett and lanning. It starts with annihilation and goes up to the thanos imperative. It features the guardians of the galaxy and that run is the basis of the film apparently, also nova, Quasar, silver surfer and galactus plus more of marvels heavy cosmic hitters. It is excellent. There is a post that has the reading list, I'll try and see if I can find it.

As also mentioned Silver Surfer Requiem is brilliant. Also Thor god of Thunder is absolutely superb, brilliant story and stunning artwork </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-03 16:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nova the Richard Rider version because he is the greatest hero of all time and silver surfer for marvel. For DC I would go with Flash and Martian Manhunter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-02 23:39:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the marvel comics done by Abnett and lanning, the fault is a giant tear in time and space that is caused by the t-bomb set off by Black Bolt who is leading the inhumans and the kree during the war against Vulcan who leads the Shi'ar. This is then what allows the cancerverse into our universe. It also causes the marvel universe to lose it greatest hero. RICH RIDER REPRESENT!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-22 22:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mark I love you and don't actually know what to ask so.....erm..... 

Who's your favourite superhero character? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-16 00:55:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The reveal that you are Revan in Knights of the Old Republic. Still love it to this day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-16 00:49:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Felt completely disconnected from the world, things I loved like sport, my friends, videos games, movies etc didn't matter. Hated myself more than i usually did and felt suicidal, not god I wish I was dead but I went and bought rope and was getting everything ready for when I did it. Told my friend and she pretty much went off on me for keeping it a secret and not telling anyone, told me she would be there for me and help out and convinced me to go to the doctors. Was on tablets for about a year and have been off them for about 5 months now and feel like a new man. Still feel shit somedays but it's a hell of a difference to what I was like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-16 00:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dad's an alcoholic who used to beat me so never really wanted to continue in his path. Feels great to be judged by people when out though as if someone not drinking is fucking well weird and I'm a compete freak for not partaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-20 05:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't know how to properly link on alien blue but here

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/uknews/crime/9014449/Thieves-dig-100ft-tunnel-to-reach-cash-machine.html

Only know because I'm from Manchester and I had a good laugh about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-20 03:57:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not exactly a brilliant caper in regards to money stolen and things like that but I remember a story of a gang digging a massive underground tunnel to steal a cash machine from a blockbuster. They got like ten grand but I loved the planning and prep work that went into it and the fact that nobody got hurt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-19 21:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To keep calm I breathe in through my nose and slowly exhale through my mouth for about 15 seconds, makes me feel at ease and makes me laugh about whatever it was I was getting stressed about. I know it seems small and stupid but it really works.

When my nana died I just tried going for runs with music playing and tried be around people as much as possible to help move on. It worked quite well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-19 21:30:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was one I did when I was bored and was nothing more than childish but I gave out 2 notes on asking people to call back "Mr C Lyon" and "Mr G Raff" The number I gave them was for a zoo. Childish but made me chuckle watching them on the phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-19 17:07:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hot wheels cars, they were just badass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-17 00:11:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't know if already posted but I'll go with James Bond shooting the camera and the blood trickling down  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-06 16:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Martian Manhunter, should have had one from the off with the new 52 launch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-04 03:21:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being interested in physics and SPAAAACCCEEEE!!! Not even at school this either this is where I work at now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-04 03:19:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go to songs are duality by slipknot and how you like me now by the heavy. Go to band is either AC/DC, Audioslave or Alice in Chains </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Batman vs t'challa (black panther) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:39:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kryptonite

But in all seriousness a picture of a scary clown/IT would make me break down. Went to a circus once and had to leave when the clowns started coming into the audience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Prison break. First season was brilliant then it just went horrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just wear a green lantern ring and make sure you have a blue lantern close by just in case </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No matter how dark the night gets, the sun still rises in the morning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-20 19:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The smiley gang. They were around an area where apparently they got kids and slashed their faces (like the jokers) Obviously everyone believed it even when there was not one person walking around with any scars like that (myself included)

This was in Manchester  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-14 15:14:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It. Penny wise the fucking clown. Scared of clowns because of this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-14 15:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Toy Story 3. It's when the little girl picks up Woody and makes him wave to Andy that got me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-14 09:00:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All it takes is one bad day to reduce the sanest man alive to lunacy. Thats how far the world is from where I am. Just one bad day. You had a bad day once, am I right?

The Joker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-13 12:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> R2D2  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-13 12:20:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man utd vs bayern Munich 1999 champions league final. The last 3 minutes I nearly collapsed. Just look at the bayern players to see the devastation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>