<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7011</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lucas is my bet for Big A and Marion is BW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just talking out my ass here, but being in a mental asylum may undernourish someone. I've seen lots of blondes dye their hair black. You never know. We've never seen lucas' parents. We don't know if he's adopted. But again, I'm just trying to justify it. I could be completely wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:35:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't know. Either Charles is dead and he's impersonating him or hes somehow Charles. People can look years younger than what they really are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just compare the activity of him and someone like Julian Morris.  I know people may say that Julian won't post to give it away, but I think Brendan is posting more because he knows he'll be revealed as A. He hasn't appeared on PLL since the Xmas episode yet all of a sudden he's posting a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:27:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right but there was also a coincidence for Charles and Melissa in Black Widow Farm, yet people believe that. I'm just saying it's odd Freddy was used at the end of the episode and then there's a photophrapher named Freddy Lucas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:25:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol no but the name. lol the name and the fact that he's a photographer and look as this https://twitter.com/brendanrobinson

He is SO PLL Active compared to Drew and Julian, even Vanessa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Freddy...Lucas...Photo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:16:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Freddy...Lucas...Photo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It HAS to be Lucas. I am 1,000% sure now it's Lucas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So spoiler...but look at this website...hmmmm </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:09:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:25:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And you get cake, and he gets cake, and EVERYONE GETS CAKES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:17:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pll themed shower thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wait a fucking minute...if the time jump is five years later and they're graduating in 2012, that means they'll be in the future, 2 years ahead of now. So we'll know who Uber A on the same year they do, 2017. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:12:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hahahah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If you were on the phone with the president, what is the funniest line you can think up that would make him giggle? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 23:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently all my responses are unpopular except the obvious ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:17:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right, like the latest anagram "so wren is charles" is then not enough to determine wren is charles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's also "Nerd Lucas is the Liar". How is the black hoodie misunderstood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh okay. Maybe you're right. Some clues do seem like red herrings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Upvote for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:23:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you don't believe a thing that comes out of Marlene's mouth, then what's the point of acknowledging any clues she gave that link to Wren like the walking after midnight farm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it may mean someone wanting to kill someone or kill themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:10:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Link? and Pic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:10:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But he never wore a black hoodie. He was not a part of most of the 5 listed episodes. He doesn't fit into the anagram Mona gave the liars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:51:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The actress playing Cece has already stated she's appearing in the finale and so did Lucas and we saw Jason. The actor for Wren never said he'd be making an appearance. Never was seen on set. Never was seen in this whole season. I think it's clear by now Wren is not A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I think it's safe to say Wren is not A anymore. We don't see Wren in any of 6x09 and we most likely won't see him in 6x10 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry Wren theorists, but Wren is not Big A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no it's lucas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that the dress from the instagram post? Ugh my brain! #Livingforittho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:59:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe he's just a cross dresser like in the movie psycho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually I keep hearing this and it wouldn't matter his age if Charles died and he's just impersonating him. The actor will be making an appearance in the 6A finale. It's been confirmed he will be "involved" in the episodes of the finale or close to the finale. Wren will not be. And those that theorize Cece is Charles assume Cece is transgendered and was once a man. The actor who plays Lucas himself stated that would be a great reveal, but he thinks the network would not approve something like that. So if it's not Cece, the other only real suspect to be A, it has to be Lucas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:55:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They thought Wren was A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 10:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> woah so charlie pushed marion? woah nice!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 10:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.bustle.com/articles/86785-is-lucas-charles-dilaurentis-on-pretty-little-liars-that-anagram-may-hold-the-answer-to-the

http://tremolux.tumblr.com/post/112758824180/uber-a-whats-in-a-name

Though i think the person meant big a not uber a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tell me about it. We shouldn't have to guess this hard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 07:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was Wren then I said no because Marlene said we saw A in a black hoodie. I though Jason but then we never did see him in a black hoodie and he did look sincere when they revealed charles. I thought Ezra but then, he was there to rescue the girls. Toby was also unavailable because he was at the station. The only ones left are Lucas and Cece. They both were in black hoodies, they both had connections with Jason and they both were absent a lot but still in several episodes of pll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 07:37:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think Wren is Charles if that were the case then. I don't really think someone could fake being a doctor and treat people all within the timespan of 2 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 07:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if he was in radley like charles supposedly was two years ago, how would wren become a licensed doctor that quickly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 07:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if thats true then you'd have to rule out everyone, especially wren and cece. if charles is charles and hes alive, we never saw him and all the a clues are useless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 07:06:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wasnt he homeschooled after he got tired of Mona blackmailing him. He even mentioned, he has a lot of free time. He could have easily just impersonated Charles in order to hide his true identity. Besides, we haven't seen Wren or Jason in a black hoodie. But we have Lucas and Cece. And i think lucas is a transgendered person so i definitely think it's him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Illustrator Turns Peoples Deepest And Darkest Fears Into Comics </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:31:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> MMMMm you speaking to my heart right now. I'd drink the whole bottle with some smoked gouda and graham crackers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lucas was in 3 out of the 5 episodes on Marlene's list and the first episode he was in had the word "homecoming" in it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if Alison saw her mom give Charles a yellow dress? And then her mom told her to forget him? That could tie in the real yellow dress and the metaphor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:41:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Alison saw her mom buy Charlie a yellow dress and then her mom made her forget she saw Charlie altogether and the dream became the two yellow dresses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yaaaaassssssssss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:35:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not if charles died and he's just impersonating him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cute dogs Confused at sound of music </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:23:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lucas is A. He was seen with a black hoodie, he has motive, he may have been adopted, he loves toy planes and cars. Yeah I think he's Charles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you so much for the pictures. I now think and I think it seems to fit more, that Charles is Lucas. But thank you very much for the pics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:38:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks for posting original link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dunno it happened in an episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You only saw one yellow dress </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:01:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 00:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lucas is Charles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 00:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Its just bad writing.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/zjvox7f.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I think Lucas is Charles, this video convinced me of it! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:46:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:35:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/zjvox7f.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> show me a pic plz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GIVE ME THE results :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't even know anymore :*( I can't do anything with the PLL plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Mona was lying. We'll have to wait and see if the writers and Marlene make sense of it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 20:36:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We'll see in the finale. They haven't really shown anything before Allison went missing that has to do with her family other than that Charles clip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Based on this version of the "anagram": "I saw mom throw aunt Marion from rooftop, Charlie rises now." I think I know what happened </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 20:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jason was the cause of Charlie's death.

Jason got locked away in Radley.
Jason saw Marion get pushed by his mom.
Jason assumed the Charlie persona.
Jason's mom got him out of Radley.
Bethany dies.
Jason reassumes Charles Persona.
Alison comes back, Charles starts working with Marion.

Charles is Jason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 19:54:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You got the last part. You did it though. So it's your credit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> foxf4ce got it. She said:  "I saw mom throw aunt Marion from rooftop, Charlie rises now." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 15:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> woah!!!!!!!!!!! you got it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 07:05:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should write a book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 06:37:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I, I saw mom throw Aunt Marion from the rooftop, Charlie Worsens.

there, solved. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 06:09:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I got it then :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:05:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NICE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:19:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:10:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw mom throw aunt Marion from the rooftop, Charlie Worsens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The line that should be uttered the last episode of pll </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "People don't care about what's fair. They care about what feels right."

*mic drop

Feel free to add your last line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 01:46:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EXACTLY! That's what I'm saying. The quality has suffered throughout the years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 01:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I honestly don't think it is. I think it's some of the problem, but not big enough to sacrifice quality. Ever hear of writer strikes? And MOST IMPORTANTLY, isn't Marlene King producer as well??!? Pretty sure she has a lot of say when it comes to PLL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 01:41:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't BASHED anyone. The cast, crew, and actors all brought the show to life too. Writers are just one part of it. And also, ratings have continually plummeted and writers have more say then you think. So regardless of what the network thinks fans want, less and less fans are watching, so something is going wrong with the formula.

Also if you look at series similar to this that have mysteries, they've handled the plot better and catered to a young audience. Look at Buffy the Vampire Slayer, Veronica Mars, just to name a few. The plot was not soooooooooo drawn out. You can have fillers, that's understandable, but have fillers that connect and progress the main plot. That's all we ask for. It just feels like the plot moves from one point, and then jumps to the end without any middle area to explain things. It feels disjointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 07:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here is the artist: http://www.deviantart.com/art/Car-Wash-547180494 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 07:18:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *solidarity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 07:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wuv you :*( and I miss my granma!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 06:32:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EXACTLY and aww you're so awesome (Grandmas rule) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 06:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree, but as you can see by declining ratings, people are fed up. I"m fed up. I don't think I will watch until 6x10 if I know it will all be just filler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If Marlene King Ever Reads This... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 06:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why have you made this show so annoyingly hard to like? 

If it were not for the amazing cast and crew, your continually frustrating red herrings and lackluster reveals would have cancelled the show ages ago.

I'm not saying Marlene lacks in talent. She is an excellent writer.

I'm just saying: COME ON NOW.

You're not even giving us any way to make sense of who Charles is, even 6 episodes in.

I just think if you want less frustrated fans and more viewers for the last season, you have to give something throughout the season. Let it be a gradual buildup not filler...filler...filler...then the last episode BAM half hearted answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:32:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey I think you're awesome for directing such a cool show and I like Finding Carter too. I'm sorry I'm late but, was wondering why the design of Pretty Little Liars was split into A and B, is that to enable more viewership? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>