<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2141</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> California senate votes to open up Obamacare to 2.5 million illegal residents </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:34:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 22:53:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How about not safe for feelings?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two portapotty's? I mean really? Is there some sort of BBC regulation that requires segregated bathrooms to be made available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dedication </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 20:31:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes I did!

Now back now work for another 2 min. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> No one yet.... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> HD Projector question </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 14:04:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was thinking it would be fun to have back yard movie nights with my friends. I wanted to get an HD projector without going to crazy price wise (around $500). However when I started looking around I noticed projectors on places like ebay for 50-300 dollars that claim to be HD while other vendors charge 10 times as much. 

I was wondering what exactly the catch is. Why are they so cheap compared to proper projectors. Also any recommendations you guys have for projectors would be really appreciated.

Here is an example

[Example 1](http://www.ebay.com/itm/3000-Lumens-HD-1080P-Home-Cinema-Theater-Multimedia-LED-LCD-Projector-HDMI-3D-/161621153797?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0 hash=item25a15f1805)

[Example 2](http://www.ebay.com/itm/HD-Home-Theater-Multimedia-LCD-LED-Projector-1080-HDMI-3D-AV-DVD-TV-Paystation-/281633294609?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0 hash=item4192a70911)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This post must be fairly new because I can see your awesome reply instead of 10 people bitching about their "asshole" parents and how they overcame it to become a top poster on /r/raisedbynarcissists. 

I miss my dad too. It never gets easier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When two people kiss, they create a tube with an asshole at each end. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 03:59:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 17:22:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [The Taming of The Shrew (1967)] (http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Taming_of_the_Shrew_(1967_film))  was a great movie and way under appreciated in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 19:20:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am a beautiful person who is the best of luck to you by the way to get the best of luck to you by the way to get the best of luck to you...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An old lady at the bank asked me if I could help her check her balance. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 15:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I pushed her over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mama June - Bring 'Honey Boo Boo' Back Or I'll Sue for a Million Bucks!!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 13:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-23 05:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Saying a banned word with intent to hurt someone's feelings. 

Examples include
The N word. 
The R word (formerly retard) 
Calling something gay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 05:27:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for erasing the last .1% of doubt I had that this whole story was BS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tonight, on things that totally happened! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-22 04:37:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Boy Scouts put an end to dangerous water gun fights </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:30:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was told that I participated in vote brigading. Still not exactly sure what that means. They said I could be unbanned if I agreed not to do it anymore. I told them that I would not do it again but so far no reversal. Still whether I was wrong or not isn't the real problem, its that they just shadow banned me without any warning. If they had banned me from the sub or deleted my account I would have at least known I did something wrong and changed the way I behaved.

Small solace I can take is that this account now has way more karma then my old one ever did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not a very active user and most of my comments hardly ever get seen. I'm used to having 1 or two people upvote my posts every once in a while. I got suspicious one day when I made what I thought was a good comment on a new thread and got nothing. So I went to /r/shadowban and confirmed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a way reddit originally fought spammers. They make it so none of your posts are visible to anyone except you. You can't tell that you where banned. It was a good way to fight spam bots because they wouldn't know they where tuned out and go on doing their thing without bothering anyone. 

Now they use it for anyone they don't agree with. You get no message or warning. I didn't know it happened to me for at least 2 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was not primarily a financial decision But this has more to do with the long-term direction of the station.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think its a lottery. Every year I remember just after the last day to enter. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes folks this is an alt account(My main was shadowbanned), yes I'm too lazy to make a new meme.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 14:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I often see stocks taking big dives or surging but am unable to locate any news to go along with it from sources like the AP or CNN.  Is there some source most novice investors don't know about or don't have access to that the professionals do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We had been working together almost daily. Guess he forgot my name and was afraid to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My name plate was right above me! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>