<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7370</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:04:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's just how they are spelling deli </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crab cake sandwich from Chick and Ruth's Delly in Annapolis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is Chessie and today is her first day at her new home </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 23:44:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I've seen 3 different ones just this morning </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 13:18:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:15:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They had just finished eating so that's partially true  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Yesterday we picked out our new family member, can't wait to bring her home in 4 weeks </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:58:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pic of a bridge near my house at sunset </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How I imagine America will react to the DeflateGate results </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 22:12:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Would you rather be Bill Gates or Harry Potter? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 15:14:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Makes the day just a little better </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-03 16:32:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MRW when I'm at the club talking to some girls and I suddenly can't find them </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 02:55:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MRW I'm talking to some girls at the club and I suddenly can't find them </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-06 02:45:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-28 00:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was young, maybe 6-7, I woke up in the middle of the night to my mom looking out the window and mumbling. She kept saying some like How come the sun isn't up? Its going to be in so much trouble when I tell its mother." I was understandably confused and kind of scared and when I asked her what she was doing she kept mumbling about the sun not being up. She then went to bed. I brought it up to her and she swears it never happened. I've always just assumed she was sleep walking but it was super weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:59:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like good sushi a lot but I know what you mean, I'm never full after eating it and neither is my wallet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WaWa coffee is the best for a gas station, way better than Sheetz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:44:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never heard of this place, where are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:43:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They were pretty decent before they became a nationwide chain but now sadly I would have to agree with you. I do still buy their salt and vinegar dry seasoning for use at home, shit is delicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What restaurant do you not understand why its popular, and why do you dislike said restaurant? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-19 01:14:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FRANK AND BEANS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-15 15:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> STELLLLLLLAAAA!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-15 15:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CANTSTANDYA! CANTSTANDYA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-08 23:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never had a tinder myself but my buddy has shared a couple interesting stories with me. So back story, there's a college near where I live and this friend would come down on the weekend, find a girl on tinder that was from the college and go perform the deed with her. On one occasion he went over and started chilling with her friends in the dorm room and whatever, after awhile the friends left and him and the tinderella(stolen from another part of this thread) began hooking up. At the end of the performance, she wanted him to finish in her mouth, after he did, she looked him dead in the eyes and winked. He said he didn't know how to react and it was both awesome/awkward. Another story involved him going and picking up a tinder slut from the college and bringing her back to the spare bedroom that my friends and I had in the house we shared. Since he had brought her back after my other roommates were asleep they had no idea there was a girl in the spare bedroom. My roommate busts in the room at around 7am with them both butt naked and yells HEY BRIAN!!!!!" to see both Mr. Tinder and Ms. Tinder in all their nakedness. Made for some good stories before he found his SO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I have a pic from inside a car that is focused on the raindrops as well </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-06 07:35:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-01 03:35:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Forgive People </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-08 23:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We had somebody in college who would poop all over the common bathroom and the write The Poopster was here" in his own feces on the mirror. He disappeared for awhile until one night when we saw The return of the Poopster" written on the mirror. The Poopster was never apprehended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-02 03:40:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks OP! Got mine shipped for $60.82, I told myself that is buy these if they went down to the $50-$60 range, this should be my last S/S item I needed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-31 14:15:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a bar near where I live that makes every person who has a hat on backwards turn it around and if they refuse then they are kicked out. Apparently one time they had someone with a backwards hat on start a fight so now everyone who wears their hat backwards is looking to fight. Makes no sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 11:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man, good find, I was really wanting a sea stripe sweatshirt and was able to get one. You got an upvote from me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-27 04:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's a canvas leather belt, I don't actually own it but I've been thinking about buying it for awhile and I think they might still be having some good sale or something. http://www.gap.com/browse/product.do?pid=941520042 locale=en_US kwid=1 sem=false vid=1 sdReferer=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gap.com%2Fproducts%2Fmens-belts.jsp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-25 17:27:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The exact point where you move from conscious to unconscious when falling asleep, there has to be a certain point where you switch over and I just can't grasp when or why that happens. By the way never think about this while trying to get to sleep because you'll be up all night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-25 13:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A guy I know drove the opposite way while heading back to his hometown. Was supposed to be driving west and actually drove 2 hours east and ended up at the beach. In the same trip he also ran out of gas because he wanted to stop at the same gas station he always stops at on his way home. This was last year and he had a GPS and Smartphone. Also, he once told us that he wouldn't ask the bank to send him a new debit card because he didn't trust the mail, when we asked him how the bank received a debit card to give him at their building he said I thought they just had a machine to create them in the back." Another time, he attempted to do a backflip off the side of an in ground pool and busted his face on the side of the pool, this guy is a huge guy and stated that the chances of me hitting my face on that pool were astronomical." There are more examples but I'm starting to feel bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-24 21:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you can find it on sale ever, Dolce Gobanna The One is my favorite cologne, smells amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 17:29:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Sunset Brown](http://www.orionleathercompany.com/32mm-sunset-brown-dress-work-or-casual-belt-p/32hsnstcfstdloopl3370govblk.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 17:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which one would be more versatile, Natural or Sunset Brown? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 12:10:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, thanks for the offer but those are a little too small for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 03:58:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the info and pics, it's nice to see how they wore in and they look in good condition for 4 years in. That's definitely a huge plus for the Nike canvas if I can get them to last that long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Versatile Gray Sneakers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 02:17:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, I'm looking for a pair of gray sneakers that will be versatile and be able to be paired with outfits for the spring/summer. I've narrowed it down to three pairs but would like an opinion which is best or if there are any other suggestions for versatile casual spring/summer sneakers. Here are the three I'm considering: [New Balance 574](http://www.amazon.com/New-Balance-Lifestyle-Sneaker-Silver/dp/B001AO20BW/ref=sr_1_1?s=shoes ie=UTF8 qid=1395191429 sr=1-1 keywords=new+balance+574) [Nike Canvas](http://www.amazon.com/Nike-CANVAS-SKATE-SHOES-MEDIUM/dp/B004W4T11Y/ref=sr_1_3?s=shoes ie=UTF8 qid=1395191503 sr=1-3 keywords=nike+canvas) [Adidas Campus II](http://www.amazon.com/adidas-Originals-Campus-Sneaker-Micinder/dp/B0021AF6QU/ref=sr_1_3?ie=UTF8 qid=1395191544 sr=8-3 keywords=adidas+campus). Also, wondering if I can get any of them cheaper anywhere else. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-18 17:37:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As of last night this was still a valid deal, I just bought some more
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 05:05:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's on the last page before you actually place your order, you can apply it and make sure it is applied before placing the order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 04:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That really sucks, I wear a size 10 so the medium's max size is my size, but I like my socks to be tight, hopefully they get some in stock for you soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 04:05:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just bought a pair of white color size medium about a half hour ago, maybe its just certain size/color combinations that are sold out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 03:37:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't actually worn either of these but I purchased the ninjasox just now based on this thread http://www.reddit.com/r/frugalmalefashion/comments/1d48s1/no_show_socksseriously/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 50% Off Your Order From Ninjasox.com With Discount Code DISH50 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 03:17:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really good no show socks for loafers or boat shoes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Some people would say I'm a monster </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-10 15:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jaime Garcia My Father an old fashioned and blues equals a very good night </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-02 02:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I just want to see them for the first time during the Superbowl, its part of the experience. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-02 02:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> They had special bags made for a handful of people. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-29 02:38:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> To the balding bad luck Brian. [FIXED] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-18 15:13:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-17 23:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did in r/pics when I first started submitting to Reddit, was going through old posts and noticed that I probably should've put it in r/gaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw this in the store a couple months back </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-17 07:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-17 07:05:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scumbag: So who's the new boss?"

*homeless guy walks in*

Scumbag: Oh Shit"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw a video of this scumbag on Facebook </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-17 06:55:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MRW I show up to the Christmas party in an ugly sweater and everyone is dressed up but they're playing my favorite song </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-15 03:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-07 17:06:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know its not the same kind of cat, but this reminds me of Homeward Bound so much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Googled pictures of beard styles and I found this.... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-26 05:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Starting off the week right </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-18 23:39:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First time watching The Lion King </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-18 22:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Should be a hit with 90s kids. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 22:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 18:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea that's the point I've reached after biting it for the 30th time during breakfast this morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My mouth has been in a vicious cycle as of late </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-11 18:08:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-10 19:51:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This actually made me lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I couldn't remember the word scent when I came home from the store. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-10 19:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-30 21:09:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a 400 level electrical engineering course:

*Awkward guy in class raises hand in the middle of the lecture*

Guy: Whats a derivative?"
Professor: You're telling me that you're getting ready to graduate with an engineering degree and you don't know what a derivative is?"
Guy:Well I know what it is"
Professor:Well then explain it"
Guy: ............."

*Class busts out laughing and the teacher goes back to teaching* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-30 21:03:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a college algebra class as we're discussing inequalities:

Girl: Wait, why are there letters and where's the equal sign?"
*Class gets awkwardly silent and the teacher stares at her for a good 10 seconds in silence*
Teacher: The letters are variables or numbers we dont know yet and there's  no equal sign because this is an inequalitity"
Girl: If there's no equal sign then you can't do anything"
*professor turns back around and goes back to teaching

She dropped the class the next day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-25 15:49:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, Maryland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw thus in my local grocery store </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-25 04:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-24 00:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A little back information: my Dad and Grandma were notorious for playing pranks on each other when they'd visit each other, putting stuff on each other's face while they slept, my dad hid a full bag of trash in her car when she went on a trip back home, etc. Well it was Christmas in like '97-'98(I was about 9) and we had received a package from Grandma and were supposed to open it on Christmas Eve. We open it to see a bunch of what look like gourmet chocolates, so we all enjoy the evening and each the chocolates without anyone noticing. We get a call from our family who lives near my Grandma and they're just laughing it up and barking throughout the entire conversation, come to find out that she ate all the actual chcolates and dipped dog food bits in chocolate and repackaged the box. Come to find out, apparently chocolate covered dog food isn't that bad tasting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Grandma pulled this one on my family when I was a kid </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-23 23:09:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dinner tonight: Bratwurst with Guinness caramelized onions and hot mustard cheese </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-29 02:34:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This guy hangs out with me on the couch all the time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-21 15:52:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It was a total letdown when I actually read it. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-18 04:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 22:17:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really don't know looking back on it, regret not keeping him sometimes, but I'm glad he found a good home though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 20:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We actually had a really hard time letting him go, surprised we didn't keep him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 19:59:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He got adopted and is in a good home  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tried to get directions to my hotel that was 15 miles away, Google maps gave me this. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 19:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 19:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blue Moon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rio, our former foster, loved to cuddle </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 15:09:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 14:41:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was trying to throw it from the sink behind my back into the trash can and it miraculously landed up there, horrible shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I threw this balled up paper towel on top of that wall on my first day of work 20 months ago, still there. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 05:11:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 03:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly, you got it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> N" word dropped as soon as I opened the door.... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-14 03:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-09 00:01:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Must've been it, how thoughtful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm not done yet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-08 23:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 18:22:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool, I live about an hour south of DC  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 17:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its normally $8.99, but it was their lunch special that day so it was $7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 16:00:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's it, didn't even know that they had a website, just found this place this week.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 15:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The mayo is actually the bit of green on the bottom layer since its mixed with pesto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 15:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> St. Inigoes General Store in St. Inigoes, MD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 15:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? Whereabouts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 15:23:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BTW, the place I got this is a little general store called St. Inigoes General Store and it was a huge surprise when I found out they served food this good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 15:20:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mozzarella </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 15:18:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> East coast, the Chesapeake Bay area, sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 15:12:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its mozzarella, and it was delicious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 15:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in southern Maryland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 15:09:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $7, not a bad deal
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New restaurant close to work, chicken bistro sandwich on focaccia with prosciutto and pesto mayo </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-04 20:47:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-19 22:14:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rumors today were that apple is releasing a gold colored iPhone for the 5s  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Whenever I'm served food </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-02 17:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The bad luck has struck my roommate </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 18:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-30 04:10:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He must've worked for this company

 http://assmann.us/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Close one at the buffet today, almost unknowingly ate pork </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-18 19:19:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-17 17:15:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Taking me to Uganda, and then it's a flip between typing N for United States of America, or S for USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Found myself thinking this while filling out a form this morning </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-17 16:47:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 22:50:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We were happy with the turn out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 17:44:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually read your first comment wrong and thought you were asking if it was ice cream, sorry. If it was ice cream, there wouldn't have been time to take the picture because we would've eaten it already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 17:18:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, it's just layered white cake and red velvet. Then the blue is white cake with blue food coloring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Our attempt at a freedom surprise cake </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 05:26:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A friend of mine is at the White House tonight and just sent me this picture </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 04:47:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw this drawing while standing in line for ice cream </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-08 04:29:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Realized this at dinner the other night </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-05 17:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw this pretty good drawing while standing in line for ice cream </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-26 01:48:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-21 05:07:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your username is awesome, I feel like we're late to this game, but we were pretty pumped about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Trying to get directions to my hotel when this happened </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 18:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 05:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This one was the only one we had a hard time with because he had such a good personality and we got attached but the others haven't been bad. We've fostered probably 10 now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rio, out favorite foster cat so far </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 05:03:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 14:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Normally just microwave them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We've been fostering this guy (Diego) for almost a month now until he can find a permanent home </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 05:07:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 05:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's going over the bridge on Atlantic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 04:59:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.fatgirltrappedinaskinnybody.com/2011/04/bacon-egg-cups/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Duck Faces </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 01:50:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First attempt at bacon wrapped eggs came out well, works for a week of keto breakfasts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 01:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 00:43:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 23:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never been to Wisconsin though I have spent some time across the lake from it in Michigan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 23:20:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, appreciate it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 21:12:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I've learned that now, being from the northeast I thought it was always sunny and nice there, learned my lesson on that trip  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 18:19:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I realized after I submitted it that messed it up but didn't feel like changing it, my bad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 18:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea, the cat is always the master in the relationship  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw this at a store this week, didn't know things like this existed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 16:57:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 12:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was taken on Atlantic, it had been raining my whole trip and then the clouds broke while I was going to lunch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 05:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea we did, it was an awesome place and nobody was around, we couldn't believe it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Visited JAX last month, new to Reddit, took this photo there and thought you guys might like it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 05:26:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 05:13:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, my girlfriend and I were playing cards up on the lookout when I took this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 03:25:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lexington Park here, just joined Reddit and found this, I've been here a little over a year
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Visited Oakland back in October, just joined reddit, thought you guys might like a pic from a park I took there </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 03:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Happy Birthday Tard! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 02:09:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw this sign on my way to work this morning </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 14:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>