<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1637</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 07:29:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, I also wish you the best too. That sounds like a great idea. I am willing to try anything. From memory my mum has a few oils, will give her a buzz and borrow some. I'm willing to try anything. I do breathing exercises which helps anxiety a bit but my depression isn't so easy today. Thank you again for your response, I really appreciate it. Feel like I'm a record on repeat, seems to happened every 6 months or so that depression gets the best of me. Was close to deleting this as I hadn't had responses. Thank you again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-09 04:06:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This has helped me a lot today, Thank you. I was diagnosed with anxiety and depression about 15 years ago. Today isn't a good day for me, one of the many thoughts in my head is that I should "suck it up" and "other people have it worse". I know it won't last and then I'll feel silly/stupid for my mood. Want to give a shout out to my partner and family. They have gone through it all with me. Everyone deserves to be heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 01:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a feeling she is going to be getting a lot of attention today. Lots of hugs just to start with. Could watch her sleep all day. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> After being up most of the night not feeling well (coughing a lot) she is finally resting. She looks so cute and peaceful. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-11 00:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Old photo found on my phone, our girl when she was a puppy. First day home. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-26 03:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> She loves heat packs, casually trying to steal it from me. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-13 19:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 01:47:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is very true. Am tempted to adopt another one soon. &#128522; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Our girl sunbathing in the Bathroom - Sorry about pic quality </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-09 01:26:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-22 06:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't he also in tv series Doll House? Love him!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-19 02:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's absolutely lovely. Warmed my heart. Have been told that it would also depend on the reason as to why the animal was surrendered, if it was just because the animal is too old then they probably wouldn't let you adopt. There are some nasty owners out there, in saying that there are some awesome ones &#128522; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-05 20:51:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the reactions of everyone in the background. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-25 03:28:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like sliggoo? Common guys it's not fat green and purple it's majestic as fuck with blue and white. Dratini likeness overload. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>