<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7930</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [LF] Any G-Rank HH Bias [H] Blue Kut-Ku, Kut-Ku, Kirin </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 20:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blue Yian Kut-Ku (Lv. 90)
Weapon Bias SA, CB, IG
Tri Series F (Waist)

Yian Kut-Ku (Lv. 90)
Weapon Bias GS/LS
Freedom Series D (Head)

Kirin (Lv. 120)
Weapon Bias GS/LS
Original Series B (Arms)


Gathering Hall ID: 14-8649-6233-8143
PIN: 2552
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm near that area and looking to adopt a cat! Let me know if any of them need a home! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-17 05:53:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same happened and I had the game drop completely as if it never existed after trying to get into with the 'firewall bug'. Thankfully it was ARAM, but since then I've tried to play and the game keeps randomly failing to register mouse clicks and keystrokes for seconds at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-17 04:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just happened to me too around the same time and less than a minute into an ARAM. Couldn't reconnect due to a 'firewall issue'. Log in again and the game has disappeared as if it never existed. :\ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-24 20:40:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are literally living my dream. I'm about to start my second year of law school and am still trying to edge my way into the video game industry. What sort of interning experience does a video game attorney have while in school? Is this what you expected to do when you were still studying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-26 00:13:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Back when I worked at a lab, we used to splash a bit of listerine on donated human cadavers while they were thawing to make them smell a little more bearable for surgeons in training. Whenever I smell listerine now, I associate it with corpses and feel sick.

deadbodiesinmymouthpleaseno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-23 17:00:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP, did you end up finding an Eevee? I've bred several from the ones I caught in your Safari if you're still interested. Most have the hidden ability and 3-5 perfect IVs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-21 17:28:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Added, info is in flair!

Also, if you need Eevee, I can trade you a caught Eevee from your own safari. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-21 17:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Added you. My information is in the flair. :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Xiulan [3024-5755-2401] [Water] [Octillery, Gyarados, Azumarill] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-19 20:27:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Add me and I'll add back -- leave your friend code in the comments. In particular, I'm looking for someone who would have Eevees in their safari. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-14 03:59:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also remember to turn off internet because O-bond expiration notifications will interrupt the walking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tip for anyone trying to hatch eggs in X/Y.. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-14 03:52:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lumiose's center can be used as a never-ending walking loop if you just clip down some tweezers and leave it going. 

http://imgur.com/7aC3XDu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-21 15:11:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> D: Oh, it's you! On my frontpage! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 11:58:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, what a coincidence. I just drove past your restaurant a couple days ago and was wondering what kind of pies were there. Sounds delicious. I'll definitely try it soon. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-03 18:32:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just realized.. will steam add the four copies all to my inventory if I purchase or will it automatically add one to my library and only give me 3? I already have a copy and only want one for a buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-03 18:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm willing to purchase the 4 pack if you guys are still looking for people. I only want one copy for a friend. I'm in the u.s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-12-09 18:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad to see that so much understanding from fellow dog people. :3 I work in a research lab and my own Jake is a study animal that I adopted out. Whenever possible, we try to adopt our animals out. If not, then they are used for training purposes. The dogs are well cared for while they are in our possession. People always tend to give some dirty looks whenever animal research is brought up, but it's easy to criticize others for doing the dirty work that is necessary for everyone else to be able to benefit from medical advances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:44:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would have been nice not to have this spoiler right in the title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-08-06 18:04:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw this at Battle and Brew the other night. ^^ Nice job. It looks amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Loki decided she wanted to play too </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-16 07:21:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-14 04:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much for this. I've been flip-flopping about whether or not to buy Tera forever, but this pretty much sealed the deal. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-30 07:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure. I just cut out a stencil in freezer paper, ironed it to a shirt, and then sprayed it over with a 50-50 mix of bleach and water. There are tutorials online and I can also send you the stencil I made if you want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-30 07:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably not because I don't want my ass sued to oblivion and back, but if there's any interest I can post up the stencil that I made once I get back to my computer if anyone is interested in making their own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The fruits of my labour this past weekend! Loki tanks! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-05-30 02:01:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [NA] Looking for some friendly players to queue normals with </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-03-11 20:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started playing about a month or so ago. I'm level 22 and mostly playing normals (still learning a bit). Just looking for some more players to possibly invite to games with my friends who are mostly 30's. (: We have skype. I mostly play either Irelia or Sejuani right now. 

In-game username: Litrain_subject7930 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-23 20:40:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much! I'm so excited! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-02-23 20:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like one too if there are any more left! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-01-15 10:27:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am also a college senior about to enter my second semester. I can't say that I know exactly the best method to deal with this since I'm also going through the same fears, but I've been going to therapy for the past several months and it has certainly helped me a lot. This next semester, my therapist will be signing me up for group therapy sessions for social anxiety. I would suggest doing the sames -- many universities will have free therapy for students or similar programs for help. Best of luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-01-11 05:19:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I personally really dig earrings on guys. Studs especially. I just really like the look, especially on Asian guys. :b It really depends on the guy, but I've found that most Asian guys have been able to rock this look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-01-09 06:01:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry this happened. ): Experience has taught me to be extremely weary of guys who refer to themselves as "good guys".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-01-09 04:40:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. Okay. I am thoroughly creeped out. Mission accomplished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-12-08 22:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was just diagnosed with double depression a couple weeks ago, which is basically dysthymia with a major depressive episode happening on top of it. I had the same sort of realization as you a couple months ago when I realized that normal people do not actually feel the same way.

My experience with dysthymia has been mostly with my complete apathy. Currently, I only speak to two people regularly. I'm more of a loner and I tend to cut people out of my life easily. While, I'm not suicidal, I also feel like I'm not particularly attached to living. As in, I feel like I would not particularly care as to whether or not I wake up in the morning. I feel quite isolated as a person, although I usually thought this was just my personality since middle school to feel like I cannot relate to other people.

Consider talking to someone about this, especially your parents if you are close. Although I've never had a significant relationship in my life where I felt I could confide in another person, including my parents, I know it does a lot of damage to carry this kind of burden yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-12-07 05:30:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This clip creeps me out just about every time. D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-30 06:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work at a research lab for medical device testing. I'd just want to point out that animal testing is not about "ooh, let's strap down this animal and stab it with a bunch of needles and sharp things because we like to see it suffer" like the media would to make it seem. A lot of people that I know in this type of work genuinely care about these animals and about making their lives easier during their stay here. Granted, I'm not saying this is true for every facility, but I think there are plenty more good facilities than the bad ones that tend to be overrepresented. To me, it's a necessary evil that's more about the choice of scientific progress over stagnancy because there's no way to create an accurate artificial model with what we know now (although that would be nice).

It's much easier to just label testing as a purely evil practice while personally enjoying the benefits. If it goes against your morals that much, then decline treatment that uses any pacemakers, any drugs, stents, prosthetics -- pretty much any medical device made and approved for use (including surgical tools and techniques that were tested on animals). It would do these animals a world of benefit if medical companies weren't so pressured from social backlash to keep testing hidden from the public eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-30 06:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the same reason why I finally went to get help -- my depressive episodes were repeated, but I felt that the intervals between them were getting shorter and shorter. Has your experience with dysthymia been pretty consistent? Because I feel like I do normally have a pretty low mood, but I also feel like there were definitely some days scattered in there where I felt better than others. My therapist asked me how comfortable I was with the idea of starting on medications but I don't think I'm quite comfortable with it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-30 06:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I believe that's what my therapist was talking about. She basically explained that my baseline mood is much lower than most people's at a neutral level. When bad events happen, this triggers a major depressive episode at the same time and when I do recover, it's always back to my low baseline, so never really quite up to the mood level that most people are operating at.

I mostly went to see my therapist after years of putting it off (the last time I saw a counselor was in middle school but I stopped after I felt she violated my trust -- I'm now in my last year of college). In between those times, I've been basically suffering from repeated depressive episodes spaced every couple years, although recently the interval between these episodes has been getting shorter and shorter. Between my episodes, I'm usually quite apathetic and feel quite isolated from people still. I had hobbies that I was extremely passionate about that eventually dwindled down to nothing. Same with the amount of friends that I had due to my inability to feel connected to them. I am close to my family but I would say that I've never had a relationship where I felt close enough to reveal these sort of intimate feelings that I have. I tend to be extremely private as a person, even to my own family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-28 00:25:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I usually give cigarettes to the first one or two people that ask, but it really bothers me when people feel entitled to getting one of your smokes just because they asked. I've definitely been called a selfish bitch for not immediately handing over a smoke. I told her to get over herself and buy her own damn pack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-28 00:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went once on my 18th birthday with some friends and my boyfriend at the time. Way more men. It was also very awkward because the stripper that was performing during the time we were there was crying during her dance. I don't think I've ever had to sit through anything as awkward as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-24 03:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope, but that's never stopped other girls from doing that to me.
At the same time, guys who do this are just as much at fault as the girls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-23 07:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Heart Skipped a Beat by the xx](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DjUX2LESOpM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-23 01:07:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, we'd been in a long-term relationship for a while. It just happened that some girl he met expressed interest in him a month after they met, so he made plans to dump me to get with her. Classy guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-22 22:19:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right after sex. I hadn't even gotten dressed yet and we'd spent the whole weekend together after several months of long-distance. I found out after it was because he'd started seeing some other girl at his college without telling me about a month before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-22 22:11:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I sit next to fidgety people in class and they pretty much jig their legs up and down for the entire length of the class, making my own chair or table shake as well.  Nneerghh.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-21 00:56:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cleaning out shredded bits of human cadaver from some surgical tools (think something like a flexible cheese grater). Yum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-17 04:11:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dead giant yellow hairy spider stuck on the other end of my straw when I pulled it out after finishing my drink at Harvey's.

Nope nope nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-16 11:49:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not anti-weed. I'm all for legalization, but I don't believe weed really lives up to the pedestal that people usually put it on. I hung around with some people who were avid tree-lovers in high school, but I never really got much enjoyment out of it.

I honestly think there are some types of people that would do better without it. Of course, I'm all fine with medical use and those who are capable of using it to enhance rather than hurt their lifestyle. 

What I definitely find weird is this strange sort of entitlement that comes with those who get really obsessive about it to the point that they feel superior to those that choose not to partake. People who will end up relying on smoking as a form of validation for their life should not go near it. It got very sad to see my friends have to resort to smoking every couple of hours because apparently not being high was just that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-09 08:10:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Three piece suits are amazing-hot.

Nice collarbones are my personal lady boner. Actually, that whole neck/shoulders area. Hurr durr.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-09 08:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I like your face hole."

In reference to my dimple. I guess he didn't know what it was called. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-09 08:02:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want the slipperiest butt imaginable. The most slippery butt you can have is the kind of butt I want.

I want this because of reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-08 18:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. Thank you for ruining my life. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-11-03 19:57:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm down for a meetup. 
Not sure about other Emory redditors, but I'm a senior with a car.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-29 10:36:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Told me when I said I was leaving that I'd never do any better than him. This after cheating and leaving me several times with different women.

It was a horrific experience for a first relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-29 10:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surgical masks are designed for the sneeze to basically flow out back through the sides. Generally, you're supposed to sneeze facing the surgical field. If you turn away, the sneeze would be directed right into it. 

Other than that, I think you'd just prepare yourself and put down those instruments before you kill someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-26 03:47:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember the earliest meme-ish website I remember being on was Emotion Eric. Or Hamster Dance. Oh, how far we've come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-26 03:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> French fries and mayonnaise. Nomnomnom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-21 09:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 21, 5.5

Being Chinese, I used to mess around with people in high school and tell them I had my feet bound when I was younger.
They believed me. I: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-21 09:46:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went to work and brought cake for all my coworkers. And then I went out with my then-boyfriend and his best friend who had a thing for me to two mostly-dead bars. Very awkward.

The bartender did buy most of my drinks for the night though, so that was a plus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-21 09:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surprised [My Dick](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LnzYG0ZkrXg) hasn't been posted yet. But then again, I am not a Reddit male. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-21 09:03:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm getting paid to be on Reddit right now. (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-21 04:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to think that it all happens just like in [The Egg](http://galactanet.com/oneoff/theegg_mod.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 23:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your incident really reminds me of [that Jack Nicholson scene](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6wtfNE4z6a8). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, what's been your absolute worst dining experience? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 22:45:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This one time, I was finishing my Coke at a restaurant. I pulled out the straw when I was done and saw this giant dead hairy yellow spider somehow clinging onto the tip of the other end in a way that could only mean that it had been stuck there the whole time. I had been drinking all that Coke that was washing over its dead spider carcass.
I will never drink out of a straw ever again without checking both ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 07:23:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went to a French immersion middle school and we had this one particular teacher that stuck out. We called him Monsieur Sohier and he had this reputation with students for resembling something like an angry leprechaun (pointed ears, grizzled facial hair, balding). Whenever it seemed like we weren't paying enough attention, he'd actually scream at us for being horrible students until he got red in the face. And then he'd straight up throw things like chalkboard erasers or textbooks across the room, aimed at specific students whenever they talked in class. This one time, he walked up to a particularly talkative classmate and calmly pointed out this dictionary sitting on the shelf. He then stated in French something along the lines of, "If I were to hit you full-force with this dictionary, you'd probably drop dead before even knowing it."

To be honest, I'm surprised he never had an aneurysm in all his years of teaching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 07:14:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know some people who are very averse to sad music. I know for me, listening to extremely depressing music is a peculiar kind of catharsis. I hope you feel better soon. (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 07:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends if you really like extremely depressing songs. I compiled the ultimate playlist of the most depressing breakup music I could find when I was going through a particularly rough one.

[lyric-heavy](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TYT8XUKO-58)

and if you're not into acoustic, [heart skipped a beat](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cHYZy8SFp54)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 06:05:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I lost as soon as pelvic thrust guy started squeaking his way into frame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 05:48:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Pinkie Pie?](http://gifsoup.com/MjA3MjY2OA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 05:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 5'3" (actually more like 5' 2.75"). I think that's considered a pretty decent height for an Asian girl. I still wish I was taller though. It's kind of sad when I need to ask for help because I can't reach the shelves at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 02:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I spent a good portion of my high school years trying to dress like a [gothic lolita](http://lolitachan.org/scbt/src/130109239385.jpg). Nnnergh, whyyyy?

also, [slap bracelets](http://slapbraceletsonline.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/05/slap_bracelets_pile.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 01:43:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agnes. I'm not quite sure if I like it or not. It makes me feel like a crotchety old lady. I've also had people mistake it for "Haggis". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 01:37:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Getting distracted by your own cleavage all the time. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 00:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll just put it this way -- my inability to meet people has screwed me over already in non-romantic aspects of my life. So I guess at this point I'd rather change things now than realize later in life that I missed out on a lot of opportunities to meet people when I was younger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 00:49:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not unless you're that alien diva from Fifth Element.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 00:45:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's funny that you say that because I was actually considering making a full Boba Fett armor this year to anonymously creep people out on campus for Halloween. Maybe I should really do it. xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-07 00:33:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will probably try to increase my sample size. I guess this means I'll just have to be more active in approaching others then since I rarely get approached at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-06 06:13:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will try to work on it. And I'm way far away from NYC. I'm unfortunately stuck in the South for the time being. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-06 06:01:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know why this happens, because these types of people are the only ones that ever approach me. I don't really ever take initiative with asking guys out although I'll hang around them until they ask me if I'm interested. 

Other types of guys have never really approached me though and I feel extremely awkward trying to go for people outside of what I'm familiar with. Usually I'm willing to give it a try if someone approaches me and I find them interesting and physically okay-looking. But right now this is the only type that I've been with, which is making me wonder if it's to do with my age group or if I'm putting out all the wrong signs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-06 05:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It usually takes something extraordinary for me to approach people directly. If I like someone enough, I try to approach them by giving them more opportunities to be around me. 

I've been told I give off a very intimidating aura, even though I'm really just really kind of terrified of people though. I usually can't talk very freely with people I don't really feel comfortable with yet, and that's usually misinterpreted as a sign of that I'm completely disinterested and annoyed about talking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-06 02:46:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, I've just kind of had to accept the risk of being objectified as a fetish because of my race. It's something that is pretty much impossible to avoid in the geek community and difficult to detect immediately sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-06 02:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I only had one ex that was really into anime and even studied Japanese. You'd think he would have been more into me, but he actually showed the least interest. A good summation of our relationship would be that he never saw anything wrong with playing on his DS across the table from me when we went to lunch in public, leaving me to eat by myself on the other side in silence. The sad thing is that we met through the university Pokemon League. I really tried to make that one work because we had the same interests  and he was interesting to me for almost a year.

Another had a reputation of having that kind of fetish. And then another one developed an Asian fetish after dating me. One ex that cheated on me actually said that they hoped I'd never have the self-confidence to realize that I could be doing so much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-06 02:35:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's hard to say. Most of my relationships would start out okay enough before the amount of stuff I could forgive without thinking about it too much started piling up. I've had an ex that was generous but it seemed more like he was going through the motions of boyfriend-ness without actually being sincere about it. I've also had one that would act kindly but then would be completely stingy when it came to financial stuff (like telling me to pay for condoms out of 'sexual equality' but then would never offering to pay for my birth control).

Like I said before, I rarely approach people, so a lot of my exes were people who initially expressed interest in me and then seemed to just lapse into disinterest/coldness as soon as I reciprocated and it became a stable relationship. I don't really think I'm "crazy" either, so that might not be it. I've been snapped at for asking for sex too much. Also told to "get off" for trying to hold his hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My name is G G G G, baby baby baby. GD, GD, baby baby. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-06 00:31:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 23:40:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't really know what to say to help since I tend to suffer from the same type of crippling social anxiety. I try not to think about it on the grounds that there's nothing I can do about something that's already been done and that thinking about it will only do me harm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 23:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On the contrary, I have a very healthy relationship with my dad. He is the reason for my introduction into geekery. When I was kid, I would stay up late with him to play Super Mario World or watch Batman movies. I don't see him very much now that I'm away from home though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 23:06:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Somehow, this doesn't surprise me. Every time someone doesn't use their turn signal, I want to kick them in the face. Especially when it ends in me needing to slam the brakes on the highway because they think it's ideal to merge directly in front of a car without signaling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 23:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get drunk.

The sad thing is that that really is the only time when I feel like I'm not being suffocated by my own introspection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 22:39:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Deoxygenated blood is actually blue cause our veins are blue too."
"Aren't eggs a dairy product?"
"Can penguins fly? I mean, they have wings."

All by the same girl in my introductory logic class. And I'm going to a supposedly "good" school.

EDIT: I forgot another one from my biology course. "If saliva breaks down starch, then why is it that a fry doesn't just disappear when I lick it?" I don't know. It's a close tie for whichever one's more stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 22:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I promise I wasn't burned in a fire. I'm definitely okay-looking.

It's not like I seek out men that ignore me. It's more like they show an interest in me and then immediately drop into "I don't care anymore" mode once I express interest back. Not really sure why that happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 22:13:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I gotta finance my 'Vette though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 22:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like /r/shittyadvice. I don't really get how it's the business of my friends to know what my SO thinks about my body.. \: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 22:06:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was a little puzzled about that too. Most of the excuses would always be things like "I have a headache" or "I'm too tired" or "I'm already tired from studying for orgo/chem. Not tonight." Guess that's what happens when you go to a school where most of the students are pre-med. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 22:05:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm, it's not like I've never rejected guys. Most of my criteria generally involves having about the same interests/sense of humour. I'm a pretty quiet, introverted person though, so I rarely approach others and really only pick from people who approach me first.  Also, I'm not very insistent on things like being paid for -- I'd much rather either split bills or take turns paying for stuff, but that usually leads to me having to usually pay for almost everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 22:01:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahah, I will consider it. But I'm pretty sure wearing a Boba Fett helmet is not going to help me get non-geeks, as suggested. ;b

The helmet's actually a pretty common children's toy from Target. It just happens to fit me because I apparently have the same-sized head as a twelve year-old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 05:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely everyone is looking out for only themselves. Give them the chance and they'll all screw you over. College kids are nothing but vultures. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, is this something that just gets better with age or am I doing something wrong? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-10-05 05:19:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just recently turned 21. Female in college with mildly geeky interests --  decent looking in my own opinion. The majority of the guys I've dated have been around my age and have just about been all-in-all uninterested in me. As in they'll rarely want to actually go out and their idea of spending time together is coming over to my apartment and then ignoring me all night to watch gaming vlogs (I only wish I was joking). The majority of them have also been pretty much disinterested in sex, saying that it's too tiring. I've had it happen to me where one of them actually told all my friends except me that I was getting fat and that I was a complete turn-off in the hopes of getting them to make me feel bad enough to go to the gym more. Another said he was into me because he's into fat girls. Reddit, I know I am definitely not [fat](http://i.imgur.com/fz0p4.jpg), but my dating history has left me pretty self-conscious.

Why is it that I only ever meet the men that don't know how to treat a lady and that all insist on putting me down? What gives? Is this just an age thing or is there something wrong with me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-09-27 00:09:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really quite sure, I guess. I mostly have problems meeting people that I genuinely really want to get to know more. That and I tend not to go easy on friends. I have a tendency of cutting people off completely as soon as they do something I find morally despicable. So I guess I've been slowly whittling down my pool of friends.

That and I mostly like to spend my time alone, something which people don't seem to understand and take offense to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-09-25 19:12:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hamlet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-09-22 01:04:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Couldn't agree more. Those eyes! *swoon* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-09-21 04:56:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For Asian hair, Gatsby Moving Rubber is your friend and can easily achieve that same sort of hairstyle. (: It's very easy to use too -- just take a little bit of it and rub it between your hands until it gets warm and then scrunch your hair with your fingers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-09-21 04:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look absolutely adorable, especially in the second picture. I have to agree that you have a great smile. Your teeth look fine to me. Not ugly at all. (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2011-09-08 04:21:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This definitely sounds like a great idea. I'd definitely be interested. I've always had very few close friends already (I'm a fairly introverted person and find it hard to feel close to more than a couple of people at a time). Not to mention most of my friends have been male. I've only ever had two absolute closest female best friends who both turned out to be people who lied to me and spoke so badly of me behind my back to the point that it started affecting my reputation. As a result, I've just generally been uncomfortable and distrustful around girls that I meet ever since.

But, yes, definitely interested in an opportunity to finally have down-to-earth, chill girlfriends that won't be catty and two-faced. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>