<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6494</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:09:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't really ever gotten far enough to experience pain I think. Like I've never been in more than a half or quarter of a finger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had a therapist since middle school, who I see on a weekly basis. I first got her to work through self harm and depression. And lately we've been working through anxiety. I've known her for so long, would it be strange to try and work through this with her? The mental aspect I mean  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe I do. I'll look into one, but what I'm really asking is what could be the reason for how i am? Why do I react the way I do before anything is even close to inside of me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have no recollection of any trauma in the past. I don't have a gyno as I'm still a teenager  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:16:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm young, so I don't have a gyno yet. And my mother still stays in the room with me during appointments. I'm not looking for a diagnosis, just some ideas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Question/Advice] What is happening to me? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:35:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I think I have vaginismus. I've never been able to insert a tampon, and have never been penetrated, through sex or masturbation. What's different is that I have a mental reaction to thinking about penetration. When trying to insert a tampon, I get nauseous and sweaty before I can get even a quarter of an inch in. The idea of fingers or toys make me dizzy and sick. The idea of a penis penetrating me doesn't scare me, but I'm almost positive it wouldn't be a pleasurable experience. I've had a girlfriend for two years, and on a few occasions we have tried to use fingers. Sometimes if I'm distracted during sex, she can get a tiny bit of her finger in, but once I realize what's happening I immediately start crying and shaking. I simply cannot control my emotional/mental reaction. So I guess my question is what's happening to me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lots of questions [Help] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been reading this subreddit, and I think I have vaginismus. I've never been able to insert a tampon, and have never been penetrated, through sex or masturbation. What's different is that I have a mental reaction to thinking about penetration as well. When trying to insert a tampon, I get nauseous and sweaty before I can get even a quarter of an inch in. The idea of fingers or toys make me dizzy and sick. The idea of a penis penetrating me doesn't scare me, but I'm almost positive it wouldn't be a pleasurable experience. I've had a girlfriend for two years, and on a few occasions we have tried to use fingers. Sometimes if I'm distracted during sex, she can get a tiny bit of her finger in, but once I realize what's happening I immediately start crying and shaking. I simply cannot control my emotional/mental reaction. So I guess my question is what's happening to me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:33:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god! I'm from bay city!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! What city?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 18:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm hoping this way works out for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 18:06:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Question: me and my friend both got tickets for Of Monsters and Men. But he ended up with GA tickets and I have GAB1 tickets. What do we do to end up in the same place? We don't want to enjoy the concert separately  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 21:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got  samples of Brier Path, Zazz, Cozy Sweater, Imp, and Twice is Nice as well as a PB in Zazz (smaller size was sold out, so I hope it was worth buying the full size). 

I'm new to perfumes, so I'm hoping these scents will be great!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 22:10:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /u/trollabot train_subject6494 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 22:06:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /u/trollabot train_subject6494 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 05:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally will once I become more familiar! It's funny how different perfumes can be for people. I've been wearing Vice all day and I'm falling in love with it more and more. It's unlike anything I've ever worn. I still have to pass judgement on the others though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-29 04:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This totally happened to me at the Psychiatry of Death exhibit in LA. I didn't even realize until months later  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe I'll try that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was going to get a sample of cozy sweater but ran out of money! Cozy Rose sounds amazing! Maybe I'll try it one day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely! I've been wearing Vice for about two hours and I think I'm going to marry it. I sniffed out of the bottle and really thought I wouldn't like it, but I'm finding that I really like it the longer I wear it. The coffee and chocolate smells delicious!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I totally made that mistake  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cold sniffed rose city and fell in love! I think I'll wear it tomorrow! I'm wearing Vice right now, and I thought I wouldn't like it but I'm finding the longer I wear it the more I'm liking it. the chocolate and coffee smell is so delicious!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:18:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! I smelled all of them, I immediately fell in love with Rose city, but was meh about the rest and REALLY didn't like vice. BUT I just put vice on an hour ago a FELL IN LOVE. so I'm thinking my cold sniff first impression may not be valid compared to wearing them!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bought samples of Vice, Satyr, Lavender Sugar, and Rose City, they threw in Ruth for free! I'm brand new to perfume so I'm very excited to try these out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First order from Haus of Gloi!!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 03:57:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The real question is could anyone say anything bad about Panic at the Disco </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 03:57:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing, they're amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:03:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A less patchy version on KVD'S Vampira  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-08 04:21:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Swatching lipsticks is my go to anxiety reliever! When life gets too much I compare lipsticks in my collection until I calm down. It's nice go know I'm not the only one who does this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 20:40:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But whose to say it isn't worth it to keep him in her life? A pedophile is not always a criminal (and in this case he is not) nor does he have any intentions on becoming one (that we know of). Yes, he needs help, but she doesn't have to get out of the relationship. Just because he has these thoughts doesn't make him any less of a human being. Like any other person, he has feelings. Just because he considers himself a pedophile, doesn't mean we can dehumanize him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 19:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You better be joking,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 19:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is no problem with having a strong opinion about something, but you have an extreme bias towards this topic, and I don't think it's fair to want everyone else to condemn pedophilia the way you do. They're real people, and plenty of pedophiles do not want to act on their feelings. Should we condemn them instead of giving them help just because there's something wrong? In prison, many activities are in place to rehabilitate criminals. The same applies here. Shunning pedophiles will not help prevent child abuse, but doing research and finding ways to treat and even cure them can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 19:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You really think something like this could be so simple? Your comment is extremely insensitive and offensive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 18:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Product list: 

Face: 
Rimmel Stay Matte Primer
Rimmel Stay Matte Powder in Creamy Natural 
Kat Von D Lock it Tattoo in #44
NYX Full coverage concealer in fair 
Milani Baked Blush in 05 luminoso 
Wet n Wild bronzer in Reserve Your Cabana (highlight) 

Eyes: 
Dipbrow in medium brown 
Too Faced Shadow Insurance
Wet N Wild Creme Br&#251;l&#233;e 
Smashbox mini Full Exposure Pallet 
   All over M4
   Crease M1 
   Brow bone/inner corner M3
Nars dual intensity eyeshadow in Himalia (on lid only) 

Lips: 
Wet n wild  Vamp it Up 

Urban Decay de-slick setting spray  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Im proud of my work today FOTD CCW </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-15 18:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/xstDC1L
http://imgur.com/5VEGz8Y
  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 01:00:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess you'll never know!!!! 


(Srs it's totally serious, I love CJ and I don't take any offense to it at all) 

Edit: I like the title "The Surpreme Circle-Jerker" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-07 00:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (Srs) Oh my god I was waiting for someone to CJ my post! I totally take it in good faith. I was merely posting something makeup related into a makeup sub. 

( I love muacj so thanks for making me laugh!)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-06 19:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally thought they were the same person when I first heard about all that Lime Crime stuff!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ssssamanthaa is no longer supporting/promoting Limecrime </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-06 16:40:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/sEpHYAc
http://imgur.com/6B7K4Ya
http://imgur.com/YpDAJ9K


(Sorry these uploaded strangely, read them from bottom link to top)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:46:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't heard back yet, I've checked my email as well as junk mail. I'm getting a little anxious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 21:52:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I get some details? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 06:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 06:40:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahaha thank you! Your vocabulary is magnificent!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 05:39:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kinda how I live me life &#9996;&#65039;&#9996;&#65039; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [18F] Honesty is good. Tell me what you think </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 05:18:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tell me what you think

 http://m.imgur.com/a/mWn1R

EDIT: with all the PM's im getting you think I could get an upvote!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:46:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glad to hear it's probably just a mix up, I was just worried I might've done something wrong 



P.S thank you for being so sweet! r/makeupaddiction would have made me feel like a fool already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:41:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was looking around for a TAT and maybe im just dumb, but I couldn't find it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:40:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great! I'll check my email in the morning!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:40:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I contacted her about 10 minutes ago through the website, so I'll be awaiting her reply! I had really no idea how long or how short of a wait it was supposed to be, im glad I did waitany longer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:35:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I gave them a month or so because I didn't know what the TAT of an indie company usually is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh oh! Could it be lost? How do I know if this is a fault of mine!?!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Have I been waiting too long? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:32:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ordered Nic Cage Churning Butter One Crisp Thanksgiving Morn from Shiro in December, and I still haven't received it. This was my first indie purchase, so I'm not really sure if it should have come by now.  I messaged Shiro about it, but I was hoping to get more immediate answers of what might've happened from reddit. Besides contacting Shiro, what should I do?



UPDATE:  she messaged back and we got everything figured out. And you guys were right! She is so incredibly sweet!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 06:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From Left to Right
NYX Wicked Lippie- Power
NYX Butter Lipstick - Little Susie
Wet'N'Wild Lipstick - Pinkerbelle
Lanc&#244;me Rouge In Love - Pink Bon Bon 
Wet'N'Wild Lipstick- name has rubbed off
NYX Soft Matte Lip Creme- Antwerp 
Kat Von D liquid Lipstick- Berlin 
Kat Von D liquid Lipstick- Backstage Bambi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Pink Lipsticks </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 06:11:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-07 01:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also "Asleep" by The Smiths. Gets me everytime  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 04:40:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ugh, so infuriating. Poor Kristen. I can't understand why people can't wrap there heads around a world that is non-binary  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 04:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually 5! They're all musicals! Every year like clockwork! It's a little crazy, but my school takes musical theater very seriously  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 03:56:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so cool! My school does on musical in the fall (Brigadoon), a One Act in the winter (Pippin), a Musical in the spring (Adams Family), and two summer musicals (undecided)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is the best shot of me from homecoming this year! I'd love to see your interpretations! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 02:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 02:48:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's exactly what we do! But it goes on for about two months, like there's a districts, regionals, and states plus festivals put on by various school. So every weekend for two months we travel to a different school in the state and compete against others. We're in the middle of our one act season right now! What are you guys doing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-03 01:42:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And it's like a competition? Like a traveling one-act?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-02 22:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool! What show are you doing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-02 21:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One acts? Isn't that just a Michigan thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-01 23:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jane Porter or Meg. I don't know why but I related to their strong personalities so much   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-04 22:56:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Fuck me gently with a chainsaw" is my answer for everything &#128514;&#128514; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-04 19:28:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dream!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-04 03:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dying for Heathers and Sad Girl. I hope they're referencing Heathers the movie because it is my ALL TIME FAV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-01 22:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-01 22:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone have guessed on the price of this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 17:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god that's so amazing! Thank you so much it's absolutely adorable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 17:06:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll totally try that!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My girlfriend and I after our production of Tarzan. The artist here are so good, I would love to see someone draw us! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 05:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 05:35:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do and I love love love them! But the post so many unique OCC colors that I have a hard time re-creating them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 05:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll swatch anything you want!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 05:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely! Here you go! http://i.imgur.com/uZ4NYdL.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/qYqPS6t.jpg (a little hard to catch the shimmer but it's very very pretty!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 05:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't get over how great my family is! My mom has an eye for great products!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 05:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got the mini Smashbox Full Exposure palette and it's absolutely adorable! It's so think and sleek and I'm still so excited about it! AHHH a I can't get over how cute it is! http://i.imgur.com/yXwaqQE.jpg
http://i.imgur.com/cRIMTIW.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 05:12:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone have some good lipstick inspo pictures? I would love to try some crazier looks than just one color on my lips!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 05:06:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Product List: 
Kat Von D studded lipstick in Lolita 
Givenchy Mascara (100 point perk) 
LUSH Cosmetics lip scrub in Mint Julip 
MAC lipstick in Heroine 
Kat Von D Foiled Lipstick in Valentine 
Kat Von D Foiled Liquid Lipstick in Adora 
NARS dual intensity eyeshadow singles in Himalia and Dione 
Mini Smashbox Full Exposure pallet 
Real Techinique Brushes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A late Christmas haul! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 05:02:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Swatches and Mini Review of NARS Dual Intensity Eyeshadow Singles </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 04:52:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These shadows are absolutely gorgeous. I received them as a Christmas gift and was floored at how beautiful they were. They're called Dual Intensity because they're meant to either be applied wet or dry (like you can do with most shadows) but the difference between the two is crazy. They're a light sweep of shimmer when applied dry, but the pigment when applied wet is so gorgeous. It's a little bit pricey for eyeshadow singles, but I am so happy they were gifted to me! I'm IN LOVE with them!  



http://imgur.com/hOTrreE
http://imgur.com/4mYZSbb
http://imgur.com/RPhwbwo
http://imgur.com/agOgSz1
http://imgur.com/W0Bd2sx
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-28 04:46:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The two shades are Himalia (left shade in picture, top two swatches) and Dione (right shade in picture, bottom two swatches). I got these as a Christmas gift and they are honestly so gorgeous. They're made to either be applied dry or wet, and as you can see they are both absolutely gorgeous either way. They're so creamy, and the pigment when wet is absolutely beautiful. They're a bit pricey for eyeshadow singles, but I am absolutely IN LOVE with them!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 23:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am signed up to be a rematcher actually! I love giving gifts, I just had hoped the one i received would have at least a fraction of the effort I put into mine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 23:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, done and done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 23:37:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, but none of these seem to help in my situation, I'm more looking to see if I'm eligible for rematch due to my gift being under the 20 dollars and what looks to me as a "send as little as possible so I still receive a gift"

Edit: of course this is just perspective on the gift.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 23:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess my added frustration is that I had a very detailed likes and dislike plus an extended wish list from the Reddit Marketplace, and my secret Santa never once contacted me. They also retrieved my info the day before shipping was supposed to happen. I will post it to the gallery without complaining because I honestly don't want to hurt my SS's feelings, I was just wondering if there was anything I could do to  make my gift exchange experience more positive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thoughtless Gift </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 23:11:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 07:36:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My girlfriend and I do that! We call it "playing dead" and it mostly happens when one of us is pouting. It's so nice to hear it's not just us!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-25 04:04:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh gosh! I didn't even realize this is considered a haul! It's not new or gifted to me. I though a haul was lots of things. My mistake!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-24 23:46:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oops! Kat Von D's foiled lipstick in Valentine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-24 23:06:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wear a lot of bright lip colors, and a lot of boys just don't understand how it works....like your lips? Being different colors???????   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-24 23:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! I have an awful camera quality, and I attempted to capture it, but it is super sparkly. I feel like Barbie! 


Here's an attempt to capture it (it's not very good, but you can kind of see what I mean on the bottom lip)
http://i.imgur.com/7HOX0f8.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can we appreciate this Kat Von D Foiled Lipstick? It's stunning! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-24 22:51:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-23 22:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was super helpful! Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-23 00:30:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I'm glad to hear that! Will I get an email saying I can sign up for rematch soon? Like....what do I do and when do I do it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 19:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It just sucks that I spent so much money and time on a person only to get nothing in return...call me selfish but.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-22 06:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do I do if the person sending me a gift hasn't shipped yet? I have gotten zero messages from them, and they last retrieved my info on December 18th. Is there any way j can contact them to figure out what's going on? Or do I just have to blindly wait?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 20:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oops! I assumed it was a woman since its a makeup subreddit which is totally wrong of me! I apologize!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-24 13:24:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She said she would also do non makeup pictures, i was specifically her to draw this for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-21 17:14:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/3MV26Ao.jpg


I know it's not makeup related, but it's almost Christmas and a drawing of my girlfriend would be wonderful! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 01:02:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe one day :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-17 00:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I've never had bangs before, I think I'm too afraid of change! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 23:21:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bold brows would be beautiful! You're gorgeous!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 23:19:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/mFEd4rB.jpg 

This is no makeup, Id love any suggestions! But I'm definitely looking for a pretty wearable brown lip
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-31 02:59:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely love a few of their songs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 16:37:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm being Mary Poppins! Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-25 00:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not that I recall, they're LE and I will admit I wasn't paying much attention, anyone know if they're the same price?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 20:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I absolutely love it! I'm not one who normally wears nudes or mlbb shades but I absolutely love this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 19:35:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope they do, it is honestly much better, it's...less cheap looking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 19:35:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish they would switch it! I like it a lot this way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 18:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry my old packaging example is scratched up, but I picked up sweet cream last night and I was surprised that the packaging was different! It's blacker, and sleeker, I really like it! The cap to the lipstick hasn't changed at all, but overall im happy they changed it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New Wet N Wild lipstick packaging! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-24 18:47:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 19:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heh, multiple orgasms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-16 19:09:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I have 10+ lipsticks just for putting my lip of the day in my purse and forgetting to take it out!' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 23:00:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone's got a different type  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 13:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, I didn't understand why you were jugs saying "no"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm actually a little underweight, I have a very round face which could probably make someone think I'm chubby  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 06:10:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope!  I just found this subreddit today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 06:10:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To each their own! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:41:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cutie pie 100000000000/10 I love you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha thanks! I was in a play,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:34:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 18/f just found this subreddit, I'm curious, </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here are some more recent pictures I'm interested in what you have to say! 

http://imgur.com/Z1iiVZW
http://imgur.com/IDXji1P
http://imgur.com/8Me63hO
http://imgur.com/Qjj3gVl
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:23:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 18/f be honest, brutally honest </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here are some pictures, I tried to get a range of different styles or whatever 

http://imgur.com/4iHkhSJ
http://imgur.com/Z1iiVZW
http://imgur.com/IDXji1P
http://imgur.com/8Me63hO
http://imgur.com/Qjj3gVl
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-08 04:38:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't see the rules on mobile, I saw that there was a 16 year old on the front page so I assumed it wasn't just 18+. Just thought this would be a fun experience. Sorry that made you feel like you had to be sassy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I just finished a run as Jane Porter in Tarzan the Musical. They got this amazing shot and it would be so amazing too see it drawn! All styles welcome! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-11 01:48:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-08 00:19:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 22:28:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:27:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rant: all the Ulta stores within my immediate area (about a 3 city radius) are completely disgusting when it comes to their displays and testers. I recently went to try and look for a nice black lipstick (to no avail unfortunately) but was dumbfounded by the mess that was specifically the NYX and Benefit areas 

Rave: my new 24 Hour Color Tattoo in tough as taupe. I'm still trying to get a hold of creamy contour. But I absolutely love it so far!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:23:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think I've ever heard that song and NOT cried  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-04 07:29:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No they posted on their Instagram at it's July 31-August 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-02 23:43:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please let this be true  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-01 22:54:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Already seen 2 people caught smoking pot and it was confiscated, and it's not even 4 on the first day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-07-29 03:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm new to makeup! Id love to try all those products since I don't own any of them, and always have wanted to but I mean... A teen girl doesn't make enough money for all that   :((( I would love it if you picked me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-29 14:18:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live by central so I SHOULD be going there, but I go Glenn because of their theater program  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-29 00:05:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely, the homeless people seemed to spike in the past two or three years and now they're everywhere, the polish festival is going on right now and they're just wandering around it piss drunk. The city is getting more dangerous at night. But other than that the downtown area is super cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-28 19:06:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hell yeah, I don't think I've been there yet and not seen a homeless man sleeping on it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-28 04:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An hour away from Ann Arbor here in Bay City! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-24 23:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She was the most obnoxious, loud mouthed, inconsiderate girl I had ever met,  we've been dating a year  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 16:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tri-city area in Michigan, maybe he reads reddit and just stole it, because I mean what are the odds that this thread is on the front page of r/askreddit AND the town radio host happens to share stories about bad break-ups that include getting a membership to the KKK  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-17 16:26:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude I just heard my local radio guy that happened to him on air, this better be the same fucking guy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-14 03:53:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What does it mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-11 00:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd rather be a little slow and safe than aggressive and reckless when it comes to driving  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This can't be true right? Found is Seventeen Magazine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-10 04:07:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-03 17:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sucks! I wish it would have worked out better for you :( it's annoying know that no matter how many people tell you a foundation is great, every person's skin is different and we all need different things. I wish there was just one mega-foundation that worked for everything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-03 03:58:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the clarification!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-03 01:59:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could I be mistaken and thinking of photo ready instead if colorstay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-03 00:04:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you sure you used the Whipped ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-03 00:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to refer to myself as "cancer patient pale" if that give you any idea. The two lightest shades are very pale, one with yellow undertones and one with pink, I use the pink undertoned one which would be the "second lightest" but I think it is very pale, if you can I would try it on in stores but I don't think you'd be dissapointed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-02 13:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rave: Tarte Amazon Clay 12 hour Foundation. I have an unbelievably oily face and this is the only foundation I've discovered that's able to control it. It is my exact shade and doesn't make me break out, plus I can't even feel it when it's on my face. Truly the best item of makeup I own to date. 

Rant: Revlon colorstay whipped. It's got glitter in it??????? Who wants glittery foundation!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-18 02:03:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Product List 

NYX Mosaic Blush 
Random Brown Eyeshadow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Brother wants to be a MUA! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-18 02:02:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-18 01:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She gets this certain tone of voice when she's trying to be cute and it's absolutely adorable. Works on me 100% of the time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 03:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much! I ended up getting Tarte Amazon Clay foundation, Smashbox primer, and NYX matte setting spray! I hope it looks nice, I'll be testing it tomorrow to see what it looks like throughout the day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-09 03:15:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ended up getting Tarte foundation with Smashbox primer and NYX matte setting spray! Got rice papers just in case, but i think there won't be a speck of shine on my face with all that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Crosspost] Good Prom Foundation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 23:17:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As the title says, im looking for a good Prom foundation.
Skin tone: Not exactly sure, but im very pale, i would say slighty pink undertones but thats an honest guess 
Skin type: very oily and acne prone. 
Why?: Need a good coverage, long lasting, foundation thatll keep my not shiny in pictures OR real life 
Context: I normally use Revlon Photo Ready BB cream, or Bare Minerals in the lightest color, both look great in the morning at 7 am, but by 11 im super shiny and uncomfortable. i want something that i can put on, and not worry ( or worry very little) from 6pm to 5 am, 
Budget: Really any, my mother is paying, but i am going to ulta to shop so anything that would be in stock there or a drugstore would be preferable 
Makeup Experience: Moderate experience, im doing my own makeup for prom, but its not anything crazy hard. i would say i learn very quickly so i can take any advice and do my best with it 
Special considerations: Going to ulta this evening, i need it by Saturday ( so i cant order anything online)
Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [ADVICE] Good Foundation for Prom! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 23:13:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As the title says, im looking for a good Prom foundation. 

Skin tone: Not exactly sure, but im very pale, i would say slighty pink undertones but thats an honest guess

Skin type: very oily and acne prone. 

Why?: Need a good coverage, long lasting, foundation thatll keep my not shiny in pictures OR real life

Context: I normally use Revlon Photo Ready BB cream, or Bare Minerals in the lightest color, both look great in the morning at 7 am, but by 11 im super shiny and uncomfortable. i want something that i can put on, and not worry ( or worry very little) from 6pm to 5 am, 

Budget: Really any, my mother is paying, but i am going to ulta to shop so anything that would be in stock there or a drugstore would be preferable

Makeup Experience: Moderate experience, im doing my own makeup for prom, but its not anything crazy hard. i would say i  learn very quickly so i can take any advice and do my best with it
Special considerations: Going to ulta this evening, i need it by Saturday ( so i cant order anything online)

Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-08 23:02:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a form!? I'll look for it and  edit my post right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-21 04:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIYBOB 

This just so happens to be my 200th comment so yay me! 

I am in love with the super purple one. I am in desperate  need of a color like that! I love that there has been so many give aways on this sub! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-21 03:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I really like it! I'm not sure if it has as much coverage as I'd like but when I'm not completely covered in blemishes I really like how light it is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-21 03:02:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just tested it and realized there's glitter!? What the heck? I bought the bb cream so maybe I'll return it after i put it ok with a full face. Any suggestions of alternative foundations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-21 02:06:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NYX Jumbo Eye Pencil in Milk 
Eco Tools starter brush set and mineral powder set 
Revlon Photo Ready Airbrush foundation in vanilla, BB cream in fair, and Concealer in fair 
NYX Butter lipstick in Mary Jane and Little Susie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Surprise Easter Haul! (Products in the comments) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-21 02:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:49:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the little heart tattoo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:47:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh stahp :) I'll try to follow the rules next time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That makes total sense! thanks for telling me! It won't happen again, :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry! I'm a mobile only user so I cannot see any of the rules . I had no idea. My previous post was hidden for for questions if it had a subjects name in it, so I thought it'd submit something else, I did not realize it was a violation. Thank you for notifying me though. May i ask why that's a rule in this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better than what I could ever do! Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:22:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is hilarious! Thank you so much!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adorable! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:21:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is precious!  Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Im a sailor! (Or at least wish I was!) can anyone draw me? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 13:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 13:27:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, it's not a name of one of the subjects, it's the association that held the event where we took the picture  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> These are my very best friends, Show me what you've got! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 02:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-14 18:31:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 143 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-11 19:24:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have bare minerals mineral veil, does that count? Should I bring a powder in my purse to reapply periodically throughout the day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Good products to control an oily face? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-11 17:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Face washes, moisturizers,  or any makeup would help. My face gets super shiny around 11am (only a couple of hours after I put my makeup on). And I want to find a product that can prevent that. 

Edit: I'm oily and acne prone if that helps  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-09 04:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mother had this and I once put it on my lips and wore it around the house because I thought it was some cool shade of lipstick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My cats like to take care of each other! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-07 18:21:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-03 19:00:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sleep paralysis  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-29 02:13:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hit it and quit it. That's the best way to get experience  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-29 01:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm also 15, and currently in a long term relationship with a woman. I guess you could say I found my girlfriend by pure luck, but I think letting your sexuality be known (though scary) will help attract interested people. I completely understand what you mean by practice. I think young love is something you need to experience. Just because it's "young love" doesn't make the feelings any less valid. A ton of people are being condescending on this thread, and I think it's completely unhelpful. Go out and get to know the other lesbians at you school (if any) make friendship, and see where those lead you! Good luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 23:18:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I loose weight dramatically when I regularly smoke weed. I was about 125-130 when I was smoking a few times a week, but now that I've stopped completely I'm more like 150. I don't know why, but it's still a dramatic shift in weight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-18 23:55:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My SO has PTSD towards all types drugs, (though it's mostly marijuana) and so whenever I mention or insinuate anything that has to do with drugs she gets really incredibly upset. (Needless to say I've stopped my drug habit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-09 21:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm almost sure it isn't an infection, because both me and my girlfriend are clean. "Diaper Rash" as silly as it sounds could definitely be it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-09 20:50:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you explain why? I don't really think it's something that needs to be taken to a doctor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-22 01:28:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obviously the fax machine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Woke my babies up from a nap </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-17 20:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-30 14:32:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd have to disagree, I guess it depends where you're from and what lesbians you've met. It's very hard to tell where I'm from, people around here don't treat it as something special,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-28 21:17:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bay City is present!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-23 18:59:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My teacher was like 60 too,  I literally stealing from the elderly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-23 18:48:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I stole money from my teacher for a gram. Probably the most shameful thing I've done  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-23 18:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Story of my life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An Old Friend's Last Tweet Before Losing the Battle With Cancer, RIP AJ, </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-22 03:25:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Paper Hats </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-20 04:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Black and white </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-20 03:20:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-16 20:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now that's pure Michigan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-15 15:43:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is an amazing setlist, I wish far too young to die was on it but I'm so excited to see nearly witches and nicotine. Can't wait to see them on the 26th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 15:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I though Matt and Kim 2013 was amazing, I've never had more fun in a crowd, but The Postal Service set was on a whole other level  of astounding  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 15:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reignwolf was amazing, never heard of him before lolla last year (I was waiting for MK) but he's a truly amazing performer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 15:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fall out boy is touring over the summer with Paramore, I think they're in Texas around the lolla dates, so I think it's unlikely, though id love to dream they'd be there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 15:17:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Panic would be amazing to see at Lolla. They've only gone once  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 14:43:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm underage so it's a little difficult to get a supply of alcohol let alone enough to get drunk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 13:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it still asexual if I really really really feel sexual attraction though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 05:06:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much, could you explain what some of the sexual dysfunctions are? PM me or comment it doesn't matter  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:35:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is definitely something ill have to try? Do you suggest doing it myself or waiting until I'm with my SO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:25:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very, very, VERY well  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:17:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not that I know of, the only think I could think of it accidentally watching someone give birth on a health channel when I was 4 or 5, I don't remember it, but my parents said I cried for weeks. I still never want to have babies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:12:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, I guess it hasn't been such a relevant part of my life until now, im in my first sexual relationship so I guess the problem has never arose  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know one is fine and one makes me pass out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:04:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a therapist that I have been seeing for a few years now, (mainly for anxiety and depression) do you think she could be able to help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:02:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone I know uses some kind of drug. From coke to caffeine. I don't  know If it's a small town thing, but here drugs is an everyday occerance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 03:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Arctic Monkeys, their new album is brilliant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 03:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is very much being afraid of something inside of me, I am not freaked out by my gf at all, but when I put a finger inside I get really nauseous. It's very weird and hard to understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-14 03:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, I never think I've gotten far enough in to be painful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-01-08 01:22:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had to stop reading this AMA to masturbate  on pornhub. Thanks for the great AMA  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-25 15:57:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From Michigan, it's sweeping high schools everywhere up here, it's hella crazy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 03:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg type of soup she was using. I imagine someone pours soup into their vagina!!!! But thank you, my girlfriend has mentioned that she has sensitive skin,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-04 03:44:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg type of soup she was using. I imagine someone pours soup into their vagina  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-03 13:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She says it doesn't bother her but I can suggest it, maybe she'll like that better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-03 01:10:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i am shaved. it could just be irritation i havent really payed attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 04:43:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ive been taking lexapro for about4 months now and have noticed a little weight gain, but not a drastic weight gain. have you asked your doctor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-26 05:35:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you so much for taking the time to write this out! i as of right now identify with the whole "Who the fuck cares" because i mean ive had a boy, ive had a girl, i guess ill see where i takes me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I would love some advice. Here is my story </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-26 05:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am 15 and know i have a long time to figure myself out. I am in no rush to identify myself sexually. Growing up i just assumed i was straight. i was attracted to boys and as i grew up and puberty hit, i definitely looked a boys a different way than girls. I've had two boyfriends and have had very fulfilling relationships with them. I had never really questioned my sexuality. As i entered high school i met a girl and we quickly became very close as friends. Throughout our relationship something has happened to where we have a FWB type thing going on. We make out with each other all the time and really have an emotional attachment to each other. I've been noticing how sexually interested i am in her as well as romantically which has been very confusing for me. This is the first girl i have looked this way and though we could get into all the details about our relationship and my confusion (she is also "straight") i just want to know if this is common in the bisexual world or if anything is possible. Thanks for the help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-25 06:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FUCKING NOPE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Attachment Therapist Terrorizes Child. Attachment Therapy (AT) is illegal in many states for being too cruel </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-17 06:24:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i need your advice </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-10 08:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So i am a recovering self harmer, i was really addicted to cutting when i was 13-14 and have been doing very well with recovery...so far, but, i have made a friend who i have become very close to in the past year who is currently self harming. I thought i was completely recovered but seeing her cuts talking to her about it is extremely triggering for me. i had a feeling she was cutting so i texted her and she said everything was fine. i asked her if she was lying and she said yes. i immediately went to the razor and cut again...for the first time in a year. I love her to death, she's my best friend...but i dont want to go back to self harm. what should i do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-06 06:15:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> reignwolf and The Drowners! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-01 08:58:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So funny  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-01 08:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shut up and have faith that some people Aren't creeps :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-01 08:57:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The tri cities. Bay city to be specific.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if youre down to hang out with teens i dont have a problem! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome! I'm 16 but would love to meet up! I'll make a new thread soon so we can have a group </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We should all make flags. I'll post mine once it's finished  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol supa creep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:13:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotcha, I'll remember  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:13:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We should have a big meetup  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old are you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 08:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:47:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> almost 16! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:42:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> michigan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:32:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> awesome! how old are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:16:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a mix. The Cure it headlining this year, its alot of well known as well as obsucure bands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:15:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm super excited for alt-j and icona pop, but the big ones like Phoenix and Steve Aoki are going to incredible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> awesome! you going all 3 days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:04:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its a 3 day music festival in Chicago. its pretty amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:04:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i didnt think it was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> any teens in this subreddit who are going by themselves/small groups and are willing to chill? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 06:30:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im going in a group of three and really want to meet new people, i am going all three days

EDIT: if someone wants to make a thread or a page for us to talk/plan meetups that would be awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 06:27:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh shoot! is that a rule here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any teens going to Lollapalooza this weekend? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-31 06:20:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-18 22:35:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will thank you,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-17 05:24:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what price? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-17 05:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no problem! I got a few offers around my area </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 07:27:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 07:08:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Serbia Film is the most disturbing one ive seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 07:07:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i vomited after watching it, and im not easily disturbed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 07:06:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn, im from michigan so its a little difficult. should i look for someone in my state to get it from? im only r/concerttickets is that any more reliable than craigslist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 06:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> invisible monsters is beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 06:54:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they made us read this in my 8th grade class, terribly morbid for 13 year olds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 06:10:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i live a good 4 or 5 hours away, what is the best method of getting the tickets through craigslist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-15 04:16:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, I will check it out, is it reliable?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [B] Lollapalooza 3 day wristband, Chicago, Aug 2-4 any price </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-14 05:22:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (reasonably priced, ill really take any offer) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-11 08:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats good enough for me. thank you, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In need of a 3 day pass. PM me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-11 08:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> complications happened and i no longer have mine. help would be appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-11 07:59:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm from Michigan! You couldnt mail it to someone? especially someone as close as michigan? i'm in dire need of a wristband </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-11 07:41:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i watched. i cried. i vomited. but... i conquered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-09 07:26:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow, i totally get this. i always seem to make dumb decision that are really influenced by my anxiety </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-09 07:23:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i am also 15 and lurk on this subreddit! i've been seeing a therapist for anxiety for over a year. PM me we can talk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [B] Lollapalooza 3 Day Pass; Any Price (1 or 2 passes) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 00:34:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-08 00:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> am i too late? id like to buy
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-06 06:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dust?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-06 06:11:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no problem! its been about 24 hours since i smoked and ive just been sleeping and lying in bed all day. I asked the guy i smoked with how he was doing and he said it was amazing for him. He smokes a ton everyday so i feel i cant really compare myself to him. It might be fair to mention that i took my anti-anxiety/depression pill right after i smoked because i have to take it at night. i take lexapro, just info if anyone knows if this contributes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-06 06:01:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks! you might has misunderstood as i have smoked alot before. i started in january and really usually just sit on the computer or talk to my friends when i'm high. I never really know what strain i'm smoking because where i live it doesnt really matter. that's what concerns me the most, is WHAT i was smoking seeing as it wasnt like the other times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-06 05:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my friends we sober, they hadnt smoked anything. It is bad if it was laced? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> at a [10] last night and had a terrible experience, anyone know what happened to me? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-06 05:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so im a fairly new smoker and have never really gotten to high when i smoked with friends. Last night i smoked out of a gravity bong with some guys and then went home with my 2 best friends. almost immediately i knew something was weird throughout the night i would start sobbing uncontrollably, shaking and being unresponsive to my friends. they said everything i said made absolutely no sense at all. When i woke up this morning i remembered very little from last night. can anyone explain to me what happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> help in really high and really suicidal </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-05 09:52:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> two of my friends are over but i just want to end it. I cant think or breathe. i need help

EDIT: thank you for the messages, i woke up this morning and cannot remember much from last night except for shaking and crying, i just logged on to see your messages on a post i dont remember making.i just wanted to say thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-01 07:15:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> god, my friends love die antwoord, they listen to them all the time, i think its horrible and creepy!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-01 07:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great game! those damn crows are freaky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 04:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's just giving me a lot of anxiety </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 04:05:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i wouldnt deny it. im gald i did because it made me 100% sure of my sexuality but people can be mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 04:04:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3333 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 04:00:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i dont want the reputation its going to give me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 03:59:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh god youre so right how can i ever make up for my tomfoolery?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 03:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you can suck my dick for starters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 03:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im not a lesbian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 03:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me and my friend's realtionship is fine, but im worried my mother will find out, (she works closely with the summer program that all my school kids are in) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 03:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the girl who is telling everyone is doing it specifically to hurt me. how do i deal with her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 03:57:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry i wasnt asking the opinion of an immature nerdy dweeb  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 03:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> way to be an asshole you self righteous prick xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> really need some help figuring out what to do. Help. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 03:49:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So here's the story, my best friend and i are both quirky strange people who are really affectionate to eachother. we hold hands in the hallway and hug; though we both know that its purely platonic. We're both girls. One night while she was staying the night we were both really horny and decided to make out. After we were done we both laughed it off and said it sucked, and everything was back to normal with us. We're both straight. BUT someone found out and told everyone that we made out, everyone knows and i dont know what to do about it. I'm more embarassed than upset but i dont want to be labeled "that girl" any advice on what to do?

TLDR: i made out with my best friend of the same gender. there are no awkward feelings towards eachother. everyone knows now. what do we do now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Brendon Urie of Panic At The Disco Singing "Carry on my Wayward Son" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-23 06:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-14 07:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> youre from Michigan!?! so am i! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-14 06:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i was really rooting for Hitler there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-07 04:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ICONA POP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-29 02:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats really lovely :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-29 02:58:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-29 02:58:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-28 04:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good! I hope it stays that way for both of you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 16:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i got them at Hot Topic back in 2009 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no problem. maybe taking a break will be best for both of you. I am glad i could help :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> only if you get caught. im just messing with you. its something you should experience once in  your lifetime at least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there you go :) i like helping people come to this realization. i had the exact same problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you should. i found that if you try and force them to change it only makes yourself come of as overbearing and selfish. You cant critisize  your friends boyfriend because even though you may be right, you're coming off as jealous and trying to get her away so you can have her. even though those are not your intentions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the freshman life is tough, love iseven more difficult </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lot of things are illegal. doesnt mean they're bad

cigarettes are legal and those are fucking lethal. 

marijuana is something that is gaining more respect in the mainstream lately. soon enough, by the time we actually get employed, we wont have to be drug tested.  it will be as common as a cigarette smoker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cool, my guy friend and are are both 15. So are you freshman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:43:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> try to not talk about things that are so heavy. dwelling on the bad is only going to make both of you worse. you may not like her boyfriend, but it is her choice and you dont have a right to make judgement. tone down on that and find ways to help her. you arent selfish you just want whats best for her. but you have to let her make her own choices </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dont worry about it, it can be a positive influence on you. you have to just try it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:38:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how old are you and your friend? just curious to see if this gets better or worse with age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:37:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't get yourself down, you bring joy into her life. thats all you could ask for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:36:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats gotta be a little awks. i was friends with my guy friend's past girlfriend, i was respectful to them because you shouldnt put people in a situation like that. im glad that she has the message </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:33:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol piss on her. she'll get the message </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i feel you, do you know that she likes you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:29:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i feel ya, i have clinical depression and severe anxiety,  my emotions were getting the best of me to the point where i had to be hospitalize over what i like to call a broke heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:28:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i wish i had the courage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:27:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats a great point. i think our friendship is more important than  the risk of losing him to awkwardness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow that was really interesting! seeing that helped me realize what type of relationship i have with my friend. we dont talk about feelings. we just hang out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:24:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im glad you guys were able to talk through it, its really mature to acknowledge feelings and try to figure them out and move past them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:22:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my situation seems like that, only the opposite. I feel that way. we've been friends for about 5 years now and i only recently discovered my feelings for him (the beginning of high school helped me figure it out) but i dont have the knowledge of whether he ever did like me and i didnt see it or if his feelings are purely platonic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm worried that our friendship will end/ not be the same. i care about him too much to not have him in my life over something silly like unrequited love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:17:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it seems to be a reoccurring thing, having a best friend of the opposite gender and falling for them, why do you think that is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i seem to have the opposite problem, i am a girl who has a guy best friend, i fell in love with him and i just can't read him well enough to figure out if he does or has ever felt the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:07:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'd love to. dont have a skype though, we could email? IM maybe? im old fashion but i'd love to help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> boys of r/teenagers, i have a question! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:06:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do any of you have girl best friends? how to you think of them? I have a best guy friend who i can never seem to understand sometimes. What to boys usually feel about a girl like that?

EDIT: thanks for all the comments! i love talking to all of you! upvote for visibility? i fell like this could help give answers to a lot of people, not karma whoring i promise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 05:03:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well... 

https://mail-attachment.googleusercontent.com/attachment/u/0/?ui=2ik=4d9a44be73view=attth=13ee3efddb85fabaattid=0.1disp=inlinerealattid=166124773f121f4f_0.1safe=1zwsaduie=AG9B_P9-9z6MwW3bT61ZRlyDsEXbsadet=1369623797726sads=rBnQy83WtIOmngcbDLX6CIj-6VYsadssc=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 04:56:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> find a friend who does, hang out and smoke with them. let them teach you the ropes. dont worry about feeling lame when you smoke. if you aint choking you aint smoking :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 04:55:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> panic at the disco
passion pit
icona pop
the shins
fall out boy :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 04:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Time to  relllaaxx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 04:52:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it feels fucking good man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 04:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> drugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 04:51:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i really enjoy makeup, i dont put much effort into it, simple mascara and powder. I like using makeup to enhance your features, not hiding your flaws. you feel me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First Time Lollapalooza Attendee, wondering what cool and interesting things there are to do when we aren't watching a set </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 04:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for the record, i am going with 2 other people (15-18) and don't have tons of extra cash to spend. Thanks for any help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 03:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no problem! i hope you're able to sell them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 03:55:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> one of my favorites! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-25 23:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn, it looks like i cant afford the tickets. I am going to Lollapalooza this year also and have put most of my money into that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-24 23:27:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how much are you selling for?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-23 21:53:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> an excellent point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-20 22:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Skins is also a good show. Episodes are very short so you arent bored and i find them enteratining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-20 22:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sherlock is amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-20 22:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Supernatural!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-20 22:12:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant choose, most of Pretty Odd is so poetic and wonderful. Ryan was a beautiful writer; not saying Brendon isnt but ryan just had a way with words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-30 18:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good idea! I'll look for them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-30 18:33:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for letting me know, I'm a casual smoker usually only at parties  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 13:52:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any tips for while I'm in school besides breathing? Also no recreational drug use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 13:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks ill try this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 03:17:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll go and listen to it sometime!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 03:13:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a lot of people my age are really into imagine dragons, i havent really heard them but im going to Lollapalooza this year and theyre playing. i might check them out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 03:07:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Passion Pit- Little Secrets  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 03:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No way! so am i! I saw icona pop open for Passion Pit a few months back and i fell in love instantly. Not usually my genre but its so good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 02:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats a new way to look at it! I'm honestly more concerned about my health rather than the humiliation part of it, I'm a vocalist and performer so having to constantly throw up its the best for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 02:50:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks for the tip! i'll try it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 02:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Icona Pop!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 02:24:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a therapist and she has explained that it's natural and that i should try not to let things get me anxious. easier said than done.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Help] I cant stop throwing up </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-29 02:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While i'm at school i have this problem of getting really high anxiety over something and having to leave class and vomit for 10 or so minutes. It only happened rarely at first but it has slowly gotten to about 2 or 3 times a week. Anyone have (or had) a similar problem? It's very difficult to deal with and i'd like it to stop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-20 21:30:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fuck you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 15:53:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> getting colder! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 01:11:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry kid, try again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 17:05:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> asssssshoooolllleeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 03:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dont be an asshole  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Slipped this to my friend yesterday </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-25 22:24:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-19 02:44:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, with a new life comes new problems, but I wouldn't go back to where I was for anything in the world  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-19 00:58:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> exactly, i switched schools and im in a much better situation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-19 00:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-18 12:29:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That must be heartbreaking, I'm sorry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-18 03:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My god, thank you so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-17 20:38:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-17 20:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PM me if you think theyre something i need to keep in mind or specific things pertaining to a certain sentence/paragraph. overall comments can be on the thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-17 20:19:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes it is an I Search paper! i dont understand the point of doing that vs a research paper but you know, i do what i have to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-17 20:18:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you can do either. and i am fully aware that we cant use I in normal research papers. This one it set up differently ( i dont know why this is just how she assigned it) the first two paragraphs (what i know and what i want to know) can use i you us etc. as well as the last paragraph </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-17 19:59:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> new link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-17 19:59:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry! ill try and fix it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> would anyone like to peer edit? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-17 19:34:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wrote a paper on how mental illnesses affect teenagers and i would love if i could get feedback/criticism before i turn it in

Thank you so much for your help!



Here is the link:
http://www.writing.com/main/view_item/item_id/1924397-Isearch-Paper


Edit:I think i fixed the link  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-17 19:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that truly terrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-15 14:10:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-15 14:10:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-15 03:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-15 03:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well gross  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 16:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH MY HANDS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 15:11:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lovely :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 15:09:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I switched schools thankfully  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 15:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man fuck you and your fairly tale life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 15:06:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guess my ironic sense of humor doesn't bode well with you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 15:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perfectly awkward  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 15:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PIMP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 00:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> get it where you can amirite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 00:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sounds lovely :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 00:33:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> golden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 00:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it sounds like a middle school experience!!! how old were you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 00:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> awks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What was your first kiss like? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 00:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> being a teenager it goes without saying that mine was incredibly awkward. what was yours like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 00:08:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sleeping :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 00:07:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really into tattered combat boots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-13 23:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It all depends on the day for me, some days i think they show that i am strong and how brave i am for living my life with them. other days i just find them repulsive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-13 23:14:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-13 12:52:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! It's not really appreciated where I go to school, where uggs and northfaces prevail over everything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-13 12:51:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you very much!  I'm flattered :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-13 12:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-13 01:56:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you fool, just your style and your body type makes me smile. not to be creepy or anything, i just think youre attractive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-13 01:54:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When i'm feeling punk rock: http://imgur.com/KE2FuXnsolbBoW34AGDoL#1

When i'm feeling indie 
http://imgur.com/KE2FuXnsolbBoW34AGDoL#2

A night out: 
http://imgur.com/KE2FuXnsolbBoW34AGDoL#0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-13 01:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> youre beautiful O___o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-08 04:37:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's just terrible, kids are so mean. I wish more people understood what cutting means and how its just as bad as someone with a broken arm. you should care that theyre injured. not taunt them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-07 03:48:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i am on fluxotine as well! i only take 10mgs a day, and it has little to no effect on me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-06 18:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am on non addictive medications which I believe is the best for young adults. So many kids are abusing pills that it isn't safe. Of course many non addictive medications aren't as strong as their addictive relatives, which sometimes poses a problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-06 18:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a good point. We are becoming more self aware of mental illnesses. I've also noticed it becoming a "trend" in young teens. Could anyone attest to the same?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-06 18:15:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love that show! I'm doing that this summer along with The Little Mermaid and Young Frankenstien </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-06 18:15:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry, adults sometimes don't react like they should  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-06 05:01:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i guess i have a lot of questions; let me start out with how you feel about young adults being put on anti-depressants, and how social media affects young adults with mental disorders. you can PM me if you wish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-06 05:00:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry! i guess i misinterpreted what you said! i just dont like upseting people :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-06 05:00:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i wish they would have just ignored mine? what show were you in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-06 04:59:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> can you tell me your opinion how why it is more common for young adults in america to have mental illnesses than it was in the past? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-06 04:55:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-06 04:54:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-06 04:52:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the look of disappointment hurts me the most </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 20:30:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 20:29:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's fair enough, judging based on the story should be the best fit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 19:48:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you dont sound mean at all! i've been doing plenty of research and was just wondering if anyone is this sub would like to be apart of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm doing a research paper on the affects of depression and other mental disorders on young adults. Does anyone have stories or articles that they'd like to share? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 19:30:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As my title said, I have a paper for class that i have chosen to do my paper on. I want to understand why depression and other mental disorders are showing up more and more recently in high school/ college students. Any help would be greatly appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 19:27:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you really should. They work for YOU and only YOU. if you tell them that you want to keep it confidential and are open and willing to talk about it with her/him than he/she must not tell anyone by law. I've tried keeping things from  my therapist but i found its much better for both of us if i just tell her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 19:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry, no need to be sassy. i just didnt want to mess it up :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 19:23:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im so sorry your mother has reacted this way, do you have a therapist? my mother was crazy until i had someone talk to her and explain the right and wrong ways for her to act around me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 19:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> exactly. its ridiculous that she enjoys hurting your feelings. I'm glad you have people in your family who support your feelings  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 19:21:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why? i'm 14 years old, was diagnosed with depression at age 11. My family has a long line of depression running through the family, I've witnessed my cousins suicide, ive attempted suicide, i'm on medication and making final adjustments on those meds, and im a recovering self-harmer. why couldnt you take me seriously just because of my age? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 18:31:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hold on to him, try to find other sources of help (i.e therapist, friends, realatives) because nothing lasts forever. (not trying to be morbid, i just want to help you)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 18:20:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> aha, even though i've been a redditor for over a year now, i'm still lacking a lot of knowledge of how things work. I'cm not exactly sure how to approach it/ where to contact them/ etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 18:00:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should we suggest to the mods that we get some? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:59:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :D thank you, it means a lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have another story i'd like to share, when i was in 8th grade i had fallen asleep in English class while we were watching a movie. A few boys who sat near me thought it would be really funny if they took red pen/marker and drew lines all over my wrists and legs. I woke up to bouts of laughter from the people around me and as i looked down i saw crimson lines everywhere, I ran out of the room and went to the bathroom, once i realized they were just marker i began to wash them off. By this time one of the councilors had heard of what happened and came in to help me wash off. As we were cleaning she said "i cant seem to get this one off!" i turns out she was trying to rub off one of my actual cuts and i had to explain to her that i self harmed. I didnt get into any trouble, but it was truly the most embarrassing time of my life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> any time, i'm here for anybody and everybody </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> exactly. your beliefs are yours and no one should dictate you on what you think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:49:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tangents are fine! Its rough when people assume i try to "kill myself" or "cut" for attention because i'm the exact opposite. I'm in theater so when we are changing of course you're going to see some old scars. That's not me trying to cry for attention, that's me trying to live with the mistakes i've inflicted onto my body. I've been ridiculed countless times about my view on how i live with old scars. I see them as something i cant change and i refuse to be worried about them. They are there and if you see them its nothing you should need to worry about. 

i went off on a tangent as well, oops! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:46:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i've been in therapy for a year or so, and we're slowly figuring out what it is, this helps when i have to explain it to people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:42:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry that happened to you. From what i've read i feel that your boyfriend cares a lot about you, I'm glad you have that in your life. He could help you immensely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:40:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've read it so many times! I think its absolutely fantastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:40:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's absolutely terrible. Try to remember that she isnt the only opinion in the world, she could say the worst things, but i promise there is someone out there who is saying that exact opposite of you :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Understandable, tons of people go through this. I am an open atheist in my house but my parents aren't very religious. Just remember you are in control of YOU and no one can dictate what you believe in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:37:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that could work, i dont know how to use flair, but if someone could explain it i'd be happy to do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:37:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you so much, it was a dark time in my life, but i've grown from it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:36:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that has to suck. I get really angry when people try to tell me praying or god is the answer. I usually yell back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:35:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats terrible, i cant believe someone would do that as a joke! And thank you, i'm a lot better now, it was almost a year ago, i'm attempting to recover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:32:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im so sorry that happened to you, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:53:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she shouldnt act like that. How does she think that will help you? public humiliation isnt the way to go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i love that one! i've read it so many times! Have you read NoEnd House? thats another one that i find equally well written </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll look into it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that sounds really creepy? The only two Stephen King books i have read are The Dome and The Stand. But this one sounds interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:21:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's a great question! i really think it depends on the crime, criminals age, current mental state, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:19:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its a haunted video game pasta, its alright, not terrifying by any means </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you! i look forward to reading it :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:15:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> about to read it right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what is it about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:13:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i've read squidward suicide and i find it really disturbing. could you send me a link to Ted the Caver? i havent read that one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:12:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that makes sense. I dont like to pull out the "self harm" card because i dont want to come off as unstable or attention seeking. I like to focus more on why and what is causing my depression as i know it has led to my self harm and anxiety </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is the best scary story/creepypasta you've ever read? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is your opinion on the death penalty? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:00:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm so sorry that happened to you, stay strong :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:55:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pray? are you personally religious? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's a great idea, how can we get them to see this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> care to elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that must have sucked, at least she was discreet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:53:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fair explanation. Do you think there is a way to differentiate teens from adults in this subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 02:49:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This used to happen to me a lot when i was full-out addicted to self harm and was trying to stop. I felt like i wasnt me without cutting. I've been clean for about a month now and i still get random urges to cut "for old times sake" its truly something difficult that we have to deal with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Whats the worst experience you've had with someone finding your cuts? (TW?) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 02:44:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in a summer production of "Chicago" and at rehearsal i was very overwhelmed. I went back into the dressing room and used a hanger to cut two thin lines on my wrist. Once I calmed down a bit and had paper towel wrapped around my wrist, a girl from the cast walked in. She gasped as she saw the blood-stained towel around my wrist. I tried to call out and stop her but she was gone. She ended up telling everyone in the cast and i was taken out of the show, as well as hospitalized for a week for "unstable behavior" what kinds of stories do you have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 02:24:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fair enough, i only ask because its hard to explain where my depression came from and why i have it. People always assume i'm "exaggerating" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:17:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can feel the same way, one moment i'm leveled and calm, and the next i feel like curling up on the ground and not talking to anyone. Its very hard for me to get out of these situations, if its possible to remove myself i always do. It's whats best in that situation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> acquired a new skill last night </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-24 18:22:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-23 23:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I completely understand how you feel  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-22 21:40:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you! I unfortunately reside in high school, so when i have my attacks within school its very hard for people to know what is going on. My teachers handle it very well, but you can't expect every person in your school to be mature and respectful towards you, you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone else feel guilty after they have anxiety attacks? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-22 19:21:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always feel guilty about what i do when i'm in the middle of an attack. When people try to help i always flinch away  terrified, like a wounded animal. Days later i have this lingering guilt and paranoia about what that person thinks of me now that they've seen me act this way. This only brings on more anxiety. Anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-22 19:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it just interest me, this whole subreddit interest me a lot, somethings (like this) may be a little too much for me, but many other posts i thoroughly enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-22 19:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm aware now, curiosity got the best of me, can you blame me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-21 04:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish i had a cat or dog to help me, as i know they are proven to help people with depression, but its not something that is available to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-21 02:03:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is really well done, i spent an hour or two getting through it, ive ended up exactly where i am right now. It makes me feel a little better knowing that it's all "normal"

(P.S a little part of me got attached to the kitten in the story, i think ill have to get myself one) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-20 23:05:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i dont know what to feel, i stumbled across this and i am a mere 14 years old. im shaking....most things dont faze me either but this....i cant even think right now.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-20 21:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BAD VIBES BAD VIBES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Its mind blowing to me, really, </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-14 03:25:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-14 02:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i personally loved Toy Story 3, it was a tear-jerker for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is your favorite Disney Movie of all time and why? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-14 02:42:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-14 02:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like my coffee like i like my women,

without a dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-14 02:39:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hide and seek with you friends someone abandoned  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-14 02:38:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i was aloud to sleep over at boys houses all my life. As long as i said i wasn't "dating" said boy i had no restrictions on where i went and where i slept. You can see how my young immature self took advantage of that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-13 04:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> awks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-22 03:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought that "God" was always watching so i showered with shorts and a tank top on until i was probably 10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-21 02:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no matter where you are, who you are, or what you do, there is always someone who hates your guts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-21 02:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wanted to be a pirate princess warrior from space

im still working out the kinks but i def working on it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-20 02:02:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it really grinds my gears when i fuck bitches and dont get money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-19 03:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i do! it is that of a mouse :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is one physical and one emotional trait you love about yourself? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-19 03:43:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lets spread self love and confidence. 

i love my eyes and my sneeze! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-19 03:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my ability to help others work through their problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The last thing i expected to see at school </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-19 03:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-19 02:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are tons of amazing stories on this thread, and it kind of makes me feel a little boring. I spent my last day on my roof listening to The Strokes.  I had taken enough pills to (what i thought) end me, and i just relaxed. though suicide is not a light subject, i do admit what was supposed to be my  last day was very peaceful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2012-06-13 03:16:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you could menstruate with lipstick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>