<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject888</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-19 03:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it may actually be sadder to have recognized whose body that is.. Like I did, I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:21:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I how you are eventually fruitful. Still a very cute piece! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 22:48:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes!!!!! A bowl for us gayz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 21:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, I was wrong. Just zoomed in and saw the horizontal watermark. Never mind. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 09:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I&#8217;ve had the Organics you&#8217;re talking about (in RAW Cone form). They are solid white, it&#8217;s pretty strange. As far as I have noticed, RAW Classics, the brownish ones, aren&#8217;t labelled organic anywhere on the package. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 09:23:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A bag of weed.

P.S. Why are you crying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 06:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bad Girls by M.I.A. probably </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-18 05:30:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A recent letter from her website:
 
 Years ago I began the process of trying to remove myself from an abusive relationship that started when I was a teenager. Over the course of that relationship I was systematically cut off from anyone and everyone that I could truly be close to. I was talked down to, yelled at, locked into rooms and criticized daily about my abilities, my weight, my looks, my intelligence and almost every move I made. When I couldn&#8217;t take it anymore and I wanted to end the relationship I was threatened, then I was told I was loved, and the cycle would begin again.
 
 I want young women and young men to understand that this kind of treatment of others can happen where it might be least expected. Even in environments that thrive on creativity and open-mindedness, that advocate artistic and counter-culture ideals. Sometimes people will use these things to camouflage themselves so that their abuse might go unnoticed. So that you wouldn&#8217;t think to consider it could be happening right in front of you.
 
 The clarity I&#8217;ve gained since getting out of that situation has opened up my life in a way that I didn&#8217;t imagine was possible. Although some of the pain and anger still lingers, my life finally feels as though it has value and meaning. I speak out now hoping that I can encourage other young women and young men to affirm their value within their relationships or get out. Abuse isn&#8217;t always obvious and it doesn&#8217;t have to involve black eyes, blood and broken bones. Emotional and psychological abuse can be just as damaging, and it is extremely difficult to remove yourself from.
 
 Those that have known me throughout my career might be surprised that someone who publicly gave the impression of being fearless and seemed as though they didn&#8217;t take shit from anyone could find themselves being severely mistreated and manipulated by someone they were close to. This person nearly stripped me of myself.  And for years I felt as though they were waiting for my life to end.
 
 Stillbirth was written by myself and Jupiter Keyes in our basement. There is no label involved. It will be available through iTunes, Spotify, etc. beginning July 18. All proceeds for digital purchases of this song will benefit organizations (like the nonprofit RAINN) that help survivors of domestic abuse, sexual violence and incest. You can donate directly to them at https://donate.rainn.org or via the link on my website at http://www.alice-glass.com/
 
 There is a sister song to Stillbirth that I hope to release soon, she is a lullaby and she can&#8217;t wait to meet you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alice Glass &#8211; Stillbirth (electronic) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:49:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:23:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> JESUS CHRIST IN HEAVEN **THank youuuuuu** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:52:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They want us (and our dollars) all trapped in this cesspool of sin/tourism I'm sure. Also: public transit in AVL is the farthest from the pits (having previously lived in Louisville, KY and having gotten around in D.C., NYC, L.A., and some of Western Europe. I'd say ART mostly has its shit together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:47:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slow news day, I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:42:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The "**Right now**" part of "Right now, I live in the cloud" is just a bit ominous to me.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> HEALTH &#8211; STONEFIST [noise rock] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:27:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here on SP2..... but you have to think of non-proprietary device users. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That ^ is the after photo. [This is the before photo.](http://i.imgur.com/r7eq8tu.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Got it in a little head shop in downtown Asheville, NC ;-)

Edit:  This one's a TasteBuds (a brand I'd never heard of), all of the Grav Labs was sold out online &#128148; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:17:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:38:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don&#8217;t know where I am on &#8220;the scale,&#8221; but I just smoked a column of pure cannabis &#8213; a very stoney hybrid called Oracle &#8213; and it was actually wonderful. But now I wanna clean it :&#8221;-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> M.I.A. Releases Audiovisual Project "Matahdatah Scroll 01 Broader Than a Border" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:13:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Test? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:29:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I heard that it may be out sometime earlier this week, perhaps because of the staggered release of Developer Beta 3 and the Public Beta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:53:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Low Power Mode for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crystal Castles &#8211; Frail [electronic] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uhhhhh.... Google Maps for sure. Hell, even Here Maps by Nokia or Waze is better than Apple Maps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:16:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so very sorry that you were prescribed this poison.  Much of my former half of 2015 was spent discovering, starting, and then quickly trying to wean myself off of venlafaxine, and it was hell.  Way more trouble than it's worth in my humble opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:25:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Notice the 'September 2015' estimated ship date.  If these guys aren't simply scamming us, I'll wager that September will be the time anything major happens in terms of shipping of backers' Hoppers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine is very crashy. I can open it, but doing a small number of things within the app quickly crashes it. Lame.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blood Orange &#8211; Do You See My Skin Through The Flames? [soul] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:45:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I seriously love these things. Makes me want Krispy Kreme to come out with a Cap'n Crunch glazed doughnut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:17:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It will probably be another full week before we get anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I personally think and hope it will arrive along with the first public beta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:53:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I&#8217;m not having issues with the crashing of the control center tray, but on tray pull-up there is some lag and dropping of frames, which is annoying. So I suppose that I hope for the continued smoothing-out of interface elements as well as the continued improvement of battery life, wi-fi issues (for those who have them), and of course the addition of Apple Music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:46:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They just seem to prefer releasing things on Tuesdays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 15:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never said I believe her every word, just that she does her homework and is a pretty swell analyzer. She seems intelligent and open-minded to me, so while I may not end up siding with her on everything, we still share a similar (and in my opinion healthy) distrust of government and mass media. Her striking analysis of Family Guy's "prediction" of Robin Williams' death is what really got to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 15:53:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow&#8230; that is extremely unsettling, not unlike looking over similar presentations regarding NSA data mining. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 15:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 15:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, there are occurrences of what some have termed "predictive programming," which just a term for conditioning/priming the mass conscience using media laced with subconscious "clues" which are, as some believe, the Elite's way of "warning" the public of catastrophic events. A good example of such a phenomenon is Family Guy, a show perfect for subconscious brainwashing due to its off-the-wall, seemingly "random" nature, correctly "predicting" some major occurrences, such as the Boston Marathon bombings and Bruce Jenner's transition into Caitlyn. Saturday Night Live has also supposedly been used to push secret agendas (including that of the 9/11 attacks) before they had come to full fruition. If anyone else has more info/examples, I'd certainly appreciate it.

Source: Betsy McGee on YouTube. Please check out her channel; she's a bona fide, homework-doing badass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 09:05:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apologies for lacking any relevant or helpful information, but how are you 89,968 builds ahead of everyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crystal Castles &#8211; Deicide [electronic] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:15:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 11:26:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Over 300 under-the-hood fixes in addition to the new Hero wallpaper  lockscreen (which I personally dislike). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Beach House &#8211; Sparks [dream pop] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-02 08:29:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, well that's&#8230; incredibly vague. I have a feeling it will be a full two weeks between betas 2 and 3, the latter of which will bring the real Apple Music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes but it's honestly not that annoying to me, for whatever reason. I really hope iOS 9 beta 3 improves upon issues in the second beta in addition to improving overall stability  battery life. At first (in beta 1) I hated the font change, but now I've learned to love it.

New OS improvements like those found in iOS 9 are a large part of the reason why I love sticking around in the leisurely and confident Apple ecosystem, just to see what Apple does (Low Power Mode has been amazing, for example). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Death Grips &#8211; Centuries of Damn [hip hop] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:29:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-23 05:48:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **Smoking kills** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 10:09:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great description. I recently decided that if one were to paraphrase the "high experience" in one word it would be "nostalgia." Just that feeling of longing warmth and comfort. Nostalgia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jamie xx &#8211; I Know There's Gonna Be (Good Times) ft. Young Thug  Popcaan [trip hop] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Florence + The Machine &#8211; Which Witch (Demo) [indie rock] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 23:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 12:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 09:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Link to the latest Preview build of the Dopamine player (from the developer's Dropbox:
https://www.dropbox.com/sh/ssuncmgmk2kat9h/AACoIXL1bRNkpRmu0GFqIUlra/Previews/Latest/Dopamine%201.0.0%20%28Build%20221%29%20Preview.msi?dl=0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dopamine Music Player for Windows </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-07 08:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 00:48:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If worse comes to worst you can always perform an upgrade and then do a refresh/reset after. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 23:40:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 10:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is wonderful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 10:12:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i&#8217;m gonna hurl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 10:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Little Cancer Stick&#174; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 07:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ever tried weed? Just wondering.

&#8230;It helps me, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-20 02:44:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice repost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:32:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kitty /3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:30:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hommies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 05:52:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LMFAO i&#8217;m stoned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 23:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, in fact the libido side of things has generally remained untouched.  Then again, I've always had a pretty good libido (I was assigned Male at birth, in case you're wondering). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 23:05:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took it for a small number of months as well... Now I feel trapped in a fog of apathy.  Withdrawal was awful but I knew that the medication was doing nothing but poisoning me.  My father is a retired physician (cardiologist) and I must say that having some of the "most accurate" knowledge of Western medicine at one's fingertips is not always such a blessing.

If anything, the few psychotropic drugs I have tried&#8212;zoloft (sertraline), celexa (citalopram), and effexor (venlafaxine)&#8212;have done nothing but worsen my apathy and general desire to stop living.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mitski &#8212; Francis Forever [Rock] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 21:30:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Prurient &#8212; Dragonflies To Sew You Up [Noise] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 06:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here y'all go...](http://www.customink.com/designs/nancyreagn/uzn0-00a3-zrgg/hotlink?pc=HL-142344cm_mmc=hotlink-_-5-_-Header_txt-_-prehead1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 06:10:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, it technically is an "RB" (i.e. genre-specific) album.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Snoop Dogg &#8211; California Roll (feat. Stevie Wonder) [x-post from /r/RepublicOfMusic] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Snoop Dogg &#8211; California Roll (feat. Stevie Wonder) [RB] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:38:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 08:52:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *looks around nervously* conspiracies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 08:47:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no problem :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Devonte&#769; Hynes drops an unreleased 45-minute film score - for you to 'zone out to' </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-12 06:24:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:38:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> joints </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 03:15:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "A while ago..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 03:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ayy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 03:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing has been released that will actually be on the album, as far as I know. Have you heard ["Go?"](https://youtu.be/vIi57zhDl78) I realize it's a collaboration, but still:  It is evidence of her experimenting sonically. *shrug* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Grimes &#8212; REALiTi (Experimental pop) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 01:45:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 00:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here. I have found that the medicinal/therapeutic effects also depend on the quality/type of weed, but mostly my mind-state before and during consumption (i.e. if I'm feeling negatively or overtly anxious it's probably not going to be much fun). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone else here use marijuana to ease emotional pain? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 22:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 08:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I&#8217;m sorry&#8230;. Hopefully a new build will be out this week to move your experience in a better direction.

On the upside, just be glad you&#8217;re not using the just-released Surface 3&#8230;apparently 10074 is rather unusable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 06:55:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I realize they&#8217;re of entirely distinct ethnic origins, but your mother and Bj&#246;rk bear some striking visual similarities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 05:49:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uhhhh.... Ever read much into the Holocaust? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 03:32:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I my personal experience, tiles are too visually inconsistent--they provide similar functionality to "true" Start menu pinning, but in a package that I just have never warmed up to.  Hopefully somewhere down the line basic Windows 7-style pinning will come back into play, but until then, they'll remain excluded from my Start menu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 02:18:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-10 01:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 14:20:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I honestly kind of like them...very minimalistic.  But the new Aero blur would be beautiful as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 14:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm on a Surface as well ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 14:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ..my-my eyes.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone else just genuinely hate him/her self? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 14:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 12:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's still Windows 10, either way.  I just thought the Defender app and my desktop wallpaper went especially well together. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 10:07:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that design choice may be up to the app (in this case Spotify) developers, not Microsoft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 09:52:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> seems she took it down - same fate as the last teaser, CanSeeCanDo.
here are links for both.

Platforms - https://youtu.be/pMynQPOhTtM

CanSeeCanDo - https://youtu.be/QAunBvcUYhg

#MIA2k15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I personally think Windows 10 is shaping up rather beautifully. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 09:02:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 07:25:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For a tasty twist on the traditional formula, try Rishi's [Earl Grey Lavender](http://www.amazon.com/Rishi-Tea-Earl-Lavender-Ounce/dp/B00AR6LZR4/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8qid=1431149338sr=8-1keywords=rishi+earl+grey+lavender) or Ambessa's [Earl of Harlem](http://www.amazon.com/Harney-Sons-Ambessa-Harlem-Sachets/dp/B00ARKQ1YC/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8qid=1431149294sr=8-1keywords=earl+of+harlem) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> M.I.A. - Platforms [Hip-hop] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 02:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 00:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **"Platform" lyrics:**

**verse one**

Neon lights on the dust on the ground on the bus

Dirty roads makes that scarf wrap a must

Rolling by scrolling for the future on the app

Data mine my mind like a diamond in the ruff

**chorus**

Platforms here's a train of thought

Getting to the bright side of me is why I fought

I'm gonna say what else have I got

Maybe there's glory in all the things I'm not.

**verse two**

If oil is the god then the cranes all pray

The crude is so rude

It makes the people pay

On the side of the road men make money

A flower for a dollar man

He wants a family

If I rose to power

It'll be a bouquet

Emoji a smiley

And say I'm OK

The tech dudes are the only ones having a good day

And talking is cheap

Coz they make it easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone else feel lobotomized by medication? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:09:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 10:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the useful info and for your constructive comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 21:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of all, please make a change in your diet.  Eat more unprocessed, actual foods... i.e. fresh fruits and vegetables.  I like to drink a strong roasted dandelion root tea to soften stools and to cleanse the liver.  Also you can try ginger to aid digestion; I do not, however, know of any laxative or stool-softening effects in ginger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 06:11:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> okay, fair point. my family maintains a small organic farm, and yes, we do use pesticides. but they are formulated to be safer than those normally used. 

so my wording was a bit off. teavana teas have been shown to contain dangerous levels of pesticides, and i have actually felt a nauseating, toxic sensation upon consuming some of their teas. now i find it practical and even necessary to be discerning, but i realize there are many people who have desirable experiences with tea regardless of the product&#8217;s &#8216;organic&#8217; status. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> thoughts on organic tea? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:46:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alright r/tea, question time.

what are your thoughts on organically-grown and processed teas? are they frivolous luxury, absolute necessity, or complete nonsense altogether?

personally, i tend to go for the organic stuff; this habit arose after having several not-so-pleasant experiences with (teavana) teas grown using pesticides.

sometimes, though, i feel as if i&#8217;m missing out on some great tea experiences because of strict standards and a reluctance to deviate from any product that lacks organic certification.

what are your thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:35:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> also, if you don&#8217;t mind me asking, where does one purchase a &#8216;top-shelf&#8217; fukamushi? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 02:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> let me know what you think! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 02:03:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :) a few months back i purchased a pound of organic fukamushi from Den's Tea, and i tend to agree with this assessment. my only question is... how does the extra steaming affect the leaf's health benefits? obviously the leaf becomes more particulate with the fukamushi process, but does that indicate any damage to the leaf's nutritional integrity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-02 01:15:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i personally prefer fukamushi for its grassy overtones and particular cloudiness. just curious what others prefer between these differently-steamed Japanese greens and why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what do you prefer and why: sencha or fukamushi-sencha? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:19:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hello,
i am going to be posting a simple preference-based question every few days just to help myself and others flesh out a greater understanding of the subtle-*teas* inherent to the world and culture of *camellia sinensis*.

so, for round one, the questions arises from the japanese tea tradition.  do you personally prefer the delicate freshness of a traditionally-steamed sencha or the heavier, more robust cloudiness of a more thoroughly-steamed fukamushi-sencha?  why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:04:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> interesting! good to know (more incentive to stick to beans, rice, and salads...the good ol' unprocessed staples of my diet). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-30 03:38:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tea&#8212;or more specifically the caffeine in tea&#8212;is indeed a diuretic. despite that, though, i really don&#8217;t know what to make of your case. really quite bizarre!

edit: grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:10:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the reply.

I have mainly been reaching out via company websites' "Contact Us" forms, and have received a few lukewarm&#8212;but thoughtful&#8212;responses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm in need of some advice concerning a career in tea. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 14:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello,

I need some help. I am only 20, but so far college has been quite rough for me and I believe working with tea is my true calling. Upon discovering several small, ethical tea companies around the country (America), I have begun reaching out but so far have not been too lucky.

My passion is clear, I think, as is my willingness to work. Am I doing something wrong? Are these companies looking for something specific that I am lacking or perhaps failing to mention? Is there just not a great labor demand among these smaller companies?

Please respond with any relevant or potentially helpful information; particularly if you work for/have worked in the tea industry. This is my dream and, as I said previously, my true calling in life. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-24 10:47:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I personally recommend ZeroWater! It is the only five-stage water filter on the market that removes 99.9% of dissolved solids in water. They are available on Amazon in differently-sized pitchers and dispensers, and from my personal experience, are ideal for tea (and general water drinking). :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 06:41:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, why are you against the recreational use of marijuana? Not trying to incite a war or anything. It's just not an opinion one hears a lot these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 06:31:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 06:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're in the mood for something a bit different (smokier) than your standard Earl G., Harney amp;amp;amp;amp; Sons' Earl of Harlem is supposed to be pretty excellent.

I've been meaning to pick some up myself, because their teas are pretty damn awesome:

https://www.harney.com/ambessa-the-earl-of-harlem-20-sachets-tin.html

Also&#8212;and I am speaking from experience here&#8212;Rishi Tea's Earl Grey Lavender is absolutely delicious (and pretty luxurious, particularly with some cream and honey):

http://www.rishi-tea.com/product/earl-grey-lavender-organic-black-tea-blend/black-tea

For something a bit less pricey and in bags (although the flavor profile may not be as "interesting"), here is Rishi's plain Earl Grey in sachets:

http://www.rishi-tea.com/product/earl-grey-organic-fair-trade-tea-bag/tea-bags </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 23:48:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone know of a place to get a good tea needle and knife? I tried Amazon, and perhaps I was just not patient enough, but everything seemed pretty questionable and/or overpriced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 23:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! I live in Western North Carolina (where Panther Moon is based) and was able to try a few of their puerh teas at a tea festival in Black Mountain.

Everything about their tea 'friendship caravan' was wonderful; although they were very busy I received a thorough explanation on each tea I tried, all of which were delicious.

I ended up taking two ounces of a 2009 Zhang Lang sheng/raw puerh home, which was nice because I have been too lazy/forgetful to invest in a tea needle and knife. The tea is of superb quality&#8212;very fresh and light for a puerh&#8212;although if you want something with more age or in a different family of tea altogether, I can personally vouch for the value and quality of Panther Moon Tea Co. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Which books have helped you cope? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 22:43:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They don't have to be books about dealing with grief or mental illness, nor do they need to have 'saved your life.' Just try and recall any book that has helped you break a depressive cycle or gain some new, maybe reinvigorating perspective.

Please avoid religious texts if you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>